<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="16365" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>Qualifying Group, 4th Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Asia Cup Qualifiers, 2016</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Hong Kong</home>
		<away>United Arab Emirates</away>
		<teamsabbr>HK vs UAE</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>HK</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>UAE</awayabbr>
		<homeId>8</homeId>
		<awayId>7</awayId>
		<venue>Khan Shaheb Osman Ali Outer Stadium, Fatullah</venue>
		<startdate>21 02 2016</startdate>
		<enddate>21 02 2016</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner></winner>
			<decision></decision>
		</toss>
		<state>preview</state>
		<status></status>
		<result type="">
			<winningteam></winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>09:00</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
	</match>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/><br/>The Asia Cup 2016 qualifier has seen plenty of drama in the first two days, and when Aamir Kaleem mankaded Mark Chapman it became clear that the teams are going for the win at any cost and mean business.<br/><br/>After their 16-run win over Afghanistan, UAE will try and consolidate their spot when they take on Hong Kong in Fatullah on Sunday (February 21).<br/><br/>UAE came up with a commanding performance against Afghanistan with Rohan Mustafa ensuring they posted 176 for 4 before the bowlers collaborated to rock the Afghanistan top order.<br/><br/>However, the blip in UAE's performance was that they failed to contribute after Mustafa's blitz and going ahead in the tournament it'll be important that the batting clicks as a unit.<br/><br/>Hong Kong impressed everyone with their performances in the ICC World T20 Qualifiers last year. Led by Tanwir Afzal, Hong Kong are coming into this tournament having played a drawn T20I series against Scotland in Mong Kok.<br/><br/>The bowlers were really impressive in the first game and kept the visitors to just 66 for 7 in ten overs in a truncated clash before the batsmen joined the party and chased it down with over three overs to spare.<br/><br/>What will bother Hong Kong the most is that the team isn't clicking as a unit. In their game against Oman, it was Babar Hayat's 60-ball 122 that took the team close. The second best performance came from Aizaz Khan, who scored 15.<br/><br/>Nadeem Ahmed picked up 3 for 27 in the last game and the bowling is expected to revolve around him.<br/><br/>Going into the match, UAE emerges clear favourites but Hong Kong, after a moral boosting performance against Scotland, will be eyeing another upset to show what they are capable of and keep their campaign on track.?]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>United Arab Emirates</b> (From): Rohan Mustafa, Muhammad Kaleem, Shaiman Anwar, Amjad Javed(c), Mohammad Usman, Mohammad Shahzad, Usman Mushtaq, Ahmed Raza, Swapnil Patil(w), Farhan Ahmed, Mohammad Naveed, Zaheer Maqsood, Qadeer Ahmed, Saqlain Haider, Fahad Tariq]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hong Kong</b> (From): Anshuman Rath, Kinchit Shah, Babar Hayat, Mark Chapman, Nizakat Khan, Tanwir Afzal(c), Aizaz Khan, Waqas Khan, Haseeb Amjad, Christopher Carter(w), Nadeem Ahmed, Tanveer Ahmed, Adil Mehmood, Ninad Shah, Waqas Barkat]]></line>		
		</commentary>
</scorecard>



