<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14797" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>2nd T20I</gameDesc>
		<series>England tour of South Africa, 2015-16</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>South Africa</home>
		<away>England</away>
		<teamsabbr>RSA vs ENG</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>RSA</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>ENG</awayabbr>
		<homeId>11</homeId>
		<awayId>9</awayId>
		<venue>New Wanderers Stadium, Johannesburg</venue>
		<startdate>21 02 2016</startdate>
		<enddate>21 02 2016</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner></winner>
			<decision></decision>
		</toss>
		<state>preview</state>
		<status></status>
		<result type="">
			<winningteam></winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>12:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
	</match>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/><br/>The caravan returns to Johannesburg, the venue that changed South Africa's fortunes on this limited-overs leg with Chris Morris digging the Proteas out from what looked like an improbable victory in the fourth One-Day International (ODI). He delivered yet again in the first Twenty20 International on Friday (February 19) when the rest failed to turn up.<br/><br/>In the decider on Sunday (February 21), the batting units from both sides will be in focus yet again after their shoddy display in the first game. England especially will be looking to break the shackles after losing four consecutive games on this tour.<br/><br/>"Very disappointing; I think the fact that we got the game that close is a huge credit to our bowling unit," said Eoin Morgan after the defeat. What's been more disappointing is his batting form and he desperately needs a good hit out in the middle.<br/><br/>Alex Hales is the only batsman who has looked good in the last two matches and the rest need to step up. And the conditions will help the batsmen if the recent records are to go by. Last year, the highest ever run-chase in a T20I happened at this venue when West Indies chased down 232 against the hosts with Faf du Plessis' ton going in vain.<br/><br/>Moeen Ali has not looked comfortable in his new role at No. 7 in T20Is after initially spending time batting at the top of the order. It will be interesting to see if the think tank promotes him.<br/><br/>Reece Topley was the unfortunate villain in the first match where he bowled some full tosses in the final over helping South Africa's cause. He will look to make amends on his 22nd birthday. The two teams also play each other in the group stage of the World Cup next month, so the winner of this contest might have a mental edge going into that clash.<br/><br/>England are likely to be unchanged but South Africa might bring in Farhan Behardien for Rilee Rossouw. AB de Villiers will continue to keep wickets in Quinton de Kock's absence.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>South Africa</b> (From): Hashim Amla, AB de Villiers(w), Faf du Plessis(c), Jean-Paul Duminy, Rilee Rossouw, David Miller, David Wiese, Chris Morris, Kyle Abbott, Kagiso Rabada, Imran Tahir, Quinton de Kock, Dale Steyn, Aaron Phangiso, Farhaan Behardien]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>England</b> (From): Jason Roy, Alex Hales, Joe Root, Eoin Morgan(c), Ben Stokes, Jos Buttler(w), Moeen Ali, Chris Jordan, Adil Rashid, David Willey, Chris Woakes, Liam Plunkett, James Vince, Sam Billings, Reece Topley]]></line>		
		</commentary>
</scorecard>



