<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="12860" >
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>6th Match, Pool A</gameDesc>
		<series>WC 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>New Zealand</home>
		<away>Scotland</away>
		<teamsabbr>NZ vs SCO</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>NZ</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>SCO</awayabbr>
		<homeId>13</homeId>
		<awayId>23</awayId>
		<venue>University Oval, Dunedin</venue>
		<startdate>17 02 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>17 02 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>New Zealand</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>New Zealand won by 3 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>New Zealand</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>3</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Simon Fry</Name>
			<Country>Aus</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Nigel Llong</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Marais Erasmus</Name>
			<Country>RSA</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>David Boon</Name>
			<Country>Aus</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>22:00</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>true</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150217032007</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>NZ</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>Sco</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>146</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>7</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>24.5</batteamovers>
		<status>New Zealand won by 3 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>205</playerid>
			<name>Daniel Vettori*</name>
			<batsman-name>Vettori</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Vettori</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>8</runs>
			<balls-faced>4</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>7625</playerid>
			<name>Adam Milne</name>
			<batsman-name>Milne</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Milne</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>1</runs>
			<balls-faced>3</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>8423</playerid>
			<name>Iain Wardlaw*</name>
			<bowler-name>Iain Wardlaw</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Iain Wardlaw</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>9.5</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>57</runs>
			<wickets>3</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>6657</playerid>
			<name>Josh Davey</name>
			<bowler-name>J Davey</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Davey</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>7</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>40</runs>
			<wickets>3</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>143</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>1396</playerid>
<name>Luke Ronchi</name>
<player-runs>12</player-runs>
<player-balls>10</player-balls>
<runs>137</runs>
<wicket-nbr>7</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>6657</bowlerid>
<bowlername>J Davey</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>5</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>6</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[2 . 1 . . 2 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 . . . 2 4 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 W 4 W 1 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>2 1 . 1 4 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_WC/NZ_SCO_FEB17/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[So, that's all we have from this game. Many thanks for your company. Do join us tomorrow for the battle between two Asian nations, Afghanistan and Bangladesh. On behalf of <b>Akshay, Pradeep, Sonali, Sriram, Krishna</b> and <b>Bhanu</b>, this is <b>Sidhant</b> signing off. See you tomorrow folks. Take care.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Let's take a look at some of the interesting <b>tweets</b> about this game:<br/><br/><b>Mohandas Menon</b>:  New Zealand won by 3 wkts with 151 balls to spare: this is the narrowest win with most balls to spare in ODI cricket history #NZvSco #CWC15<br/><br/><b>Mazher Arshad</b>: New Zealand's last 10 completed ODIs: W W W W L W W W L W<br/><br/><b>Iain O'Brien</b>: Saying that @CricketScotland have "fought admirably" is doing them a disservice. They’ve just gone out there and played cricket.<br/><br/><b>Jamie Alter</b>: A win for NZ, but plenty of concerns with the batting. Well bowled, Scotland. If only the fielding and batting were better #NZvSCO #CWC15<br/><br/><b>Roshan Abeysinghe</b>: NZ may not lose to the Scots but they are definitely wobbling. Great start to the tournament for the 2 associates.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Brendon McCullum:</b> "It was a tough one. Credit to Scotland in the way they hung in there, especially after being four for 12. Lesser teams would have been rolled over there. Credit to them for the way they hung in and managed to post a total which was going to be tricky on that sort of a surface. It was just nibbling enough. And they had the bowlers who could extract a little bit out of it. Pleased with the result at the end. Probably a little bit nervous towards the end. With 25 overs to go, we will take the result and the points from this game. They are world class bowlers (Boult and Southee). They have stood up in red ball cricket for a long time. And as a pair we have seen how effective they can be, with one swinging it away from the right-hander and the other swinging it away from the left-hander. So, they were outstanding. When you win the toss and bowl, you hope to take early wickets. And getting them to 4 for 12 was an outstanding achievement. And also with the way we finished off the innings and after a partnership with a couple of their guys. It was a really good performance in the field and with the ball  and with the bat we showed glimpses. I guess, we need to improve on that. Obviously a different situation, different surface, different ground. It is a day/night game as well (talking about the next game). It is going to be a great challenge and it is nice to have started the competition with two wins. But there is a long way to go in this competition, we know that. And we are just going to keep making small improvements on the way but we are playing some good cricket. England we know, are probably hurting a little bit at the moment. They will turn up and they will be tough to beat over here. So we have to play incredibly well and I believe it's a full house at Wellington. So it should be a great atmosphere. This is certainly the strongest side I have played in (replying to a twitter question asking whether it was the strongest team that McCullum has played in)."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preston Mommsen:</b> "It was a very tough start for us. The ball was doing a little bit more than expected. And to be fair they bowled really well and exploited the conditions. Unfortunately, we lost a few early ones but credit to the way Matthew (Machan) and Richie (Berrington) batted in the middle. I think they showed what we are capable of. Unfortunately they couldn't go on and we were well below par in the target we set. I think when we put the ball in the right areas, we got the rewards. Joshy (Josh Davey) and Wardy (Iain Wardlaw) bowled well for us. Unfortunately we couldn't pick those extra three but I am very proud of the fight in the end there. Great character. We are not shy of the fact that we are a very inexperienced team performing at the World Cup. So, it is good to get the first game out of the way. I am very proud of the performance and now ready for England."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Trent Boult:</b> "I felt pretty good. I thought the ball swung around pretty nicely and I guess wicket had a bit of assistance in it as well. Pretty good bowling performance and everyone had a bit of a bat as well. And we got the job done. I actually slept alright. We got there in the end anyway. And I had a big role to play today. Like I said, everyone played well and we got the job done. The ball did swing for a little bit longer. Like I said the pace was there as well. We didn't really expect that. We just came in and tried to do what we have been doing for the last couple of weeks. And things fell into place and we got the result. It's going well and I am really enjoying the white ball form. A lot more opportunities coming up and need to make most of those."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Trent Boult</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his figures of 2/21 in 6 overs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Black Caps batters looked like they were in a hurry to chase the total down and kept playing their shots even after a wicket had fallen. One can never know if things would have been any different had Scotland not dropped a couple of catches as well. As it turns out, the Kiwis managed to scrape through to a 3-wicket win, but it was not a convincing one. Davey and Wardlaw both finished with 3 wickets for Scotland.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, Scotland got off to a disastrous start, losing 4 wickets in under 5 overs. 3 out of those 4 wickets were ducks. However, Machan and Berrington showed resolve and batted sensibly after that. Machan got to his fifty and perished soon after, caught at mid-on, with Brendon McCullum taking a superb catch to end his 97-run stand with Berrington. After Machan got out, the floodgates opened. Anderson picked up his second wicket, dismissing the well-set Berrington on 50. From there on, it was all Vettori, who took the final three wickets to end the Scottish innings on 142. Two of those Vettori wickets came off consecutive balls. Overall, it was the <b>third occasion</b> in the innings, when a bowler had picked <b>2 wickets in 2 balls</b>. First Boult did it, then Southee and finally, Vettori. Five Scottish batsmen got out on ducks and out of those, <b>4 were golden ducks</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[New Zealand started the run-chase in superb fashion, with Guptill going hard at the new ball. However, he got out after hitting 4 boundaries and then Brendon McCullum took over the aggressor's role, smashing three boundaries, before he departed as well. The Kiwis were 48/2 at that stage when Taylor joined Williamson at the crease. Both of them then batted sensibly for two overs, before lunch was taken. After lunch, New Zealand came out looking to finish the job quickly, but Taylor soon fell trying to slog one out of the park. Elliott and Williamson then put on a good 40-run partnership but Williamson, who was looking in great touch, got out to Davey in the 18th over. Elliott also departed after making a good looking 29 to leave the Kiwis stuttering at 117/5. Anderson was dropped by Wardlaw on 5, but failed to cash in on the reprieve he got. Ronchi also got out soon, trying to play his shots, with the score reading 137/7 at that stage. But, Vettori and Milne made sure that they didn't lose any more wickets and took their team home.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players shake hands with each other. The New Zealand dressing room looks relieved. The Scotland players walk back solemnly. They did well to ruffle the hosts, defending such a meagre total.]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Vettori, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>New Zealand win their second game in the tournament</b>! They had to fight hard for it but they have finally crossed the line. It was a length delivery on off, Vettori looks to pull it across the line, closes the bat face early, gets a thick leading edge and the ball flies to the third man fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Milne, 1 run, back of a length and outside off, Milne runs it down to third man with an open bat face, the scores are <b>tied</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Milne, no run, fuller around off, Milne gets forward and taps it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Vettori, 1 run, fullish on the pads, Vettori leans forward and clips it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Vettori, 2 runs, shortish and outside off, Vettori drags the pull to deep mid-wicket, where the fielder runs along the rope to his right and cuts off the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Milne, no run, length delivery on middle and off, Milne blocks it off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Vettori, 1 run, back of a length on leg, Vettori works it off the pads to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Adam Milne, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Ronchi, <b>out</b> Caught by Gardiner!! This is almost comical by New Zealand! It was a shortish ball from Davey, Ronchi gets back and pulls, finds the man at deep mid-wicket to perfection. He shakes his head as he walks away. <b>Ronchi c Gardiner b Davey 12(10) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Davey to Ronchi, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Ronchi, <b>FOUR</b>, fuller on middle and leg, Ronchi leans forward and flicks it to the deep mid-wicket fence, just beats the fielder and goes through]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Daniel Vettori, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Corey Anderson, <b>out</b> Caught by Iain Wardlaw!! Another one goes! New Zealand are just 10 runs away from a win and they are falling down rapidly. Anderson picks this one from his pads and flicks it in the air, ends up top-edging it to fine leg. Wardlaw does well to judge the catch and snaffle it in front of the rope. <b>Corey Anderson c Iain Wardlaw b Davey 11(16) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Davey to Corey Anderson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Corey Anderson, <b>FOUR</b>, fuller on middle, Davey was searching for the yorker there, Anderson leans forward nicely and flicks it between mid-wicket and mid-on to take New Zealand closer to victory]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Ronchi, <b>FOUR</b>, this time Ronchi has managed to pierce the gap well. Shortish and offering good width, the batsman goes on the back foot and slaps it to the deep backward point fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Ronchi, 2 runs, shortish and outside off, Ronchi cuts it towards square third man, where the fielder dives near the rope and cuts it off]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Ronchi, no run, length delivery coming back in, Ronchi bunts it just in front of point]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Ronchi, no run, fuller on off, Ronchi gets forward and jams it back to the bowler, who mock throws it at Ronchi]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Ronchi, no run, fullish and coming back into the batsman, Ronchi drives it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[A couple of slips in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Corey Anderson, 1 run, length delivery just outside off, Anderson drives it to mid-off for a brisk single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Ronchi, 2 runs, length delivery on middle, Ronchi looks to pull it and mistimes the shot towards long-on but it falls in no-man's land, the man from mid-on backtracks and stops it before the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Ronchi, no run, back of a length and coming back in a touch, Ronchi works it into the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Ronchi, no run, defends it off the inside half of the bat towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Corey Anderson, 1 run, <b>dropped</b> by Wardlaw at fine leg! Anderson swivels on the back foot and pulls this short of length delivery hard and flat towards fine leg, where Wardlaw gets his hands to the ball but spills it. That was as easy as it could get, really poor by Wardlaw to drop it]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Corey Anderson, no run, length delivery around off, Anderson defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Corey Anderson, 2 runs, fullish on middle, Anderson leans in front and works it to mid-wicket for a couple]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Luke Ronchi, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Elliott, <b>out</b> Caught by Matthew Cross!! What are New Zealand doing? They have lost half their side in chase of this paltry total. Wardlaw gets his third! It was a back of a length delivery from him, Elliott presses forward and hangs his bat away from his body, nicks it off to the keeper. <b>Elliott c Matthew Cross b Iain Wardlaw 29(31) [4s-5]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Iain Wardlaw to Elliott, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Elliott, 2 runs, leans forward to this fullish ball on middle and leg and clips it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Elliott, no run, defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Elliott, <b>FOUR</b>, nicely done by Elliott, he has just clipped that away elegantly to the leg-side, it was a full toss bowled onto the pads by Wardlaw, Elliott flicks it in the air to the deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Elliott, no run, shortish and around off, Elliott looks to cut, it was not all that wide, gets a thick under edge that goes on the bounce to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Corey Anderson, 1 run, on middle and leg, Anderson leans forward and clips it to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Corey Anderson, 1 run, short of length on middle, Anderson goes on the back foot and pulls it through backward square leg, finds the fielder in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Corey Anderson, no run, slower delivery from Davey this time, Anderson watches it closely and lets it go through]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Corey Anderson, no run, fullish and wide from Davey, Anderson reaches out and mistimes it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Corey Anderson, no run, on a good length on middle and off, Anderson gets forward and taps it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Corey Anderson, no run, on the pads, Anderson leans forward and turns it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Corey Anderson, no run, back of a length on middle and off, Anderson defends it by taking his bottom hand off the bat into the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Elliott, no run, almost edged that one! A swing and a miss by Elliott. It was a shortish delivery moving away, Elliott flashes at it, misses and the ball travels into the keeper's gloves]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Corey Anderson, 1 run, shortish on leg, Anderson swivels back and pulls it along the ground to fine leg, finds the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Corey Anderson, no run, short of length on middle and leg, Anderson hops inside the crease and defends it back]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Elliott, 1 run, outside off, Elliott comes on the front foot and drives it square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Elliott, no run, oh dear, he almost chopped this back onto the stumps! It was a fullish delivery that shapes back in slightly, Elliott pushes at it away from his body, the ball takes the thickish inside edge and almost goes onto the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Elliott, no run, fuller around off, Elliott gets forward and drives it straight to mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Iain Wardlaw [6.0-0-33-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Corey Anderson, no run, stays on the back foot on this back of a length delivery and blocks it with a straightish bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Corey Anderson, <b>wide</b>, slides it down leg, Anderson is not able to connect with the glance]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Corey Anderson, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Williamson, <b>out</b> Caught by Matthew Cross!! Williamson perishes! He was looking good for a fifty here. He steps out of the crease to his length delivery and looks to hammer it, gets a thick inside edge and the ball goes through to the keeper, who moves to his left to snaffle it. It was dying down on him but Cross does well to hang onto the take. Williamson was unsure whether that had carried but the umpire sends him off. <b>Williamson c Matthew Cross b Davey 38(45) [4s-6]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Davey to Williamson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Williamson, 2 runs, a leg-side half volley by Davey, Williamson leans forward and clips it to deep mid-wicket for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Williamson, no run, skips out of the crease and looks to defend, the ball lobs off the inside edge, swirls in the air for a while and drops into the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Williamson, no run, in that channel outside off, does not interest Williamson into playing at it]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Williamson, no run, good-looking shot by Williamson but he finds the mid-off fielder, presses forward to this full delivery around off and drives it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Elliott, no run, gets down on one knee and drags the sweep from outside off behind square]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Elliott, <b>FOUR</b>, short, wide and punished by Elliott. He comfortably goes on the back foot and slaps it to the sweeper cover fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Williamson, 1 run, comes on the front foot and drives it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Williamson, no run, leans forward and pushes it towards mid-wicket, where the fielder dives to his left and cuts it off]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Elliott, 1 run, flighted on middle and off, Elliott drives it softly towards long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Williamson, 1 run, fullish on middle and off, Williamson works it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Elliott, no run, touch shortish and outside off, Elliott cuts it off the back foot, finds the man at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Williamson, 1 run, fullish on middle and leg, Williamson leans forward and works it through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Elliott, 1 run, length delivery on middle and leg, Elliott turns it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Elliott, no run, a beauty by Davey this time! It was a length delivery that nips back in sharply, Elliott looks to defend off the front foot, the ball just about whistles past the inside edge of his bat and goes through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Elliott, no run, stays back and looks to defend, the ball brushes his thigh pad and rolls into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Elliott, <b>FOUR</b>, 'catch it' is the call but the ball was just out of reach of the short cover fielder. It was a fullish delivery outside off, draws Elliott on the front foot, who creams the drive through the off-side, the fielder at short cover dives to his left but does not get to the ball as it races away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, drifts it in, Williamson is quick to get down on one knee and sweeps it to the backward square leg fence. He wants to get this done with as soon as possible]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Elliott, 1 run, flighted on middle, Elliott gets forward and drives it past the diving mid-on fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Williamson, 1 run, gets forward and wrists it to deep mid-wicket for a comfortable single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Williamson, no run, steps out once again and looks to drive it into the on-side, the ball turns in, takes the inside half of the bat and rolls towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Williamson, no run, stays on the back foot and punches it softly towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Elliott, 1 run, skips out of the crease and drives it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Williamson, no run, fuller on middle and off, Williamson gets forward and defends it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Williamson, no run, comes on the front foot and defends this good length ball into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Elliott, 1 run, opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Elliott, <b>FOUR</b>, another boundary for Elliott. It was a length ball just outside off, Elliott gets forward and drives it square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Elliott, no run, length delivery on middle and off, Elliott defends it to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Elliott, <b>FOUR</b>, fantastic shot from Elliott, he sees the width on offer by Davey, stays back and has a crack at it, sends it racing away to the deep backward point fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Josh Davey [1.0-0-7-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, short delivery on middle and leg, Williamson pulls it to the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Williamson, no run, steps out of the crease and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Williamson, no run, leans forward and turns it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Elliott, 1 run, presses forward and pushes it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Elliott, no run, Elliott gets down on one knee and looks to sweep, misses the ball and it goes off his forearm through to the slip fielder, who moves across and snaffles it. Cross was sure that came off the glove and the Scotland players go for a review but the replays were quite clear on that. Good call by umpire Nigel Llong]]></line><line><![CDATA[Loud appeal for a catch taken by the slip fielder. But the umpire is unmoved. Scotland <b>review</b> it after a bit of consulation. Replays show that the ball came off Elliott's forearm. Should be NOT OUT. Yes, the onfield decision stays.]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Williamson, 1 run, lunges on the front foot and works it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jamie</b> has something to say about Taylor's wicket: "Taylor's wicket hasn't really dimmed the crowd's enthusiasm. Whooping from a section down behind deep point. The DJ's selection of tracks also keeps people swaying."]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Elliott, no run, length delivery on middle and off, Elliott presses forward and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Elliott, no run, on a good length on off, Elliott blocks it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Elliott, no run, fuller on middle and off, Elliott defends it off the front foot towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Elliott, no run, fuller and shaping away from the batsman, Elliott shoulders arms to it]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Elliott, no run, in the channel outside off, left alone by Elliott]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Williamson, leg byes, 1 run, looks to flick, the ball goes off the pads behind square, the batsmen scamper through for a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Williamson, <b>wide</b>, high bouncer on off, Williamson gets away from it at the last moment and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Elliott, no run, presses on the front foot and wrists it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Williamson, 1 run, gets forward and taps it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Grant Elliott, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Ross Taylor, <b>out</b> Caught by Rob Taylor!! Ross Taylor departs in search of some quick runs. He charges down the track and slogs it hard across the line. He has mistimed that however, ends up finding the man at deep mid-wicket to perfection. Rob Taylor does well to hold onto the catch at the edge of the rope. <b>Ross Taylor c Rob Taylor b Haq 9(14) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Haq to Ross Taylor, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Ross Taylor, no run, stays inside the line and taps it to the right of the bowler, who quickly moves across and cuts it off]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Ross Taylor, no run, leans forward and works it to the on-side once again]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Haq to Ross Taylor, no run, flighted on middle and off, Taylor turns it just in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Majid Haq, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Spin from the other end. Haq comes into the attack]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Williamson, no run, full and angled in, Williamson knocks it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Ross Taylor, 3 runs, straying on the pads, Taylor leans forward a touch and flicks it to deep mid-wicket, the fielder drags back the ball just before the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Ross Taylor, no run, on a good length and around off, Taylor pushes it to backward point, where the fielder dives to his left and stops it]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Ross Taylor, no run, fuller on middle and leg, Taylor defends it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Ross Taylor, no run, shuffles across a touch and defends it to the left of the bowler, who just has to move slightly across to field it]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Ross Taylor, no run, fullish and around off, Taylor presses forward and bunts it in front of point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Wardlaw will continue after the break. A slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back. New Zealand are only 80 runs away from securing a comfortable win. Williamson is looking in fine touch and would want to chase this down as quickly as possible.]]></line><line><![CDATA[New Zealand started off brightly, but Guptill got out early after hitting a few fours. Williamson then joined McCullum at the crease, who played aggressively for a little while, but perished while trying to run it down to third man. Currently, Williamson and Taylor are at the crease and Williamson looks in superb nick. New Zealand need 80 runs from 41 overs to win this game. It should be easy, but they need to be wary of the Scottish bowlers. Take a break and join us in a short while to follow the final part of the run-chase.]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, shuffles across and pulls this short delivery outside off to the deep mid-wicket fence, nice way to <b>go into lunch</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Williamson, no run, fullish delivery on off and middle, Williamson goes slightly across and drives it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Williamson, no run, in the channel outside off, Williamson puts his front foot forward and defends it behind square on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Williamson, no run, length delivery around off, Williamson defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Ross Taylor, 1 run, on a good length and around off, Taylor bunts it down in front of mid-on and sets off for a single, makes it comfortably at the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Williamson, 1 run, on middle stump line, Williamson nurdles it behind square for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Williamson, <b>wide</b>, another one well down leg, wided by the umpire as the keeeper dives to his left and stops the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Josh Davey, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Ross Taylor, no run, fullish delivery around off, Taylor was looking to work it into the on-side, he gets an inside edge on the pad, there was an appeal, but the umpire knew that there was bat involved]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Ross Taylor, no run, good ball from Taylor to Taylor, it was on a good length and angled across off, Taylor shuffled across and was looking to push it down to long-off, but the ball shapes back just a touch and beats the inside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Ross Taylor, <b>FOUR</b>, fuller in length and slightly wide outside off, Taylor presses forward and drives it to the deep extra cover fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Williamson, 1 run, around middle stump line, Williamson clips it towards mid-wicket and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Williamson, <b>wide</b>, bowls this one well down leg, wided by the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Ross Taylor, 1 run, the running between these two has always been a problem, Taylor bunts this towards cover-point and sets off for a single, but Williamson was right to send him back, Taylor makes it in time as the fielder fires in the throw and the batsmen then run on the overthrow as there was no one backing up]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Williamson, 1 run, slightly back of a length delivery outside off, Williamson goes on the back foot and punches it past a diving backward point for a single, the batsmen were thinking about the second, but it's not there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ross Taylor, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Brendon McCullum, <b>out</b> Caught by Matthew Cross!! McCullum departs 10 minutes before the lunch break. It was just short of a good length and shaping away outside off, McCullum was looking to run it down between the keeper and slip, but ends up edging it to the keeper, who moves to his right to snaffle it. <b>Brendon McCullum c Matthew Cross b Iain Wardlaw 15(12) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Iain Wardlaw to Brendon McCullum, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Williamson, 1 run, length delivery outside off, Williamson waits inside the crease, opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Williamson, no run, on a good length and around off, Williamson gets behind the line and defends with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, another shortish delivery and Williamson gives it the treatment it deserves. He gets on top of it and cuts it square of the wicket, the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Williamson, no run, slightly fuller and on off this time, Williamson defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, not a great delivery to start the over, it was short and outside off, Williamson goes deep in the crease and has enough time to pull it to the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Williamson, 1 run, on the pads this time, Williamson works it to deep mid-wicket and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Williamson, no run, on a good length and on off, Williamson defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Williamson, <b>wide</b>, down the leg-side, Williamson fails to glance it and the umpire calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Williamson, no run, driven to mid-off after leaning forward to this fullish delivery]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Williamson, no run, fullish around off, Williamson drives it to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Williamson, no run, angles this one across off, Williamson was looking to run it down to third man, but the ball was too close to him and he ends up getting an inside edge that rolls past the off stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Williamson, no run, on a good length and around off, Williamson defends from the crease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Brendon McCullum, no run, slightly back of a length delivery around off, McCullum hangs back and punches it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, super shot from McCullum, it was short and wide, McCullum goes on the back foot and cuts it square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Brendon McCullum, no run, jags back in towards McCullum, who was on the back foot and was pushing at it, but the ball beats the inside half of the blade and the keeper collects, the ball went over the stumps as well on that occasion, good bowling this]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Brendon McCullum, no run, just short of a good length and shapes back in towards the batsman, McCullum was looking to cut it hard, but was cramped for room]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Brendon McCullum, no run, bunts this back of a length delivery towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, gives the charge this time and takes this length delivery on the full, he drives it past a diving extra cover and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Our man <b>Jamie</b> describes Guptill's dismissal for us from the ground: "Martin Guptill wafted at the air after getting out. Not a dismissal he'll look back on fondly, obviously. Ian Wardlaw didn't celebrate much. Matt Machan, down at third man, shouting support"]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, back of a length delivery outside off, Williamson punches it to the deep extra cover fence, good shot from the Kiwi vice-captain]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Williamson, no run, on a good length and angling away, left alone by Williamson]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, on leg stump line, McCullum works it behind square for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Williamson, 1 run, dabs this one to the left of backward point and sets off for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, <b>dropped!</b> That's a big let off by Scotland, it was on the pads, McCullum flicks it in the air and Gardiner at deep square leg runs to his left and dives, but can't hold onto the catch. McCullum was very lucky there]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, uppish but in the gap, it was fuller outside off, McCullum leans into the drive and hits it uppishly, wide of cover and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Williamson, no run, slightly wide outside off this time, Williamson is happy to let that one go through]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Williamson, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Williamson jumps in the crease and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kane Williamson, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Guptill, <b>out</b> Caught by Matthew Cross!! Guptill goes and Scots draw first blood in this innings. It was fuller and just outside off, Guptill was looking to drive, but the ball shapes away and takes the outside edge instead. The keeper moves to his right and takes a simple catch. <b>Guptill c Matthew Cross b Iain Wardlaw 17(14) [4s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Iain Wardlaw to Guptill, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Guptill, no run, slightly fuller this time and swings away outside off, Guptill is happy to leave this one]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Guptill, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>crunched!</b> Superb shot from Guptill and this is poor bowling from Wardlaw, it was short and wide outside off, Guptill stays back and cuts it square of the wicket, the ball went to the fence like a tracer bullet]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Guptill, <b>FOUR</b>, good shot from Guptill, it was short and outside off, Guptill latches onto it in a flash, he dispatches the pull to the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Brendon McCullum, no run, full and angled across off, McCullum was early into the drive and ends up chipping it a little uppishly towards mid-off, luckily for him, he didn't hit it too hard and the ball bounced before the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Guptill, 1 run, bit too straight again in line, Guptill moves across and works it through square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Guptill, no run, on the pads this time, Guptill looks to glance it fine, but can't connect at all. The ball rolls away to short fine leg off the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Guptill, no run, good length delivery around off, Guptill looks to defend, the ball rolls away into the off-side off the outside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Guptill, <b>FOUR</b>, full delivery on off, Guptill closes the bat face and drives it uppishly to the left of mid-on, the fielder had no chance of cutting that off]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, full and angling away outside off, McCullum chases it and goes hard at it, he got it off the toe-end of the bat and the ball goes over the cover infield, the batsmen take a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rob Taylor, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Taylor will share the attack with Wardlaw. There are two slips in place as well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Guptill, no run, on a good length and on off, Guptill bunts it dead straight and the ball hits the timber at the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Guptill, no run, leaves this full delivery outside off for the keeper to collect]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Guptill, <b>FOUR</b>, good shot to get off the mark, it was fullish and around off, Guptill drills the drive back towards the bowler, who puts his right hand out, but only manages to parry it over the umpire's head and the ball beats the mid-on fielder to the fence, Nigel Llong was ducking for cover there]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Guptill, no run, bit of width on offer and Guptill looks to cut, but ends up chopping it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Guptill, no run, fullish delivery shaping away outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Guptill, no run, on a good length and around off, Guptill goes slightly across and works it towards mid-on, the ball disturbed the surface when it landed there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Guptill and Brendon McCullum are at the crease. Guptill is on strike. Iain Wardlaw will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Black Caps openers are making their way out to the middle. Scotland players are in a huddle. Wardlaw will open the bowling for the Scots and Guptill will be on strike first up. There are 2 slips in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Scotland made a dubious record today - <b>5 batsmen got out on a duck</b>, out of which <b>4 were golden ducks</b>. This is the most number of ducks for Scotland in an ODI innings.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The New Zealand new ball bowlers - Southee and Boult are becoming an exciting combination. They might be the best exponents of the new cherry going around the world. Milne went past the edge on a number of times, but was unlucky not to have picked up a wicket. Anderson provided the crucial wickets and Vettori ran through the tail. Now upto the hosts' batsmen to chase this down.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Machan and Berrington saw off the threatening spell with some solid batting. The pair did all the hard work and then started to play freely. They added 97 runs for the 5th wicket and got to their respective fifties. However, they fell in quick succession and left Scotland in deeper trouble. The lower-order was no match for Vettori, who outfoxed them with his variations. New Zealand will now come out to bat in 10 minutes time and will bat till the scheduled lunch time, that means they will bat for around 40 minutes.]]></line><line><![CDATA[McCullum at the toss said, that the ball would do a bit for the first 30-45 minutes and it certainly did. But it needed the bowlers to land it in the right areas, Boult and Southee did just that. The latter started with a maiden and the former backed it up with two wickets in the over. Southee then picked up two more to reduce Scotland to 12/4. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Iain Wardlaw, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Floated up on off and middle, Wardlaw goes forward for the defensive push, but the ball strikes the pad first instead of the bat. The umpire gave it 'Not Out', but Vettori and McCullum were confident that the ball hit the pad first. As it turns out, it was crashing into middle and it was a good review from the Kiwis. <b>Iain Wardlaw lbw b Vettori 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Vettori to Iain Wardlaw, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[New Zealand have decided to review an LBW decision. Wardlaw is the man in question. Was it pad first? Let's see. Vettori's front foot is fine. There were two noises, but it looks to have hit the pad first. The umpire is taking his time, checking all the angles. It definitely hits the pad first. The height looks good as well. Marais Erasmus is the TV umpire.  I can't understand why the third umpire is taking so much time. Hawk-Eye shows that the ball is hitting top of middle and <b>Scotland are all out for 142</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Iain Wardlaw, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Haq, <b>out</b> Caught by Ross Taylor!! Vettori gets another one, two in two overs for him. It was floated up just outside off, Haq was pushing at it off the front foot, the ball doesn't spin back and goes on with the angle, takes the outside edge and Taylor moves to his left to take a simple catch at slip. <b>Haq c Ross Taylor b Vettori 0(2)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Vettori to Haq, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Davey, no run, bumper from Anderson, Davey ducks under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Davey, no run, bowls this one on a length and around off, Davey defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Davey, 2 runs, banged in short and at the batsman, Davey pulls, but can't time it right, the ball falls in no man's land and rolls towards deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[The <b>batting powerplay</b> is currently going on]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Davey, <b>FOUR</b>, shortish and wide outside off, Davey cuts it square of the wicket and the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Davey, no run, just short of a good length and around middle stump line, Davey pushes it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Davey, no run, back of a length delivery angling in from round the stumps, Davey looks to push at it, the ball goes past the inside edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Haq, no run, flatter delivery outside off, Haq dabs it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Majid Haq, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Rob Taylor, <b>out</b> Stumped!! Vettori strikes now. Vettori gave this one more around off, Taylor was looking to work it through the off-side, but the ball goes straight on. He misses the shot and falls over after losing his balance. Ronchi collects and whips the bails off in a flash. Scotland in deep toruble now. <b>Rob Taylor st Ronchi b Vettori 4(6)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Vettori to Rob Taylor, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Stumped!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Davey, 1 run, slows this one on middle and leg, Davey nudges it behind square for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Rob Taylor, 1 run, floated just outside off, Taylor drives it wide of mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Rob Taylor, no run, flatter around off, Taylor stays back and punches it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Davey, 1 run, drifting on the pads, Davey works it to deep square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Daniel Vettori [7.0-1-21-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Vettori comes back, replacing Milne]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Rob Taylor, 2 runs, bit too straight this time, Taylor clips it off his pad to the right of fine leg, who runs across to field the ball, the batsmen take two]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Davey, 1 run, shortish outside off, Davey hangs back and cuts it square of the wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Rob Taylor, 1 run, just short of a good length and outside off, Taylor hangs back and dabs it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Rob Taylor, no run, on a good length outside off, Cross lifts his bat and leaves it for the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[Back to over the wicket to the left-hander]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rob Taylor, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Matthew Cross, <b>out</b> Caught by Ronchi!! Anderson strikes yet again. Scotland are seven down now. It wasn't a wicket-taking delivery though, but the Kiwis won't mind it. It was short and a little wide outside off, Cross hangs back and looks to cut, goes off the toe-end of the bat to the keeper. Anderson celebrates in delight. <b>Matthew Cross c Ronchi b Corey Anderson 14(18) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Corey Anderson to Matthew Cross, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Matthew Cross, no run, just short of a good length and just outside off, Cross hangs back and defends]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> arrive on the field! Scotland have recovered well after being in a precarious situation. Machan and Berrington got to their respective fifties and threw it away. They would have loved the pair to carry on for a little while longer. Anyway, the New Zealand bowlers well now look to wrap up the lower-order as quickly as possible.]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Davey, no run, short of length on off, defended down the wicket with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Matthew Cross, 1 run, length ball on off, Cross stays in the crease and eases it wide of cover with an angled bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Davey, 1 run, good length ball around off, Davey drives it on the up towards mid-off, Baz fields the ball running to his right]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Davey, no run, quick bouncer on middle and leg, Davey goes down and lets it go through to Ronchi]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Matthew Cross, 1 run, on a length outside off, Cross checks his shot and pushes it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Matthew Cross, <b>FOUR</b>, top shot! Back of a length just outside off, Cross stands tall and punches it sweetly through cover-point. He didn't try to hit it hard, relied more on timing than power]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Davey, no run, bumper and just outside off, Davey looks to ramp it over the slip cordon, fails to make contact]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Davey, no run, once again finds the backward point fielder, he tried to steer it and picked up Guptill]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Davey, no run, slightly short and just outside off, Davey goes hard on the cut, chops it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Davey, no run, shortens the length further, Davey jumps up and fends it with soft hands in front of point]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Davey, no run, back of a length just outside off, Davey gets behind the line and blocks it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Davey, no run, bumper outside off, Davey lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Matthew Cross, no run, <b>dropped!</b> Pitched up outside off, Cross slices the drive to backward point. The ball flew low towards Guptill, who gets both hands to it but can't hold on. The standars that he sets for himself, he should have taken that]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Matthew Cross, 2 runs, too straight, on the middle stump line, Cross leans forward and whips it behind square leg, Vettori runs across from fine leg, slides and makes a fine stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Davey, 1 run, fuller and on off, Davey shuffles across and flicks it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Matthew Cross, 1 run, slants back in from short of length, Cross stays back and nurdles it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Matthew Cross, no run, sharp bouncer, Cross was shaping to play the pull, but decides against it at the last instant. The square leg umpire signals one for the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Matthew Cross, no run, fuller and on off, Cross presses forward and knocks it in front of cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Matthew Cross, 1 run, almost another one! Good length ball just outside off, Cross pushes at it away from the body, the ball takes the outside half and flies to the left of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[Switches it to round the wicket!]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Matthew Cross, no run, drags the length back outside off, Cross lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Matthew Cross, no run, slanted across the right-hander, Cross covers the line and lets it pass]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Josh Davey, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Berrington, <b>out</b> Caught by Milne!! Once again it is that man, Anderson! He has now got rid of both set batsmen. Well directed short delivery, it was angled in from round the wicket, Berrington goes for the pull, top-edges it to fine leg, Milne runs forward and completes a simple catch. <b>Berrington c Milne b Corey Anderson 50(80) [4s-4 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Corey Anderson to Berrington, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Berrington, 2 runs, this time manages to evade the backward point fielder, short again and Berrington cuts it square of the wicket. Southee does well to keep them down to a couple. That brings up the <b>fifty</b> for Berrington. Another crucial innings from the Scottish batsman]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Berrington, no run, goes round the wicket, drops it short and outside off, Berrington chops the cut straight to backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Matthew Cross, no run, bumper to end the over, Cross ducks under it and allows it to sail over him]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Matthew Cross, no run, good length ball on off, Cross defends solidly off the front foot to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Matthew Cross, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! Fast and targeted at the stumps, Cross leans slightly forward and works it wide of mid-on. It was just a push and the pace of Milne took it to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Matthew Cross, no run, lifter that jags back in, Cross does well to hoist his bat and get out of the way. That kept raising on him]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Matthew Cross, no run, beaten! On a length and in the corridor of uncertainty, Cross' feet went nowhere as he tried to defend, the ball whizzes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, 1 run, back of a length and held its line, Berrington is opened up slightly, the ball squirts off the outside edge to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Adam Milne [4.0-0-16-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Berrington, 1 run, shortens the length, Berrington hangs back and tucks it behind square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Matthew Cross, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Machan, <b>out</b> Caught by Brendon McCullum!! Anderson strikes! Some consider him as the golden arm and that is why. He provides the crucial breakthrough. It also needed a superb catch from Baz to send back Machan. Banged in short, Machan fetches the pull from outside off, splices it over mid-on, McCullum runs across from mid-off, dives full length and holds onto a terrific catch. <b>Machan c Brendon McCullum b Corey Anderson 56(79) [4s-7 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Corey Anderson to Machan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Machan, no run, back of a length around off, Machan defends it in front of point]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Machan, <b>FOUR</b>, drilled! Gives the charge to Anderson, converts it into a length delivery, flat-bats it wide of mid-off. That came right off the meat of the bat as the ball rocketed away to the fence. It was a shot of authority from Machan]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Machan, no run, little extra bounce for Anderson, keeps it back of a length and gets it to shape away, Machan pushes at it and is beaten comprehensively]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Machan, no run, shortish and outside off, Machan misses out on the cut shot as the ball beats the outside edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Corey Anderson, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Berrington, <b>FOUR</b>, Ronchi shouted "catch", but it evaded Williamson. Full and slanting into the pads, Berrington leans forward and clips it in the air to the right of square leg, Williamson dives full length, but the ball is too far away from him]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Machan, 1 run, slower delivery that is dragged back, Machan goes back and pulls it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Berrington, 1 run, just a bit of width, Berrington uses it and steers it wide of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Machan, 1 run, too full and just outside off, Machan squeezes the drive to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Machan, no run, angling in on off, Machan defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Berrington, 1 run, good length ball on off, Berrington stays in the crease and pats it to cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, 1 run, slows this up and gets it to drift, Berrington is early into the shot, he checks his drive, the ball lobs to the right of Vettori, who dives and can't get there]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, no run, pushed through on off, Berrington looks to force it off the back foot, is beaten by the extra bounce. That was not far away from the off-pole either]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, no run, dabs it off the back foot towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, no run, arm-ball on off, Berrington goes back and taps it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, <b>SIX</b>, fabulous shot! Great use of the feet, dances down the wicket, meets the pitch of the ball and lofts it handsomely all the way over long-on. That ball hit the wall and came back onto the ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, 1 run, Machan brings up his <b>3rd ODI fifty</b>. It has been a fine innings. We can hear a few bagpipes in the background. Quicker and around off, Machan guides it towards backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Berrington, no run, slower ball to end the over, Berrington gets inside the line and turns it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Machan, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Machan drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Machan, no run, slanted in on middle, Machan looks to work it through the on-side, misses and wears it high on the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Berrington, 1 run, slower delivery in the blockhole, Berrington squeezes it out to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Machan, 1 run, angled in on off, Machan drops it wide of point, looks at Berrington who scampers through for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Machan, no run, starts from round the wicket, on a length close to off, Machan guides it to backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Grant Elliott, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jamie</b> on how the mood around the ground is, "Had a stroll around one section of the park. Fans milling around the various kiosks. One part of the stands is particularly cheerful, chanting for the home team. The assault against Tim Southee in his last two overs did silence them momentarily, but otherwise the crowd is largely backing New Zealand."]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, 1 run, comes down the track, Vettori sees that and fires it down leg, Machan adjusts well and nudges it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, no run, tossed up on off, Machan comes half-forward and defends it to the right of Vettori]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, 1 run, tad short and just outside off, Berrington chops the cut to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, no run, flighted on off, Berrington presses forward and blocks it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, 1 run, nurdled away behind square leg for a comfortable single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, no run, slower and on the stumps, Machan turns it softly to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, no run, on a length just outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, <b>FOUR</b>, poor delivery from Southee, short and plenty of width on offer, Berrington goes deep in the crease and cuts it past a diving backward point. The fielder at third man had no chance of stopping that]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Machan, 1 run, dug in short, Machan fetches it from outside off and pulls it in front of square for a run. The fielder did well to keep it to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Machan, <b>SIX</b>, follows the yorkers with a short delivery, Machan is up for it, he swivels and pulls, gets a top-edge and the ball flies over the fine leg fence for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Machan, no run, another yorker on off, Machan opens the bat face and digs it out to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, 1 run, how did that miss the stumps? Southee spears in a yorker, Berrington gets his front leg out of the way, jams it off the outside edge, the ball misses the off-pole by inches. Baz asked Ronchi whether it hit the pad first, he says no and New Zealand don't review it. The ball went to the right of Ronchi, who dived and got a glove to it. Even if he had caught that, it wouldn't have mattered as the ball bounced before going to him]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, no run, an acrobatic save from the veteran, even the batsman has a smile on his face. It was quicker and on off, Machan squeezes it to the left of the bowler, Vettori dives full length and plucks it out of thin air. He was parallel to the air when he collected it]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, no run, goes on with the arm, Machan uses the angle and steers it to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, no run, slower and on middle, Machan turns it gently to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, no run, opens the bat face and runs it to short third man, shouts "no" for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, 1 run, fraction short and outside off, Berrington cuts it square of the wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, 1 run, comes down the track and eases it down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, no run, on a length just outside off, Berrington has a go at that, the ball zips past the outside edge. Loose shot from Berrington!]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, <b>FOUR</b>, superb shot! Southee provides a bit of width and Berrington does not miss out. He comes forward and square drives it, he rolled his wrists on top of that to get it in the gap. Elliott at extra cover dived and got a fingertip, but could not stop it completely]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, no run, now Berrington decides to advance down the wicket, the ball straightens a touch, he closes the bat face and gets a soft leading edge towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, no run, good length ball on off, Berrington plays it with soft hands and the ball rolls to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Machan, 1 run, banged in and aimed at the batsman, Machan fends it rather awkwardly to fine leg. The ball got slightly big on him]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Machan, <b>FOUR</b>, cracking shot! Southee comes round the wicket, bowls it on a length outside off, Machan charges down the wicket and drills it through extra cover. There was no stopping that as the ball scooted away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, 1 run, slider that goes on with the arm, Machan looks to punch and gets a thickish outside edge wide of short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, no run, flighted on off, Machan gets inside the line and tucks it in front of short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, no run, slower and on the stumps, Machan turns it gently towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, no run, kneels down and looks to sweep, gloves it to short fine leg, thought about the single but Berrington was not interested]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, no run, walks down the pitch, Vettori holds it back, defended down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, 1 run, throws this up outside off, Berrington takes a step down the wicket and drives it to wide long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, 1 run, pitched up just outside off, Berrington goes hard on the drive, the ball takes the inside half and rolls towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, no run, good length ball on off, Berrington leans forward, guides it to point with an angled bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, no run, hint of inward movement, Berrington is half-forward and defending to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, no run, fuller and close to off, Berrington presses it to cover after coming forward]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Machan, 1 run, keeps it back of a length around off, Machan stays in the crease and dabs it to square third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, 1 run, on a length just outside off, Berrington walks across his stumps and works it to the right of mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tim Southee [5.0-3-11-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, no run, tossed up around off, Machan presses forward and defends it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, 2 runs, quicker and outside off, Machan cuts it in front of square, the fielder at deep point runs to his left and tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, no run, flighted on off, Machan drives it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, 1 run, short and outside off, Berrington cuts it square of the wicket, sweeper runs to his left and keeps it to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, no run, slows this up considerably, Berrington drops it in front of point, shouts "no" for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, no run, comes down the track and whips it towards short mid-wicket, where Guptill dives and saves a run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, 1 run, angled in on middle, Berrington leans forward and flicks it to the right of mid-on, Vettori gives chase and keeps it to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, 2 runs, fuller on off and middle, Berrington squirts it off the outside half of the bat to sweeper cover, Guptill and Anderson restrict it to a couple. That also brings up the <b>50</b> for Scotland]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, no run, shortens the length and gets it to hold its line, Berrington has a tentative poke at it and the ball fizzes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, <b>wide</b>, bumper down leg, Berrington sits down and lets it pass, umpire Llong calls it a wide for line]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Machan, 1 run, dug in mid-way down the wicket, Machan stands tall and fends it to the off-side, Berrington calls him for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Machan, no run, top stop from Williamson, half volley outside off, Machan leans forward and creams the drive towards cover, Williamson dives to his right and makes a fine save]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Machan, no run, pitched up just outside off, Machan drives it towards cover, the fielder makes a half stop, but the batsmen don't risk the single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, no run, tossed up close to off, blocked off the front foot towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, no run, fires it in around off, Berrington lookes to punch it, but is beaten by the extra bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, no run, floated up around off, Berrington defends it in front of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, no run, takes a couple of steps down the wicket, is beaten in the flight, ekes out an inside edge onto the pad and the ball dribbles to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, no run, quicker and bit of extra bounce, Berrington looks to force it off the back foot, the ball takes the outside edge and rolls to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, no run, straighter one just outside off, Berrington goes for the cut and misses, that was not far away from the edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now. Some recovery from Scotland after Boult and Southee threatened to blow them away. New Zealand are well ahead though.]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, 3 runs, nicely played by Berrington, half-volley outside off from Milne, Berrington leans half forward and drives it past extra cover, McCullum gives chase and keeps them down to three runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Berrington gets behind the line and defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Machan, 1 run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Machan hangs his bat at that, gets a thick edge towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Machan, no run, on a good length and shaping away from outside off, Machan fiddles at that and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Machan, no run, the bumper from Milne, well directed by Milne, Machan drops his wrists and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Machan, no run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, bowled at 147.1 kmph, sliced away towards backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, no run, Vettori drifts one onto Berrington's pads, he looks to flick and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, 1 run, Vettori fired this one on Machan's pads as he came down the track, he does well to open the stance and clips it in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, no run, pushed through and on Machan's pads, nudged towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, no run, the slider from Vettori, Machan goes back and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Berrington, 1 run, this one is given more air, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Machan, 1 run, flatter and on Machan's pads, nudged in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Daniel Vettori, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, no run, that's a nothing shot from Berrington, short and holding its line, Berrington was in two minds, decides late against attempting the pull, the ball whizzes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, 2 runs, fuller length delivery and on Berrington's pads, he pushes forward and gets an inside edge past square leg for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jamie</b> sends us this from the ground: "Those two punched boundaries by Machan off Boult last over got the Scottish fans cheering. They'd be hoping for a lot more."]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, no run, full and swinging away from outside off, Berrington went chasing after that and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Berrington gets behind the line and defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, no run, fuller length delivery and in that channel outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, no run, on a good length and on the stumps, Berrington shuffles across and defends it towards the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, <b>FOUR</b>, this is even better! Tad fuller and just outside off, Machan leans half-forward, gets to the pitch of the ball and drives it fluently past the bowler for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, <b>wide</b>, Boult slips one full and well down leg-side, wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, full and wide from Boult, Machan leans forward and drives it sweetly through extra cover for a boundary, the timing was sublime there]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, <b>wide</b>, the bumper from Boult, too short and too high, wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, short and on the stumps, Machan rides with the bounce, plays with soft hands and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Berrington, 1 run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Berrington drives and gets a thick edge towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Berrington, no run, short of a length and shaping away from off, Berrington pushes at that, the ball beats the outside edge and rips through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Berrington, no run, on a good length and shaping away from outside off, left alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, 1 run, fuller length delivery and on Berrington's pads, he pushes forward and gets an inside edge towards long leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>short, wide and four</b>, width on offer from Milne, Berrington cracks it up and over point for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, driven back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, no run, that one almost went through Berrington! This was full and shaped back into Berrington, he was looking to drive and gets an inside edge onto the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, no run, appeal for LBW, but this one nipped back a long way, Berrington was caught in his crease and is struck high on the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Berrington, no run, that's a good start from Milne, on a good length and straightening after pitching, Berrington prods forward and is beaten by a long way]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Adam Milne, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, Machan gets across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, half-volley outside off, Machan leans half-forward and punches it straight to the fielder at cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, short of a length and angling into Machan, Machan shuffles across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, edged and short of 3rd slip, this was very full and nipped away late, Machan was pushing forward in defence, gets a thick edge that drops well in front of the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, fuller length delivery and angling into Machan's pads, he looks to flick and is struck high on the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, Machan shuffles across and defends it towards mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, no run, fuller length delivery and on off, punched back towards the bowler, he gets a hand onto the ball and deflects it away towards mid-off. McCullum gets in and fires a wild throw towards the striker's end]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, no run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, Berrington doesn't need to play at those, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, no run, fuller length delivery and angling away from outside off, easy leave for the batsman]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, no run, that's a peach from Southee, but Berrington's foot movement was very poor, Southee came from wide of the crease and got this one to shape away from off, Berrington was rooted to his crease as he pushed at that and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, no run, on a good length and well outside off, Berrington gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, left alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, 2 runs, too full and on Machan's pads, clipped away backward of square on the on-side for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, short and wide from Boult, Machan throws his bat at that and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Berrington, byes, 1 run, how did that miss the stumps? This was full and shapes back into Berrington, he was looking to flick and was clearly late on the shot. Ronchi was going the wrong way initially, he can't grab it cleanly and allows a bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Berrington, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from well outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA["Drummers doing their thing vigorously but its not doing much to change the feeling of a one-sided contest here." - <b>Jamie</b> chimes in his thoughts]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Berrington, no run, Boult keeps it full and gets it to shape away from well outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Berrington, no run, fuller length delivery and holding its line outside off, left alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Machan, no run, on a good length and in that corridor outside off, dabbed with an open face towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Machan, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Machan gets behind the line and defends it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Machan, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Machan gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Machan, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a cracking shot, too short from Southee, Machan rocks back, rolls his wrists and pulls it past mid-wicket for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Machan, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Machan prods forward and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, worked to the right of cover-point for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Berrington, 1 run, nicely played by Berrington, fuller length delivery and a hint of shape back into Berrington, he covers for the movement and guides it behind square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Berrington, no run, another excellent yorker from Boult, that one nipped back in late as well, Berrington does well to jam his bat down and digs it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Berrington, no run, the inswinger from Boult, Berrington was caught on the move, just about gets his bat down in time and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, 1 run, almost a catch and then almost a run-out! This was banged in short by Boult, Machan went on the pull, doesn't get hold of the shot, the ball loops and falls in front of mid-wicket. The batsmen look for a quick single and Machan has to rush to make his ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, tad fuller and shaping away from off, Machan covers for the movement, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, fuller length delivery and in that channel outside off, Machan covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, no run, too good from Southee, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, Berrington is drawn forward into the forward push, the ball swirls away very late and beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, no run, that's a peach from Southee, tad further and shaping away from outside off, Berrington prods forward and is beaten by a long way, that was pretty much unplayable]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Berrington, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Berrington gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[Three slips and a gully for the <b>hat-trick ball</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Richie Berrington, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Mommsen, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Disaster for Scotland. They have now lost their fourth wicket. <b>Southee is on a hat-trick</b>. This was full and nipped back in late, Mommsen was caught on the shuffle, the ball clipped his pad and then went on to hit the bat. The impact was around middle and it was crashing into leg-stump. <b>Mommsen lbw b Southee 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Southee to Mommsen, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mommsen has been given out <b>LBW</b>. He wants a review. No problems with the no-ball, it is pad first. The impact was around off and middle, the original call is OUT, it has to miss the stumps completely for this decision to be overturned. Three REDS, Mommsen is <b>OUT</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preston Mommsen, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Coetzer, <b>out</b> Caught by Elliott!! Southee strikes! This was full and on Coetzer's pads, he gets across and flicks it in the air, finds Elliott to perfection at mid-wicket. He can't believe his misfortune, yanks his head in the air and walks back in absolute disbelief. Scotland have well and truly been rocked here. <b>Coetzer c Elliott b Southee 1(10)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Southee to Coetzer, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, Machan gets across and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, <b>wide</b>, full and slanting well down leg-side, wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, Boult shortens his length and gets this one to hold its line outside off, Machan gets behind the line in defence]]></line><line><![CDATA["Trent Boult is getting good pace and bounce off the surface. Many plays and misses. Lovely bowling. No breeze, else it could be much tougher for Scotland," - says <b>Jamie Alter</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Machan presses across and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, tad too full and just outside off, Machan leans forward, plays with an open face and works it square past cover-point for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, this is superb bowling from Boult, tad fuller and a hint of shape away, Machan is lured forward before being beaten on the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, Machan shuffled across a long way as he covered for the movement, gets beaten by a long margin]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Four slips and a short-cover in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Coetzer, no run, on a good length and well outside off, Coetzer gets behind the line and punches it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Machan, 1 run, the cross seam delivery from Southee, gets it to shape across the left-hander, Machan was committed into pushing at that, gets a thick edge past 2nd slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Machan, <b>FOUR</b>, that's easy pickings for Machan, too full and on Machan's pads, whipped away towards fine leg for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Machan, no run, on a good length and shaping away from well outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Coetzer, 1 run, first run off the bat, short of a length and well outside off, steered away square behind point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Coetzer, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Coetzer shuffles across and defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, that's another cracker from Boult, shortens his length and gets it to straighten after pitching, Machan is opened up as he looked to defend, the ball sneaks past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, Machan throws his bat at that and misses, that's a poor shot under the circumstances]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, excellent bowling from Boult, on a good length and a hint of shape away from off, straightens at the last moment, Machan had to play, pokes forward and the ball whizzes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Machan, no run, not the best ball though, pitched up and shaping away from outside off, Machan covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[Five slips and a gully for the <b>hat-trick ball</b>. That gets the crowd going at Dunedin according to <b>Jamie</b>, "The bagpipes blow as Matt Machan enters at 1/2. Not a good start for Scotland. The crowd's behind New Zealand."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Matt Machan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Gardiner, <b>out</b> Lbw!! This is high-class bowling from Boult, he has rocked Scotland's top-order here! This was pitched up and nipped back in slightly, Gardiner was prodding across in defence, misses and the ball brushes the back-pad, halfway up, it was going on to hit the middle stump. Gardiner doesn't need to think about the review as well, off he walks. <b>Gardiner lbw b Boult 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Boult to Gardiner, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hamish Gardiner, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to MacLeod, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Lovely piece of bowling from Boult. This is as plumb as it gets! Pitched up and nipping back into MacLeod, he was caught on the shuffle, the bat came down at an angle, he missed and is struck plumb in front of middle. That wasn't going anywhere but the middle of middle stump. MacLeod simply turns back and walks away to the hut. <b>MacLeod lbw b Boult 0(1)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Boult to MacLeod, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[MacLeod has been given out LBW, he is <b>walking</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to MacLeod, <b>wide</b>, swing for Boult, but this one nipped back sharply and well down leg-side, he looks to flick and misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Trent Boult, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Coetzer, no run, Southee starts off with a maiden over first-up, on a good length and shaping away from outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Coetzer, no run, on a good length and holding its line around off, Coetzer presses across and defends it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Coetzer, no run, tad fuller and a hint of shape away from off, Coetzer covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Coetzer, no run, back of a length and well outside off, Coetzer stands tall and pushes it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Coetzer, no run, Southee nips one back into Coetzer, he was shuffling across on the flick, misses and the ball lobs off the pads, goes close to the leg-stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Coetzer, no run, fuller length delivery and a hint of shape away from off, Coetzer covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Coetzer and MacLeod are at the crease. Coetzer is on strike. Southee will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Our man, <b>Jamie Alter</b>, is at the ground and he has this to say: 'Here come the two teams, to generous applause. Dunedin being Edinburgh's sister town here in New Zealand, the Scottish touch is evident. Makes for an enjoyable setting."]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players are out in the middle.. Can Boult and Southee exploit the early morning moisture and pave the way for another win for the hosts?]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pitch Report:</b> 'It's a nice looking surface. There is some nice grass cover, that's the main thing about it. That should give some pace to the track. The seamers will get some assistance for sure, a little bit of movement early on. If you get through the first 30-45 minutes, it's going to be easy to bat on. No surprises that New Zealand are going to bowl first, they wanted to bowl first in the SL match that was played here (NZ were reduced to 92/5 before being lifted to 360 by Grant Elliott and Luke Ronchi). Look out for Southee and Boult to make some inroads early. For Scotland, get through the first 8-10 overs and they might prosper with some runs, the outfield is in great condition, the shorter boundaries should help the batsmen as well,' reckons <b>Simon Doull</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>New Zealand</b> (Playing XI): Brendon McCullum(c), Martin Guptill, Kane Williamson, Ross Taylor, Grant Elliott, Corey Anderson, Luke Ronchi(w), Daniel Vettori, Tim Southee, Adam Milne, Trent Boult]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Scotland</b> (Playing XI): Kyle Coetzer, Calum MacLeod, Hamish Gardiner, Matt Machan, Preston Mommsen(c), Richie Berrington, Matthew Cross(w), Josh Davey, Rob Taylor, Majid Haq, Iain Wardlaw]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>New Zealand have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preston Mommsen:</b> 'We are also looking forward to the game, very excited to be back at the World Cup. We were looking to bat first anyway, need to get runs on the board and then hopefully put them under pressure. Looks like a good wicket. We want to show off our skills and hopefully today provides us that opportunity. We are very happy with our preparations and feeling very confident. We had some good results against Ireland and took West Indies pretty close as well.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Brendon McCullum:</b> 'We will <b>bowl</b> first, there will be a bit in it for the first 45 minutes, will look to exploit the early moisture on the wicket. We had a training session yesterday. Great to be at Dunedin. Looking forward to the match, we will treat it as any other World Cup match. Great opportunity to execute our skills, no changes to our team.']]></line><line><![CDATA[The Scots were here last October as part of the ICC warm-up programme where the Associates were given an opportunity to get useful match practice in these conditions. Up against a New Zealand XI that included as many as 8 players currently featuring in the World Cup, they came close to upstaging the fancied Kiwis. Chasing 263, they fell short by the smallest margin of one run. Can they pull off a stunning heist today?]]></line><line><![CDATA[On the other hand, <b>Preston Mommsen</b>, Scotland's captain, is quietly confident of putting up a good show against the co-hosts, who are also one of the top favourites to win the prestigious tournament. "I think we have quite a dynamic side. Obviously inexperienced in terms of playing on the world stage, but at the same time, I think we can use that to our advantage. Very raw team, so there will be a huge amount of energy there, a huge amount of passion, and the boys will be playing very hard," he said.]]></line><line><![CDATA[New Zealand captain, <b>Brendon McCullum</b>, spoke ahead of the match and said he was expecting a good fight from the inexperienced Scotland team. He also ruled out any complacency by the hosts. "We've got to make sure we're on our game and treat it as if we're playing one of the bigger teams, as well, because in this World Cup I think we've seen at the moment with West Indies under a little bit of pressure, as well, that the Associate teams certainly have players capable of standing up and making things pretty uncomfortable for you," he said.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather Report:</b> It's a bright and sunny day at Dunedin with the temperature expected to hover around the 20 degree mark. There's no threat of rain and the wind is expected to blow from the Northeast direction.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>History Book:</b> The two teams have met each other twice and it isn't a massive surprise that New Zealand recorded thumping wins in both encounters. They haven't played each other since 2008 though and that means the current set of Scottish players would have very little in terms of scars from the last hiding.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>09:45 Local Time, 20:45 GMT, 02:15 IST:</b> The World Cup carnival has moved across to the southern most city of New Zealand. We are at the University Oval in Dunedin where the hosts entertain Scotland in their second match of the World Cup. The hosts have already started on a winning note, demolishing Sri Lanka in the inaugural match of the tournament. For Preston Mommsen and his merry band of Scottish cricketers, it's an opportunity to prove themselves in front of the global audience.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview</b><br/><br/>Moments before Preston Mommsen walked in for his final interaction with the media before Scotland's World Cup opener against New Zealand at University Oval on Tuesday, the sound of Scottish bagpipes could be heard coming from one of the adjacent playing fields on the campus of the University of Otago. It must have been part of the university band's practice routines for orientation week - the campus is starting to get active with new arrivals and their parents, as well as returning students - but the sounds of bagpipes was another reminder of where Mommsen's Scotland team are based: Dunedin, known as the Edinburgh of the South, and indeed planned in light of its Scottish predecessor.<br/><br/>Game six of the World Cup pits Scotland against New Zealand, who hammered Sri Lanka by 98 runs in the tournament opener in Christchurch, but Mommsen will be hoping that a bit of Dunedin's Scottish heritage rubs off and motivates his Associates-level team against the in-form home team.<br/><br/>Mommsen was born in South Africa, but today proudly leads Scotland into their third World Cup - after winless runs in 1999 and 2007 - and was confident of the way the team has entered the tournament. "I think we have quite a dynamic side," he said. "Obviously inexperienced in terms of playing on the world stage, but at the same time, I think we can use that to our advantage. Very raw team, so there will be a huge amount of energy there, a huge amount of passion, and the boys will be playing very hard."<br/><br/>Scotland's two warm-ups in Australia resulted in a 179-run win over Ireland and a three-run defeat to West Indies when they were chasing 313, but they will also take a bit of confidence from a practice game against a New Zealand XI featuring Martin Guptill, Brendon McCullum, Corey Anderson, Luke Ronchi, Daniel Vettori, Mitchell McClenaghan and Kyle Mills in Lincoln, last October.<br/><br/>"We watched a video this morning of that game, and we took a huge amount from that game. We took them very close, and really we should have won that game," said Mommsen. "A lot of the guys playing tomorrow played in that game, so we've got that to call upon, and hopefully we can produce a similar performance tomorrow and take the game deep. The buildup has been near perfect for the boys. We're very realistic about the opposition that we're up against. Obviously, New Zealand are a quality team, and the form they are currently in, they're going to be a difficult team to break down. But at the same time, we've prepared as we have for every other game in the leadup to this game tomorrow, and hopefully we can put in a good performance."<br/><br/>Brendon McCullum was part of that game a few months ago, and he too spoke of the team sitting down to watch the video of it. "Yeah, we did some scouting this morning on the bowlers. I've had plenty of footage the last little while that we can get our hands on and I've obviously tried to cover that, as well," he said. :That's one of our big things as a team, that we make sure we go in well planned and well prepared, but they gave us a good run for our money at Lincoln a few months ago. Yeah, we've got to make sure we're on our game and treat it as if we're playing one of the bigger teams, as well, because in this World Cup, I think we've seen at the moment with West Indies under a little bit of pressure, as well, that the Associate teams certainly have players capable of standing up and making things pretty uncomfortable for you."<br/><br/>New Zealand have been a dominant team over the last 15-odd months, winning big series home and away, and this World Cup is being talked of in certain circles as their best shot at victory. Fully aware of the level of competition Scotland are up against, Mommsen sounded confident when assessing his team.<br/><br/>"I don't think we're daunted by the way they play. Obviously, the focus has very much been on the way we want to play our game tomorrow," he said. "At the same time, we know they're dangerous. It's a dangerous lineup from 1 to 11. At the same time, they're still human beings, they still can nick the ball and get caught at slip. We have to put the balls in the right areas and make sure we're able to contain them. Obviously, we can draw on that experience of coming up against West Indies, a very dangerous batting lineup with Chris Gayle, Darren Sammy, Andre Russell towards the deaths, so that was good experience and very recent for us, and we'll call upon that. We're going into this game tomorrow with a huge amount of confidence."<br/><br/>The wicket at University Oval looks a good batting surface, but as both captains said, the angles on a small ground are what could be the deciding factor. While Mommsen felt Scotland would have to play 'smart cricket' on this ground, McCullum harked back to two ODIs played here in January with Sri Lanka, in which New Zealand made 360 and 315.<br/><br/>"Obviously, Australia is a different kettle of fish in terms of their size grounds and things like that, but I think our grounds are really, really good," he said. "They've got some quirks about them, and this one, as well, with the boundaries straight, obviously a little bit shorter, but there's certainly some getout areas, as well, for bowlers with the big boundaries, but I think the pitch looks really good. I'd expect a lot of runs, especially if we get, I guess, some clear skies over here, which I believe is forecast, then I'd expect a lot of runs, I guess, similar to the games we had against Sri Lanka down here."<br/><br/>Hamish Gardiner, who batted at No 3 in the warm-ups and made 12 and 7, could be swapped with Freddie Coleman who batted at one-drop in the UAE last month. The bowling is unlikely to change much from those fixtures, with Scotland heavily dependent on the offspin of 31-year-old Majid Haq - only the second player from the country to cross 200 caps - and medium-pacer Alasdair Evans, with seven wickets in the warm-ups. They will, as Mommsen pointed out, expect a lot from their new-ball pair of Ian Wardlaw and Josh Davey, who earlier this year took ten wickets between them to rout Afghanistan for just 63.<br/><br/>There have been suggestions that New Zealand could make changes for this match, but McCullum dodged that question by saying: "We're going to play our cards pretty close to our chest with the team, but all the guys are fit and available, and it's a good space for us to be in. We've got a fully fit and strong team to pick from, so we'll just work out the strategy that we want to go in with tomorrow."<br/><br/>Probable XIs<br/><br/>New Zealand: 1 Martin Guptill, 2 Brendon McCullum (capt), 3 Kane Williamson, 4 Ross Taylor, 5 Grant Elliott, 6 Corey Anderson, 7 Luke Ronchi (wk), 8 Daniel Vettori, 9 Tim Southee, 10 Trent Boult, 11 Adam Milne/Mitchell McClenaghan<br/><br/>Scotland: 1 Kyle Coetzer, 2 Callum MacLeod, 3 Hamish Gardiner/Freddie Coleman, 4 Matt Machan, 5 Preston Mommsen (capt), 6 Richie Barrington, 7 Matthew Cross (wk), 8 Josh Davey, 9 Alasdair Evans, 10 Majid Haq, 11 Ian Wardlaw]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Scotland</b> (From): Kyle Coetzer, Calum MacLeod, Hamish Gardiner, Matt Machan, Freddie Coleman, Richie Berrington, Matthew Cross(w), Josh Davey, Preston Mommsen(c), Majid Haq, Rob Taylor, Iain Wardlaw, Safyaan Sharif, Michael Leask, Alasdair Evans]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>New Zealand</b> (From): Brendon McCullum(c), Martin Guptill, Kane Williamson, Ross Taylor, Grant Elliott, Corey Anderson, Luke Ronchi(w), Daniel Vettori, Tim Southee, Adam Milne, Trent Boult, Mitchell McClenaghan, Nathan McCullum, Kyle Mills, Tom Latham]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>142</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>10</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>36.2</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Scotland">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1415</playerid>
					<name>Kyle Coetzer</name>
					<batsman-name>K Coetzer</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Coetzer</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Southee</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1057</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Grant Elliott</fielder>
						<fielderId>1064</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1416</playerid>
					<name>Calum MacLeod</name>
					<batsman-name>C MacLeod</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>MacLeod</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>T Boult</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8117</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9523</playerid>
					<name>Hamish Gardiner</name>
					<batsman-name>H Gardiner</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Gardiner</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>T Boult</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8117</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6565</playerid>
					<name>Matt Machan</name>
					<batsman-name>M Machan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Machan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>56</runs>
					<balls>79</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>CJ Anderson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8982</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Brendon McCullum</fielder>
						<fielderId>201</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6744</playerid>
					<name>Preston Mommsen</name>
					<batsman-name>P Mommsen</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mommsen</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Southee</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1057</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1398</playerid>
					<name>Richie Berrington</name>
					<batsman-name>R Berrington</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Berrington</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>50</runs>
					<balls>80</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>CJ Anderson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8982</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Adam Milne</fielder>
						<fielderId>7625</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9365</playerid>
					<name>Matthew Cross</name>
					<batsman-name>M Cross</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Matthew Cross</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>14</runs>
					<balls>18</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>CJ Anderson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8982</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Luke Ronchi</fielder>
						<fielderId>1396</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6657</playerid>
					<name>Josh Davey</name>
					<batsman-name>J Davey</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Davey</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>11</runs>
					<balls>19</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8327</playerid>
					<name>Rob Taylor</name>
					<batsman-name>R Taylor</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rob Taylor</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[stumped]]></status>
					<bowler>Vettori</bowler>
					<bowlerId>205</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Luke Ronchi</fielder>
						<fielderId>1396</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>646</playerid>
					<name>Majid Haq</name>
					<batsman-name>M Haq</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Haq</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Vettori</bowler>
					<bowlerId>205</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ross Taylor</fielder>
						<fielderId>521</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8423</playerid>
					<name>Iain Wardlaw</name>
					<batsman-name>Iain Wardlaw</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Iain Wardlaw</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Vettori</bowler>
					<bowlerId>205</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1416</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>1</runs>
				<overs>1.1</overs>
				<batsman>Calum MacLeod</batsman>
				<batsman-name>C MacLeod</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9523</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>1</runs>
				<overs>1.2</overs>
				<batsman>Hamish Gardiner</batsman>
				<batsman-name>H Gardiner</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1415</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>12</runs>
				<overs>4.1</overs>
				<batsman>Kyle Coetzer</batsman>
				<batsman-name>K Coetzer</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6744</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>12</runs>
				<overs>4.2</overs>
				<batsman>Preston Mommsen</batsman>
				<batsman-name>P Mommsen</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6565</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>109</runs>
				<overs>27.5</overs>
				<batsman>Matt Machan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Machan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1398</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>117</runs>
				<overs>29.3</overs>
				<batsman>Richie Berrington</batsman>
				<batsman-name>R Berrington</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9365</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>129</runs>
				<overs>33.2</overs>
				<batsman>Matthew Cross</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Cross</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8327</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>136</runs>
				<overs>34.5</overs>
				<batsman>Rob Taylor</batsman>
				<batsman-name>R Taylor</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>646</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>142</runs>
				<overs>36.1</overs>
				<batsman>Majid Haq</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Haq</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8423</playerid>
				<nbr>10</nbr>
				<runs>142</runs>
				<overs>36.2</overs>
				<batsman>Iain Wardlaw</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Iain Wardlaw</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>1</byes>
			<wides>5</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>6</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="New Zealand">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1057</playerid>
					<name>Tim Southee</name>
					<bowler-name>Southee</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Southee</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>3</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8117</playerid>
					<name>Trent Boult</name>
					<bowler-name>T Boult</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Boult</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>6</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>21</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>4</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7625</playerid>
					<name>Adam Milne</name>
					<bowler-name>Milne</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Milne</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>32</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>205</playerid>
					<name>Daniel Vettori</name>
					<bowler-name>Vettori</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Vettori</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8.2</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>24</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1064</playerid>
					<name>Grant Elliott</name>
					<bowler-name>Elliott</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Elliott</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>11</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8982</playerid>
					<name>Corey Anderson</name>
					<bowler-name>CJ Anderson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Corey Anderson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>18</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<bowler-name>B McCullum</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Brendon McCullum</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1457</playerid>
					<name>Martin Guptill</name>
					<bowler-name>M Guptill</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Guptill</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6326</playerid>
					<name>Kane Williamson</name>
					<bowler-name>Williamson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Williamson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>521</playerid>
					<name>Ross Taylor</name>
					<bowler-name>Ross Taylor</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ross Taylor</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1396</playerid>
					<name>Luke Ronchi</name>
					<bowler-name>Ronchi</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ronchi</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>146</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>7</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>24.5</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="New Zealand">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1457</playerid>
					<name>Martin Guptill</name>
					<batsman-name>M Guptill</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Guptill</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>17</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Iain Wardlaw</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8423</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Matthew Cross</fielder>
						<fielderId>9365</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Brendon McCullum</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>15</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Iain Wardlaw</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8423</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Matthew Cross</fielder>
						<fielderId>9365</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6326</playerid>
					<name>Kane Williamson</name>
					<batsman-name>Williamson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Williamson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>38</runs>
					<balls>45</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>J Davey</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6657</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Matthew Cross</fielder>
						<fielderId>9365</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>521</playerid>
					<name>Ross Taylor</name>
					<batsman-name>Ross Taylor</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ross Taylor</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Haq</bowler>
					<bowlerId>646</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Rob Taylor</fielder>
						<fielderId>8327</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1064</playerid>
					<name>Grant Elliott</name>
					<batsman-name>Elliott</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Elliott</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>29</runs>
					<balls>31</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Iain Wardlaw</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8423</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Matthew Cross</fielder>
						<fielderId>9365</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8982</playerid>
					<name>Corey Anderson</name>
					<batsman-name>CJ Anderson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Corey Anderson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>11</runs>
					<balls>16</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>J Davey</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6657</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Iain Wardlaw</fielder>
						<fielderId>8423</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1396</playerid>
					<name>Luke Ronchi</name>
					<batsman-name>Ronchi</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ronchi</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>12</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>J Davey</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6657</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Hamish Gardiner</fielder>
						<fielderId>9523</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>205</playerid>
					<name>Daniel Vettori</name>
					<batsman-name>Vettori</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Vettori</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>8</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7625</playerid>
					<name>Adam Milne</name>
					<batsman-name>Milne</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Milne</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1057</playerid>
					<name>Tim Southee</name>
					<batsman-name>Southee</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Southee</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8117</playerid>
					<name>Trent Boult</name>
					<batsman-name>T Boult</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Boult</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1457</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>18</runs>
				<overs>2.4</overs>
				<batsman>Martin Guptill</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Guptill</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>201</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>48</runs>
				<overs>6.6</overs>
				<batsman>Brendon McCullum</batsman>
				<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>521</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>66</runs>
				<overs>10.4</overs>
				<batsman>Ross Taylor</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Ross Taylor</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6326</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>106</runs>
				<overs>17.5</overs>
				<batsman>Kane Williamson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Williamson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1064</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>117</runs>
				<overs>20.6</overs>
				<batsman>Grant Elliott</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Elliott</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8982</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>133</runs>
				<overs>23.2</overs>
				<batsman>Corey Anderson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>CJ Anderson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1396</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>137</runs>
				<overs>23.4</overs>
				<batsman>Luke Ronchi</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Ronchi</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>5</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>6</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Scotland">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8423</playerid>
					<name>Iain Wardlaw</name>
					<bowler-name>Iain Wardlaw</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Iain Wardlaw</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9.5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>57</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8327</playerid>
					<name>Rob Taylor</name>
					<bowler-name>R Taylor</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rob Taylor</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>27</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6657</playerid>
					<name>Josh Davey</name>
					<bowler-name>J Davey</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Davey</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>40</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>646</playerid>
					<name>Majid Haq</name>
					<bowler-name>M Haq</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Haq</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>21</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1415</playerid>
					<name>Kyle Coetzer</name>
					<bowler-name>K Coetzer</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Coetzer</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1416</playerid>
					<name>Calum MacLeod</name>
					<bowler-name>C MacLeod</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>MacLeod</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9523</playerid>
					<name>Hamish Gardiner</name>
					<bowler-name>H Gardiner</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Gardiner</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6565</playerid>
					<name>Matt Machan</name>
					<bowler-name>M Machan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Machan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6744</playerid>
					<name>Preston Mommsen</name>
					<bowler-name>P Mommsen</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mommsen</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1398</playerid>
					<name>Richie Berrington</name>
					<bowler-name>R Berrington</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Berrington</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9365</playerid>
					<name>Matthew Cross</name>
					<bowler-name>M Cross</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Matthew Cross</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



