<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="12861" >
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>7th Match, Pool A</gameDesc>
		<series>WC 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Bangladesh</home>
		<away>Afghanistan</away>
		<teamsabbr>BAN vs AFG</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>BAN</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>AFG</awayabbr>
		<homeId>6</homeId>
		<awayId>96</awayId>
		<venue>Manuka Oval, Canberra</venue>
		<startdate>18 02 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>18 02 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Bangladesh</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Bangladesh won by 105 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Bangladesh</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>105</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Steve Davis</Name>
			<Country>Aus</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Joel S Wilson</Name>
			<Country>WI</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Aleem Dar</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Jeff Crowe</Name>
			<Country>NZ</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>03:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150218105756</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>AFG</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>Ban</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>162</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>10</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>42.5</batteamovers>
		<status>Bangladesh won by 105 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>3015</playerid>
			<name>Shapoor Zadran</name>
			<batsman-name>Shapoor</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Shapoor</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>2</runs>
			<balls-faced>2</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
			<batsman>
				<name />
				<runs />
				<balls-faced />
				<fours />
				<sixes />
			</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>544</playerid>
			<name>Shakib Al Hasan*</name>
			<bowler-name>Shakib</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Shakib</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>8.5</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>43</runs>
			<wickets>2</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>8548</playerid>
			<name>Taskin Ahmed</name>
			<bowler-name>Taskin Ahmed</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Taskin Ahmed</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>7</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>23</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>268</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>6476</playerid>
<name>Aftab Alam</name>
<player-runs>14</player-runs>
<player-balls>12</player-balls>
<runs>162</runs>
<wicket-nbr>10</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>0</bowlerid>
<bowlername></bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>2</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>3</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[. . . . 1 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>2 . . 6 . W <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. . . . W 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 . . 6 W ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_WC/BAN_AFG_FEB18/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[Tomorrow, Zimbabwe will take on UAE at Nelson in the battle of the minnows. Folks, many thanks for your company today and we hope that you will join us tomorrow as well. On behalf of <b>Ramakrishnan, Pradeep, Krishna, Sonali, Raju</b> and <b>Sriram</b>, this is <b>Sidhant Maheshwari</b> signing off.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Take a look at some of the interesting <b>tweets</b> of the day:]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mazher Arshad</b>: 105 runs is Bangladesh's largest victory in World Cup matches. #cwc15]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohandas Menon</b>: This is Bangladesh's 6th ODI win in a row since 21 Nov 2014. Have now won four of their last six WC games since 25 Feb 2011]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sanjay Manjrekar</b>: Again like most Associate Nation teams Afghanistan more impressive with ball than bat. That's where Ireland is different.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mashrafe Mortaza</b>: 'First match is very important and we set the tone. It is very important for me and my team that I bowl well and I hit the right areas. We had a reasonable start today, but we collapsed at the end. Once again, Mushfiqur (Rahim) and Shakib (Al Hasan) played really well. These kind of matches always have a lot of pressure, but I am very happy that the boys adapted very well. Thank you to all the supporters as well.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Nabi</b>: 'First 35 overs we bowled well, especially the fast bowlers. We took quick wickets as well. Mushfiqur and Shakib played well and took them above 250. Batting-wise, we were 3/3 and it was difficult from there on. The wicket was good for batting if you played in the right manner. Thanks to the supporters, they especially came in from Melbourne, Sydney to Canberra, they came and supported the team. Also the fans back home, they watched the game on TV. So, good support for us.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mushfiqur Rahim</b>: 'At the end, the team won, so it is a great feeling now. I think credit also goes to the openers, they didn't get the runs, but upfront it is not that easy. Me and Shakib, we just knew that if we stay on the wicket, it was good to bat on. We just made a plan to bat till the 45th or 48th over. Thanks to the crowd, they have come all over from Australia and also back home (talking about the support). My father and my uncle are also here. Hopefully, the boys will carry the momentum.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mushfiqur Rahim</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his <b>71 off 56</b> balls]]></line><line><![CDATA[Skipper Mohammad Nabi came to their rescue next and along with Najibullah Zadran added 58 for the sixth wicket. However, things changed dramatically once again in the batting powerplay. Najibullah got a tough one on 17 and Nabi perished the very next ball for a well made 44. The tail-enders played a couple of good shots but were not able to hang on for long. Mashrafe Mortaza was the pick of the bowlers and scalped three wickets, giving away just 20 runs in his 9 overs. He was well supported by Shakib, who finished with two wickets as well. Overall, the bowlers made sure that Afghanistan could never really get going and remained behind the required run rate throughout their innings.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bangladesh have comfortably managed to win their first game of the World Cup by a big margin. After posting a competitive 267 on the board, they enjoyed a fantastic start with the ball as well. They reduced Afghanistan to 3 for 3 in the first three overs. Although not entirely comfortable at the crease, Nawroz Mangal and Samiullah Shenwari somehow managed to stabilize the innings for a while and shared a 62-run stand for the fourth wicket. However, both departed within a space of three overs, which pushed Afghanistan into further trouble.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players walk off the field and shake hands with each other. The Bangladeshis are delighted as they have taken their revenge for their Asia Cup loss. The Bangladeshi players are also taking a <b>lap of honour</b> around the ground, thanking their vociferous supporters.]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Aftab Alam, <b>out</b> Aftab Alam Run Out!! <b>Bangladesh win by 105 runs</b>. Aftab goes for the single after driving the ball towards cover, where the fielder dives to his left and stops the ball. He fires in the throw at the striker's end, the non-striker didn't respond and Aftab was stranded in the middle of the wicket. Rahim takes his time and whips the bails. <b>Aftab Alam run out (Soumya Sarkar/Rahim) 14(12) [4s-2 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shakib to Aftab Alam, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Aftab Alam is <b>run-out</b> and it's all over for Afghanistan]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Aftab Alam, <b>SIX</b>, gives the charge this time and launches this flighted delivery over the long-on fence, it didn't come off the middle of the bat, but had enough to go the distance]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Aftab Alam, no run, gives the charge and looks to go inside-out, the ball goes off the thickish outside edge and rolls away behind square on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Aftab Alam, no run, gives this one more air around off and the ball turns away ever so slightly, Aftab blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Shapoor, 1 run, flatter from Shakib, Zadran goes back and pulls it to deep square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shapoor, 1 run, fuller delivery outside off, Shapoor looks to drive, gets it off the toe-end of the bat and the ball runs away to third man, the batsmen take a single and Shapoor will be on strike next over]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shapoor Zadran, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Hamid, <b>out</b> Caught by Anamul!! Another one bites the dust and that's wicket number 9. It was full and outside off, Hamid was looking to slog it, but ends up slicing it to point, who moves to his right and takes another simple catch. Just a wicket to go for the Bangladeshis. <b>Hamid c Anamul b Taskin Ahmed 0(5)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Taskin Ahmed to Hamid, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Hamid, no run, slightly wide outside off, Hamid leaves it]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Hamid, no run, short delivery outside off, Hamid was in two minds whether to pull it or leave it alone, in the end the ball hits the bottom edge and rolls across the pitch to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Hamid, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Hamid decides to let that one go through]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Hamid, no run, on a good length and on off and middle, Hamid pushes it to the on-side off the inside half of the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Taskin Ahmed [6.0-0-22-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hamid Hassan, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Mirwais, <b>out</b> Caught by S Rahman!! Mirwais' knock comes to an end. It was flighted outside off, Mirwais looks to loft it over the long-off fence, but he can't middle it right. He ends up giving a simple catch to the man at long-off. <b>Mirwais c S Rahman b Shakib 10(15) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shakib to Mirwais, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Mirwais, no run, tossed up on off, Mirwais lunges forward in defence]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Mirwais, <b>SIX</b>, floated on the stumps, Ashraf slogs across the line, the fielder at deep mid-wicket was well inside the rope and the ball goes over him. It just about manages to clear the fence as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Mirwais, no run, floated around off, Mirwais defends this time around]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Mirwais, no run, pushed through on the stumps, Mirwais pushes at it, the ball beats the inside edge and hits the pad, it was going down though]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Mirwais, 2 runs, floated around off and middle, Aftab slog sweeps it towards deep square leg, the batsmen take two before the fielder from deep mid-wicket runs to his right, slides and stops the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[The <b>batting powerplay yielded 20/2</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Aftab Alam, no run, Aftab was lining up for a loft over mid-off, but decides against it. He pushes this full toss to cover and decides against taking the single as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Mirwais, 1 run, back of a length delivery on the stumps, Mirwais gives the charge and mistimes the heave towards mid-wicket, gets to the other end with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Mirwais, no run, just short of a good length outside off, Mirwais punches it to the left of the bowler, who goes across and collects the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Mirwais, no run, in the channel outside off, Mirwais stays inside the crease and bunts it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Mirwais, no run, slightly back of a length outside off, Mirwais punches it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Mirwais, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Mirwais punches it to the left of the bowler, who moves across to stop the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Aftab Alam, <b>FOUR</b>, boundary to finish the over, it was floated just outside off, Aftab steps out of the crease and flat-bats it straight down the ground, the ball crashes into the fence on the bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Aftab Alam, no run, gives this one more air on off and middle, Aftab presses forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Mirwais, 1 run, flatter around off, Mirwais goes on the back foot and punches it to the right of the bowler, the batsmen take an easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Mirwais, no run, flighted delivery on off, Mirwais lunges forward and dead-bats it]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Mirwais, no run, quicker on middle and leg, Mirwais goes deep and punches it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Mirwais, no run, slows this one on off, Mirwais gets behind it and defends]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Aftab Alam, no run, slower delivery this time and slightly fuller outside off, Aftab pushes it towards cover from the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Aftab Alam, no run, another short one from Mortaza, Aftab has another wild swing at it, but this time he can't connect and the ball goes over his bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Aftab Alam, no run, bumper at the batsman, Aftab ducks under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Aftab Alam, <b>FOUR</b>, slightly wide outside off, Alam just goes hard at it and manages to get it over cover, the ball runs away to the fence and Aftab is off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Aftab Alam, no run, full and on the stumps, Alam defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Aftab Alam, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Nabi, <b>out</b> Caught by Soumya Sarkar!! Two in two balls for Bangladesh. Now, Mortaza takes his third wicket of the innings. It was slightly fuller and outside off, Nabi goes for the loft, but doesn't get the elevation nor the timing right. He ends up giving a simple catch to the man at mid-off. <b>Nabi c Soumya Sarkar b Mortaza 44(43) [4s-5]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Mortaza to Nabi, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mirwais Ashraf, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Najibullah, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Shakib gives this one more air outside off and gets it to turn back into the batsman, who was looking to tuck it through the on-side, he fails to connect with the ball and is rapped on the pad. The umpire, after thinking about it, gives it out, much to everyone's surprise. Hawk-Eye showed that the impact was umpire's call and the ball was hitting middle. Because the on-field umpire gave him out, the decision is upheld  For me though, it looked as if the impact was millimetres outside off and the batsman was unlucky there. <b>Najibullah lbw b Shakib 17(34) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shakib to Najibullah, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Najibullah has been given out lbw. He has decided to review the decision. The impact looked outside off, but wait a minute, Hawk-Eye shows the impact to be umpire's call. He has to go and Najibullah must not be happy with that decision]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nabi, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Nabi drives it to cover off the front foot, the batsman takes on the throw and manages to reach the non-striker's end in time]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nabi, no run, floated on off and middle, Nabi leans forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Najibullah, 1 run, drifting on the pads, Zadran helps it behind square and the batsmen take a quick run]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nabi, 1 run, pushed through just outside off, Nabi goes across and punches it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nabi, 2 runs, flatter on the stumps, Nabi goes deep in the crease and punches it wide of long-on, the batsmen take two before the fielder from long-on gets around]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan [5.0-0-18-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Najibullah, no run, on a good length and on middle stump, Zadran pushes it into the off-side with an open face]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Nabi, 1 run, another slower delivery around off, Nabi goes across and turns it past square leg, the batsmen cross over]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Nabi, no run, slower delivery outside off, Nabi leans forward and drives it to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Nabi, <b>FOUR</b>, good shot from Nabi, it was on a good length and around off, Nabi dances down the track and lofts it over wide mid-off and the ball runs away to the fence, the fielder was inside the circle and hence, it was a good shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Nabi, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Nabi pushes it into the off-side and says 'No' for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Nabi, no run, on a good length and outside off, Nabi makes room and looks to cut it hard, the ball didn't bounce as much as he expected and goes under the bat and through to the keeper]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mashrafe Mortaza [6.0-2-10-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>batting powerplay</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Najibullah, no run, slower ball from Rubel, Zadran dabs this one towards point and was looking for the single there, his captain sends him back as the fielder was close to the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Najibullah, no run, angles this one across off, Zadran backs away and has a wild swing at it, drags it back onto the pad off the inside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Nabi, 1 run, on a good length and on middle stump line, Nabi stays inside the crease and drops it in front of cover-point, the batsmen take a quick run]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Nabi, no run, back of a length delivery around off, Nabi opens the face of the bat and pushes it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Nabi, <b>FOUR</b>, back-to-back boundaries for the Afghani captain, it was a poor delivery from Rubel, full and on the pads, Nabi just tickles it and the ball runs away to the fine leg fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Nabi, <b>FOUR</b>, first boundary after the drinks break. It was short and at the batsman, who had backed away, he pulls it to the cow corner fence and the ball runs away]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for <b>drinks</b>. Afghanistan are struggling here. Despite Shenwari and Mangal putting on a 50-run stand, Afghanistan's scoring rate has been very poor and they need 151 runs to win now. It's a tough ask considering that they only have 5 wickets in hand. If they pull this off, it would be some batting at the fag end of the innings. Can they pull off an improbable win here?]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nabi, 1 run, Nabi gives the charge and drills it uppishly past the non-striker, his partner had to duck for cover and the batsman take an easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nabi, no run, tossed up on off, Nabi lunges forward in defence]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nabi, <b>FOUR</b>, pushed through outside leg, Nabi goes down on one knee and sweeps it behind square, the fielder at short fine leg could only watch the ball race away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nabi, no run, floated up on the stumps, Nabi gives the charge and looks to drive, gets and inside edge onto the pad and the ball rolls away into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Najibullah, 1 run, flatter outside off, Zadran pushes at it, the ball goes towards cover off the outside half of the bat, the batsmen pinch a quick run]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nabi, 1 run, on middle and leg, Nabi goes back and works it through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan [4.0-0-11-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shakib comes back into the attack, replacing Sarkar. He will start from round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Najibullah, no run, 139.3kph bumper from Rubel, Zadran ducks under it and lets it pass]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Najibullah, no run, just short of a good length and on off, Zadran gets behind the line and blocks it with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Najibullah, 2 runs, on a good length and outside off, Zadran makes room and cuts it past backward point for a couple, the third man fielder tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Najibullah, no run, angling away slightly wide outside off, Zadran flashes at it, but can't connect and the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Nabi, 1 run, back of a length delivery around off, Nabi clears the front leg and swings across the line, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Nabi, 2 runs, short delivery outside off, Nabi goes for the pull after coming down the track, gets a top-edge that goes fine towards the third man region, the batsmen take two before the fielder gets around]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rubel Hossain [4.0-0-13-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Soumya Sarkar to Nabi, 1 run, banged in short and at the batsman, Nabi pulls, but can't get it off the middle of the bat, Shakib at deep mid-wicket runs forward to his right, but the ball bounces in front of him]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Soumya Sarkar to Nabi, no run, yorker just outside off, Nabi jams it out towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Soumya Sarkar to Najibullah, 1 run, fuller in length and on the pads, Zadran flicks it in the air over square leg and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Soumya Sarkar to Najibullah, no run, on a good length and on off, Zadran leans forward and defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Soumya Sarkar to Nabi, 1 run, fuller on middle stump line, Nabi drives it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Soumya Sarkar to Nabi, no run, full toss outside off, Nabi backs away and drives it to mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nabi, 1 run, touch flatter and on the stumps, Nabi goes deep and punches it to the right of the bowler, the fielder from mid-wicket runs across and puts in the dive, but he can't prevent the single as the ball rolls away to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nabi, no run, gives this one more air around off, Nabi pushes it towards point off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Najibullah, 1 run, slower delivery drifting onto the pads, Zadran works it to square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Najibullah, no run, flighted delivery outside off, Zadran knocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nabi, 3 runs, floated on off, Zadran goes down one one knee and paddles it fine, the short fine leg fielder gives chase and hauls the ball back in before the boundary, the batsmen take three, <b>100 up</b> for Afghanistan as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Najibullah, 1 run, flatter and outside off, Zadran goes deep in the crease and cuts it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Soumya Sarkar to Nabi, no run, short and wide from Sarkar, Nabi gets back and misses the cut]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Soumya Sarkar to Najibullah, 1 run, shuffles across and tucks it off the pads through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rubel is back on the field]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Soumya Sarkar to Najibullah, no run, fuller and outside off, Najibullah drives and finds the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Soumya Sarkar to Najibullah, no run, shuffles across and turns it behind square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Soumya Sarkar to Najibullah, no run, length delivery outside off, Najibullah drives it hard towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Soumya Sarkar to Najibullah, no run, length delivery on middle, Najibullah blocks it off the front foot, the ball rolls towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Soumya Sarkar [1.0-0-9-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nabi, <b>FOUR</b>, full and good width on that one, Nabi comes on the front foot and powerfully drives it to the deep backward point fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Najibullah, 1 run, makes room and cuts it to sweeper cover for a comfortable single]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Najibullah, no run, gets forward and pushes it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Najibullah, no run, touch short from Mahmudullah, Najibullah backs away and cuts it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nabi, 1 run, flatter on off, Nabi moves across and turns it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nabi, no run, shuffles across and wrists it behind square on the leg-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Rahman to Najibullah, no run, offers another front foot defence]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Rahman to Najibullah, no run, comes on the front foot and defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Rahman to Najibullah, no run, flighted delivery on off, Najibullah defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Rahman to Najibullah, 2 runs, gets back and pulls, finds the fielder at deep mid-wicket this time]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Rahman to Nabi, 1 run, gets forward and drives it hard to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Rahman to Najibullah, 1 run, poor short delivery to start off from Sabbir, Najibullah gets back and mistimes the pull to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sabbir Rahman, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Najibullah, 1 run, touch short and outside off, Najibullah cuts it off the back foot to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Najibullah, <b>FOUR</b>, nicely done by Najibullah! He has timed this well, gets down on one knee and drags the sweep from outside off to the fine leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Najibullah, no run, offers a solid front foot defence]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Najibullah, no run, leans forward and defends it towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nabi, 1 run, goes on the back foot and punches it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nabi, no run, gets forward and defends it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nabi, <b>wide</b>, slides it down leg, Nabi does not connect with the glance]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Najibullah, no run, good length ball around off, Najibullah defends it back]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Najibullah, no run, length delivery, angled across, Najibullah gets forward and pushes it at but is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Najibullah Zadran, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, <b>out</b> Shenwari Run Out!! 1 run completed. It was a back of a length delivery from Taskin, Shenwari shuffles across to his right and short-arm jabs it to fine leg, Sabbir runs across and gets to the ball, fires the throw at the striker's end as the batsmen were taking the second run. Mushfiqur does well to collect the ball and whips the bails in an instant. Shenwari dived in an attempt to get back but he fell just short. <b>Shenwari run out (S Rahman/Rahim) 42(75) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire has been pressed into service. Shenwari is the man in question. Bangladesh are quite confident and they've got their man. Shenwari is short of his crease. OUT flashes on the big screen]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, no run, back of a length around off, Shenwari gets forward and defends it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, <b>FOUR</b>, full on off, Shenwari picks it up well, hammers it to the long-on fence for the first boundary in 10 overs]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, no run, back of a length and outside off, Shenwari bunts it towards point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nabi, no run, presses forward and defends it with an angled bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Shenwari, 1 run, gets down on one knee and drags the sweep from outside off to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nabi, 1 run, moves across and works it off the pads to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nabi, no run, stays back and looks to work it towards square leg, misses and is rapped on the pads. Loud appeal from Mahmudullah for lbw but that was easily sliding down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Shenwari, 1 run, moves across and clips it through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nabi, 1 run, slower through the air on middle, Nabi punches it softly towards long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Nabi, 1 run, shortish and outside off, Nabi gets back and drags the pull, mistimes it to deep square leg, it was in the air for a while but falls well short of the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, 1 run, comes on the front foot to this good length ball and drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, no run, back of a length and coming back in a touch, Shenwari punch-drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, no run, length delivery around off, Shenwari gets forward and taps it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Nabi, 1 run, back of a length and outside off, Nabi punches it off the back foot to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, 1 run, shuffles across and clips it to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Taskin Ahmed [4.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nabi, no run, continues to offer a solid front foot defence]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nabi, no run, presses forward and defends it back]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Nabi, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Looks like Rubel has twisted his calf muscle and he has gone off the field.]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nawroz, <b>out</b> Caught by Rubel!! Outstanding catch by Rubel at deep backward square leg. He has tumbled awkwardly and the physio comes in straightaway to have a look at him. Nawroz gets down on one knee and slog sweeps it powerfully, he had middled that but ends up finding the fielder. Rubel rushes in initially but realizes that he had misjudged it, did well to run back, timed his jump properly and grabbed it with both hands before landing badly on the ground. <b>Nawroz c Rubel b Mahmudullah 27(57) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mahmudullah to Nawroz, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Shenwari, 1 run, drifts it on middle, Shenwari shuffles across and pulls it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Shenwari, no run, flighted and outside off, Shenwari drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Shenwari, no run, gets forward and works it into the leg-side, wants a single but turns back as the mid-wicket fielder cuts it off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nawroz, no run, shuffles across and drives it off the inside half of the bat towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nawroz, no run, gets forward and works it towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nawroz, no run, stays back and defends it into the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Shenwari, 1 run, gets forward and drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Shenwari, no run, shuffles across and manages to tuck it behind square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Shenwari, no run, drifts it on middle and leg, Shenwari defends it towards mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan [3.0-0-10-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nawroz, no run, shortish and outside off, Nawroz backs away for the cut but is beaten as the ball stays low]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nawroz, no run, comes down the track and drives it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nawroz, no run, outside off, Nawroz dabs it behind point]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nawroz, no run, flighted on off, Nawroz gets behind the line and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nawroz, no run, shortish, Nawroz stays back and punches it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Shenwari, leg byes, 1 run, turns it off the pads behind square, they scamper through for a brisk run as the throw comes in at the striker's end, however, it was a wayward throw and Nawroz makes it back successfully]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Soumya Sarkar to Shenwari, 1 run, drives this widish delivery square of the wicket for a comfortable single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Soumya Sarkar to Shenwari, 2 runs, short of length and wide of off, Shenwari makes room and cuts it to third man for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Soumya Sarkar to Nawroz, 1 run, length delivery outside off, Nawroz drives it square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Soumya Sarkar to Nawroz, 2 runs, back of a length and outside off, Nawroz cuts it to point, Shenwari was backing up too much and Anamul fires a throw at the bowler's end, Shenwari gets back in time before the throw disturbed the stumps. The ball then ricochets away towards the deep mid-wicket boundary and they pick up two]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire has been called out for a run-out chance. Shenwari is well in, so an easy call for the ump.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Soumya Sarkar to Nawroz, 2 runs, outside off, lures Nawroz on the front foot and he drives it to deep extra cover for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mortaza seems a bit agitated. He is ordering his fielders around]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Soumya Sarkar to Shenwari, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, Shenwari punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Soumya Sarkar, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Shenwari, 1 run, gets down on one knee and drags the sweep to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Shenwari, no run, gets forward and works this fullish ball off the inside half of the bat to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nawroz, 1 run, moves across and wrists this flatter delivery through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Shenwari, 1 run, works it towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Shenwari, no run, presses on the front foot and drives it to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Shenwari, no run, full around off, Shenwari moves across and pushes it to the right of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Shenwari, 1 run, flatter delivery around off, Shenwari stays back and punches it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Shenwari, no run, looks to defend a flighted delivery on off, gets an inside edge towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Shenwari, no run, drifts it on leg, Shenwari turns it behind square]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Shenwari, no run, pushes it back to the bowler once again]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Shenwari, no run, stays on the back foot and punches it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nawroz, 1 run, shortish and just outside off, Nawroz makes room and guides it square of the wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nawroz, 1 run, shuffles to his right and wrists it to square leg for another single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nawroz, no run, moves across a touch and drives it to the right of the bowler, the fielder from mid-wicket, runs and dives to his left and makes a fine stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Shenwari, 1 run, full on off, Shenwari gets forward and drives it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Nawroz, 1 run, drifts it around leg, Nawroz works it to long-on for a comfortable single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Shenwari, 1 run, shuffles across and turns it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Shenwari, no run, flighted on off, Shenwari defends it back to the right of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mahmudullah, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now. After being 3/3 at one stage, Afghanistan have somehow managed to recover, putting up a 41-run stand for the fourth wicket. The Bangladeshi bowlers are bowling good lines and lengths and the Afghan batsmen have not looked comfortable out there. They have survived a few close chances and will have to work even harder to keep the Bangladeshi bowlers at bay.]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nawroz, no run, tossed up on off, Nawroz blocks it solidly off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Shenwari, 1 run, comes forward and softly drives it towards long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Shenwari, no run, stays on the back foot and punches it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Shenwari, no run, drifts it onto the pads, Shenwari wrists it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Shenwari, no run, flighted around off, Shenwari presses forward and pushes it to point, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nawroz, 1 run, comes down the track and drives it to long-on for a comfortable single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, no run, short of a length and angling away from outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, no run, on a good length and just outside off, punched towards mid-off, that was played with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Nawroz, 1 run, <b>dropped by Shakib at third man</b>, Bangladesh's best batsman and bowler, but perhaps not the best fielder. This was short and just outside off, Nawroz waits on it, opens the face of the bat and runs it towards third man. Shakib runs a long way across to his left, puts in the dive, takes the catch, but the ball pops out when his elbow hit the ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Nawroz, <b>FOUR</b>, that should give Nawroz some confidence, this was banged in short and just outside off, Mangal rocks back, rolls his wrists and pulls it in front of mid-wicket for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, 1 run, Taskin keeps it short and wide outside off, punched away off the backfoot towards deep cover, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Nawroz, 1 run, back of a length and well outside off, punched off the back-foot towards deep cover, just a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nawroz, 1 run, flatter and on Nawroz's pads, flicked away backward of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nawroz, 2 runs, Shakib drifts one fuller and wider outside off, driven past cover for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nawroz, 2 runs, that's nicely done by Nawroz, slower and on the stumps, he gets down, uses the pace on the ball and paddles it past the keeper, good enough for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nawroz, no run, pushed through by Shakib, Nawroz gets forward and drives it towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Nawroz, no run, flighted and just outside off, Nawroz gets a good stride forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Shenwari, 1 run, tossed up and on Shenwari's pads, clipped away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, 1 run, back of a length and well outside off, punched away off the backfoot, the man at sweeper cover gets across quickly and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Nawroz, 1 run, short of a length and well outside off, cracked away behind square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, 1 run, Rahim almost pulled off a stunner! This was banged in short by Taskin, Shenwari took his eyes off the ball as he ducked into it, kept his bat hanging like a periscope, the ball grazes the top-edge, loops high and goes towards short fine, Rahim ran all the way, puts in the dive, but the ball drops just wide of him]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Nawroz, 1 run, width on offer from Taskin, cracked square on the off-side past backward point, there's a man in the deep, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Nawroz, no run, that goes past the outside edge once again, Nawroz is struggling, this was pitched up and nipped away off the seam, Nawroz pokes at that and nearly edges it through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Nawroz, no run, short and angling away from well outside off, Nawroz went chasing after that and missed]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Shenwari, no run, that's an excellent ball, Shenwari made it look even better with his clumsy footwork, this was banged in short and came back with the angle, Shenwari went nowhere, pushes his bat in front of his hands and just about manages to fend it away towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Shenwari, no run, fraction fuller and just outside off, Shenwari gets well forward and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Shenwari, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Shenwari wasn't in any position, lunges forward at the last moment and blocks it]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Shenwari, no run, the slower ball from Mortaza, Shenwari went hard on the drive, mistimes it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Shenwari, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Shenwari closes the face of the bat and gets an inside edge on the drive, the ball rolls towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Shenwari, no run, another bouncer, this time by Mortaza, Shenwari ducks underneath it and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Nawroz, no run, tad fuller and holding its line outside off, Nawroz shuffles across, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, 1 run, short and wide from Taskin, Shenwari hops across, gets on top of the bounce and cuts it over point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, no run, tad fuller and on off, Shenwari gets forward and defends it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, no run, tad fuller and on off, Shenwari gets forward and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, no run, back of the length and just outside off, punched with an angled bat towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, no run, Taskin bangs one short and well outside off, left alone, called as one bouncer for the over]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Shenwari, 1 run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Shenwari is happy to stay back, punches it in front of mid-off and calls for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Shenwari, no run, fuller length delivery and in that channel outside off, Shenwari gets forward and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Shenwari, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Shenwari prods across and defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Shenwari, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>the first boundary for Afghanistan</b>, this was full and wide, a real floaty half-volley from Mortaza, Shenwari was hanging on the back-foot, he has to reach out in the end, manages enough bat to rifle it over extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Shenwari, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Shenwari gets behind the line and angles it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Shenwari, no run, appeal for LBW, but the angle was taking it down leg, Mortaza came from wide of the crease and got this one to angle back in sharply, Shenwari was falling over on the flick and missed]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mashrafe Mortaza [4.0-1-5-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Nawroz, no run, full and on Nawroz's pads, he presses across and defends it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Nawroz, no run, short and wide from Nawroz, he throws his bat at that and misses, this is poor batting from the former captain]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Nawroz, no run, this is much closer from Taskin, short of a length and a hint of nibble away from off, Nawroz prods at that and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Nawroz, no run, short and wide from Taskin, Nawroz's eyes lit up as he went for the cut, misses by a long way]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, 1 run, full and angling back into Shenwari, nudges it towards mid-on. The fielder makes a direct hit at the bowler's end, quite unnecessary, Nawroz was well in. He ends up conceding a run as the ball rolls away wide of mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Shenwari, no run, good pace from Taskin, hits the bat hard as Shenwari went back, the ball rolls towards short cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Taskin Ahmed, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Change of bowling, Taskin replaces Mortaza]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Shenwari, 1 run, fuller length delivery and shaping away further, Shenwari throws his bat at that and slices it behind square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Shenwari, 2 runs, that's much better from Shenwari, gets behind a length ball and punches it square past point. Two men give chase and haul the ball back, the batsmen are just happy with a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Shenwari, <b>wide</b>, the bumper from Rubel, but it's too short and too high, wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Shenwari, no run, fuller length delivery and a hint of wobble across Shenwari, there's not much footwork from the batsman as he stabs it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Nawroz, 1 run, back of a length and well outside off, dabbed away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Nawroz, no run, on a good length and a hint of shape away from the right-hander, Nawroz moved across his stumps, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Nawroz, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Nawroz prods across and pushes it back towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Nawroz, 1 run, edged! This was full and wide, looking to lure Nawroz into the drive, he obliges, throws his bat at that and gets a thick edge past second slip, there's a third man in place, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Nawroz, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Nawroz stays back and defends it with an angled bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Nawroz, no run, Mortaza keeps it full and gets it to shape away from outside off, Nawroz is happy to let it go by]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Nawroz, no run, this is even better from Mortaza, tad fuller and shapes away before straightening at the last moment, Mangal prods down the wrong line and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Nawroz, no run, fuller length delivery and in that channel outside off, Nawroz gets half-a-stride forward as he defends it with soft hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Nawroz, no run, the ball is jagging around under the lights, this was pitched up in that sixth stump channel and nips away, Nawroz was rooted to his crease as he pushed forward, the ball whizzes past the outside edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Shenwari, 2 runs, short of a length and on Shenwari's pads, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Shenwari, no run, the bumper from Rubel, Shenwari ducks underneath it and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Shenwari, no run, fuller and just outside off, Shenwari waits on it and defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Shenwari, no run, Rubel keeps it full and just outside off, Shenwari gets behind the line and blocks it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Shenwari, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Shenwari, 2 runs, tad fuller and holding its line outside off, Shenwari gets behind the line and finds the gap past point, comes back for the second run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Nawroz, no run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, Mangal gets behind the line and defends it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Shenwari, 1 run, Mortaza finds the edge again, Shenwari was pushing at one that left him after pitching outside off, second slip dives to his right but can't make a clean stop, allows a single to be taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Shenwari, no run, fuller length delivery outside off and shaping away, Shenwari doesn't need to play at those, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Nawroz, 1 run, on a good length and holding its line outside off, Nawroz pushes at that and gets a thick edge towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Nawroz, no run, on a good length and just outside off, defended with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Nawroz, no run, that's an excellent channel from Mortaza, full and a hint of shape away from outside off, Mangal is lured into the drive and misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Shenwari, 2 runs, length delivery angling into the pads, Shenwari clips it through mid-wicket, there was a slight misfield that allows the batsmen to come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Shenwari, no run, tad fuller and shaping away from outside off, easy leave for the batsman]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Nawroz, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, Nawroz rides with the bounce and dabs it behind square on the off-side for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Nawroz, no run, another short ball from Rubel, the line is well outside off as well, Nawroz goes for an ambitious pull and missed, this is poor cricket so far from the Afghanis]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Nawroz, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Nawroz shuffled across on the cut, there's no bounce on the ball and it beats the bottom edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Nawroz, no run, loud shout for a <b>caught behind</b>, but there's no bat on that, lousy technique from Mangal, this was short and reared onto the batsman, he was in no position on the pull, the ball clips the flap of the pads on the way to the keeper]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Samiullah Shenwari, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Stanikzai, <b>out</b> Caught by Mahmudullah!! Edged and caught! Disaster for Afghanistan. This is poor cricket from Stanikzai, fuller length delivery and holding its line outside off, Stanikzai pushed from his crease, there was very little foot movement there, the outside edge is found and it goes at a good height to Mahmudullah at 1st slip. He grabs at the ball, it bobbles in the air and he manages to hold on to it in his second attempt. Afghanistan have been reduced to 3/3. <b>Stanikzai c Mahmudullah b Mortaza 1(7)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mortaza to Stanikzai, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Stanikzai, no run, fuller length delivery and on the off-stump channel, Stanikzai gets back and across as he pushes it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Stanikzai, no run, that's a good channel from Mortaza, fuller and just outside off, Stanikzai gets solidly behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Stanikzai, no run, Mortaza keeps it full and in that channel outside off, Stanikzai presses across and drives it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Stanikzai, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, Stanikzai shuffles across and nudges it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Stanikzai, no run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, Stanikzai gets behind the line and blocks it back towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Nawroz, no run, tad fuller and on off, Nawroz prods across and defends it with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Nawroz, no run, back of a length and in that channel outside off, Mangal hops across in his crease and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Nawroz, no run, tad fuller and shaping away from outside off, Mangal covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Nawroz, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Mangal shuffles across and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Stanikzai, 1 run, Rubel goes for the wide yorker, Stanikzai reaches out for the drive, gets a bottom edge, Rahim dives across to his right and gets a hand onto it, the ball rolls away behind the keeper. Stanikzai is off the mark with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Asghar Stanikzai, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Three slips and a gully in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Zazai, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Rubel strikes first ball! This was pitched up and nipped in from a length, Zazai was shuffling across on the clip, is beaten for pace and is struck on the pads, the impact was around off, the ball would have crashed into the off-stump. Umpire Davis lifts the dreaded finger. Zazai has a long chat with his partner and decides against reviewing it. Replays suggest that the impact was around off and it was hitting the top of the off-stump. <b>Zazai lbw b Rubel 1(5)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Rubel to Zazai, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Zazai has been given out LBW. He <b>isn't reviewing</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rubel Hossain, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Nawroz Mangal, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Ahmadi, <b>out</b> Caught&Bowled!! Afghanistan have been dented early! Mortaza has struck in his first over. He shortened his length and angled one onto Ahmadi's pads, he was looking to work it towards the on-side, closes the face of the bat and gets a leading edge. Mortaza calls for the catch, runs across to his left and completes the dolly. Not the start the Afghans were hoping for. <b>Ahmadi c and b Mortaza 1(2)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mortaza to Ahmadi, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught&Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Zazai, 1 run, tad fuller and shaping away from outside off, Zazai leans forward, plays with an open face and guides it towards third run]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Zazai, no run, on a good length and shaping away from off, Zazai is happy to let it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Zazai, no run, Mortaza shortens his length and just gets it to shape away, that stayed a tad low as well, Zazai was looking to dab it down towards third man and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Zazai, no run, tad fuller and angling onto Zazai's pads, flicked away towards mid-wicket, Ahmadi was backing up. The fielder has a shy and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Ahmadi, 1 run, short and wide from Mortaza, Ahmadi gets on top of the bounce and cuts it down towards third man for a single, the fielder at gully couldn't stop it cleanly as he got a hand onto it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ahmadi and Zazai are at the crease. Ahmadi is on strike. Mortaza will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and a gully in place as Mashrafe steams in..]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. Afghanistan started and ended well with the ball, but allowed Shakib and Rahim to build a 114-run stand for the fifth wicket - the highest partnership for any wicket for Bangladesh in a World Cup match. That helped Bangladesh post a more than competitive 267 from their allotted 50 overs. Afghanistan's batting is their weaker link. Can they put up a good show and cause a surprise?]]></line><line><![CDATA[However, Mohammad Nabi's bowlers came back strongly in the death overs, picking up 6 wickets in the last 6 overs to stem the run flow. Mirwais Ashraf, Aftab Alam, Shapoor Zadran and Hamid Hassan bagged two wickets apiece, but Shapoor was the best of the bowlers as he conceded just 20 runs in his 7 overs. Afghanistan will have to make history today if they are to win this match. This will be their highest succesful run chase against a Test playing nation. Can they do it? We'll find out in a while. Take a break and join us back for Afghanistan's reply.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, after opting to bat, Bangladesh got off to a slow start as the Afghans bowled with great discipline. Mirwais Ashraf removed Tamim Iqbal and ended his 47-run opening stand with Anamul Haque in the 14th over. Mirwais dismissed Anamul soon to put a bit of pressure on Bangladesh. Soumya Sarkar and Mahmudullah steadied the ship with a brisk fifty-run stand before both went in quick succession. The experienced duo of Shakib Al Hasan and Mushfiqur Rahim then recorded Bangladesh's highest ever World Cup stand (114) to swing the pendulum in their favour.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bangladesh have lost 5 wickets for 34 runs in the last 5 overs. When Shakib and Rahim were going great guns, it looked like 280-290 was a certainty, but Afghanistan's death bowling was great and Bangladesh couldn't keep the momentum going.]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Taskin Ahmed, <b>out</b> Bowled!! This is a strong finish from Afghanistan. Full and on the off stump, Taskin just goes leg-side a bit and swings hard at it, he misses and the ball crashes into the off stump. Aftab is absolutely pumped. <b>Taskin Ahmed b Aftab Alam 1(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Aftab Alam to Taskin Ahmed, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Taskin Ahmed, byes, 2 runs, a fine yorker from Aftab, Taskin doesn't make contact with his swing, the keeper fumbles and they race back for two]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Rubel, byes, 1 run, a run-out chance missed. Full and swinging back in, Rubel swings hard and misses, the non-striker takes off and escapes as the keeper was off target with his throw. He appeals for caught behind as well, but the umpire is unmoved. There was a sound as the ball passed the bat and the snicko shows a big spike. Afghanistan don't review again]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Rubel, no run, oh! This good length delivery hurries onto the batsman and swings back in as well, Rubel was late in trying to defend, he's hit on the pad, but it was going down the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Taskin Ahmed, 1 run, widish low full toss, Taskin reaches out and squeezes it out to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Taskin Ahmed, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Mortaza, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Full and straight, you miss, I hit! This offering from Aftab just swung back in very late, Mortaza slogs hard at it, he loses his shape while trying to meet the ball. He misses and the ball crashes into middle and leg. <b>Mortaza b Aftab Alam 14(9) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Aftab Alam to Mortaza, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Aftab Alam [8.0-0-54-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rubel Hossain, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Mortaza, <b>out</b> Mominul Run Out!! Slower delivery wide outside off stump, Mortaza swings hard and misses. The batsmen try to steal a run, but the keeper fires an accurate throw and catches Mominul well short of his crease. The non-striker was not even in the picture. <b>Mominul run out (Zazai) 3(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Hamid to Mortaza, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Mortaza, no run, low full toss on the stumps, drilled to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Mominul, 1 run, Mominul goes across the stumps and scoops it to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Mortaza, leg byes, 1 run, Mortaza tries to slog and misses, the ball rolls off the pad towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Mortaza, <b>FOUR</b>, full and outside off stump, driven hard and wide of mid-off. This is a handy innings from the skipper]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Mominul, 1 run, full and outside off stump, Mominul drives it to the left of the man at cover, the fielder gets a hand onto it and deflects it to mid-off. There was a slight hesitation between the batsmen, but Mortaza was well home before the keeper took the bails off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[The third umpire has been called for a run-out check. Mortaza is the man in question. He's well in.]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Mortaza, <b>FOUR</b>, and again! This is good batting from Mortaza. Knew that there is no one at sweeper cover, so he anticipates a short ball, goes leg-side and cuts it hard in front of point this time]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Mortaza, <b>FOUR</b>, full toss again and the Bangladeshi captain takes his counterpart for a boundary. Mortaza backs away and smashes this backward of point for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Mominul, 1 run, driven away to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mominul Haque, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Rahim, <b>out</b> Caught by Shenwari!! It's a full toss and it's a wicket. Great catch from Shenwari at deep mid-wicket. Rahim tries to smash this over the boundary, he hits it flat, the fielder in the deep runs to his right, dives to his right and takes it with both hands. The ball was dying on him but he did well to hold on. <b>Rahim c Shenwari b Nabi 71(56) [4s-6 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nabi to Rahim, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, cheeky from Rahim! Nabi looks for a yorker, but bowls a low full toss around the off stump, Rahim gets across the stumps, kneels down and paddles it fine to the fine leg boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Mortaza, 1 run, darter from Nabi, Mortaza advances and looks to go big, but yorks himself, manages to send it towards square leg though]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Fine over from Hamid. Just four singles and a wicket in it.]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Mortaza, 1 run, fullish delivery just outside off stump, Mortaza defends it to mid-wicket and gets off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mashrafe Mortaza, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to S Rahman, <b>out</b> Bowled!! There it is! He wasn't covering for the angle coming in from wide of the crease and he's dragged this on. Nothing but a good length delivery from Hamid, Rahman was very late in trying to guide it down to third man. In the end he gets a thick inside edge which shatters into middle and off. That is wicket number two for Hamid. <b>S Rahman b Hamid 3(8)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Hamid to S Rahman, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to S Rahman, no run, this short of length delivery rises steeply and beats Rahman's attempted cut. The ball came in with the angle as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Rahim, 1 run, no pace on the ball, Rahim waits and guides it to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[Fine leg goes back, third man comes in.]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to S Rahman, 1 run, slower delivery on the off stump, worked away to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Rahim, 1 run, a wild swing across the line from Rahim, the ball takes the inside half of the bat and goes to deep square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[45.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to S Rahman, no run, good fielding! Low full toss outside off stump, Rahman square-drives the ball nicely, the fielder at backward point dives to his left and makes a fine stop. That ball was heading to the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Rahim, 1 run, too straight from Nabi, Rahim flicks it through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to S Rahman, 1 run, easily flicks it along the ground to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Rahim, 1 run, low full toss outside off stump, Rahim drills it along the ground to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to S Rahman, 1 run, flighted delivery spinning back into the right-hander, Rahman turns it to backward square leg, there was a slight hesitation but Rahman made his ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Rahim, 1 run, high full toss, bunted down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to S Rahman, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, blocked gently into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to S Rahman, no run, low full toss outside off stump, Rahman drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sabbir Rahman, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Shakib, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Oh he's dragged this on! The umpires check if Hamid was cutting the crease, but he's fine on that account. Slower delivery from Hamid again, Shakib goes early into the slog, he gets an inside edge which hits the thigh pad and disturbs the stumps. End of a fabulous innings from Shakib. His effort will lift the bowlers when they come on to bowl. <b>Shakib b Hamid 63(51) [4s-6 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Hamid to Shakib, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Shakib, no run, Hamid is very lucky that Shakib didn't hit the gap. It was a low full wide outside off stump, Shakib sliced it nicely but picked out backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Shakib, <b>SIX</b>, looks like a top edge and it has gone all the way. There is a bit of a glove-love in the middle between Rahim and Shakib. Slower delivery on the stumps, Shakib slogs hard, gets a thickish top edge and it goes all the way over backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Shakib, <b>FOUR</b>, friendly full toss, Shakib swings hard, doesn't find the middle of the bat and mid-on was too square to catch it. The bowler had no chance as well and it escaped to the boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[This is the <b>highest ever partnership</b> for Bangladesh in World Cup cricket.]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Rahim, 2 runs, on the leg stump, Rahim flicks it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, this is the <b>4th 100-run stand</b> stand in ODIs between these two. There is no one at sweeper cover, hence Rahim exposes all the stumps, it was a short offering from Nabi and Rahim cut it away nicely in front of point]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Shakib, 1 run, 'catch it' is the call, but it doesn't carry to long-off. Flighted delivery just outside off stump, Shakib steps out and lofts it over the infield]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Rahim, 1 run, driven away to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Shakib, 1 run, Nabi darts this full and on the leg stump, Shakib drives it to the left of the bowler, who tries to stop the ball, but it escapes to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Rahim, 1 run, Rahim goes deep in the crease and tries to dab this flatter ball fine, but picks out short third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Shakib, no run, slower ball full toss wide outside off stump, Shakib tries to reach out and send it square of the wicket on the off-side, but only manages a thin edge that goes on the bounce to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Rahim, 1 run, a fantastic yorker from Hamid, Rahim digs it out, looks at his partner and then sets off for a sharp run. The bowler gave up very early]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Shakib, 1 run, the length is a little on the shorter side, Shakib slaps it hard to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Rahim, 1 run, Rahim swings hard at it and gets a thick inside edge that rolls to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Rahim, no run, Rahim tries to be cheeky with a scoop to fine leg, but he walks right across the stumps and fails to make contact with this yorker length ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Shakib, 1 run, Shakib gets to his <b>27th ODI fifty</b>. Round the wicket length ball from Hamid, Shakib nudges it to square leg and gets an easy run. Rahim congratulates his partner for getting to the milestone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Hamid Hassan [6.0-0-37-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Shakib, 1 run, on the leg stump, worked away to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Rahim, 1 run, that's sloppy from Afghanistan. Rahim leans forward and defends it to point, the throw was very poor and the keeper couldn't stop the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Rahim, no run, flighted delivery on the leg stump, Rahim flicks it uppishly to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Rahim, 2 runs, driven wide of long-off and it's Rahim's <b>19th ODI fifty</b>. He raises his bats and acknowledges the applause, Shakib shakes hands with his partner. It was very full and wide outside off stump, Rahim drove it along the ground and raced back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Rahim, no run, spinning back into the right-hander, Rahim nudges this to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Shakib, 1 run, quicker delivery from Nabi, drilled down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Rahim, no run, yorker from Aftab, Rahim digs it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Rahim, 2 runs, too short and way outside off stump, Rahim reaches for it and cuts it to deep point]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Rahim, <b>SIX</b>, oh he's smashed that! Full and on the leg stump, Rahim waits for the ball and slogs it handsomley over backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Rahim, no run, oh how did that miss the stumps? Hang on! Was it pad first? This fuller length delivery just tails back into the right-hander, Rahim tries to run it down to third man but the inward movement foxes him, somehow manages to get an edge and it rolls past the off stump to the keeper. There was an appeal for LBW from the bowler, but umpire Davis was unmoved. Replays show that it was pad first and a review would have given Afghanistan the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Shakib, 1 run, Aftab cramps Shakib for room as he back away and follows him with a short of length delivery, Shakib cuts it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Rahim, 1 run, slower delivery outside off stump, Rahim steers it down to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>48 runs</b> came off the batting powerplay. Bangladesh are batting well now, courtesy of these two. But, they need to carry on the good work.]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Shakib, no run, low full toss outside off, Shakib was backing away and can only drag it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Shakib, 2 runs, lofts this tossed up delivery back over the bowler, the batsmen take another couple before the long-off fielder runs to his left and collects the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Shakib, 2 runs, Shakib backs away and Nabi follows him with a fuller one, he drives it wide of long-off and comes back for the second easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Rahim, 1 run, low full toss on the pads, Rahim helps it down to long-on and gets off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Shakib, 1 run, backs away and drills this fullish delivery towards long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Shakib, 2 runs, quicker one on the stumps, Shakib goes hard at it and the ball rolls past mid-wicket off the inside half of the bat, the batsmen take a couple and even though there was a direct-hit from the deep, Rahim had made his ground at the non-striker's end]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Nabi [4.0-0-16-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Shakib, 1 run, slowish delivery angling in on middle and leg, Shakib knocks it down to long-on and he will keep the strike, the fielder at mid-on had been moved back after the boundary earlier in the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Shakib, no run, yorker on the stumps, Shakib jams it out to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Shakib, <b>FOUR</b>, back-to-back boundaries for Shakib, this is superb batting, it was a full toss outside off, Shakib drives hard and gets it front of square for another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Shakib, <b>FOUR</b>, overpitching on middle and leg, Shakib had backed away and he drills the drive to the right of mid-on, the fielder was inside the circle and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Rahim, 1 run, slowish fuller delivery around off, Rahim eases it down to long-on and gets off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Shakib, 1 run, <b>run-out chance!</b> Shakib survives though after he digs a yorker to the left of mid-off, who runs forward, picks the ball and fires in the throw at the non-striker's end. Shakib was charging to the other end, but a direct hit would have meant curtains for him]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Shakib, 1 run, on the pads once again, Shakib fails to get it fine and ends up mistiming the nurdle behind square, the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Shakib, no run, good yorker on the stumps, Shakib goes slightly across and jams it out to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Rahim, 1 run, angling in on the pads, Rahim clips it behind square for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, good shot from Rahim, it was fullish and outside off, Rahim drives it through the cover and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Shakib, 3 runs, backs away and looks to go inside-out, it was a yorker and in the end, Shakib can only get it square of the wicket off the outside half of the bat, the batsmen take three before the ball if fielded]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Rahim, 1 run, Rahim premeditates and goes right across his stumps to probably try and scoop one over short fine, Hamid follows him down leg and in the end Rahim can only push it towards mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Shakib, <b>FOUR</b>, bad, bad ball to end the over. It was full and on leg, easy pickings for Shakib, who nurdles it fine to the right of fine leg and the ball runs away to the fence, with that boundary, Shakib also goes past <b>4000 runs</b> in ODIs]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Shakib, no run, good yorker around off, Shakib jams it out to extra cover and was looking for the single, but Rahim sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Rahim, 1 run, low full toss outside off, Rahim pushes it towards cover off the toe-end of the bat and the batsmen pinch a quick run]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Rahim, 2 runs, loopy full toss from alam, Rahim pulls it wide of long-on, he didn't time it well, but good running ensures that they come back for the second easily in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Rahim, no run, on a good length and targetting the stumps this time, Rahim blocks it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Rahim, 2 runs, eases this fullish delivery down to long-on after coming across]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Aftab Alam [5.0-0-24-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Shakib, no run, shortish and wide outside off, Shakib cuts it to backward point, he would feel that he has missed out on some runs there]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Rahim, 1 run, did he get an inside edge onto the pad there? It was on a good length and angling into the pads, Rahim fails to work it through the leg-side and gets an inside edge onto the pad, there was an appeal for lbw, but it can never be given out. The batsmen sneak in a run as the ball rolls away into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, fullish delivery around off, Rahim clears the front leg and heaves it to the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Rahim, 2 runs, gives the charge to this short delivery, he was not upto the pitch of the ball and cuts it very late, the ball flies off the top-edge and runs away to third man, the batsmen take two]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Rahim, no run, back of a length delivery on off, Rahim defends off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Shakib, 3 runs, comes from round the wicket and bowls this on a length outside off, Shakib goes for the drive, but gets a thickish inside edge that runs past the off stump and goes fine, the batsmen take three before the short fine fielder hunts it down]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Hamid Hassan [4.0-0-17-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's <b>batting powerplay</b> time. Bangladesh need a move on from here.]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Shakib, 1 run, full and outside off, Shakib drills the drive to sweeper cover and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Rahim, 1 run, drifting on middle and leg, Rahim works it behind square for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, dances down the track and lofts this tossed up delivery around off inside-out, the ball runs away to the fence in no time, good shot from the former captain]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Rahim, 2 runs, flighted delivery on the stumps, Rahim goes for the slog sweep, but can't time it that well, the ball goes towards the deep mid-wicket region and the batsmen take two]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Rahim, no run, shortish from Ahmadi, Rahim cuts but picks out backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Rahim, no run, floated on off and middle, Rahim pushes it to the right of the bowler, the fielder at mid-wicket moves to his left and prevents the single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Shakib, no run, shortish delivery at the batsman, Shakib was looking to pull it, but can't connect and wears it high on his thigh pad, the ball rolls away into the off-side and the batsmen were looking for the single, but they decide against it at the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Shakib, no run, yorker on off, Shakib jams it out to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Shakib, <b>wide</b>, another one down the leg side, Shakib fails to glance it fine and the umpire signals a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Rahim, 1 run, fuller in length and around off, Rahim leans forward and drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Shakib, 1 run, did that come off the pad or bat? The umpire thinks it came off the bat, it was full and on the leg stump line, the ball rolls away fine after clipping the pad, the batsmen cross over]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Shakib, no run, slightly fuller on middle, Shakib goes slightly across and turns it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Rahim, 1 run, back of a length delivery outside off, Rahim knocks it square of the wicket off the back foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Rahim, <b>wide</b>, not a great delivery to start your new spell as he splays this one down leg, wided by the umpire]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Aftab Alam [4.0-0-19-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Aftab Alam comes back, replacing Shapoor]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Shakib, no run, another flatter one outside off, it was quicker too. Shakib was looking to cut it hard, but the ball goes past his blade and the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Shakib, no run, shortish and slightly wide outside off, Shakib cuts and picks out the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Rahim, 1 run, flighted delivery on middle and leg, Rahim bunts it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Shakib, 1 run, flatter outside off, Shakib chops it to the right of the cover and the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Rahim, 1 run, poor ball from Ahmadi, too short and Rahim pulls it to deep mid-wicket, luckily for Ahmadi, there was a fielder there and it is only a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Javed Ahmadi [3.0-0-21-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[What has happened here? Umpire Davis gives him the <b>second warning</b> and <b>Shenwari is off</b> the bowling attack. He can't bowl anymore in this game.]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shenwari to Shakib, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Shakib drives it wide of mid-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now. After losing the openers in quick succession, Mahmudullah and Sarkar then put on a 50-run stand to stabilize the Bangladeshi innings. However, both of them got out and Afghanistan are back on top. Shakib and Rahim need to bat sensibly and accelerate at the same time if Bangladesh are to post a respectable total. It will be interesting to see how they go about their job during the batting powerplay as well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Shakib, 1 run, another shortish delivery on the pads, Shakib helps it to fine leg after a swivel, with this run Shakib becomes the <b>highest run-scorer</b> for Bangladesh in ODIs]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Rahim, 1 run, banged in short and slightly wide outside off, Rahim stays back, hangs his bat at it and the ball rolls away towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, full and outside off, Rahim presses forward, opens the face of the bat at the last moment and drives it through backward point for his first boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Rahim, no run, yorker from Shapoor, Rahim digs it out to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Rahim, no run, touch fullish this time and around off, Rahim pushes it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Rahim, no run, short of length delivery on off, Rahim gets right behind the line and blocks solidly]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Just after the over, umpire Steve Davis has given an <b>official warning</b> to Shenwari for landing on the danger area.]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shenwari to Shakib, no run, bowls this one quicker and outside off, Shakib was looking to cut it, but fails to connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shenwari to Shakib, no run, tossed up on middle and leg, Shakib goes deep and works it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shenwari to Shakib, no run, flatter around off, Shakib goes back and cuts it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shenwari to Shakib, no run, on the pads, Shakib nudges it to short fine, he was looking for the single, but the non-striker sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shenwari to Rahim, 1 run, floated outside off, Rahim comes on the front foot and drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shenwari to Rahim, no run, gives this one more air on middle and gets it to turn away, Rahim defends off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Samiullah Shenwari, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shenwari comes onto bowl for the first time today]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Shakib, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Shakib hangs back and defends, the ball rolls away to his right off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Rahim, 1 run, full and outside off, Rahim comes forward and looks to drive it hard, the ball rolls away down to third man off the outside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Rahim, 2 runs, fullish in length and on middle, clipped through mid-wicket for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Rahim, no run, good bumper from Shapoor, Rahim ducks underneath and the umpire signals one bouncer for the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Rahim, no run, full toss angling in around off, Rahim helps it down to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place for Rahim]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mushfiqur Rahim, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Mahmudullah, <b>out</b> Caught by Zazai!! Shapoor strikes again and Mahmudullah has to go. It was just short of a good length and outside off, Mahmudullah was looking to run it down to third man and opens the face of the bat. The extra bounce on the ball catches the edge and the keeper takes a good catch diving low to his right. Bangladesh are 4 down now. <b>Mahmudullah c Zazai b Shapoor 23(46)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Shapoor to Mahmudullah, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Shakib, <b>FOUR</b>, drags this one short and Shakib is quick to rock back, he pulls it to the deep mid-wicket fence and collects four, this is great batting, he has now raced to <b>13 off 7 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Mahmudullah, 1 run, on middle and leg, Mahmudullah works it behind square and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Mahmudullah, no run, goes down on one knee and looks to sweep, he gets a top-edge that falls to his left, but the keeper couldn't get to it on time]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Shakib, 1 run, floated up on middle and leg, Shakib eases it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Shakib, no run, darted on the pad, Shakib leans forward and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Shakib, 2 runs, shortish and slightly wide outside off, Shakib rocks back and cuts it past backward point for a couple]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Mahmudullah, no run, yorker around off, Mahmudullah jams it out into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[The umpires are having a discussion. Maybe, it is about three fielders behind square on the leg-side. Shakib complained to the umpires about something. Not really sure about what.]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Shakib, 1 run, full and around off, Shakib goes across and wrists it towards mid-wicket, the batsmen take a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[A leg slip is in place now]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Mahmudullah, 1 run, short of length delivery on top of off, Mahmudullah nudges it towards mid-wicket and sets off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Mahmudullah, no run, full and slightly wide outside off, Mahmudullah chases it and goes after it, but fails to make a connection and the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Mahmudullah, no run, was that going down leg? Yes, it was. It was the fuller one from round the wicket, it comes in sharply around middle and leg, Mahmudullah fails to clip it into the leg-side and is hit on the pad, the ball was snaking down leg though]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Mahmudullah, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Mahmudullah goes back and defends]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Mahmudullah, 1 run, drifting onto the pad, Mahmudullah works it towards square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Shakib, 1 run, flatter on the stumps, Shakib backs away and cuts it towards cover, the batsmen take a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Mahmudullah, 1 run, floated around off, Mahmudullah leans forward and wrists it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Mahmudullah, no run, an appeal from the Afghanis, but that was too high. It was slowish and turning in on middle, Mahmudullah fails to work it into the on-side and wears it on his pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Mahmudullah, no run, gives this one more air, Mahmudullah works it towards mid-wicket, who dives to his left and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Mahmudullah, no run, flighted delivery just outside off, Mahmudullah defends off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Javed Ahmadi [1.0-0-10-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Shakib, <b>FOUR</b>, Shakib gets off the mark with a boundary, this was a poor ball, full and on the pads, Shakib tickles it to the fine leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Soumya Sarkar, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Shapoor gets the breakthrough. Sarkar departs after hitting a six and a four in the previous over. It was fuller and tailing in on middle stump line, Sarkar was looking to whip it through the on-side from the crease, he fails to lay bat onto it and the ball hits the front pad first and then gets deflected onto the back pad. The umpire took his time and then raised his finger. Shapoor is pumped and celebrates in delight. Sarkar had a chat with Mahmudullah and maybe, he was unaware that the review had already been used up by Anamul. <b>Soumya Sarkar lbw b Shapoor 28(25) [4s-3 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shapoor to Soumya Sarkar, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Back over the wicket to the left-hander]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Mahmudullah, 1 run, touch straighter in line, Mahmudullah goes slightly across and tucks it away to fine leg, this single also brings up the <b>50-run stand</b> between these two]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Mahmudullah, no run, length delivery outside off, Mahmudullah leans forward and blocks it to cover with an angular bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Mahmudullah, no run, just short of a good length and angling in on off, Mahmudullah defends it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Mahmudullah, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Mahmudullah hops and defends it towards point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shapoor Zadran [3.0-1-4-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Zadran comes back, replacing Ahmadi. Zadran only gave away 4 runs in his first 3 overs. Let's see how his second spell goes. He will start from round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, strays this one onto the pads, Sarkar leans forward a touch and flicks it hard to the fine leg fence, <b>15 runs</b> came off that over]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Mahmudullah, 3 runs, fuller and just outside off, Mahmudullah presses forward and drives it between extra cover and mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Mahmudullah, no run, fullish around off, Mahmudullah steps out of the crease and defends it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, back of a length delivery on middle, Sarkar closes the bat face early, gets a leading edge to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Soumya Sarkar, <b>SIX</b>, fantastic shot from Sarkar! Great use of the feet, comes charging down the track and pulls this back of a length delivery across the line to send it over the wide long-on fence for a big maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Mahmudullah, 1 run, back of a length and coming back into the right-hander, who moves across a touch and clips it to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Mahmudullah, 1 run, shuffles across and softly wrists it to mid-wicket for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, presses on the front foot and drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Mahmudullah, 1 run, gets forward and gently taps it towards long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Mahmudullah, 2 runs, shuffles across and clips it through backward square leg, sets off for the run, the fielder fires a direct hit at the non-striker's end but Mahmudullah was safely in, the batsmen then run for the second on overthrow]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire has been called for a run-out chance. Mahmudullah was the man in question. Not out is the call.]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, guides it with an open bat face towards backward point, a slight misfield allows the batsmen to run a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ahmadi to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, what a welcome for Ahmadi! He bowls this one quite short, Sarkar had all the time in the world to rock back and pulls it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Javed Ahmadi, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Mahmudullah, no run, stays behind the line and blocks it back, the ball keeps a little low as well, <b>third maiden over</b> from Mirwais]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Mahmudullah, no run, a bit of a mix-up there. Mahmudullah stays back and dabs this back of a length delivery outside off with an open bat face to backward point, the fielder dives, makes a fine stop and has a shy at the non-striker's end, Soumya Sarkar has to hurry back and a single is prevented]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Mahmudullah, no run, shuffles across and turns this length delivery around off towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Mahmudullah, no run, touch fuller around off, Mahmudullah solidly defends off the front foot with an angled bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Mahmudullah, no run, length delivery coming back into Mahmudullah, he wrists it towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Mahmudullah, no run, fullish on off, Mahmudullah defends it gently into the leg-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Mahmudullah, 1 run, shuffles across a touch and works it to square leg for a brisk single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, drifts it onto the pads, Sarkar clips it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Soumya Sarkar, no run, makes room and cuts this shortish delivery behind point]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Mahmudullah, 1 run, full and on the off stump, driven to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, on the off stump, tucked for a single through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Soumya Sarkar, no run, flatter ball on the stumps, defended]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Mahmudullah, no run, fuller around off, Mahmudullah gets behind the line and defends solidly. He wants a single but is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Mahmudullah, no run, fullish and around leg once again, Mahmudullah works it behind square]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Mahmudullah, 2 runs, straying onto Mahmudullah's pad, Mahmudullah leans forward and flicks it through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Mahmudullah, <b>wide</b>, full and going down leg, Mahmudullah does not connect with the glance]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, opens the face of the bat and guides it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Mahmudullah, leg byes, 1 run, slides it down leg, Mahmudullah misses the glance and the ball goes off the pad behind square, a muted appeal for lbw but that was comfortably missing the leg-stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Mahmudullah, no run, fuller around off, Mahmudullah brings his bat down and defends it towards mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Mahmudullah, 3 runs, back of a length and coming back in, Mahmudullah shuffles across and clips it to deep mid-wicket, sloppy fielding there, allows the batsmen to take a third run]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Mahmudullah, no run, fuller around off, Mahmudullah pushes at it, gets a thickish inside edge towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, leans forward to this full delivery on off and works it to mid-on for a brisk run]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Mahmudullah, 1 run, length delivery around off, Mahmudullah shuffles across a touch and clips it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Mahmudullah, no run, bouncer on off, Mahmudullah ducks underneath it]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, fullish around off, Sarkar taps it to cover-point and calls for a quick single, Mahmudullah responds well, good running between the wickets by the batsmen]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, opens the face of the bat and helps it to third man for a comfortable single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, nicely picked up by Sarkar! It was a full delivery from Mirwais straying onto Sarkar's pads, he just leans forward slightly and whips it to the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Soumya Sarkar, no run, Sarkar presses forward and pushes this full delivery around off towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Soumya Sarkar, no run, keeps it full and angles it across the batsman, Sarkar drives it softly to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Soumya Sarkar, no run, fullish on middle and off, Sarkar knocks it towards cover-point, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Soumya Sarkar, no run, fuller and angled across, Sarkar gets forward and drives it to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Mahmudullah, no run, opens the face of the bat and dabs this outside off delivery behind point]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Mahmudullah, no run, low full toss coming back into the batsman, Mahmudullah pushes it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Mahmudullah, no run, fullish around off, Mahmudullah defends it with an angled bat towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Mahmudullah, <b>wide</b>, a very high bumper from Alam outside off, Mahmudullah ducks under it and lets that go through]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Mahmudullah, no run, fuller and in that channel outside off, Mahmudullah shoulders arms to it]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, knocks it towards square third man for a comfortable single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Soumya Sarkar, no run, appeal for a caught behind from the bowler but that seems to have come off the pad. It was a full ball around leg, Sarkar misses the glance and the ball goes off the pad into the keeper's gloves. Replays showed that there was no bat involved]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Aftab Alam [2.0-0-11-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Alam is back into the attack. Just a wide slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Mahmudullah, 2 runs, Mahmudullah shuffles across, leans forward and clips it through backward square leg for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Mahmudullah, no run, length delivery around off, Mahmudullah presses forward and defends it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mahmudullah, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Anamul, <b>out</b> Lbw!! It was a back of a length delivery from Mirwais, Anamul gets forward and looks to push into the off-side, the ball nips back in and raps his back pad instead. The bowler and the wicketkeeper appealed straightaway. Hawk-Eye showed that impact was just around the off-stump, it was a 50:50 call. And the ball was just clipping the top of off-stump. Anamul will have to go! <b>Anamul lbw b Mirwais 29(55) [4s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mirwais to Anamul, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Anamul has been given out lbw. He has reviewed that after consultation with his partner. No problems with Mirwais' front foot. No bat is involved. The impact is umpire's call and it was just clipping off. The onfield decision stays and Anamul is OUT!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Anamul, no run, fuller and around off, Anamul gets forward and drives it straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Anamul, no run, presses forward once again and drives it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Anamul, no run, fullish and just outside off, Anamul gets forward and knocks it towards point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Anamul, 1 run, on middle, Anamul gets forward and drives it softly to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Anamul, no run, looks to turn it down the leg-side, gets a soft leading edge back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Anamul, <b>FOUR</b>, quicker delivery by Nabi this time, Anamul uses the pace on that and steers it to the square third man fence, no chance for the fielder to stop that one. The bowler is not very happy about it]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Anamul, no run, stays on the front foot and defends comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Anamul, no run, fullish around the leg stump, Anamul nudges this into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Anamul, no run, gets forward and knocks it in front of point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Soumya Sarkar, no run, fullish around off, Sarkar gets forward and defends it into the off-side. A <b>maiden wicket over</b> from Mirwais]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Soumya Sarkar, no run, presses on the front foot and pushes it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Soumya Sarkar, no run, length delivery on middle and off, Sarkar gets forward and pushes it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Soumya Sarkar, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Tamim, <b>out</b> Caught by Zazai!! Brilliant catch by the keeper and what a huge wicket for Afghanistan! It was a short of good length delivery by Mirwais, no feet movement from Tamim as he just looks to run this down to third man, gets a thick outside edge instead. Zazai dives full length to his left and snaffles the take with one hand. The Afghan players are ecstatic, they have finally got their man. Tamim had survived a caught behind chance on 6 earlier. <b>Tamim c Zazai b Mirwais 19(42) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mirwais to Tamim, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Tamim, no run, keeps it full and around off, Tamim gets forward and drives it towards mid-off again]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Tamim, no run, fuller and coming back into the batsman, Tamim drives it hard to mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Anamul, no run, shuffles across a touch and works it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Anamul, no run, stays behind the line and pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Tamim, 1 run, gets down on one knee and sweeps it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Anamul, 1 run, gets forward and pushes at it, gets a thick outside edge to short third man for a streaky single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Tamim, 1 run, opens the face of the bat to this quicker delivery outside off and gets a bottom edge to short third man for a brisk single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Anamul, 1 run, gets forward and gently taps it towards long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Tamim, no run, length delivery on middle, Tamim gets forward slightly and defends it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Tamim, no run, short of a good length around off, Tamim bunts it just in front of point]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Anamul, 1 run, comes down the track and clips it to mid-wicket for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Anamul, no run, length delivery coming back into the batsman, Anamul defends it from the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Tamim, 1 run, <b>direct hit and Tamim would have been a goner</b>! He comes forward to this length delivery around off and taps it to cover, wants a single and comes halfway down the track, the fielder at cover fires a throw at the striker's end and Tamim has to hurry back. The ball does not hit the stumps and the batsmen take a single on the overthrow]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Tamim, no run, shortens the length and shapes it away from the left-hander, Tamim came down the track and slashed hard at it but missed it completely]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Anamul, no run, pushed through slower by Nabi, Anamul gets a good stride forward, plays with the spin and turns it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Anamul, no run, slower and on off, Anamul gets well forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Anamul, no run, flighted and on the stumps, Anamul presses forward and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Tamim, 1 run, tossed up and on off, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Tamim, no run, another shout, for LBW this time, but the angle was taking it down leg, Tamim was looking to work one towards the on-side and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Tamim, <b>wide</b>, appeal for a <b>caught behind</b>, but the umpire isn't fooled and signals it as a wide. This was slanted down leg-side by Nabi]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nabi to Anamul, 1 run, tossed up and on the stumps, Anamul works it in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Nabi, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Tamim, no run, a <b>maiden over</b> from Ashraf, nothing really special, just bowling to his field, this was full and in that channel outside off, Tamim presses forward and drives it straight to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Tamim, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Tamim prods forward, meets the ball on top of the bounce and drives it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Tamim, no run, Ashraf goes full and just outside off, Tamim goes hard on the drive, gets an inside edge towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Tamim, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Tamim gets a good stride forward and pushes it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Tamim, no run, back of a length and in that channel outside off, Tamim hangs back and defends it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Tamim, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Tamim works it to the left of mid-wicket and calls for a single, Anamul isn't so sure and asks his partner to go back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Anamul, no run, fuller length delivery outside off and shaping away, Anamul doesn't need to fiddle at those, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Anamul, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Anamul gets well forward and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Anamul, no run, that's much better from Alam, pitches this one further up and gets it to shape away, draws Anamul into the drive and beats his outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Anamul, <b>FOUR</b>, this is poor bowling from Alam, he overcompensates and offers this one plenty of width outside off, cracked away square past cover for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Anamul, 2 runs, Alam isn't getting his line and length right, drifts one onto Anamul's pads, whipped past square leg for a couple of more runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Anamul, <b>FOUR</b>, way too short from Aftab Alam, he doesn't have the pace to trouble the batsmen, Anamul swivels across, rolls his wrists and pulls it past mid-wicket, the ball races away to the mid-wicket boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Anamul, 1 run, full and nipping back into Anamul, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Anamul, no run, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, Anamul gets a good stride forward and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Anamul, no run, on a good length and angling back into Anamul, defended towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Anamul, no run, pushed up further and just outside off, not much bounce on that, Anamul was looking to pull and missed, the ball hits the thigh pad and rolls away towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Anamul, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Anamul presses across and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mirwais to Tamim, 3 runs, poor start from Ashraf, a half-volley on Tamim's pads, clipped away in front of square on the on-side, a long chase for the fielder and the batsmen get back for the third run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mirwais Ashraf, right-arm medium fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Anamul, no run, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, Anamul presses across and defends it with an angled bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Anamul, no run, back of a length and in that channel outside off, Anamul isn't sure of his footwork, limply hangs his bat at that and the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Tamim, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, Tamim presses across and nudges it in front of mid-wicket, there was a bit of hesitation between the two batsmen, but the single was always on]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Tamim, no run, short of a length and well outside off, Tamim stays back and slaps it straight to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Tamim, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Tamim presses across and defends it towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aftab Alam to Tamim, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Tamim shuffles across and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Aftab Alam, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Anamul, no run, Hassan shortens his length outside off, Anamul watches it all along, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Anamul, no run, on a good length and a hint of shape back into Anamul, he closes the face of the bat and defends it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Anamul, <b>FOUR</b>, Hassan releases the pressure, poor ball, full and on Anamul's pads, he gets inside the line and flicks it very fine, the fine leg is pretty square, first boundary for Anamul]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Anamul, no run, tad fuller and in that corridor outside off, Anamul gets a good stride forward, presents the full face of the bat and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Anamul, no run, Hassan keeps it full and in that corridor outside off, Anamul isn't tempted at playing those, good carry and hits the keeper's gloves hard]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Anamul, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Anamul gets well forward and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[A slip and a short cover in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Tamim, no run, Shapoor shortens his length and gets this one to drift into Tamim, turned away towards square leg, a <b>maiden over</b> from Shapoor]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Tamim, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Tamim presses forward and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Tamim, no run, back of a length and well outside off, punched off the back-foot, but can't get past extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Tamim, no run, Shapoor is hitting the deck hard, gets good bounce on this back of a length delivery, Tamim hops across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Tamim, no run, Shapoor shortens his length and gets it to hold its line outside off, Tamim drops his gloves and sways away from the line]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Tamim, no run, short of a length and angling acros Tamim, defended towards the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Anamul, no run, appeal for LBW, but there were two noises on that, must have been the inside egde of the bat. Anamul fell over as he went for the flick, umpire Davis says NO]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Tamim, 1 run, good shot but equally well fielded at mid-on, this was full and on off, Tamim presents the full face of the bat and drives it to the right of mid-on. The fielder tumbles and makes a half-stop, saves some runs for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Tamim, no run, tad fuller and shaping away from outside off, Iqbal covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Tamim, no run, much better from Hassan, on a good length and in that channel around off, Tamim presents the full face of the bat as he blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, too full and too wide from Hassan, Tamim gets a big stride forward and crashes it through extra cover, no one moved, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Anamul, leg byes, 1 run, Hassan goes full and on Anamul's pads, he looks to flick and misses, the ball rolls away behind square on the on-side for a leg-bye]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Anamul, 1 run, that's poor cricket from Nabi at cover, he did exceedingly well to get across and intercept the drive. Anamul was looking for a single, would have been in trouble had Nabi gathered the ball. In the end, the return is poor and the ball rolls away towards square leg, Anamul gets the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Anamul, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Anamul presses across and defends it with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Anamul, no run, that's a cracker from Shapoor, Anamul was completely taken by surprise, does well to drop his wrists at the last moment and sways out of the way. This one pitched around middle and reared from a length as it angled away, Anamul was pushing forward and is surprised as the ball jags past his outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Anamul, no run, back of a length and shaping away from outside off, Anamul covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Anamul, no run, short of a length and just outside off, rears up from a length, Anamul rides with the bounce and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[The replays are out on that Tamim call. There's a spike mark when the ball went past the bat, on the snicko. It can't be anything other than a thin edge. Why didn't you refer, Afghanistan?]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Anamul, 2 runs, short of a length and on Anamul's pads, clipped away past square leg for a brace, poor running, there was a third run there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Tamim, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, lures Tamim into the drive, there was a clear noise as the ball went past the outside edge. Zazai was sure, so was the bowler, but umpire Steve Davis says NO]]></line><line><![CDATA[Loud shout for a <b>caught behind</b>. Almost the entire Afghanistan team deliberate on a review, and then decide against it]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, that's nicely played! Tad fuller and wider from Hassan, Tamim gets well forward, opens the face of the bat at the last moment and caresses it past cover-point for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Tamim, 2 runs, Tamim is off the mark, Hassan gets his line wrong, shortens his length and angles one onto Tamim's pads, flicked past square leg for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Tamim, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Tamim gets a good stride forward and drives it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Tamim, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Iqbal presses across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Tamim, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Iqbal rides with the bounce and defends it with an angled bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Anamul, no run, on another day this might have well crashed onto the stumps, Shapoor shortens his length and angles across Anamul, he was looking to pull and gets an inside edge onto the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Anamul, no run, tad fuller and on that off-stump channel, not much movement on offer for Shapoor, defended with an angled bat towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Tamim, leg byes, 1 run, too straight from Shapoor, ends up drifting onto Iqbal's pads, he looks to flick and misses, the ball goes off the pads towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Tamim, no run, short of a length and angling onto Iqbal's ribs, he hops across, rides with the bounce and is hit high on the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips for Tamim as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Anamul, 1 run, back of a length and in that corridor outside off, Anamul rides with the bounce and dabs it down towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shapoor to Anamul, no run, fuller length delivery and in that channel outside off, Anamul prods forward in defence and gets a thick edge to the left of backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shapoor Zadran, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place for Shapoor]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Tamim, no run, on a good length and on the stumps, Tamim presses across and defends it towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Tamim, no run, nicely bowled by Hassan, goes full and looks to shape it away from outside off, Tamim just about gets his bat down in time and jams it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Anamul, 1 run, too straight from Hassan, ends up drifting onto Anamul's pads, clipped away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Anamul, no run, extra bounce for Hassan, on a good length and holding its line around off, rears off a length and hits Anamul high on the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Anamul, no run, tad fuller and angling back into Anamul, he shuffles across on the flick and is struck high on the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Anamul, no run, on a good length and a hint of nip away from off, Anamul is slightly opened up as he looks to defend, gets a thick edge towards gully]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hamid to Anamul, <b>wide</b>, an extra to start with, Hassan floats one full and gets it to shape away further, wide called by the umpire]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Anamul and Tamim are at the crease. Anamul is on strike. Hamid will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Right, the anthems are over. The Afghanis are in the middle of the team huddle. Hamid Hassan, their opening bowler, is a contrast, with a head band and the Afghanistan flag painted on his cheeks. He will open the bowling as well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The team anthems are in progress.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Afghanistan have won <b>8 ODIs</b> since January 2014, while Bangladesh, who are ranked ahead of them, have just won <b>5</b>. Don't count this as a low-key affair.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Afghanistan</b> (Playing XI): Afsar Zazai(w), Javed Ahmadi, Nawroz Mangal, Asghar Stanikzai, Samiullah Shenwari, Mohammad Nabi(c), Najibullah Zadran, Mirwais Ashraf, Aftab Alam, Shapoor Zadran, Hamid Hassan]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangladesh</b> (Playing XI): Tamim Iqbal, Anamul Haque, Mominul Haque, Mushfiqur Rahim(w), Sabbir Rahman, Shakib Al Hasan, Mahmudullah, Mashrafe Mortaza(c), Soumya Sarkar, Rubel Hossain, Taskin Ahmed]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangladesh have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mashrafe Mortaza:</b> "First match is very important for everyone. It has been set up nicely. Hopefully we will do well today. We will bat first. It looks to be a very good track and hopefully we will make a good total. No changes to our side."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Nabi:</b> "This is our World Cup and it is very exciting. Everyone is fit and hopefully we will do well in the tournament. We have three fast bowlers in our side. Hopefully the ball will reverse after 25 overs and hopefully we will chase a low total."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pitch Report:</b> "It is a fantastic looking pitch, hardly a blade of grass on it. It is very hard and well rolled. We have cracks here and there. There can be a bit of crumbling. 300 would be a good score here and it will be a good chase as well. Afghanistan will compete, I think it will be even stevens (on Afghanistan giving a fight to the Bangladesh batters). Build your innings and maximise the score. Perfect batting pitch. Win the toss and bat first", reckon <b>Russell Arnold</b> and <b>Ramiz Raja</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[We are just minutes away from the toss and team updates. How will the pitch play? What will be a par score on this track? Answers coming up in a short while.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather</b>: It is bright and sunny out there and the great news is that there is no forecast of rain during the course of the match. It is currently 27 degrees and the maximum is expected to be around 29 degrees.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The story is quite different for Bangladesh though. They lost to Pakistan in their first match and then couldn't conquer Ireland either. This puts a bit of extra pressure on the team, but with world-class players like Shakib Al Hasan and Mushfiqur Rahim in their ranks, they don't have to look far ahead for inspiration. The team had an intense three-hour training session at the Manuka Oval a couple of days ago and with coach Chandika Hathurusinghe revealing before the tournament that his side is targetting a place in the quarterfinals, it is quite clear that Bangladesh want to make a statement in their first game.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Building up to this game, there is no doubt that the momentum is with the Afghans. Although they went down to India in their first warm-up game, they made sure that India couldn't bowl them out. A few days later, they posted over 300 and held their nerve to edge UAE by 14 runs in their second warm-up fixture. In fact, Afghanistan believe that they have the fast bowlers to exploit the pace and bounce and trouble the Bangladeshi batsmen, most of whom are short.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ever since 2008, the rise of <b>Afghanistan</b>, who are making their <b>World Cup debut</b>, has been great. They were ranked as the top Associate nation just a few days ago, placed 11th in the ICC ODI rankings, ahead of Ireland, Scotland and Kenya. Their journey has been an inspiring story so far, considering that they emerge from a war-torn country.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The mind games have already started! Speaking ahead of the match, Afghanistan captain Mohammad Nabi said that Bangladesh are under pressure coming into this contest. Their coach Andy Moles has also said that his side will give a tough fight to Bangladesh. On the other hand, when reminded about Bangladesh's loss at the hands of Afghanistan in the 2014 Asia Cup, captain Mashrafe Mortaza was quick to say that his side was not bothered by the defeat.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>13:15 Local Time, 02:15 GMT, 07:45 IST:</b> It's time for Canberra to join the 2015 World Cup party as the picturesque Manuka Oval gears up to host its second ever World Cup match. We have Bangladesh taking on Afghanistan today in this Group A fixture. Well, these two teams might have the tag of 'minnows', but this contest has all the makings to be an exciting match, especially after Afghanistan's win over Bangladesh in their own backyard last year.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/><br/>The sleepy town of Canberra will be shaken out of its slumber when the World Cup party reaches the Manuka Oval, which hosts the Pool A fixture between Bangladesh and Afghanistan. They may not be cream of the subcontinent but both teams are capable of putting up eye-catching performances in the hope to make a winning start to their campaign.<br/><br/>While Afghanistan make their debut at Canberra and would look to impress, Bangladesh's stay as an ICC Full Member has been filled with disappointments intertwined with the odd success. Mashrafe Mortaza's men would look to invoke their 2007 campaign where they upset India in the tournament opener, and a winning start here would go a long way in boosting their confidence.<br/><br/><b>Venue:</b> Manuka Oval, Canberra<br/><br/><b>Date:</b> February 18<br/><br/><b>Time:</b> 0900 Hrs (IST)<br/><br/><b>Weather:</b> Mostly sunny with a high of 28 degrees<br/><br/><b>Team news</b><br/><br/><b>Bangladesh</b><br/><br/>Bangladesh lost both their warm-up games in the lead-up to the tournament to Pakistan and Ireland, and their second defeat would have hurt them more. Bangladesh's short batsmen would be wary of Afghanistan's fast bowlers who can generate good pace and bounce and a hard Manuka Oval pitch would assist their kind of bowling.<br/><br/>After losing both their warm-up matches, the biggest problem for Bangladesh would be to find the right balance of fast bowlers and spinners, as they are used to playing a slew of spinners on turning pitches at home. Mortaza would need to shepherd a promising but green pace attack with Taskin Ahmed set to partner him, and a battle for the third seamer in Rubel Hossain or Al-Amin Hossain to follow.<br/><br/>On the batting front, seniors Shakib Al Hasan and Mushfiqur Rahim would be hoping they get solid support from the top order and not let the pressure fall on them to revive the innings.<br/><br/><b>Probable XI:</b> 1. Anamul Haque, 2. Tamim Iqbal, 3. Mominul Haque, 4. Soumya Sarkar/Mahmudullah, 5. Shakib Al Hasan, 6. Mushfiqur Rahim (wk), 7. Nasir Hossain, 8. Mashrafe Mortaza (capt), 9. Taijul Islam, 10. Taskin Ahmed, 11. Rubel Hossain/Al-Amin Hossain.<br/><br/><b>Afghanistan</b><br/><br/>Afghanistan don't consider themselves to be the giant killers that a team like Ireland can turn out to be, but they sure aren't here to make up the numbers, as their coach Andy Moles had clearly said. Against India in their second warm-up game, their batsmen went after the 365-run target gamely and don't need to look beyond Ireland's performance against the West Indies for inspiration.<br/><br/>Afghanistan would rely heavily on their bowlers to make quick inroads into the Bangladesh batting to limit them, and give themselves the best chance of going after their target.<br/><br/><b>Probable XI:</b> 1. Javed Ahmadi, 2. Usman Ghani, 3. Nawroz Mangal, 4. Asghar Stanikzai, 5. Samiullah Shenwari, 6. Mohammad Nabi (capt), 7. Afsar Zazai (wk), 8. Mirwais Ashraf, 9. Dawlat Zadran, 10. Hamid Hassan, 11. Shapoor Zadran.<br/><br/><b>Watch out for</b><br/><br/>While all the attention will be taken up by Shakib in the middle order, <b>Mominul Haque</b> has revelled in the No 3 position for his team and come up with some eye-catching performances. Although yet to score a century in ODI cricket, he averages 63 in Tests, pointing to a good future ahead for the stylish left-hander. Against a pace Afghanistan bowling attack he would have to play the anchor's role and guide Bangladesh to a position of strength with the bat.<br/><br/><b>Usman Ghani</b> is just 17 but looked unperturbed against the likes of Mohammad Shami and Umesh Yadav in the warm-up game against India on his way to 44. Although he started explosively, Ghani settled into playing second-fiddle to No 3 Nawroz Mangal, who took over the senior batsman's responsibility. Against Bangladesh, Ghani would come out all guns blazing as he is expected to at his age.<br/><br/><b>Quotes</b><br/><br/>"If they do [win] they'll be dancing in the streets of Kandahar and Kabul and Jalalabad and wherever else," said former Australian fast bowler <b>Geoff Lawson</b>, who coached the Afghanistan Under-19 team previously.<br/><br/><b>Stats</b><br/><br/>Afghanistan beat Bangladesh in the only time they squared off in an ODI during the Asia Cup in Dhaka last year.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Afghanistan</b> (From): Usman Ghani, Javed Ahmadi, Nawroz Mangal, Asghar Stanikzai, Mohammad Nabi(c), Samiullah Shenwari, Mirwais Ashraf, Afsar Zazai(w), Najibullah Zadran, Dawlat Zadran, Shapoor Zadran, Aftab Alam, Hamid Hassan, Gulbadin Naib, Nasir Jamal]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangladesh</b> (From): Tamim Iqbal, Anamul Haque, Mominul Haque, Shakib Al Hasan, Mahmudullah, Mushfiqur Rahim(w), Nasir Hossain, Mashrafe Mortaza(c), Sabbir Rahman, Rubel Hossain, Taskin Ahmed, Al-Amin Hossain, Arafat Sunny, Soumya Sarkar, Taijul Islam]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>267</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>10</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>50</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Bangladesh">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8237</playerid>
					<name>Anamul Haque</name>
					<batsman-name>Anamul</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Anamul</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>29</runs>
					<balls>55</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Mirwais</bowler>
					<bowlerId>3013</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>612</playerid>
					<name>Tamim Iqbal</name>
					<batsman-name>Tamim</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Tamim</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>19</runs>
					<balls>42</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mirwais</bowler>
					<bowlerId>3013</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Afsar Zazai</fielder>
						<fielderId>8278</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8233</playerid>
					<name>Soumya Sarkar</name>
					<batsman-name>Soumya Sarkar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Soumya Sarkar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>28</runs>
					<balls>25</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Shapoor</bowler>
					<bowlerId>3015</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1121</playerid>
					<name>Mahmudullah</name>
					<batsman-name>Mahmudullah</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mahmudullah</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>23</runs>
					<balls>46</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Shapoor</bowler>
					<bowlerId>3015</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Afsar Zazai</fielder>
						<fielderId>8278</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>544</playerid>
					<name>Shakib Al Hasan</name>
					<batsman-name>Shakib</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shakib</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>63</runs>
					<balls>51</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Hamid</bowler>
					<bowlerId>3001</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>394</playerid>
					<name>Mushfiqur Rahim</name>
					<batsman-name>Rahim</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rahim</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>71</runs>
					<balls>56</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Nabi</bowler>
					<bowlerId>3007</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Samiullah Shenwari</fielder>
						<fielderId>3011</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8231</playerid>
					<name>Sabbir Rahman</name>
					<batsman-name>S Rahman</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Rahman</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>8</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Hamid</bowler>
					<bowlerId>3001</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>323</playerid>
					<name>Mashrafe Mortaza</name>
					<batsman-name>Mortaza</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mortaza</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>14</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Aftab Alam</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6476</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8219</playerid>
					<name>Mominul Haque</name>
					<batsman-name>Mominul</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mominul</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Afsar Zazai</fielder>
						<fielderId>8278</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1736</playerid>
					<name>Rubel Hossain</name>
					<batsman-name>Rubel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rubel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8548</playerid>
					<name>Taskin Ahmed</name>
					<batsman-name>Taskin Ahmed</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Taskin Ahmed</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Aftab Alam</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6476</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>612</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>47</runs>
				<overs>14.3</overs>
				<batsman>Tamim Iqbal</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Tamim</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8237</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>52</runs>
				<overs>16.4</overs>
				<batsman>Anamul Haque</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Anamul</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8233</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>102</runs>
				<overs>25.5</overs>
				<batsman>Soumya Sarkar</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Soumya Sarkar</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1121</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>119</runs>
				<overs>29.1</overs>
				<batsman>Mahmudullah</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mahmudullah</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>544</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>233</runs>
				<overs>44.4</overs>
				<batsman>Shakib Al Hasan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Shakib</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8231</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>241</runs>
				<overs>46.5</overs>
				<batsman>Sabbir Rahman</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Rahman</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>394</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>247</runs>
				<overs>47.3</overs>
				<batsman>Mushfiqur Rahim</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rahim</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8219</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>263</runs>
				<overs>49</overs>
				<batsman>Mominul Haque</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mominul</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>323</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>263</runs>
				<overs>49.1</overs>
				<batsman>Mashrafe Mortaza</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mortaza</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8548</playerid>
				<nbr>10</nbr>
				<runs>267</runs>
				<overs>49.6</overs>
				<batsman>Taskin Ahmed</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Taskin Ahmed</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>3</byes>
			<wides>6</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>4</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>13</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Afghanistan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>3001</playerid>
					<name>Hamid Hassan</name>
					<bowler-name>Hamid</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Hamid</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>61</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3015</playerid>
					<name>Shapoor Zadran</name>
					<bowler-name>Shapoor</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shapoor</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>20</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6476</playerid>
					<name>Aftab Alam</name>
					<bowler-name>Aftab Alam</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Aftab Alam</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>55</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3013</playerid>
					<name>Mirwais Ashraf</name>
					<bowler-name>Mirwais</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mirwais</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>3</maidens>
					<runsoff>32</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3007</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Nabi</name>
					<bowler-name>Nabi</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nabi</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>58</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7614</playerid>
					<name>Javed Ahmadi</name>
					<bowler-name>Ahmadi</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ahmadi</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4.5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>32</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3011</playerid>
					<name>Samiullah Shenwari</name>
					<bowler-name>Shenwari</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shenwari</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1.1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>2</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8278</playerid>
					<name>Afsar Zazai</name>
					<bowler-name>Zazai</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Zazai</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3008</playerid>
					<name>Nawroz Mangal</name>
					<bowler-name>Nawroz</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nawroz</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3004</playerid>
					<name>Asghar Stanikzai</name>
					<bowler-name>Stanikzai</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Stanikzai</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8375</playerid>
					<name>Najibullah Zadran</name>
					<bowler-name>Najibullah</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Najibullah</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>162</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>10</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>42.5</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Afghanistan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7614</playerid>
					<name>Javed Ahmadi</name>
					<batsman-name>Ahmadi</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ahmadi</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mortaza</bowler>
					<bowlerId>323</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mortaza</fielder>
						<fielderId>323</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8278</playerid>
					<name>Afsar Zazai</name>
					<batsman-name>Zazai</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Zazai</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Rubel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1736</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3008</playerid>
					<name>Nawroz Mangal</name>
					<batsman-name>Nawroz</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nawroz</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>27</runs>
					<balls>57</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mahmudullah</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1121</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Rubel Hossain</fielder>
						<fielderId>1736</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3004</playerid>
					<name>Asghar Stanikzai</name>
					<batsman-name>Stanikzai</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Stanikzai</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mortaza</bowler>
					<bowlerId>323</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mahmudullah</fielder>
						<fielderId>1121</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3011</playerid>
					<name>Samiullah Shenwari</name>
					<batsman-name>Shenwari</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shenwari</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>42</runs>
					<balls>75</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sabbir Rahman</fielder>
						<fielderId>8231</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Mushfiqur Rahim</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>394</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3007</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Nabi</name>
					<batsman-name>Nabi</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nabi</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>44</runs>
					<balls>43</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mortaza</bowler>
					<bowlerId>323</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Soumya Sarkar</fielder>
						<fielderId>8233</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8375</playerid>
					<name>Najibullah Zadran</name>
					<batsman-name>Najibullah</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Najibullah</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>17</runs>
					<balls>34</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Shakib</bowler>
					<bowlerId>544</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3013</playerid>
					<name>Mirwais Ashraf</name>
					<batsman-name>Mirwais</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mirwais</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>10</runs>
					<balls>15</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Shakib</bowler>
					<bowlerId>544</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sabbir Rahman</fielder>
						<fielderId>8231</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6476</playerid>
					<name>Aftab Alam</name>
					<batsman-name>Aftab Alam</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Aftab Alam</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>14</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Soumya Sarkar</fielder>
						<fielderId>8233</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Mushfiqur Rahim</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>394</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3001</playerid>
					<name>Hamid Hassan</name>
					<batsman-name>Hamid</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Hamid</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Taskin Ahmed</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8548</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Anamul Haque</fielder>
						<fielderId>8237</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3015</playerid>
					<name>Shapoor Zadran</name>
					<batsman-name>Shapoor</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shapoor</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7614</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>2</runs>
				<overs>0.6</overs>
				<batsman>Javed Ahmadi</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Ahmadi</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8278</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>2</runs>
				<overs>1.1</overs>
				<batsman>Afsar Zazai</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Zazai</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>3004</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>3</runs>
				<overs>2.6</overs>
				<batsman>Asghar Stanikzai</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Stanikzai</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>3008</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>65</runs>
				<overs>22.4</overs>
				<batsman>Nawroz Mangal</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Nawroz</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>3011</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>78</runs>
				<overs>25.4</overs>
				<batsman>Samiullah Shenwari</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Shenwari</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8375</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>136</runs>
				<overs>36.6</overs>
				<batsman>Najibullah Zadran</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Najibullah</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>3007</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>136</runs>
				<overs>37.1</overs>
				<batsman>Mohammad Nabi</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Nabi</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>3013</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>154</runs>
				<overs>40.6</overs>
				<batsman>Mirwais Ashraf</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mirwais</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>3001</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>154</runs>
				<overs>41.5</overs>
				<batsman>Hamid Hassan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Hamid</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6476</playerid>
				<nbr>10</nbr>
				<runs>162</runs>
				<overs>42.5</overs>
				<batsman>Aftab Alam</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Aftab Alam</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>2</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>3</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Bangladesh">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>323</playerid>
					<name>Mashrafe Mortaza</name>
					<bowler-name>Mortaza</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mortaza</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>2</maidens>
					<runsoff>20</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1736</playerid>
					<name>Rubel Hossain</name>
					<bowler-name>Rubel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rubel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>6</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>27</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8548</playerid>
					<name>Taskin Ahmed</name>
					<bowler-name>Taskin Ahmed</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Taskin Ahmed</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>23</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>544</playerid>
					<name>Shakib Al Hasan</name>
					<bowler-name>Shakib</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shakib</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8.5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>43</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1121</playerid>
					<name>Mahmudullah</name>
					<bowler-name>Mahmudullah</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mahmudullah</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>31</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8233</playerid>
					<name>Soumya Sarkar</name>
					<bowler-name>Soumya Sarkar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Soumya Sarkar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>13</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8231</playerid>
					<name>Sabbir Rahman</name>
					<bowler-name>S Rahman</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Rahman</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>4</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>612</playerid>
					<name>Tamim Iqbal</name>
					<bowler-name>Tamim</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Tamim</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8237</playerid>
					<name>Anamul Haque</name>
					<bowler-name>Anamul</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Anamul</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8219</playerid>
					<name>Mominul Haque</name>
					<bowler-name>Mominul</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mominul</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>394</playerid>
					<name>Mushfiqur Rahim</name>
					<bowler-name>Rahim</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rahim</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



