<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="12878" >
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>24th Match, Pool B</gameDesc>
		<series>WC 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Ireland</home>
		<away>South Africa</away>
		<teamsabbr>IRE vs RSA</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>IRE</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>RSA</awayabbr>
		<homeId>27</homeId>
		<awayId>11</awayId>
		<venue>Manuka Oval, Canberra</venue>
		<startdate>03 03 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>03 03 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>South Africa</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>South Africa won by 201 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>South Africa</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>201</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Steve Davis</Name>
			<Country>Aus</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Ranmore Martinesz</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Ian Gould</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Roshan Mahanama</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>03:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150303105007</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>IRE</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>RSA</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>210</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>10</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>45</batteamovers>
		<status>South Africa won by 201 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>9667</playerid>
			<name>Andy McBrine*</name>
			<batsman-name>Andy McBrine</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Andy McBrine</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>2</runs>
			<balls-faced>4</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
			<batsman>
				<name />
				<runs />
				<balls-faced />
				<fours />
				<sixes />
			</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>9203</playerid>
			<name>Kyle Abbott*</name>
			<bowler-name>Kyle Abbott</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Kyle Abbott</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>8</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>21</runs>
			<wickets>4</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>608</playerid>
			<name>Morne Morkel</name>
			<bowler-name>M Morkel</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>M Morkel</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>9</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>34</runs>
			<wickets>3</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>412</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>6329</playerid>
<name>George Dockrell</name>
<player-runs>25</player-runs>
<player-balls>57</player-balls>
<runs>210</runs>
<wicket-nbr>10</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>608</bowlerid>
<bowlername>M Morkel</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>9</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>3</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>12</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[. 1 4 6 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. . . . 1 W <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. 1 . . 2 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. 4 Wd . . 2 W ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_WC/IRE_RSA_MAR03/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[So, that's all we have for you from this game. Many thanks for your company. Tomorrow there's a double-header coming your way, first up it will be Pakistan vs UAE and the second game is between Australia and Afghanistan. So don't forget to follow the action right here. Until next time and on behalf of <b>Sriram, Raju, Krishna</b>, my co-commentators, <b>Akshay, Ramakrishnan</b> and <b>Pradeep</b>, this is <b>Sidhant Maheshwari</b> signing off. Take care folks! See you tomorrow.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@cricketaakash:</b> There should be a rule that doesn't allow SA to bat first...400 is the new 250 for them while batting first.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@BrokenCricket:</b> 400 is New 350 300 is New 250 Double Century is New 150 150 is New Century.. But England & Pakistan Still lives in Stone Age]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@mohanstatsman:</b> Last three of South Africa's 400+ totals have come in just 44 days!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@rgcricket:</b> Only the second time in ODIs a side has won two consecutive matches by a margin of 200 runs. Australia did so in 2007]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@cricketaakash:</b> Fastest to 5000 ODI runs, fastest to 20 ODI centuries...from someone who isn't even considered an ODI superstar. Hashim Amla take a bow!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Let's have a look at some of the <b>tweets</b> from this game: ]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>de Villiers:</b> 'It was a good game today. I am very happy with the performance. The nice thing about the batting display today was especially the fact that we did it our way. We are not following anyone else's strategy. We followed our game plans and guys played exceptionally well upfront. It set it up nicely for the rest in the middle-order. There's been a lot of hundreds over the last 12-18 months and it's something we are very proud of. When they keep scoring centuries, we feel that it definitely helps in setting it up for the latter stages of the innings. Very proud of the way Hash (Hashim Amla) and Faf (Faf du Plessis) played today, exceptional partnership and that set it up nicely for us. Incredible, still the rock (talking about Amla) and he will always be the rock for us. He does this effortlessly, plays with a lot of class and his game plans are so set that whatever you do, he has always got an answer, it seems like it. Hopefully, his form can continue for the rest of the tour. Very much pleased will all the bowlers, we had a nice meeting yesterday chatting about how we are going to go about the rest of the tournament. The guys were very motivated for today, wanting to do well, wanted to pick up wickets and stay positive right throughout the innings. I saw every single bit of that today. It is very much a match-to-match basis decision (talking about who to play at No. 7). I am very comfortable with whatever balance we create and as long as I am comfortable and the team follows, everything will be alright. You always want your top 6-7 in good form, especially, I would say 6, 7, 8 win you a lot of pressure games in tournaments like this and they seem to be in really good form as well. Everyone that's got an opportunity throughout this tournament seems to have done well. So, just a bit more of that and hopefully, we will do well in the next one as well. We will see how we go (asked if he will bowl again in the next game), I go on my instinct. I very much did (asked if he enjoyed when the umpire told him one bouncer for the over), that was actually my slower bouncer and I very much enjoyed it.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Porterfield:</b> 'It was a difficult evening. Obviously, they came out and played very well. We got one early breakthrough and we would have liked a couple more, but once the lads got set on that deck, it was hard to claw back. You want to be taking your chances, but that's part of cricket as well and you have to move on from that (talking about the dropped catch of Amla when he was on 10). All credit to him, he played very well, but, it is just one of those things. It was obviously a very good pitch and it was difficult to try and muster up those wickets. But the lads tried to squeeze as much as they could in the middle and put some kind of pressure on. We slowed them down a bit coming down at the last 10 with a couple of wickets, but we would have liked a few more earlier on. We were 4 down coming down after 10 and they bowled pretty well, if you're 4 down after 10 chasing any score, you're going to struggle, but all credit to the lower order where they stuck at it and fought it out there. Every game is a big game and obviously the game against Zimbabwe is a big game for us. So, we are looking to pick up 2 points.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hashim Amla:</b> 'Fortunately, we got off to a good start. Myself and Faf just got something going and then we started playing a few shots. We had wickets in hand, so we kind of had the luxury to do that. We just thought that let's have a go and see what happens and thankfully it came off. And we have got a good batting line-up to come, they weren't really needed today, but that's why it gave us time to do it at the top. The guys have been batting well, it was a good wicket and fortunately, we got some runs today. We don't look too far ahead, it is always nice to win a game of cricket. No matter who you're playing against, we are just grateful that we managed to go over the line today. Any hundred is a hundred (when asked about how much it matters to be the fastest to 20 ODI tons), I am just glad to get some runs. It doesn't matter how long it takes, but I am just glad to be getting some runs upfront, setting it up for the boys at the back end and those guys are quite dangerous there. They bowled exceptionally well, I was just glad that the one that flicked Quinny's (Quinton de Kock) glove, didn't hit me in my teeth. Amazingly, it got stuck under my armpit. The guys bowled exceptionally well. Having a team four down chasing 400, the writing was almost on the wall. But they maintained their good intensity throughout the game and fortunately, we walked away with a comfortable victory.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hashim Amla</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his <b>159</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier in the day, Amla and Faf du Plessis put on a record 2nd wicket partnership to help South Africa post their second successive 400-plus score on the board. Rossouw and Miller too made useful contributions towards the back end of the innings. But, it was Amla and Faf, who stole the show with marvellous hundreds. Overall, it was a thorough performance from the Proteas.]]></line><line><![CDATA[It was a clinical display by the South African bowlers. Steyn was back to his fiery best and Abbott has made the most of the opportunities he has been given. Morkel kept it tight at one end but Tahir was a bit inconsistent today. ABD tried a few different options in Faf, Rossouw and himself. He also managed to pick up a wicket in his very first over.]]></line><line><![CDATA[However, Balbirnie departed soon after reaching his maiden ODI fifty. Kevin O'Brien, who had played the waiting game until the batting powerplay, fell off the very first delivery of the powerplay. Dockrell and Sorensen prolonged the inevitable for a while. The pair added 31 runs for the 9th wicket before Morne came back and finished things off.]]></line><line><![CDATA[It is a comprehensive win for South Africa, their second on the trot. Ireland's run-chase never got going. Porterfield and Stirling played some delightful shots, but Steyn and Abbott sent them back in quick succession. Ed Joyce followed soon after. At one stage, they were reeling at 48/5 before Balbirnie and Kevin O'Brien added 81 runs for the sixth wicket. It was Ireland's highest partnership against South Africa for any wicket.]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Dockrell, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Morkel puts the final nail in the coffin. <b>South Africa win by 201 runs</b>. Coming back to the ball, it was fuller and on off, Dockrell backs away and wanted to go inside-out, he fails to lay bat onto it and the ball crashes into the top of off. The Proteas are delighted. The Irish and the South African players shake hands as they walk off the field. <b>Dockrell b M Morkel 25(57) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[M Morkel to Dockrell, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Dockrell, 2 runs, back of a length delivery outside off, Dockrell backs away and looks to force it through the off-side, gets a thick outside edge that flies towards third man, Steyn slides to his left and stops the ball before the rope, the batsmen take two]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Dockrell, no run, back of a length delivery on the pads, Dockrell clips it towads backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Dockrell, no run, back of a length delivery angling away outside off, Dockrell leaves it for the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Dockrell, <b>wide</b>, down the leg-side, called as a wide by the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Dockrell, <b>FOUR</b>, makes room for himself and forehands the pull off a short delivery to the cow corner fence, good shot from Dockrell]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Dockrell, no run, continues from round the wicket, digs it in short and at the batsman, Dockrell hangs back and drops it to the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Andy McBrine, no run, short and wide outside off, McBrine flashes the cut, but the ball goes past the outside edge once again]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Andy McBrine, 2 runs, full and slightly wide outside off, McBrine opens the face of the bat and drives it towards deep backward point, the batsmen take a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips and two gullies in place for Abbott]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Andy McBrine, no run, back of a length delivery on off and middle, McBrine hops a little and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Andy McBrine, no run, slightly wide outside off, McBrine goes after it trying to play the cut shot, but the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Dockrell, 1 run, back of a length delivery on the stumps, Dockrell jumps in the crease and runs it to the left of backward point, the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Dockrell, no run, angles this one on middle, Dockrell defends from the crease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andy McBrine, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kyle Abbott [7.0-0-18-4] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Sorensen, <b>out</b> Caught by de Kock!! Finally, the short ball has worked after so many tries. It was short and at the batsman, who was looking to fend it away. He was not in control and the ball lobs up off the handle of the bat. de Kock takes a very simple catch and Morkel is delighted. South Africa are just a wicket away from another thumping win. <b>Sorensen c de Kock b M Morkel 22(19) [4s-3 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[M Morkel to Sorensen, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Dockrell, 1 run, fuller and on the stumps, Dockrell works it towards deep mid-wicket off the inside half of the bat, the crowd applauds as <b>200 comes up for Ireland</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Dockrell, no run, banged in short and at the batsman, who backs away and looks to cut it late, can't connect though]]></line><line><![CDATA[Morkel comes round the wicket now. A FSL is in place now]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Dockrell, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Dockrell was looking to force it through the off-side, but ends up punching it back to the bowler off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Dockrell, no run, just short of a good length and on the stumps, Dockrell pushes it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Dockrell, no run, back of a length delivery on the stumps, Dockrell defends from the crease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Dockrell, 1 run, comes down the track and looks to drive, mistimes it completely but the batsmen take a single as the ball dribbles away to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Sorensen, 1 run, touch quicker and on middle and leg, Sorensen works it towards mid-wicket, where a misfield from Steyn allows the batsmen to cross over]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Sorensen, <b>SIX</b>, this time he goes big, it was tossed up around off, Sorensen waits for it and launches it over the long-on fence for his first maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Sorensen, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>dropped!</b> It was a very tough chance though, it was floated up well outside off, Sorensen drills it to the right of the bowler, who gets a hand on it, but the ball rockets away to the fence in no time, good power on that one]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Dockrell, 1 run, gives the charge this time and lofts it towards sweeper cover, he didn't time it that well, the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Dockrell, no run, flatter and outside off, Dockrell cuts it straight to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Sorensen, no run, low full toss from Morkel, he was probably trying to bowl the yorker there, Sorensen pushes it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Sorensen, no run, another short one on middle and leg, Sorensen hops and looks to fend it away, gets an inside edge onto the body]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Sorensen, no run, banged in short and on the stumps, Sorensen jumps and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Dockrell, 1 run, <b>run-out chance missed!</b> It was on a good length and around off, Dockrell drops it in front of cover and sets off, de Villiers picks the ball up and fires in the throw at the striker's end, luckily for the batsmen, there was no direct-hit, otherwise he would have been a goner]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Dockrell, <b>wide</b>, angling down leg, Dockrell fails to connect with the clip and this time umpire Martinesz got it right, calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Dockrell, no run, short of length delivery on the stumps, Dockrell hops a little and defends it back on the track]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Dockrell, no run, back of a length delivery on middle and leg, Dockrell defends off the back foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Morne Morkel [6.0-0-24-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The batting powerplay yielded <b>18/1</b> for Ireland]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Sorensen, no run, touch quicker and on off, Sorensen pushes it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Sorensen, <b>FOUR</b>, floated up around off, Sorensen leans forward and drives it towards cover, who dives to his right and takes the pace off the ball, however the ball still had enough to run away to the fence even though Phangiso from cover gave chase]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Sorensen, <b>FOUR</b>, good shot from Sorensen, it was floated up on middle, Sorensen clears his front leg and heaves it wide of mid-on, the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Sorensen, no run, floated up around off, Sorensen drives it towards the bowler, who dives to his left, gets a hand on it and parries it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Sorensen, no run, another quicker one on leg, Sorensen fails to clip it into the on-side, the ball goes behind square on the off-side off the pad, it was going down leg though]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Sorensen, no run, quicker and on the stumps, Sorensen works it towards mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Imran Tahir [8.0-1-29-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Dockrell, no run, short delivery outside off, Dockrell has nothing to do with it]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Sorensen, 1 run, short and outside off, Sorensen dabs it down to third man in an awkward manner]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Sorensen, no run, that must have hurt! It was banged in short and at the batsman, Sorensen was looking to get out of the way but couldn't do so in time, the ball hits him bang on the left wrist and flies behind square on the on-side, it must have left a mark there]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Dockrell, 1 run, fullish delivery around off, Dockrell pushes it in front of mid-off, Dockrell takes off, de Villiers from mid-off runs forward, picks it up and fires in the throw at the striker's end, the batsmen would have made it though]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Dockrell, 2 runs, <b>dropped!</b> It was short and slightly wide outside off, Dockrell goes chasing after it and cuts it uppishly towards backward point, where Miller was diving to his right, he gets his hands on it, but can't take it. It should have been taken considering the kind of standards Miller and the rest of the South African fielders set for themselves]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Dockrell, no run, angling in on off, Dockrell gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Sorensen, 2 runs, bit of reverse swing for Abbott there as the ball shapes in from around off, Sorensen did well to get his bat down in time, he gets an inside edge that dribbles away behind square and before any fielder could get around, the batsmen take two]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Sorensen, no run, on a good length and outside off, Dockrell pokes at it away from his body, the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Dockrell, 1 run, low full toss from Abbott, was probably trying the yorker there, Dockrell pushes it wide of mid-off and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Dockrell, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Dockrell punches it towards point off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Dockrell, no run, short delivery and well outside off, Dockrell leaves it alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Dockrell, no run, back of a length delivery on top of middle, Dockrell defends off the back foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Sorensen, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Sorensen opens the face of the bat and mistimes the punch in front of backward point, he was looking for the single there but the fielder was quick to run forward, pick the ball and has a shy at the striker's end, the batsman made it in time though]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Dockrell, 1 run, touch fuller and around off this time, Dockrell pushes at it, the ball rolls away down to third man off the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Dockrell, no run, another short one on top of off and middle, Dockrell hops and drops it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Dockrell, no run, banged in short and well outside off, Dockrell has nothing to do with it]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Dockrell, no run, just short of a good length and on off and middle, Dockrell defends it towards cover-point off the outside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Dockrell, no run, full outside off, Dockrell looks to drive away from his body, the ball goes past the outside edge and through to the keeper]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Sorensen, no run, good length delivery just outside off, Sorensen pushes it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Dockrell, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off, Dockrell jumps up in the crease and dabs it down to third man after opening the face of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Dockrell, no run, short delivery this time, Dockrell hops in the crease and drops his wrists on it]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Dockrell, no run, short of length delivery angling in on middle and leg, Dockrell defends it with his bat close to the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Dockrell, no run, back of a length delivery on the stumps, Dockrell punches it to cover off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Max Sorensen, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now. It is only a matter of time before South Africa wrap it up. Things could have been worse for the Irish had O'Brien and Balbirnie not combined for a 81-run partnership. However, let's see how they go about now. Abbott has taken 4 wickets in the innings and he will look to finish with a 5-wicket haul.]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to K O'Brien, <b>out</b> Caught by Rossouw!! O'Brien throws it away, it was banged in short and at the batsman, O'Brien goes for the pull, but can't get the desired distance as the bat turns in his hand. It goes towards deep mid-wicket and the fielder there takes an easy catch. Ireland are 8 down now. <b>K O'Brien c Rossouw b Kyle Abbott 48(65) [4s-3 6s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Kyle Abbott to K O'Brien, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to K O'Brien, <b>wide</b>, splays this one down leg first up, the umpire exercises his arms]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kyle Abbott [5.0-0-13-3] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>batting powerplay</b>. Abbott comes back into the attack.]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Dockrell, no run, just short of a good length and on off, Dockrell stays inside the crease and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Dockrell, no run, how was that not a wide? The crowd starts booing the umpire. It was down the leg-side, Dockrell can't nurdle it fine and the keeper collects, the umpire just didn't think that it was a wide and that was strange]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Dockrell, no run, touch fuller and just outside off, Dockrell was feeling for it with laden feet, but the ball goes past his blade, it wasn't that far away from the off stump as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Dockrell, no run, banged in short and outside off, Dockrell is happy to leave it for the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to K O'Brien, 1 run, on a good length and outside off, O'Brien was pushing at it, gets an outside edge that rolls away down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to K O'Brien, 2 runs, fullish delivery around off, O'Brien was looking to work it through the leg-side, but closes the bat face a little too early, he gets a leading edge that goes to the left of cover, the batsmen take two before the fielder chases it down]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dale Steyn [5.0-0-31-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Dockrell, no run, touch quicker again and around off, Dockrell drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Dockrell, no run, quicker and on the stumps, Dockrell just about manages to bring his bat down in time to keep it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Dockrell, no run, pushed through outside off, Dockrell pushes at it, gets an outside edge that goes behind square on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Dockrell, <b>SIX</b>, tossed up outside off, Dockrell dances down the track and lofts it inside-out over wide long-off, the ball goes all the way, good shot from Dockrell that]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Dockrell, no run, floated up outside off, Dockrell leans forward and drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Dockrell, no run, flatter and around off, Dockrell punches it towards cover, who dives to his left and stops the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;de Villiers to Dockrell, 1 run, homing in around off and middle, Dockrell looks to push at it, the ball goes off the inside half of the bat to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;de Villiers to Dockrell, no run, bumper from de Villiers, the batsman is surprised, the umpire is surprised, Dockrell ducks and the umpire calls it one bouncer for the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;de Villiers to Dockrell, no run, length delivery around off, Dockrell shuffles across just a touch and pushes it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;de Villiers to Dockrell, no run, just short of a good length and on top of off, Dockrell wrists it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;de Villiers to K O'Brien, 1 run, short of length delivery on middle and leg, O'Brien short-arm pulls it to deep square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;de Villiers to K O'Brien, no run, on a good length and on middle, O'Brien pushes it down to mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Dockrell, no run, flighted delivery around off, Dockrell wrists it into the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Dockrell, no run, slower through the air this time, Dockrell works it towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Dockrell, no run, quicker and straighter this time, Dockrell defends from the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Dockrell, no run, googly outside off, Dockrell hangs back and guides it to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Dockrell, no run, tossed up around off, Dockrell drives it to cover off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Dockrell, no run, flatter on the stumps, Dockrell pushes it to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;de Villiers to K O'Brien, no run, angling down leg, O'Brien fails to connect with the clip and overbalances a bit, de Kock took the bails off, but his back foot was in, not sure why the umpire didn't call it a wide though]]></line><line><![CDATA[The third umpire has been called to check for a stumping chance. O'Brien is the man in question. He looks fine though. The decision will be 'Not Out']]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;de Villiers to K O'Brien, no run, was there an edge there? de Villiers doesn't think so. It was on a length and outside off, O'Brien looks to drive, but the ball goes past his outside edge, it was close though as de Kock appealed]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;de Villiers to K O'Brien, <b>FOUR</b>, that was a poor delivery from de Villiers, a short one that sits up nicely for O'Brien to rock back and pull it to the deep backward square leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;de Villiers to Dockrell, 1 run, back of a length delivery outside off, Dockrell stays back, opens the face of the bat and punches it towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>George Dockrell, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;de Villiers to J Mooney, <b>out</b> Bowled!! de Villiers comes on and takes a wicket second ball. He is pumped up and punches the air in delight. It was short of length delivery angling away outside off, Mooney went chasing after it and looks to cut, but gets an inside edge that crashes into the off stump. Ireland are 7 down now. <b>J Mooney b de Villiers 8(15)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[de Villiers to J Mooney, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;de Villiers to J Mooney, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Mooney punches it towards mid-wicket, who moves to his right and stops the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>AB de Villiers, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Captain de Villiers will chance his arm with the ball now]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to K O'Brien, no run, a googly to end the over, O'Brien wrists it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to K O'Brien, no run, leg-break outside off and turning away, O'Brien made room and was looking to go inside-out, doesn't make a connection and was nowhere near it as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to J Mooney, 1 run, on middle and leg, Mooney pushes it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to K O'Brien, 1 run, quicker delivery just outside off, O'Brien leans forward and eases it down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to J Mooney, 1 run, gives the charge and works it towards deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to K O'Brien, 1 run, 'catch' was the shout as O'Brien comes down the track and lofts inside-out, the ball was in the air but there was no fielder at extra cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to J Mooney, no run, drifting onto the pads once again, Mooney goes deep in the crease and looks to tuck it away into the leg-side, but fails to lay bat on that, the ball hits him on the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to J Mooney, 2 runs, comes down the track and works this flighted delivery on leg behind square for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to J Mooney, no run, touch flatter and just outside off, Mooney makes room and looks to cut, it was quicker as well, Mooney can't connect and it wasn't too far away from the off stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to K O'Brien, 1 run, tossed up around off, O'Brien drives it to long-off and gets off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to K O'Brien, 2 runs, floated up on off, O'Brien lofts it right over the bowler's head and the batsmen take two before long-off cuts it off]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to K O'Brien, <b>FOUR</b>, loopy delivery from du Plessis, O'Brien comes down the track and converts it into a full toss, he lofts it over the fielder at cover and the ball runs away to the fence, there was no one in the deep on the cover boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to J Mooney, no run, goes for another reverse sweep to this flighted delivery around leg, he makes a mess of it as he gets a bottom edge onto the pad, the ball didn't even cross the pitch]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to J Mooney, 2 runs, kneels down this time and scoops it towards the fine leg region, the batsmen take two before the ball is hunted down]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to J Mooney, no run, slower leg-break turning in from middle and leg, Mooney fails to clip it into the on-side and wears it on his pad, snaking down leg for sure]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to J Mooney, no run, in the blockhole this time, Mooney squeezes it out into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to J Mooney, no run, quicker and around off, Mooney defends from the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to J Mooney, no run, floated up outside off, Mooney goes for the reverse sweep, but fails to connect and wears it on the pad, the impact was well outside off though]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Imran Tahir [4.0-0-17-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to K O'Brien, no run, flatter and quicker, O'Brien was looking to cut it, but was a little late on that and was cramped for room, he ends up chopping it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to J Mooney, 1 run, Mooney hangs back and looks to play the scoop, de Kock was moving to his right to try and take the catch if possible, but Mooney doesn't get it right and the ball goes right over him, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away behind]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to K O'Brien, 1 run, pushed through on middle and leg, O'Brien pushes at it, the ball rolls away behind square on the on-side off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to K O'Brien, 2 runs, floated up this time, O'Brien gives the charge and lofts it over the bowler and to the right of long-off, the batsmen take a couple before the fielder from long-off gets across]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to K O'Brien, no run, short and just outside off, O'Brien backs away a touch and cuts, he picks out cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to J Mooney, 1 run, flatter outside off, Mooney works it past mid-wicket for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to K O'Brien, no run, angling in from around off, O'Brien fails to clip it into the on-side and wears it on the pad, there was an appeal from the South African players, but the impact was too high]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to K O'Brien, <b>wide</b>, another short one outside off but this time it is too high, O'Brien ducks and the umpire calls it a a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>John Mooney, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, <b>out</b> Caught by Rossouw!! Balbirnie falls after a fighting fifty. The umpires check for Morkel's front foot, but it is fine. It was banged in short, Balbirnie drags the pull from outside off and the fielder at deep square leg takes a rather simple catch. End of a good stand between him and O'Brien. <b>Balbirnie c Rossouw b M Morkel 58(71) [4s-7]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[M Morkel to Balbirnie, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, <b>FOUR</b>, just short of good length and outside off, Balbirnie hangs back and punches it towards deep extra cover, Amla from sweeper cover runs to his right, slides and tries to pull the ball back in, but the ball trickles away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to K O'Brien, 1 run, on middle stump line, O'Brien shuffles across just a touch and flicks it in the air, the ball goes on the bounce to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to K O'Brien, no run, on a good length and angling in on off and middle, O'Brien wrists it down to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to K O'Brien, no run, banged in short and at the batsman, O'Brien ducks and lets it pass]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to Balbirnie, no run, knocks it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to K O'Brien, 1 run, flatter and on off, O'Brien backs away and punches it to deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to K O'Brien, <b>SIX</b>, flighted on off, O'Brien clears his front leg and heaves it towards cow corner, ABD runs to his right from long-on, dives like a Superman but the ball is too far from him. The ball has enough to clear the fence. Slight delay in play as the umpire checks whether it was a four or a six. Replays confirm that it was a six]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to Balbirnie, 1 run, quicker and on the stumps, Balbirnie swipes it behind square leg, had he missed that, it would have been dead in front of middle]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to K O'Brien, 1 run, nice loopy delivery, O'Brien drives off the inside half to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to K O'Brien, no run, flighted on off, O'Brien mishits the drive back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, no run, good length ball on the stumps, Balbirnie knocks it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, <b>FOUR</b>, superb shot! Nice way to bring up a <b>maiden</b> ODI fifty. The length is short and just outside off, Balbirnie stands tall and punches it past a diving point fielder, Amla gives chase in vain]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, <b>FOUR</b>, streaky! Morne follows the batsman who was giving himself some room, steers it in the air, it was in the air, but just wide of Faf, who is standing at a wide slip position. No chance for the third man fielder to cut that off]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, no run, shortens the length around off, Balbirnie punches it gently towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, no run, lifter on off, Balbirnie sways away from the line of the delivery, the Giraffe went down in his followthrough]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, no run, back of a length on the fourth stump, Balbirnie guides it to backward point with an open bat face]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Morne Morkel [4.0-0-10-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to K O'Brien, no run, fraction short and just outside off, O'Brien cuts and picks out the point fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to Balbirnie, 1 run, pushed through on the stumps, Balbirnie punches it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to K O'Brien, leg byes, 1 run, slider on leg-stump, O'Brien can't lay bat on the glance, the ball brushes the pad and rolls towards short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to Balbirnie, 1 run, flatter and just outside off, Balbirnie punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to Balbirnie, no run, quicker and close to off, Balbirnie dabs it in front of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to Balbirnie, no run, nurdled to backward square, finds the fielder there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;du Plessis to Balbirnie, <b>5 wides</b>, poor first up delivery from Faf, darted down the leg-side, Balbirnie misses the sweep, QdK doesn't gather the ball as he was blinded by the batsman]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Faf du Plessis, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rossouw to Balbirnie, 3 runs, throws this up outside off, goes straight on, Balbirnie drives and gets an outside edge through the vacant slip region, Morne runs behind the ball and hauls it in just before the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rossouw to K O'Brien, 1 run, gives this bit more air, O'Brien milks it square of the wicket on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rossouw to Balbirnie, 1 run, short and on the stumps, Balbirnie pulls it to deep mid-wicket, picks out the fielder there]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rossouw to K O'Brien, 1 run, leans forward and works it with the turn behind square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rossouw to Balbirnie, 1 run, drags the length back, Balbirnie pulls it to long leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rossouw to K O'Brien, 1 run, steps out of the crease and chips it to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to K O'Brien, 1 run, floated up close to off, O'Brien backs away and drives it inside out to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Balbirnie, 1 run, wrong 'un on middle and leg, Balbirnie nurdles it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to K O'Brien, leg byes, 1 run, slider on leg-stump, O'Brien misses the nudge and the ball dribbles behind square on the leg-side after clipping the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Balbirnie, 1 run, straight roller on off, Balbirnie defends and the ball squirts off the inside edge to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Balbirnie, no run, googly close to off, Balbirnie looks to force it through the off-side, is beaten by the extra bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Balbirnie, no run, throws this up just outside off, Balbirnie watches it go into QdK's gloves]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rossouw to K O'Brien, no run, closes his bat face a little early and gets a soft leading edge back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rossouw to K O'Brien, 2 runs, slower and drops it short, O'Brien makes room and punches it in the air wide of extra cover, Phangiso runs to his left from long-off and keeps it down to a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rossouw to Balbirnie, 1 run, punched down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rossouw to K O'Brien, 1 run, helps it on the way to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rossouw to K O'Brien, no run, stifled appeal for lbw, but umpire Davis remains unmoved. Touch short, O'Brien goes for the pull, misses and is rapped on the pads. The ball was turning down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rossouw to Balbirnie, 1 run, flighted on off, Balbirnie eases it off the back foot between the bowler and short mid-wicket, Rossouw runs across, dives but can't stop the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rilee Rossouw, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to K O'Brien, no run, googly to end the over, O'Brien presses forward and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Balbirnie, 1 run, floated up on off, Balbirnie drives it to long-off and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Balbirnie, no run, slows this up and gets a bit of extra bounce, Balbirnie kneels down and misses the sweep, he was done in by the bounce there]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Balbirnie, no run, opens the bat face and guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Balbirnie, no run, slider on off, Balbirnie moves to the leg-side and punches it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Balbirnie, no run, the wrong 'un around off, Balbirnie leans forward and blocks]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Behardien to K O'Brien, <b>FOUR</b>, fraction short and outside off, O'Brien cuts and gets a thick outside edge to third man, Morne had to run a long way, he gets there, puts in the slide but can't prevent the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Behardien to Balbirnie, 1 run, back of a length on middle, Balbirnie punches it to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Behardien to K O'Brien, 1 run, pitched up on and off, O'Brien drives it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Behardien to K O'Brien, no run, fuller and on off, O'Brien presents a straight bat and knocks it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Behardien to Balbirnie, 1 run, good length ball outside off, driven away to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Behardien to Balbirnie, 2 runs, too straight, Balbirnie nurdles it to deep backward square leg for a brace]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to K O'Brien, no run, presses forward and blocks it to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to K O'Brien, no run, plays it around his pads, works it to backward square, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to K O'Brien, 2 runs, Tahir was excited as the ball ballooned off the top-edge, it just about evaded Phangiso at backward square, he runs back and keeps it down to a couple. O'Brien did not connect well with the sweep]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to K O'Brien, no run, googly on off, O'Brien pushes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Balbirnie, 1 run, tossed up on off, Balbirnie drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Balbirnie, <b>FOUR</b>, poor delivery from Tahir, nice juicy full toss on off and middle, Balbirnie says thank you very much and puts it away. Bends his front knee and heaves it behing square for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for some <b>drinks</b>! It has been all South Africa so far. Steyn bowled a fiery first spell, he managed to scalp two wickets. Abbott continued to impress as he picked up three. Morne has been economical at one end. These two have to get Ireland to a respectable score, else it will be an embarrassing defeat.]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Behardien to Balbirnie, 1 run, fullish and on off, Balbirnie knocks it towards mid-off and scampers across for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Behardien to Balbirnie, no run, back of a length close to off, Balbirnie punches it gently to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Behardien to K O'Brien, 1 run, drags the length back, O'Brien steers it wide of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Behardien to Balbirnie, 1 run, eased down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Behardien to Balbirnie, no run, QdK shouts "catch", but Behardien was not able to. It will go down as a <b>dropped chance</b>. Fuller and just outside off, Balbirnie push-drives it in the air to the left of the bowler, Behardien gets a finger on it, but can't hold on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Behardien to K O'Brien, 1 run, on a length just outside off, O'Brien drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Farhaan Behardien, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Balbirnie, no run, flighted just outside off, Balbirnie goes on his knee and misses the sweep this time. It was cleverly bowled by Tahir as he threw it up wide of off]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Balbirnie, <b>FOUR</b>, bit too full from Tahir, kneels down and sweeps it behind square leg. That came right off the meat as the ball raced away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to K O'Brien, leg byes, 1 run, the wrong 'un, turning in, O'Brien misses the nudge and the ball brushes the pad and rolls to short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to K O'Brien, no run, slower and on off, O'Brien knocks it back down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Balbirnie, 1 run, googly just outside off, Balbirnie eases the drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to K O'Brien, 1 run, starts with a full toss, O'Brien drives it down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Imran Tahir, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, no run, shortens the length on off, Balbirnie defends solidly off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, no run, on a length just outside off, Balbirnie stands tall and punches it on-the-up, it was in the air and drops it in front of ABD, who was standing at a widish mid-off position. He did well to get his body behind and field the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, no run, shortish and just outside off, Balbirnie chops it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, no run, targets the stumps, Balbirnie plays around his pads, knocks it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to K O'Brien, 1 run, low full toss on the stumps, it was the attempted yorker, O'Brien clips it to the right of mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to K O'Brien, no run, banged in halfway down the wicket, O'Brien was shaping to play the pull, but decides against it as it was well wide of off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to K O'Brien, 1 run, <b>direct hit</b> and O'Brien would have been on his way <b>back to the hut</b>. Short of a length around off, O'Brien taps it to the right of point and sets off, Miller gets across and has a shy at the non-striker's end, but he has failed to hit the target]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to K O'Brien, no run, another bumper, O'Brien sits down and the ball hits his left shoulder and goes to the left of the keeper, QdK dives full length and gathers the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to K O'Brien, no run, that kept a bit low, O'Brien goes for the back foot punch, the ball sneaks through under his bat. O'Brien has a look at the pitch]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to K O'Brien, no run, back of a length on off, defended down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to K O'Brien, no run, bouncer on off, O'Brien ducks and allows the ball to sail over him]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Balbirnie, 1 run, length ball outside off, Balbirnie slashes and gets it off the outer half to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dale Steyn [4.0-0-29-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to K O'Brien, no run, short of length on off, bunted in front of backward point, the call is "no" for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to K O'Brien, no run, short delivery outside off, jags away after passing the batsman, QdK dives to his right and collects the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to K O'Brien, no run, keeps it back of a length, O'Brien stays in the crease and knocks it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips and a gully in place for O'Brien..]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, 1 run, short on middle and leg, Balbirnie gets inside the line and helps it down to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, 2 runs, back of a length just outside off, Balbirnie glides it to the right of third man and scampers back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[There is a fielder at deep square leg and a fielder at short square leg. Can expect some short stuff from Morne.]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, no run, shortish and on off, Balbirnie fends it with loose hands to backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to K O'Brien, no run, pitched up just outside off, O'Brien drives and finds mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to K O'Brien, no run, full on off and middle, O'Brien turns it gently towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to K O'Brien, no run, O'Brien was put off as Balbirnie dropped his bat at the non-striker's end just when Abbott delivered the ball. It was back of a length around off, O'Brien blocks it to the off-side. He has a smile at the end of it all]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to K O'Brien, no run, back of a length close to off, O'Brien gets behind the line and defends to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kevin O'Brien, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to G Wilson, <b>out</b> Lbw!! That looked plumb. Wilson had a chat with his partner, Balbirnie told him that it looked out. He doesn't review and makes the long walk back to the pavilion. Nip-backer from a length, Wilson stays rooted to the crease and is struck on the knee-roll. The impact was on middle stump and would have crashed into the stumps. Ireland have lost half their side and have still not reached 50. <b>G Wilson lbw b Kyle Abbott 0(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Kyle Abbott to G Wilson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Wilson is given <b>OUT</b> lbw! He is not reviewing it.]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Balbirnie, 1 run, shortens the length around off, Balbirnie steers it down to third man with an angled bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, 1 run, strays onto Balbirnie's pads, whipped away to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, no run, good comeback delivery from the Giraffe, back of a length and around off, gets it to hold its line, Balbirnie pokes at it and is beaten all ends up]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, <b>FOUR</b>, short delivery from Morne, sat up nicely for Balbirnie, he swivels on the back foot and pulls it in front of square, ball bounces couple of times before reaching the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, no run, good length ball on middle, Balbirnie shuffles across and knocks it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, no run, short of length on off, Balbirnie goes back and across, blocks it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, no run, plenty of width on this, Balbirnie cuts and misses, it is too far for him to reach]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to G Wilson, no run, short of length around off, Wilson gets right behind the line and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to G Wilson, no run, too straight, on middle and leg, Wilson fails to nail the flick, the ball hits him high on the pad and drops down on the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Gary Wilson, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to N O'Brien, <b>out</b> Caught by Amla!! Amla got lucky there. O'Brien the latest to bite the dust. It was shortish and outside off, O'Brien flashes a cut and edges it to the left of the keeper, QdK goes for it with one hand, the ball hits the gloves and deflects straight into Amla's midriff, he managed to clasp his hands and cling onto it. QdK was a relieved man when he saw Amla hanging onto the ball. <b>N O'Brien c Amla b Kyle Abbott 14(9) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Kyle Abbott to N O'Brien, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to N O'Brien, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! Digs it in midway down the wicket, O'Brien swivels and pulls it over square leg, his front leg was in the air while playing that. It was a superb shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Balbirnie, 1 run, again, the line is bit too straight, nurdled away behind square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Balbirnie, no run, length ball on the stumps, Balbirnie turns it towards square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kyle Abbott [3.0-0-7-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, 1 run, in the air and safe! Short delivery right at the batsman, Balbirnie was in no position to play the pull, plays it rather awkwardly, the ball balloons over square leg, Behardien back pedals, puts his right hand up but can't reach it. That would have been a stunner had he hung onto it]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, no run, again, Balbirnie goes chasing at a wide one outside off, is nowhere close to the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, no run, another mishit from the bat off Balbirnie, it was back of a length just outside off, Balbirnie toe-ends the pull towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, no run, keeps it on his favorite length, that is short, Balbirnie pokes and is lucky not to have nicked it]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, no run, not all that short, Balbirnie pulls and mistimes it completely, picks out square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Balbirnie, no run, back of a length on off, Balbirnie defends with soft hands to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Morne Morkel, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to N O'Brien, no run, bouncer on middle and off, O'Brien sways away from the line of the delivery. He seems to be up for the challenge]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to N O'Brien, 2 runs, typical fast bowlers' response after being hit for a boundary. Well directed short delivery, O'Brien goes for the pull, the top-edge flies to fine leg, Tahir was very square and had no chance of getting to that.]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to N O'Brien, <b>FOUR</b>, top shot! 142kph short of length delivery around off, O'Brien stays leg-side of the ball and punches it through the vacant cover region. The pace of Steyn took it to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to N O'Brien, 2 runs, banged in halfway down the wicket, O'Brien pulls it over square leg with one leg in the air, no timing and the ball slows down after clearing the infield]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Balbirnie, 1 run, fullish and outside off, Balbirnie goes hard on the drive, the outside edge flies down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to N O'Brien, 1 run, drifts onto O'Brien's pads, flicked away to fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Balbirnie, no run, peach! A beauty to end the over. Angled in at back of a length, straightens a touch, Balbirnie hangs back and plays for the angle, is beaten comprehensively]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Balbirnie, no run, teasing delivery from Abbott, full and well wide of off, Balbirnie goes chasing after it, the ball beats the outside edge. Not the best of shots at this stage of the innings]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Balbirnie, no run, back of a length on the fourth stump, Balbirnie steers it to the left of backward point, diving stop by Miller]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Balbirnie, no run, attacks the stumps, Balbirnie stays beside the line and bunts it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to N O'Brien, 1 run, strays onto the pads, O'Brien stays in the crease and nurdles it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to N O'Brien, no run, short of length around off, O'Brien opens the bat face and guides it towards backward point, the fielder dives to his right and fields the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Balbirnie, no run, lifter on the stumps, Balbirnie sinks under it and lets it pass. End of a fiery over from Steyn!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Balbirnie, <b>FOUR</b>, the attempted yorker goes wrong, ends up as a full toss on leg-stump, Balbirnie stays in the crease and puts it away, flicked square of the wicket and the ball has enough to reach the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Balbirnie, no run, short of length around off, Balbirnie hangs his bat away from the body, the ball whizzes past the outside edge. Good carry through to QdK]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Andrew Balbirnie, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Ed Joyce, <b>out</b> Caught by Amla!! Ireland are falling apart in the run-chase. They have lost their third wicket in a space of 11 balls. Fullish and angled across off, Joyce drives with laden feet, the outside edge is induced and the ball flies to first slip, Amla took it calmly. This was bowled at 146kph. He softened him up with the short delivery off the previous ball. <b>Ed Joyce c Amla b Steyn 0(4)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Steyn to Ed Joyce, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Ed Joyce, no run, bouncer just outside off, Joyce brings his head down and allows the ball to climb over him]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Ed Joyce, no run, back of a length around off, Joyce dabs it towards backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Niall O'Brien, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Porterfield, <b>out</b> Caught by du Plessis!! That is a superb catch. It was similar to the one that Joyce put down in the South African innings off Amla, but Faf has held onto this. Full and on the pads, Porterfield leans forward and flicks, doesn't manage to keep it down, Faf standing at short mid-wicket, reacts quickly and snaffles a good low catch to his left. Ireland in trouble now. <b>Porterfield c du Plessis b Kyle Abbott 12(17) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Kyle Abbott to Porterfield, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Porterfield, no run, Rossouw saved some runs there, good length ball outside off, Porterfield comes forward and drives it towards cover, Rossouw dives to his left and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Porterfield, no run, shortens the length around off, Porterfield checks his back foot defence, knocks it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Porterfield, <b>FOUR</b>, "catch" shouted Abbott, but it was well wide of Steyn. Short and on leg-stump, Porterfield swivels and pulls, the ball was in the air and to the right of short fine, Steyn dived full length but couldn't get there]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Porterfield, no run, back of a length and outside off, Porterfield watches it sail past him]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Porterfield, no run, on a length just outside off, Porterfield goes for the on-the-up drive, the ball holds its line and beats the inside edge of the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Ed Joyce, no run, welcomes the new batsman with a bumper, it was on the stumps as well, Joyce ducks and evades it comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ed Joyce, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Stirling, <b>out</b> Caught by de Kock!! It was a peach of a delivery. Actually, Stirling had started to walk, but stood his ground as umpire Martinesz didn't raise his finger. South Africa reviewed it immediately and got it in their favor. It was short of length and shaping away just outside off, Stirling has a feel for it away from the body, the outside edge carries at a good height to QdK. The Snicko showed a big spike and the decision was overruled. <b>Stirling c de Kock b Steyn 9(6) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Steyn to Stirling, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[South Africa go up for a caught behind appeal and are reviewing it. Steyn is fine with his front foot, it is a legal delivery. Clear outside edge. But, umpire Martinesz didn't pick it up for the second time in the game. There is a massive spike on the Snicko. This will be overturned. Stirling is <b>OUT!</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Porterfield, 1 run, the length is on the shorter side, Porterfield stays in the crease and dabs it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Stirling, 1 run, goes hard at this back of a length delivery, the thickish outside edge runs down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Stirling, <b>FOUR</b>, this is even better, Stirling used his power this time. Plenty of room on this short of length delivery, Stirling frees his arms and crashes it between cover and point, the ball reached the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Stirling, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! Stirling too opens his account with a superb boundary. Back of a length outside off, Stirling stands tall and punches it through cover-point. The timing was exquisite on that]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Porterfield, no run, back of a length angled across the left-hander, Porterfield pulls and misses, the ball goes under his bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[Coming back to the LBW appeal, Porterfield got a bit of wood and that is what saved him. Good spot from umpire Davis. And even better by South Africa for not reviewing it.]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Porterfield, no run, short of length around off, Porterfield punches it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Porterfield, no run, full and on the pads, Porterfield clips and picks out square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Porterfield, no run, huge shout for lbw, but umpire Davis shakes his head and says not-out. It looked very close. Pitched on middle and leg, Porterfield misses the flick and is struck in front of leg-stump. The Hawk-Eye shows that the ball was hitting leg-stump, South Africa don't review and Porterfield survives]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Porterfield, no run, better from Abbott, in and around the off-stump, Porterfield covers his sticks and shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kyle Abbott to Porterfield, 2 runs, starts with a bit of width outside off, Porterfield crunches it to cover, Rossouw fumbles and the batsmen come back for two before the ball is hunted down]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kyle Abbott, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Stirling, no run, back of a length close to off, Stirling gets right behind the line and blocks solidly to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Stirling, no run, good length ball on off, Stirling presses forward and defends it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place..]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Porterfield, 1 run, holds the line back slightly, Porterfield stays back and gets a thickish edge towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Porterfield, <b>FOUR</b>, gorgeous shot! Nice way to get off the mark. Pitched up just outside off, Porterfield gets a good stride forward and caresses the drive, places it between extra cover and mid-off. The sweet timing takes it to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Porterfield, no run, fullish and on off, Porterfield push-drives it to mid-off, no real timing on that]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Porterfield, no run, good length ball close to the off-stump, Porterfield watches it carfeully and lets it go through to the keeper]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Porterfield and Stirling are at the crease. Porterfield is on strike. Steyn will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. Ireland have chased down targets of over 280 in their previous two matches. But, this is 400-plus and a more accomplished bowling attack. Can they get anywhere close to this target? We'll find out soon as Steyn steams in.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Faf</b>: "We did the basics really well again today and that's what we want to do as a top order. We want to lay the foundation for the guys at the end to have some fun. So, once again, really proud of the boys. It was nice (to bat), obviously hard work up front to get us into position and then when you do get into position, you try and have some fun as well. So nice to do it with Hash (Amla) today. It (pitch) looked a little bit better today and especially, we know as a batting unit we've got some really big power-hitters. Obviously Ireland, from a bowling point of view at the death, not very experienced. So we knew if we get into position to dominate, we could hurt them. Luckily today, it came off. It's great to bat with Hash (Amla), he's such an experienced guy, the best thing about him is the coversion rate. When he gets to 50, so many times he gets to 100. So for guys like myself, it's good to learn from that and then try and be half as good as that."]]></line><line><![CDATA[For Ireland, Mooney started the proceedings on a good note. In his first 5 overs, he picked up a wicket and just gave away 9 runs. However, during the final stages of the innings, he was smashed all around and went for 43 off just 2 overs in his second spell. George Dockrell was the only bowler, who gave away less than 6 runs an over. Apart from him, the South Africans took a toll of the other bowlers, especially Sorensen and Kevin O'Brien. Sorensen gave away 76 in his 6 and O'Brien also conceded 95 runs in his 7 overs as well. It is going to be extremely difficult for Ireland to chase this down. But, we have seen funnier things happen in cricket. Join us in a short while to follow the run-chase.]]></line><line><![CDATA[du Plessis was deceived by a yorker from Kevin O'Brien and de Villiers came out to bat after him. He started off in his usual manner, racing away to 22 off just 7 balls. However, Andy McBrine sent both Amla and de Villiers back in a space of 3 balls to halt the South African onslaught. After that Miller and Rossouw took the onus of going after the bowling. Both of them thrashed the Irish bowlers to all parts of the park and helped their team go past 400, becoming the first team to score 400 in consecutive games. Both of them finished unbeaten, with Rossouw bringing up his 3rd ODI fifty just before the end of the innings as South Africa recorded the <b>second highest score in World Cup history</b>. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[South Africa didn't get off to the best of starts, with de Kock failing one more time. Ever since he has come back from injury, he has struggled to get going with the bat. However, like the last game, Hashim Amla and Faf du Plessis got together and steadied the ship from there on. Their rotation of strike was great and they made sure that the Irish couldn't bog them down, dispatching the loose ones to the fence. Both of them were together from the 3rd over till the 39th and put on 247 runs for the second wicket. In the process, Hashim Amla (108 innings) became the fastest man to reach 20 ODI hundreds, going past Virat Kohli. du Plessis also soon reached his ton and both of them then tried to accelerate.]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to D Miller, <b>FOUR</b>, it's another edge past the stumps and O'Brien is a frustrated man. Full and outside off stump, Miller swings hard, gets an inside edge, the ball escapes past the off stump and runs away to the boundary. <b>24 runs</b> came off that over. South Africa have scored 40 runs off the last two overs]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Rossouw, 1 run, widish yorker outside off stump, driven to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Rossouw, <b>FOUR</b>, oh that's unlucky for the bowler. Full and wide outside off stump, Rossouw reaches out to squeeze the ball, it goes off the toe-end of the bat and goes fine to the third man boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Rossouw, <b>SIX</b>, <b>South Africa are the first team to score 400 in consecutive ODIs</b>. Full and on the leg stump, Rossouw slogs it hard over mid-wicket and it's gone all the way. This is brilliant batting from Rossouw]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to D Miller, 3 runs, that's a bottom edge and it's beaten the keeper's dive to his right. Short of a length delivery outside off stump, Miller goes for the slog again, but gets a thick edge, the fielder at short fine leg gives chase and saves one with a slide in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to D Miller, <b>SIX</b>, surely, 400 is a possibility now! Kev offers a juicy full ball, in the slot, Miller waits for it to come and slogs it very high over the mid-wicket boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kevin O'Brien [6.0-0-71-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Rossouw, 2 runs, yorker outside off stump, Rossouw drills it to long-on and gets to his <b>third ODI fifty</b>. Back-to-back fifties for Rossouw in this World Cup]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Rossouw, <b>no ball</b>, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a high full toss above waist height. Actually, it was a marginal call but the umpire didn't like it. Rossouw smashes it hard and sends it over extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Rossouw, no run, Rossouw gets down on one knee to paddle this fine, but toe-ends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to D Miller, byes, 1 run, a high full toss outside off stump, Miller gets across the stumps and tried to help it away to fine leg, but misses. The keeper fumbles to allow the run]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to D Miller, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a powerful blow! Slower ball outside off stump, it was very full, but Miller has smashed that hard over extra-cover and it bounces just inside the boundary line]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to D Miller, <b>FOUR</b>, Sorensen misses the yorker, it goes full and in the slot, Miller slogs it wide of the man at mid-wicket and long-on had no chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to D Miller, no run, fine yorker outside off stump, Miller digs it out back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Two overs to go and 29 runs to get? Can they get to 400?]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Rossouw, no run, full toss, reverse-swept very well but straight to backward point. Rossouw will be kicking himself for not hitting the gap]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Rossouw, <b>FOUR</b>, unlucky for the bowler. Rossouw advances down the wicket, McBrine saw him coming and fired it down the leg-side, Rossouw tries to whip, but gets an under edge and it went very fine to the fine leg boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Rossouw, <b>SIX</b>, this time Rossouw gets it right and sends it flat over long-on. The fielder in the deep was very square. Flighted delivery from McBrine, Rossouw gets to the pitch of the ball and sends it over the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Rossouw, no run, follows Rossouw as he backs away, a brilliant yorker and Rossouw could do nothing with it]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Rossouw, no run, advances and tries to slog, but misses and gets hit on the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to D Miller, 1 run, good length delivery just outside off stump, Miller punches it off the back foot to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andy McBrine [9.0-0-52-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Rossouw, no run, low full toss outside off stump, Rossouw mistimes the drive back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to D Miller, 1 run, a couple of yards either side of the fielder would have been a boundary. Low full toss outside off stump, Miller slices and picks out short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Rossouw, 1 run, widish yorker outside off stump, Rossouw sends it through cover-point, Rossouw slips while trying to turn for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Rossouw, <b>SIX</b>, thank you very much says Rossouw and smashes it over mid-wicket. Full and in the slot, around leg stump line, Rossouw takes his front leg out of the way and easily sends it over the boundary rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to D Miller, 1 run, low full toss outside off stump, Miller looks to drive through the off-side, but the bat turns in his hands and goes to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Rossouw, 1 run, to cover,]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Rossouw, 1 run, a fine yorker outside off stump, Rossouw digs it out to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Max Sorensen [4.0-0-51-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Rossouw, 1 run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Rossouw wrists it to long-on, looks for two but the fielder got there quickly]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to D Miller, 1 run, flighted delivery on the leg stump, Miller drives it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to D Miller, no run, on the leg stump, Miller glances it to short fine leg and sets off, but Rossouw says no. The fielder fires in the throw and it was a direct hit. Third umpire has been called for a run-out check, but Miller was quick to return back]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to D Miller, no run, backs away and cuts the flatter ball to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to D Miller, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Miller under-edges the sweep onto the thigh pad, Miller reviewed immediately and he was right in doing so. There was a clear edge, replays and the Snicko confirm that there was bat involved]]></line><line><![CDATA[Miller has <b>reviewed an LBW decision</b> against him. Did he hit it? It's a legal delivery. Yep! There was an inside edge. Decision will be overturned.]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Rossouw, 1 run, round the wicket, flatter ball on the off stump, driven down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Rossouw, 1 run, driven to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Rossouw, <b>FOUR</b>, Rossouw initially gestures as if he wanted to play the reverse sweep but in the end he plays the slog as O'Brien offers a friendly full toss. The ball runs away to the deep mid-wicket boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Rossouw, no run, yorker outside off stump, Rossouw digs it out back to the bowler, who has a shy at the stumps. Rossouw was outside the crease and he had to put in the dive]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Rossouw, <b>FOUR</b>, slower ball on the leg stump, Rossouw slogs and sends it very fine, there was a man at short fine leg, but it went well wide of him]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to D Miller, 1 run, length ball outside off stump, driven to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Rossouw, 1 run, low full toss, driven down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kevin O'Brien [5.0-0-60-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Rossouw, 1 run, driven down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to D Miller, 3 runs, flatter delivery outside off stump, Miller backs away and slashes, gets an outside edge that goes to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Rossouw, 3 runs, kneels down and sweeps it down to fine leg, the batsmen take three before the ball is hunted down]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to D Miller, 1 run, punched to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Rossouw, 1 run, Rossouw shuffles in the crease, but Stirling keeps him calm with a flatter ball, gently nudged to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Rossouw, <b>FOUR</b>, round the wicket, flatter delivery down the leg-side, Rossouw looks to pull but gets an under edge, there is no one at fine leg and it's a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Paul Stirling [8.0-0-52-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to D Miller, <b>SIX</b>, loses control of the slower ball. It was in the zone and in Miller's arc, he waits for the ball to come and slogs it flat over the deep mid-wicket boundary. The extra ball has cost Mooney badly. It was a decent over until then]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's a <b>free-hit</b> now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Rossouw, <b>no ball</b>, 1 run, oopsy! He's overstepped. Full and down the leg-side, flicked to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Rossouw, 2 runs, follows Rossouw as he backs away, the batsman gently flicks it into the vacant mid-wicket region and that gives him two]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to D Miller, 1 run, shortish slower ball, Miller pulls it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to D Miller, 2 runs, full delivery on the stumps, flicked to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to D Miller, 2 runs, driven along the ground to long-on, Rossouw races back for the second and they get back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mooney, who went for 27 runs in his last over, will be a relieved man now after the departure of ABdV.]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Rossouw, 1 run, full and outside off stump, Rossouw drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>John Mooney [6.0-2-36-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to D Miller, <b>FOUR</b>, he hardly seemed to have hit that! Low full toss around the off stump, Miller gets down on one knee and sweeps, looked like he was looking for a single, but he hit it too well and it almost went all the way over the deep backward square leg boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Rossouw, 1 run, tossed up outside off stump, Rossouw drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to D Miller, 1 run, driven down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rilee Rossouw, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to de Villiers, <b>out</b> Caught by N O'Brien!! This is a brilliant bowling change by Porterfield. He's got two massive wickets in a space of 3 balls. Why did you play that fancy little reverse sweep AB? It was right in the slot to go over long-on and surely, he would have hit it for six! Nothing but a flighted delivery, a bad stroke attempted by AB and he mistimes it completely. It catches him high on the bat and balloons up, point runs back and to his right to take a good catch. Massive wicket this, really massive. That will make a difference of 15-20 runs, if not more, to the final score. <b>de Villiers c N O'Brien b Andy McBrine 24(9) [4s-1 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Andy McBrine to de Villiers, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to de Villiers, 2 runs, on the leg stump, de Villiers flicks it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>David Miller, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, <b>out</b> Caught by Ed Joyce!! Not timed too well and it's an easy catch to long-off. Ed Joyce, who dropped Amla on 10, catches him on 159. Flighted delivery outside off stump, Amla steps out and looks to loft, but doesn't get it from the middle of the bat. In fact, he was looking to go over long-on but the bat turned in his hands. Amla raises his bat as he walks off. Actually, South Africa may not mind losing Amla at this stage as it brings in Miller. <b>Amla c Ed Joyce b Andy McBrine 159(128) [4s-16 6s-4]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Andy McBrine to Amla, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Andy McBrine [8.0-0-44-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[He's just faced 7 balls, AB de Villiers, and scored 22 runs already.]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to de Villiers, 2 runs, fine yorker on the stumps, de Villiers gets across and goes down on his knees to sweep it fine, but gets a bottom edge that rolls to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to de Villiers, <b>SIX</b>, no Kevin O'Brien, noooo! Can't bowl there to this man. Full and in the slot, de Villiers backs away initially but smashes it high over extra-cover and it goes way into the stand]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Amla, 1 run, yorker on the leg stump, Amla works it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Amla, <b>FOUR</b>, four more! Full and wide outside off stump, Amla square-drives it very well, the fielder at backward point dives to his right but the ball escapes]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Amla, <b>FOUR</b>, that's his <b>highest ODI score</b>! Short and just outside off stump, Amla gets across and pulls it past the man at short fine leg for four]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Amla, 2 runs, full and outside off stump, Amla drives it past the diving fielder at extra-cover and that's his <b>150</b>. He raises his bat and shakes hands with ABdV. Can he get to 200? So much time left in the innings]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[South Africa have scored <b>69/1</b> in the 5-over batting powerplay.]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Amla, 1 run, on the leg stump, Amla drags the slog to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Amla, <b>FOUR</b>, high full toss and Amla does well to slog it in the gap. It was just under waist height. He hits it between mid-on and mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to de Villiers, 1 run, follows de Villiers as he backs away, the batsman mistimes the slap to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to de Villiers, 2 runs, low full toss, de Villiers drives it past extra-cover and long-off tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to de Villiers, <b>SIX</b>, in the airrrr and the fielder doesn't get there in time. That was catchable. Did he start very late? Flighted delivery on the leg stump, de Villiers sweeps in the air, deep mid-wicket runs to his right, sticks his right hand out but the ball just escapes past him and crosses the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, boundary number one for de Villiers! Flighted delivery on the leg stump, de Villiers backs away and lofts it inside-out over extra-cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>George Dockrell [9.0-0-38-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Amla, 2 runs, full and outside off stump, Amla drives, the fielder at cover-point dives to his right and parries it towards extra-cover, AB is aware of the situation and he pushes Amla for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to de Villiers, 1 run, straightaway steps out, but O'Brien drags his length back, de Villiers runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>AB de Villiers, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Alright, ABdV is in!]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to du Plessis, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Timbahhh! Fantastic yorker from O'Brien, right at the base of middle stump and du Plessis couldn't keep it out. The batsman backs away and tries to go slog, but misses as he goes early into the shot and it rattles into the stumps. O'Brien is pumped and he punches the stumps softly in delight. That was more a soccer celebration from the all-rounder. du Plessis walks off to a standing ovation. <b>du Plessis b K O'Brien 109(109) [4s-10 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[K O'Brien to du Plessis, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Amla, 1 run, nice and full outside off stump, Amla drives it wide of long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to du Plessis, 3 runs, this time he connects with the scoop. Full and around the off stump, du Plessis sends it over short fine leg, Dockrell runs across from short third man, puts in the slide and saves one]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to du Plessis, no run, du Plessis gets right across the line and tries to scoop, but O'Brien bowls this well outside off stump and beats the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Amla, <b>SIX</b>, whoa! 4 4 6 4 6 to end the over. 27 runs came off the over and Mooney went for just 9 runs in his first five overs. Full and outside off stump, Amla waits for the ball and lofts it handsomely over extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Amla, <b>FOUR</b>, excellent placement once again! Mindful of the fact that third man was inside the ring, Amla delays the cut and slices this short ball over short third man. That was expertly done!]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Amla, <b>SIX</b>, it's a slog and it's gone all the way. Slower ball picked very early, Amla clears his front leg out of the way and sends it flat over deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Amla, <b>no ball</b>, <b>FOUR</b>, is that a no ball? Yes it is! Mooney loses control of this one and bowls a full toss above waist height. Amla waits for the ball and smashes it over cover for four more]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Amla, <b>FOUR</b>, easy ball and Amla doesn't miss out! Slower ball goes way too short, Amla had two hours to rock back and pull, he places it over backward square leg and the fielder in the deep had no chance despite running swiftly to his right]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Amla, 2 runs, a loft over mid-off, but there is a man in the deep. Actually, Amla did not time it well enough and it went very straight as well. There was a man at long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Amla, no run, Amla stays leg-side of the ball and tries to go over extra-cover, but this short of length delivery beats the bat and just goes over the middle stump. The keeper takes the bails off, but Amla had his back foot grounded]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>John Mooney [5.0-2-9-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now. This brilliant double-hundred stand has put South Africa in a great position. Ireland will have to bowl really well from here on to be chasing anything less than 375. The stage is set for the likes of de Villiers, Rossouw and Miller. Can they score 400 again? We'll find out in a while.]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, inventive shot from Faf! Good length ball outside off stump, du Plessis lines himself up for the scoop over short fine leg, but on seeing O'Brien bowl this well outside off stump, he hits it straight back over the keeper's head. 13 off the over, exactly what the Proteas wanted with field restrictions in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to du Plessis, no run, slower ball yorker again from O'Brien, du Plessis backs away, but can only dig it out onto his pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to du Plessis, 2 runs, a fine yorker following du Plessis as he backs away, but the batsman manages to work it through mid-wicket, Amla races back for the second and a direct-hit at the bowler's would have been very interesting]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Amla, 1 run, slower ball hit uppishly to long-off, who is very quick to move to his left and prevent the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Amla, <b>FOUR</b>, great placement from Hash! Full and way outside off stump, Amla opens the face of the bat at the last moment to send the drive very square, he hits it over backward point and there is no stopping that]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Amla, 2 runs, full and outside off stump, Amla drives hard, but the man at deep cover runs to his right and tidies up]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kevin O'Brien [2.0-0-21-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's good news for Ireland that they've conceded just 4 runs in the first 6 balls of the powerplay.]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Amla, 1 run, advances and slogs the flighted delivery to mid-wicket, who deflects it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to du Plessis, 1 run, <b>4th ODI hundred</b> for Faf! He's a happy man. Amla shakes hands with his partner to congratulate him. Flighted delivery on the leg stump, du Plessis turns it softly to square leg and takes a sharp run]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to du Plessis, no run, a tentative front foot push away the body, the ball goes uppishly but doesn't carry to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to du Plessis, no run, steps out and on-drive, but McBrine makes a sliding save to his left at mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Amla, 1 run, short and outside off stump, cut to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to du Plessis, 1 run, <b>double-hundred partnership</b>. Flatter delivery on the leg stump, du Plessis steps out and nudges it to backward point. du Plessis is on 99 now]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Batting powerplay</b> has been enforced. Fasten your seat belts folks!]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to du Plessis, 1 run, easily pushed down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to du Plessis, no run, on the stumps, defended straight back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Amla, 1 run, flighted delivery outside off stump, Amla drives to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to du Plessis, 1 run, a <b>huge mix-up</b>, but all is well in the end for South Africa. du Plessis flicks this flighted delivery to backward square leg, Amla was halfway down the wicket for a run, du Plessis says no, the throw came at the wrong end, Amla was struggling at the bowler's end, but by the time the keeper had a shy at the bowler's end, Amla was well in with a dive. In fact, the throw from the keeper was wayward and they get a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Amla, 1 run, full and outside off stump, Amla drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to du Plessis, 1 run, flatter ball outside off stump, du Plessis goes on the back foot and punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Amla, no run, full and down the leg-side, Amla tries to work it on the on-side, but gets a soft leading edge that rolls towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Amla, no run, slowish and on the stumps, defended]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to du Plessis, 1 run, steps out and defends wide of mid-on, the fielder at mid-wicket tries to stop and dives to his left, but he deflects the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Amla, 1 run, easily driven down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to du Plessis, 1 run, spinning away outside off stump, du Plessis taps it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Amla, 1 run, flatter delivery on the leg stump, Amla flicks it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>George Dockrell [7.0-0-30-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, du Plessis signs off the over in style as he did in Stirling's last over. Flighted ball from Stirling, du Plessis lofts it flat over mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Amla, 1 run, on the off stump, punched along the ground to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to du Plessis, 1 run, tossed up from Stirling, du Plessis steps out and drives to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to du Plessis, no run, backs away and punches the flatter ball to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Amla, 1 run, <b>20th ODI hundred</b> for Amla. Full and outside off stump, Amla drives it along the ground to long-off. His teammates stand and applaud. He raises his bat and acknowledges the applause. He gets a hug from Faf as well. <b>Amla</b> is the <b>fastest</b> to record 20 hundreds in ODIs, surpassing Virat Kohli]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to du Plessis, 1 run, hangs back and punches the flatter ball to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to du Plessis, 1 run, backs away and punches the flatter ball to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, 1 run, friendly ball on the pads, flicked away through backward square leg. Amla on 99 now]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, no run, shortish outside off stump, punched off the back foot to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to du Plessis, 1 run, waits for the ball to spin back in and flicks it through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, 1 run, 'catch' is the cry as Amla drives this uppishly off the front foot, but it went well wide of the man at cover, who dived to his right]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, no run, fired in full and outside off stump, defended off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, mid-off is inside the ring and that's a safe shot! du Plessis doesn't try to overhit the flighted delivery, just lofts it over the infield and it bounces just inside the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Amla, 1 run, full and outside off stump, Amla drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to du Plessis, 1 run, clipped away to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[This is a <b>record 2nd wicket</b> stand for South Africa in World Cup cricket.]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Amla, 1 run, almost a yorker, Amla digs it out to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to du Plessis, 1 run, delays the drive and sends it through point]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Amla, 1 run, shortish and outside off stump, Amla drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, 1 run, flatter ball outside off stump, softly driven off the back foot to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to du Plessis, 1 run, short enough for du Plessis to hang back and punch to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, 1 run, driven off the back foot through cover-point again]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to du Plessis, 1 run, a gentle flick into the on-side past the man at mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, 1 run, shortish and outside off stump, driven off the back foot to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, no run, spinning back in, bit of extra bounce, but Amla handles it well as he turns it to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andy McBrine [6.0-0-35-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Amla, 1 run, full and outside off stump, Amla punches it off the front foot to long-off and keeps strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to du Plessis, 1 run, quicker and outside off stump, du Plessis punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Amla, 1 run, flatter delivery from Stirling, Amla punches to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Amla, no run, and again! Full and outside off stump, Amla drives well off the front foot, Kevin O'Brien dives to his left and makes another good stop. Has a shy at the stumps as Amla was initially out of the crease, but he was well home in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Amla, no run, brilliant stop by Kev at cover! Amla drove this flighted delivery very hard, the fielder flew to his left and stopped it with his right hand]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to du Plessis, 1 run, quicker through the air outside off stump, du Plessis defends it towards cover-point for a run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Paul Stirling [4.0-0-26-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Amla, no run, tossed up on the off stump, Amla steps out and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to du Plessis, 1 run, slower through the air, du Plessis drives it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to du Plessis, no run, advances and tries to slap hard, but mistimes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to du Plessis, 2 runs, shot! Too short from Dockrell, du Plessis rocks back and lofts it high over extra-cover, long-off swiftly moves to his left and saves two]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to du Plessis, no run, steps out and blocks as he doesn't get to the pitch of the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to du Plessis, no run, flatter delivery on the off stump, du Plessis defends]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to du Plessis, 1 run, delays the cut shot and places it past the diving fielder at backward point, but there is a man in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, 1 run, quicker through the air and on the off stump, driven down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to du Plessis, 1 run, driven hard off the back foot but straight to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to du Plessis, 2 runs, the scoop from du Plessis. Flighted delivery outside off stump, du Plessis gets across the stumps and sends it over the jumping keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, 1 run, short enough for Amla to hang back and punch to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, no run, allows the ball to spin back in and punches it to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to du Plessis, no run, fast and outside off stump, du Plessis drives it straight to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Amla, 1 run, tossed up outside off stump, Amla drives it along the ground to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to du Plessis, 1 run, punched past the bowler to long-on and that's the <b>150-run</b> stand between these two]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to du Plessis, no run, jumps out of the crease and softly taps this flatter ball to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to du Plessis, no run, slowish and spinning away, du Plessis defends off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Amla, 1 run, short and spinning away outside off stump, driven off the back foot through cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>George Dockrell [5.0-0-24-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, 1 run, slower and on off, pushed past the bowler for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, no run, this one is given more air as McBrine goes wider, driven to the fielder at extra cover, the fielder dived there and saved some runs for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to du Plessis, 1 run, tossed up and on off, eased in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, 1 run, flighted delivery and on off, nudged wide of mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to du Plessis, 1 run, slower and well outside off, driven wide of cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, more runs, the man at square leg didn't see it at all, du Plessis was down on his knees as he swept, gets it to the left of square leg, just past the man there, Dockrell was the fielder there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to du Plessis, 1 run, on a good length and well outside off, worked away square on the off-side for a single, <b>24 came from that over</b>. Sorensen has been taken for plenty today]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to du Plessis, <b>SIX</b>, <b>that's a massive hit from du Plessis</b>, he wants to join the party as well, skips down the track, gets underneath the length and lofts it high and well over long-on, well taken by an Indian in the stands]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Amla, 1 run, tad fuller and on the stumps, driven down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Amla, <b>FOUR</b>, Sorensen has been taken for plenty, he drops this one short and wide outside off, cut away square on the off-side, the fielder in the deep is very square, another boundary for Amla]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Amla, <b>SIX</b>, this is even better! On a good length and well outside off, Amla gets underneath the length, plays with an open face, makes some room outside leg and carves it up and over extra cover for a maximum, he's on fire here]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Amla, <b>SIX</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, this was a length ball and just outside off, Amla shuffles across, gets underneath the length and hoicks it high and over wide long-on for a maximum]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to du Plessis, no run, pushed through by McBrine, du Plessis makes room and mistimes the cut towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to du Plessis, no run, tossed up and well outside off, du Plessis comes down the track, doesn't get to the pitch and defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, 1 run, fraction shorter and well outside off, Amla backs away and cuts it square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to du Plessis, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, pulled away with a vertical bat, goes to the fielder at deep mid-wicket on the bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, 1 run, Amla is playing more shots now, this was tossed up and just outside off, drilled down the ground and to the left of long on, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to du Plessis, 1 run, tossed up and just outside off, worked to the left of square leg for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Amla, no run, on a good length and well outside off, Amla drives to the left of cover where the fielder makes a tumbling stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to du Plessis, 1 run, full and on the stumps, du Plessis flicks it towards mid-wicket, the ball hits the edge of the practice turf and lobs over the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Amla, 1 run, on a good length and well outside off, Amla makes room and slashes it square past cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Amla, <b>FOUR</b>, that's clubbed by Amla, lots of power behind the shot, length ball on off, Amla makes room and drills it to the right of mid-off, the fielder dives, but the ball beats him to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Amla, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, driven towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Amla, no run, short of a length and just outside off, worked towards mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Max Sorensen [2.0-0-21-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, 1 run, pushed through and on off, nudged down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Amla, no run, tossed up and just outside off, Amla stays behind the line and pushes it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA