<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="12894" >
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>40th Match, Pool A</gameDesc>
		<series>WC 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Australia</home>
		<away>Scotland</away>
		<teamsabbr>AUS vs SCO</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>AUS</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>SCO</awayabbr>
		<homeId>4</homeId>
		<awayId>23</awayId>
		<venue>Bellerive Oval, Hobart</venue>
		<startdate>14 03 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>14 03 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Australia</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Australia won by 7 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Australia</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>7</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Ian Gould</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Richard Illingworth</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Joel S Wilson</Name>
			<Country>WI</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Jeff Crowe</Name>
			<Country>NZ</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>03:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150314084526</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>Aus</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>Sco</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>133</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>3</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>15.2</batteamovers>
		<status>Australia won by 7 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>7789</playerid>
			<name>James Faulkner*</name>
			<batsman-name>Faulkner</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Faulkner</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>16</runs>
			<balls-faced>6</balls-faced>
			<fours>2</fours>
			<sixes>1</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>1739</playerid>
			<name>David Warner</name>
			<batsman-name>Warner</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Warner</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>21</runs>
			<balls-faced>6</balls-faced>
			<fours>2</fours>
			<sixes>2</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>9383</playerid>
			<name>Michael Leask*</name>
			<bowler-name>M A Leask</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>M A Leask</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>0.2</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>7</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>6657</playerid>
			<name>Josh Davey</name>
			<bowler-name>J Davey</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Davey</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>5</overs>
			<maidens>1</maidens>
			<runs>38</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>131</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>138</playerid>
<name>Michael Clarke</name>
<player-runs>47</player-runs>
<player-balls>47</player-balls>
<runs>92</runs>
<wicket-nbr>3</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>8423</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Iain Wardlaw</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>5</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[1 1 . 1 4 W <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 W 6 4 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 4 1 Wd 6 4 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>L2 Wd 6 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_WC/AUS_SCO_MAR14/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[Alrighty then, that brings a close to another game. Australia will heave a sigh of relief that another one of their games was not washed away. They will now wait for tomorrow's result to know who they face in the quarter-final. So, join us back for the double-header tomorrow. First up, it is West Indies taking on UAE in a must win game for the Caribbean side. Then, Pakistan will face a stiff challenge from Ireland in another crucial encounter. Till next time, on behalf of <b>Mani, Sriram</b> and my co-commentator, <b>Sidhant Maheshwari</b>, this is <b>Akshay Maanay</b>, signing off. Goodbye!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Take a look at some of the <b>interesting tweets</b> from this game:]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@rgcricket:</b> Mitchell Starc has now equalled Mitchell McClenaghan's record of taking 4-wicket haul on first appearance vs SIX countries. #CWC15 #AusvSCO]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@InnoBystander:</b> Simultaneous sixes from Dhoni & Faulkner ends their respective games... #cwc15 #ausvsco #indvzim]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@mohanstatsman:</b> Most ODI wkts after 38 mts - 77 Mitchell Starc, 73 Saqlain Mushtaq, 72 Shane Bond/Ajantha Mendis, 70 Waqar Younis/Ajit Agarkar #CWC15 #AusvSco]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Clarke:</b> "Like I said at the toss it was forecasted (referring to the rain). So, fortunately we got enough time. But, credit again to the way the boys played. I thought all our bowlers did a great job. To bowl Scotland out and in the way the batters put the team first and tried to score runs as quickly as possible, it's always nice to win. I don't think there is any better preparation leading into a quarter-final than winning. So, as we have seen throughout this tournament, you have to be at your best in every single game. Now we are into the quarter-finals and we know it is a knockout stage. So, we couldn't asked for a better preparation. We had one little hiccup against New Zealand. But, the boys are excited and are looking forward to Adelaide. Everybody is been waiting for the quarter-finals, but obviously you have got to make it. So, you have to take every game as serious as each other. But, really pleased that we got there and now we got to be at our best. We are about to find out that's for sure, three games, we have to play our best and I think if we do that, we can win (when asked if Australia can go all the way). If we don't, we will on the couch watching."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mommsen:</b> "We knew it was always going to be a tough game for us. We wanted to stand up to the challenge today and unfortunately, it wasn't meant to be for us. We take a huge amount of positives from the past 6 games. I think the more we played, the better we become. As a unit we leave this competition, a much better and a much stronger team. Very impressive. I think as a team we are proud of his (Davey) achievements. He can hold his head very high, that's an awesome achievement. The focus shifts to 20-20, we have the World Cup qualifiers in Scotland in June. We will go back, refresh and refocus and hopefully qualify for that World Cup."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Starc:</b> "Yeah, can't complain. But, it was important for us to put on a bullish performance. With the bit of weather around that we knew is going to be around, the boys went pretty hard with the bat. It was great to see some selfless cricket. It's a big game and obviously it could go either way tomorrow in terms of who we play, but it's an important game for us (talking about the quarter-final). Obviously, it's the knockout stage, we are raring to go. Done and dusted with the group stages and the boys are looking forward to the back end. I have been working at it quite hard with Craig McDermott, probably since the Dubai One-Day series there. It's been coming out well, can't complain and just want to continue that in the back end."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his <b>4/14</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier in the day, Clarke won the toss and sent Scotland in to bat in conditions that were overcast. Scotland started off with an attacking mindset, but it brought about their downfall as they kept losing wickets. They were 130/8 when rain stopped play for the first time in the day. It wasn't a heavy shower, but the umpires took the players off the field anyway. After rain stopped completely, Mitchell Starc took four balls to finish the Scottish innings and he ended with another 4-wicket haul, his 11th in 38 ODIs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The rain played spoilsport for some time, but no overs were lost. Play resumed as Faulkner and Warner came out to bat. Warner hammered the first ball for a six over long-on, making it clear that the Australians were looking to chase it down as quickly as possible. Australia went like - 6 4 1 1 4 4 1 Wd 6 4 0 2lb Wd 6 - and finished the game off in 12 legal deliveries after the rain break.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Clarke, meanwhile, was paying respect to the good balls and throwing his bat at the loose ones. However, after Watson departed, Clarke smashed Wardlaw to the fence off the very next ball. He tried to repeat it again off the next ball, but Leask at deep square leg pulled off a great catch to send him back at 47. Clarke was in a hurry because of chances of rain and as soon as he got out, the heavens opened and dinner was taken early. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Instead of David Warner, Michael Clarke came out to bat with Aaron Finch. Both batsmen started off in a belligerent fashion as they went after the bowling, especially Finch, who raced away to 20 off just 9 balls. However, he fell the very next ball, chipping one straight to Coleman at cover. After that Watson walked out and tried to get his eye in before he started thrashing the bowlers. Watson was trying to play way too many shots and ended up spooning a catch for the keeper as he tried to scoop one over short fine leg. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Australia needed just 12 balls to chase down the remaining 39 runs. With this win, Australia will <b>finish second</b> in Pool A. They will <b>not be facing South Africa</b> and will take on the team who finish third in Pool B.]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Faulkner, <b>SIX</b>, <b>Australia win by 7 wickets.</b> The finisher for Australia, James Faulkner does it in style. Tossed up delivery on off, Faulkner kneels down and slog sweeps it over deep mid-wicket for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Faulkner, <b>wide</b>, darted down the leg-side, Faulkner can't reach it and wide given. Good take by Cross]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Faulkner, leg byes, 2 runs, Leask starts from round the wicket, flights it on leg-stump, Faulkner misses the sweep, the ball lobs off the pad to the left of leg slip, the duo come back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Michael Leask, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Warner, no run, gets the yorker right this time, Warner digs it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, Davey goes for the yorker, gets it wrong, ends up bowling a full toss, Warner drills it to wide long-on, the fielder runs to his left, dives full length and tries to flick it back in, but all in vain]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Warner, <b>SIX</b>, massive! Davey delivers a nice juicy full toss, it went at a good height as well, Warner clears his front leg and launches it over cow corner for a maximum. That went <b>104 metres long</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Warner, <b>wide</b>, fires it full and outside off, easy call for the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Faulkner, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Faulkner slices it on the bounce to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[The keeper comes up to the stumps..]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Faulkner, <b>FOUR</b>, the duo are in a hurry as it starts to drizzle again. Advances down the wicket and converts it into a fuller length delivery, lifts it over the infield on the off-side to pick up another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Faulkner, <b>FOUR</b>, hammered! Faulkner gives the charge, Davey sees that and drags the length back, Faulkner has no problems to make some room and slap it over mid-off. The fielder was inside the circle and it raced away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Faulkner, 1 run, even Faulkner is not holding back, slower delivery on off and middle, Faulkner drags the heave to deep backward square]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Warner, 1 run, top edge and safe! Banged in halfway down the wicket, Warner goes back on the pull, the ball skies up off the top edge and drops in no-man's land near deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, oh he has come out attacking. Shortish and on the stumps, Warner hops back in the crease and plays the short-arm pull in front of square, there was a man in the deep but he had no chance of cutting that off]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Warner, <b>SIX</b>, first ball Warner faces and he sends it soaring into the crowd. No sighters, no settling down. It was full and in the slot, he extended his arms and lofts it over long-off for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players are making their way out to the middle. Warner is the new batsman, who will be joining Faulkner. Australia need 39 more runs..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>19:27 Local Time, 08:27 GMT, 13:57 IST:</b> The covers and even the hessian are coming off. Play will resume at <b>19:35 local time</b>. It is still a 50-over contest.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sri Lanka will stay second as the teams will be tied on points, but the number of wins will be taken into consideration before the net run-rate. Since Sri Lanka have won 4 games and Australia will only end with 3 wins, Sri Lanka will finish higher.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:54 Local Time, 07:54 GMT, 13:24 IST:</b> The covers are coming off, but the hessian is still on the turf. The umpires are out in the middle conducting an inspection. It has become brighter as well. Australian coach, Darren Lehmann is out and is having a look at the clouds. Well, well, the good news lasted for 20 minutes as the rain arrives, again. The umpires are walking off the field. The covers are coming back on. Just a reminder, <b>if this game is washed out, Australia will finish third in Pool A and will take on South Africa in the quarter-finals</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:46 Local Time, 07:46 GMT, 13:16 IST:</b> Good news folks! The rain has stopped. The groundsmen are working to clear the water that has gathered around. The super sopper is being used as well. So, we are not far away from the resumption. Fingers crossed!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:35 Local Time, 07:35 GMT, 13:05 IST:</b> The dinner/supper break has ended. But, there is still no update on the weather. We will keep you informed as and when we have more news regarding the start time.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:03 Local Time, 07:03 GMT, 12:33 IST:</b> And the rain is back. It is much heavier this time. The pitch is being covered by the hessian. The players were quick to leave the field. Hopefully, it's not a long delay as Australia need only 39 more runs to win. The square also has been covered. Meanwhile, the players take the <b>dinner break.</b> So, we will be back in around 30 minutes. Hop over and follow the India-Zimbabwe game till then.]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Clarke, <b>out</b> Caught by M A Leask!! Australia are losing wickets unnecessarily. Clarke can't believe that he has picked out the fielder. Another short delivery at chest height, Clarke swivels and pulls it in the air to deep square leg, Leask moves to his right, dives full length and takes the catch. As he took it, his left hand came off, but he did well to hang on with one hand. <b>Clarke c M A Leask b Iain Wardlaw 47(47) [4s-7 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Iain Wardlaw to Clarke, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, can't bowl short at 132.8kph, Clarke is too good for that, he rocks back and muscles the pull in front of square, that was hit hard and it travelled quickly to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Watson, <b>out</b> Caught by Matthew Cross!! Davey continues to have a good World Cup. He has picked up his 15th wicket. Watson was trying to be cheeky and pays the price. Full and on off, Watson shuffles across and tries to scoop it over short fine, doesn't get it anywhere close to the middle, spoons it to the left of the keeper, Cross takes the easiest of catches. <b>Watson c Matthew Cross b Davey 24(23) [4s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Davey to Watson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! Watson picked up the length really quickly, it was a cross seam delivery on a length, Watson goes through the line, lofts it over mid-on and the ball bounces only twice before reaching the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Clarke, 1 run, short and outside off, Clarke slaps it in front of square on the off-side, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Clarke, no run, good length ball on off, defended down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Watson, 1 run, takes the pace off the short of length delivery, Watson backs away and taps it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Clarke, 1 run, slower short ball, Clarke rolls his wrists and pulls it along the ground to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Watson, 2 runs, full and outside off, Watson makes room and lofts, he got the elevation but not the distance. The ball plugs in the outfield and the batsmen only get two]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Watson, no run, banged in midway down the wicket, Watson moves to the leg-side and flat-bats it on the bounce to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Clarke, 1 run, too straight, on middle and leg, Clarke leans forward and flicks to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Clarke, no run, short of length around off, Clarke guides it with an angled bat to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Clarke, <b>SIX</b>, Clarke wants to get it over with. Length delivery around off, Clarke plays a free-flowing loft, the ball sails over the long-on fence for a maximum. Even Watson liked it]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Watson, 1 run, low full toss on the stumps, Watson digs it out to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Iain Wardlaw [3.0-0-31-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Clarke, no run, slower short ball from Davey, Clarke looks to pull but was a little too early into the shot, he misses and the ball <b>hits him on the helmet</b>, but no harm done as the ball hardly had any pace on it]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Clarke, no run, on a good length and shaping away outside off, Clarke shoulders arms to this one]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>sweetly timed!</b> It was a back of a length delivery angling away outside off, Clarke stays on the back foot and cuts it to the sweeper cover fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Clarke, no run, on a good length and on off, Clarke defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, banged in short and outside off, Clarke fetches the pull and gets it to the right of mid-on, who dives to his right, but fails to stop it. The ball dribbles away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Clarke, no run, length delivery just outside off, Clarke leans across and defends it towards mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Watson, no run, fuller in length and around off, Watson comes on the front foot and drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, short of length delivery just outside off, Watson makes room and flat-bats the pull back past the bowler, the fielder at mid-on too could only see it race away to the boundary rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Watson, no run, Watson shuffles across to work this length delivery into the on-side, close the bat face early and the ball rolls away into the off-side off the outside half]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Watson, no run, yorker on middle, Watson squeezes it out into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Watson, no run, Watson stays leg-side of the ball and looks to push it through the off-side, gets an inside edge onto the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[The keeper is up to the stumps now]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, Watson backs away to this full toss outside off, Watson slaps it to the sweeper cover fence, Taylor has a few words to say to Watson, who doesn't hold back either. Let's see what he bowls next]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Clarke, no run, fuller in length and slightly wide outside off, Clarke went chasing after it and has a swing at it, but fails to make a connection. The keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Clarke, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Clarke stands tall and punches it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Clarke, no run, on off and middle stump, Clarke bunts it towards mid-on after going across]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Clarke, no run, on a good length and on off, Clarke goes forward and pushes it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Clarke, no run, short of length delivery on off, Clarke defends it in front of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Clarke, no run, that <b>must have hurt!</b> It was banged in short and the ball doesn't rise as much as Clarke expected as he went for the pull, he wears it right on the box, the bowler also feels his pain as Davey blows some air out of his mouth too]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, great shot from Watson to end the over, it was full and outside off, Watson presses forward and lofts it to the right of mid-off, the fielder didn't move an inch and was a mere spectator as the ball raced away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Clarke, 1 run, short of length delivery on middle and leg, Clarke hops in the crease and tucks it away to deep square leg off his hips]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Clarke, no run, length delivery on middle stump, Clarke pushes it into the on-side off the inside half of the bat and shouts 'Wait' for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>uppish but safe!</b> It was fuller in length and on middle stump line, Clarke drives it uppishly past the bowler, who dives to his right but can't get a hand on it, the ball beats the chase from the mid-on fielder as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Clarke, no run, back of a length delivery around off, Clarke stays back and punches it off the inside half of the bat to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Watson, 1 run, angling away outside off, Watson hangs back and cuts it towards square third man for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Clarke, no run, length delivery outside off, Clarke looks to force it through the off-side off the front foot, gets an inside edge onto the pad, the batsmen can't take a single either as the ball rolls away into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Watson, 1 run, back of a length delivery on middle and leg, Watson tucks it away off his pads to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Watson, no run, slightly back of a length and outside off, Watson hangs back and punches it to cover-point, good shot for no run]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Clarke, 1 run, fuller and on leg, Clarke flicks it behind square on the on-side and the batsmen cross over]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Clarke, no run, just short of a good length and on off, Clarke stands tall and defends it into the off-side, shouts a loud 'No' for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place for Davey]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Watson, 1 run, angling in on the pads, Watson stays rooted to the crease and works it past square leg for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Josh Davey, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Watson, 1 run, bowls this one on the middle stump line, Watson hangs back and clips it towards mid-wicket, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Watson, no run, on a good length and outside off, Watson opens the face of the bat and pushes it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Watson, no run, fuller in length and just outside off, Watson presses forward and drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Watson, no run, length delivery just outside off, Watson puts a good stride forward and bunts it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Watson, no run, touch shortish and outside off, Watson mistimes the cut towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Watson, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Watson leans forward and defends it towards short cover, he was thinking about the single, but it is not there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Clarke, no run, banged in short and well outside off, Clarke drops his wrists and leaves it alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Clarke, no run, fuller in length and on the stumps, Clarke pushes it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Clarke, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Clarke mistimes the punch into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Clarke, no run, just short of a good length and around off, Clarke hangs back and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, shortish and wide outside off, Clarke hangs back and cuts it hard, he didn't time it that well, but places it in the gap and the ball beats the chase of the fielder from cover and cover-point and crashes into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Clarke, <b>wide</b>, bumper which is way too high, the umpire calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Clarke, <b>SIX</b>, <b>top-edge and six!</b> It was banged in short and at the batsman, Clarke looks to pull, but gets a top-edge. The ball carries with the breeze and sails over the fine leg fielder for a six]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Watson, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Finch, <b>out</b> Caught by Coleman!! Finch finally hits one straight to the fielder. It was fuller and outside off, Finch was looking to drive it through the covers and hits it uppishly. Coleman at cover dives forward and completes a good low catch. <b>Finch c Coleman b Rob Taylor 20(10) [4s-3 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rob Taylor to Finch, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Finch, <b>FOUR</b>, full and outside off, Finch leans into the drive and gets it over cover, but only just. The ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Clarke, 1 run, touch shortish and wide outside off, Clarke flashes hard at it, gets an outside edge that beats the second slip fielder, who was diving to his right and the ball rolls away towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Clarke, no run, length delivery outside off, Clarke opens the face of the bat and pushes it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a beautiful cover drive from Clarke, it was fuller and outside off, Clarke presses forward and creams the drive wide of mid-off, the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Clarke, no run, length delivery on off, Clarke defends it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Finch, no run, angling in on leg, Finch fails to work it through the on-side and wears it high on the thigh pad, it was going down leg as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Finch, <b>FOUR</b>, full delivery just outside off, Finch leans forward and drills it uppishly past the bowler, it was uppish and Machan at mid-off dives full length to his right, but can't get a hand on it, the ball crashes into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Finch, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Finch mistimes the punch to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Finch, no run, bowls this one in the channel outside off, Finch has nothing to do with it]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Finch, <b>SIX</b>, back of a length delivery just outside off, Finch waits for it and pulls it over the deep mid-wicket fence, the ball travelled the distance and cleared the rope, first maximum of the innings for Finch and Australia]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Finch, <b>FOUR</b>, splays this one on the pads, Finch flicks it magnificently through mid-wicket and the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Clarke, no run, bowls this one fuller and well outside off, Clarke shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Clarke, no run, <b>peach!</b> That was literally unplayable, it swung in and then shaped away as Clarke was caught inside the crease, squared him completely and the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Clarke, no run, angling away outside off, left alone by Clarke]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Clarke, no run, fuller in length and outside off, Clarke leans forward and drives it towards mid-off, who runs to his left, dives and saves some runs for his team, the batsmen can't take a single either]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Clarke, no run, back of a length delivery on middle and leg, Clarke fails to clip it through the on-side and wears it high on the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Finch, 1 run, <b>Finch has been dropped!</b> It was a back of a length delivery angled across off, the ball shapes away as Finch pushes at it, gets an outside edge towards second slip, where captain Mommsen dives to his left, gets both hands on it, but can't hold onto it, the ball rolls away towards third man and the batsmen take a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rob Taylor, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Clarke, no run, fuller delivery with a hint of shape away outside off, Clarke looks to drive, the ball goes towards cover off the outside half of the bat, the fielder at cover dives to his right and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, banged in short and at the batsman, Clarke rocks back and pulls it to the deep square leg fence, he didn't time it that well but the ball had enough to reach the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Clarke, no run, short of length delivery outside off, Clarke opens the face of the bat and dabs it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Clarke, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Clarke hangs back and punches it to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Finch, 1 run, fullish in length and on middle, Finch drives it to mid-on and sets off, the fielder gets a direct hit at the striker's end, but the batsman was well in]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Iain Wardlaw to Clarke, 1 run, back of a length delivery on middle and leg, Clarke gets it on the glove and drops it back on the track, the batsmen hare across for a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Clarke and Finch are at the crease. Clarke is on strike. Iain Wardlaw will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Surprise, surprise! Michael Clarke will open the innings with Finch]]></line><line><![CDATA[Even after the rain break, Australia will have to bat after a 10-minute innings changeover. Stay tuned for the run-chase.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Australian bowlers just went about their usual business. Starc gave them the perfect start, sending back the openers. Watson and Johnson made further inroads into the Scottish batting line-up. Cummins, who was expensive in his first spell came back well to pick up 3 wickets. Starc started proceedings after the rain and snared the last two wickets to end with his 11th 4-wicket haul in ODIs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Scotland have been no match for the Australians. They came out with a pre-meditated mindset, that is to play attacking cricket. But, couldn't execute it against bowlers bowling at 150kph. MacLeod was looking in good touch, but could not continue. Machan looked the best of the Scottish batsmen and was looking set to score a fifty, however, Cummins had the better of him. Davey and Leask played some free-flowing cricket before rain intervened. However, it was a short delay and Scottish tail lasted just 4 balls after that.]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Iain Wardlaw, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Starc picks up his fourth wicket and he just needed 4 balls to finish the Scottish innings. It was very full and on off, Wardlaw backs away and looks to drive it through the off-side, he can't connect and the ball crashes into the off stump. <b>Iain Wardlaw b Starc 0(2)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to Iain Wardlaw, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Iain Wardlaw, no run, very full and slightly wide outside off, Wardlaw fails to connect with it, the ball beats the blade and goes through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Iain Wardlaw, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Davey, <b>out</b> Bowled!! What a delivery from Starc! He has castled Davey with the second ball after the rain break. It was full and shaped away just a little to beat the defensive push from Davey, the ball crashes into off and middle, the middle stump is pegged back. <b>Davey b Starc 26(35) [4s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to Davey, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Davey, no run, back of a length delivery on off and middle, Davey defends it in front of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Starc will start the proceedings after the break. There are two slips in place and he will come from round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>16:52 Local Time, 05:52 GMT, 11:22 IST:</b> The covers are off finally. The Australian players are already out there. We should be starting in around 2 minutes.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>16:40 Local Time, 05:40 GMT, 11:10 IST:</b> Good news folks! The covers are coming off. Hopefully, the players will be back on the field very soon. Wait a minute, I spoke too soon. There's light rain falling and only the pitch is still covered. The good thing is that it has become much brighter than how it was 15 minutes back.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>16:22 Local Time, 05:22 GMT, 10:52 IST:</b> <b>Play has been stopped due to rain</b>. The rain is not that heavy, but the umpires have asked the players to leave the field. The Australians were a little reluctant to leave the field, but the decision rests with the umpires here. Hopefully, it won't be a long delay]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to M A Leask, <b>FOUR</b>, another boundary for Leask, he has raced away to 23 off just 11 balls, it was a length delivery around off, Leask makes room and drills it back past the bowler, the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[The drizzle is back, it is not too heavy for now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Davey, 1 run, angling in on middle, Davey tucks it away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Davey, no run, good short ball from Cummins, Davey was hurried into the push there, the ball lobs up off the face of the bat and falls in front of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Davey, no run, in the channel outside off, Davey gets right behind the line and defends solidly]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Davey, no run, overpitching on off, Davey clips it to square leg, where Maxwell collects and throws it at the bowler's end, but the batsman was in]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Davey, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Davey punches it to mid-off after standing tall]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Davey, 3 runs, low full toss outside off, Davey opens the face of the bat and drives it square of the wicket, the fielder from backward point gives chase and hauls it before the rope, the batsmen take three meanwhile]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Davey, no run, back of a length delivery on middle, Davey looks to tuck it away into the on-side, but can't connect. the ball rolls away into the off-side off the pad, it was the back-of-the-hand slower ball from Faulkner]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Davey, no run, bumper on leg, Davey sits under it and the umpire deems it legal as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Davey, no run, length delivery around off, Davey defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Davey, no run, length delivery on off, Davey was looking to clip it into the on-side, the bat turns in his hands and he ends up pushing it uppishly towards short mid-wicket, but luckily for Davey, the ball bounces in front of the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Davey, <b>wide</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Davey, <b>wide</b>, bumper from Faulkner and Davey ducks under it, the umpire calls it a wide as it was a little too high]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Davey, no run, just short of a good length and on off, Davey defends it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to M A Leask, no run, short and wide outside off, Leask went for the pull, but can't connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to M A Leask, no run, almost a yorker from Cummins, Leask jams it out towards point after backing away]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to M A Leask, <b>FOUR</b>, touch fuller and slightly wide outside off, Leask this time drives it through the covers and the ball runs away to the sweeper cover fence, 12 runs in 3 balls for Leask]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to M A Leask, <b>FOUR</b>, back-to-back boundaries from Leask, it was slightly wide outside off, Leask stands tall and lofts it over extra cover and the ball rockets away]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to M A Leask, <b>FOUR</b>, slightly short and wide outside off, Leask hammers it to the deep extra cover fence, the ball made a good sound off the bat as it raced away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to M A Leask, no run, short delivery well outside off, Leask goes for the pull but can't connect, the ball goes under his bat, Haddin appeals for a caught behind but there was nothing on that. He jokes afterwards by making the review signal, umpire Illingworth was confused there by that gesture]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Davey, 2 runs, banged in short and at the batsman, Davey goes for the pull, but mistimes it completely. Luckily for him, the ball clears the backtracking fielder from mid-on and the batsmen take two]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Davey, no run, short of length delivery on the stumps, Davey gets behind the line and defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Davey, no run, fuller and outside off, Davey drives it to mid-off after coming forward]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Davey, no run, back of a length delivery around off, Davey defends off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to M A Leask, 5 runs, it was on a good length and just outside off, Leask punches it to the left of mid-off and sets off, Starc moves across and collects it, he fires in the throw at the non-striker's end and since, there was no one backing up, the ball runs away to the fence for <b>four overthrows</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to M A Leask, no run, just short of a good length and just outside off, Leask hangs back, opens the face of the bat and pushes it towards point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Davey, <b>FOUR</b>, another great shot from Davey to end the over, it was full and on middle stump line, Davey flicks it in front of square and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Davey, no run, in the channel outside off, Davey leaves it for the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to M A Leask, 1 run, touch fuller and outside off, Leask mistimes the drive through extra cover and it is good enough for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Davey, 1 run, back of a length delivery on the pads, Davey flicks it uppishly towards fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to M A Leask, 1 run, 145.8kph yorker from Cummins, Leask does well to squeeze it out behind square on the on-side, the batsmen cross over]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Michael Leask, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Rob Taylor, <b>out</b> Caught by Haddin!! Another one falls for a duck, the fourth of the innings and Cummins picks up his third wicket. It was angled across off, Taylor pushes at it with laden feet, feathers it to the keeper, who snaffles it with ease. Scotland are 8 down and have not even crossed 100. <b>Rob Taylor c Haddin b P Cummins 0(6)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[P Cummins to Rob Taylor, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Davey, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a super shot from Davey, so pleasing to the eye, it was on a length and just outside off, Davey presses forward and caresses the drive to the left of mid-off, who gives chase but had no chance of cutting that off]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Davey, no run, on middle and leg, Davey clips it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Davey, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Davey punches and the ball rolls away to square leg off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Davey, no run, length delivery angled across off, Davey watches it carefully and shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Davey, no run, yorker outside off, Davey digs it out to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Davey, no run, length delivery just outside off, Davey leans forward and blocks it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Rob Taylor, no run, another one in the blockhole and just outside off, Taylor jams out the drive to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Rob Taylor, no run, yorker just outside off, Taylor stays back and does well to squeeze it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Rob Taylor, no run, back of a length delivery on middle stump, Taylor pushes it uppishly to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Davey, leg byes, 1 run, angling in on leg, Davey fails to nurdle it into the on-side, the ball rolls behind square off the pad, the batsmen sneak in a leg bye as the fielder at backward square has a shy at the striker's end, but the batsman was well in]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Davey, no run, very full and just outside off, the ball was shaping in as Davey decides to leave it, no harm done as the ball wasn't that close to the off stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Davey, no run, length delivery outside off, Davey lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Davey, 1 run, on middle and leg, Davey bunts it to the left of mid-on and sets off, the fielder runs across to his right, dives and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Davey, 2 runs, floated up outside off, Davey leans forward and drives it through the covers, Warner from cover gives chase and keeps them down to a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Davey, <b>FOUR</b>, flighted delivery on off, Davey kneels down and slog sweeps it to the deep mid-wicket fence, the ball rockets away, another good shot from Davey]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Davey, no run, flatter and outside off, Davey punches it off the toe-end of the bat back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Davey, <b>FOUR</b>, comes down the track and chips it wristily to the cow corner fence, good shot as the ball bounces just before the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Davey, no run, floated up just outside off, Davey leans forward and defends]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Rob Taylor, no run, just short of a good length and on top of off, Taylor defends it to point off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Rob Taylor, no run, length delivery angled across off, Taylor pushes at it from inside the crease, the ball beats the edge and goes through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rob Taylor, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Matthew Cross, <b>out</b> Caught by Haddin!! Cummins picks another one. Scotland have lost the plot here completely. It was another back of a length delivery outside off, Cross was poking at it, the ball takes the edge and flies to the keeper, who takes an easy catch. Scotland are 7 down now. <b>Matthew Cross c Haddin b P Cummins 9(20) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[P Cummins to Matthew Cross, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Matthew Cross, no run, touch fuller and outside off, Cross shoulders arms this time around]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Matthew Cross, <b>wide</b>, banged in short and well outside off, that ball went way over the batsman's head, easy call for the umpire, who exercises his arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Josh Davey, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Machan, <b>out</b> Caught by Faulkner!! Machan goes after a good looking 40. Scotland are slipping further here. It was a back of a length delivery on middle and leg, Machan goes across and tries to clip it into the on-side, the ball gets a little big on him and he ends up chipping it towards fine leg, where the fielder runs forward, slides and takes a good low catch. The extra pace on the ball did the trick there. <b>Machan c Faulkner b P Cummins 40(35) [4s-6]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[P Cummins to Machan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ohh dear! <b>That could have been nasty!</b> Pat Cummins was into his delivery stride and his back foot slips. Luckily, he gets up and walks back to his bowling mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Machan, no run, back of a length delivery on the stumps, Machan hangs back and defends]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pat Cummins [2.0-0-17-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now. Australia are right on top here. Scotland have lost 5 wickets already and the Aussies are not going to let the pressure slip away. Matt Machan has played well to reach 40 off just 33 balls, but the others have been extremely poor. Let's see how Scotland go after the drinks break. There is a slight drizzle in the air, but hopefully it will not turn into something substantial.]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Matthew Cross, no run, slower and shortish outside off, Cross was lining up for the cut, but chops it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Matthew Cross, no run, flighted delivery just outside off, Cross comes forward and defends it with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Matthew Cross, no run, flatter and outside off, Cross rocks back and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Matthew Cross, no run, shortish and slightly wide outside off, Cross cuts it hard, but can't beat the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Matthew Cross, no run, floated up just outside off, Cross pushes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Matthew Cross, <b>FOUR</b>, half volley from Maxwell well outside off, Cross leans forward and drills the drive through the covers, the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Machan, no run, bouncer on the stumps, Machan ducks underneath it and evades it comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Machan, 2 runs, it was the double bluff, bowls a slower ball on the stumps, Machan moves across and flicks it behind square leg for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[Johnson switches to round the wicket..]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Machan, no run, short of length on off, Machan stands up and drops it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Machan, <b>FOUR</b>, short and width on offer, Machan does not try to overhit, just cuts it over backward point, Cummins runs to his left from third man, dives and gets a hand, but can't stop it from rolling to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Machan, <b>FOUR</b>, 148.3kph short delivery, Machan goes back and pulls it in the air over the vacant square leg region. He played the West Indian kind of pull, with one leg in the air]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Machan, no run, back of a length on leg-stump, Machan walks across his stumps and fails to glance it fine, the ball goes over the sticks]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Matthew Cross, no run, flatter around off, Cross shuffles across and defends it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Machan, 1 run, goes straight on, Machan leans forward and nudges it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Machan, no run, comes down the track and drags the heave to short mid-wicket, the ball goes on the bounce to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Matthew Cross, 1 run, nice loopy delivery on middle and leg, Cross leans forward and works it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Matthew Cross, no run, trifle short and outside off, Cross cuts and finds cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Machan, 1 run, flighted on off, Machan drives it to the right of mid-on and takes off for a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Matthew Cross, no run, off-speed delivery from Johnson, Cross feels for it with laden feet, is beaten for the nth time]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Matthew Cross, no run, Cross does not want to get in-line of the delivery, the back foot goes towards the leg-side as he went for the drive away from the body. The ball beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Matthew Cross, no run, follows the short one with a pitched up delivery, Cross drives with feet stuck in cement, the ball fizzes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Matthew Cross, no run, lifter on the stumps, Cross was not in any position to play that. Fortunately, for him it sails over him and thuds into Haddin's gloves]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Matthew Cross, <b>FOUR</b>, pitched up outside off, Cross stays in the crease, opens the bat face and drives it to the left of backward point, the pace of Johnson takes it to the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[Three slips, a gully and short leg in place now...]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Matthew Cross, no run, back of a length outside off, left alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Machan, 2 runs, floated up outside off, Machan leans into the drive and gets it past the diving cover, but there is a fielder in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Machan, no run, low full toss, Machan mistimes the drive, drags it to short mid-wicket off the inside part]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Matthew Cross, <b>4 wides</b>, some turn for Maxwell, it pitches on leg-stump and spins away, Haddin is blinded by the batsman and doesn't gather the ball. Maxwell is not pleased with the umpire's call as he felt it was very close to the leg-stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Matthew Cross, no run, slower and on the stumps, Cross pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and short cover in place..]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Matthew Cross, no run, fired across the right-hander from round the wicket, Cross goes for it, is lucky not to have edged it]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Matthew Cross, no run, flighted around off, Cross defends to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Matthew Cross, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Berrington, <b>out</b> Caught by Warner!! Maxwell strikes with his very first delivery. Berrington puts his head down and is a bit late to make his way back to the pavilion. It was nothing but a long half volley outside off, Berrington reaches out and slices it to cover-point, where Warner accepts the catch gleefully. <b>Berrington c Warner b Maxwell 1(6)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Maxwell to Berrington, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Glenn Maxwell, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Berrington, 1 run, short and at the batsman's chest, Berrington fends it awkwardly, the ball hit the glove and runs down to third man. In fact, it deflected onto the helmet before going to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Berrington, no run, dug in midway down the track, Berrington sways away, drops his gloves and lets it go through to Haddin]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Berrington, no run, bit too straight, Berrington taps it gently to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Berrington, no run, short of length and on the body, Berrington plays it with soft hands, the ball hits the shoulder of the bat and dribbles to the left of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Berrington, no run, back of a length close to off, Berrington brings his bat inside the line and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Richie Berrington, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Coleman, <b>out</b> Caught by Clarke!! This is just too good for the Scottish batsmen. Superb take from the Australian skipper. Short of a length around off, Coleman looks to force it through the off-side, no real feet movement, the outside edge flies to the right of second slip, Clarke dives and hangs on to an excellent take. Third duck of the innings for Scotland. <b>Coleman c Clarke b Johnson 0(7)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Johnson to Coleman, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Coleman, <b>wide</b>, short and down leg, called a wide for the line]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Machan, no run, punched off the back foot to a shortish mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Machan, no run, shortens the length on off, Machan guides it to backward point and shouts "no" for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Machan, no run, targets the stumps, Machan goes back and turns it gently to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Machan, <b>FOUR</b>, magnificent shot! Machan not afraid to play his shots. It was a good length delivery just outside off, Machan presses slightly forward and lofts it through the line, sends it over mid-on and one bounce into the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Machan, 2 runs, shortish on middle and leg, Machan gets inside the line and pulls it with one leg in the air behind square leg, Smith does the tidying up]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Machan, no run, on a length close to off, Machan bunts it in front of backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Coleman, no run, short of length on off, Coleman stands tall and punches it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Coleman, no run, short delivery on off, Coleman arches back and gets away from the line. He dropped his gloves as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Coleman, no run, back of a length on middle and leg, Coleman tucks it in front of square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Coleman, no run, back of a length close to off, Coleman middles the punch and finds Warner at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[Three slips in place for Johnson..]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Coleman, no run, good length ball on off, Coleman stays in the crease and defends off the outer half to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Coleman, no run, short of length in the channel around off, Coleman hangs his bat away from the body, the ball whizzes past the outside edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Johnson, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Machan, <b>FOUR</b>, pitched up just outside off, Machan lifts it over the mid-off fielder, he didn't time it that well, but the ball had enough fuel to reach the fence. Faulkner runs behind the ball and comes second]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Machan, 2 runs, banged in midway down the wicket, Machan swivels on the back foot and pulls it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Machan, no run, back of a length around off, Machan mistimes the punch to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Freddie Coleman, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Mommsen, <b>out</b> Caught by Starc!! The Scottish captain goes without troubling the scorers. It was a short delivery, right at the batsman, Mommsen takes it on, can't roll his wrist to keep it down, top-edges the pull towards backward square, Starc runs to his left from short fine to complete an easy catch. Scotland in all sorts of trouble now. <b>Mommsen c Starc b Watson 0(2)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Watson to Mommsen, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Mommsen, no run, good length ball on off, Mommsen defends solidly to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Machan, 1 run, angled across the left-hander, Machan steers it to square third man, Starc keeps it down to a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Preston Mommsen, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to MacLeod, <b>out</b> Caught by Warner!! There he goes! MacLeod has been getting in and getting out. And this time he falls to a poor delivery. Short and well wide of off, bowled at <b>150.6kph</b>, MacLeod does not get on top of the bounce, can't control the cut and hits it to backward point, Warner leaps up and pouches it comfortably. <b>MacLeod c Warner b Starc 22(19) [4s-5]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to MacLeod, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to MacLeod, no run, ripper of a delivery! Short delivery right at the batsman's throat, MacLeod was shaping up to play that, but does well to arch back and sway away from the line of the delivery. He almost smelled the leather there]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to MacLeod, no run, back of a length on leg-stump, MacLeod fails to connect with the flick, wears it on the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Machan, 1 run, short of length on off and middle, Machan nudges it touch uppishly to the vacant mid-wicket region]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to MacLeod, 1 run, slanted across the right-hander, MacLeod glides it with an open bat face to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to MacLeod, <b>FOUR</b>, terrific shot! He has dug out a yorker for a boundary. It was on leg-stump, MacLeod gets his front leg out of the way and squeeze it behind square, backward square dives to his right in vain and Cummins comes second in the chase]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Machan, no run, good length ball on off, Machan prefers to hang back and bunt it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Machan, <b>FOUR</b>, superb shot! Tad overpitched and on off, Machan presses forward and drills it to the left of Watto, he beat the mid-on fielder as well, the timing keeps taking it away from the chasing fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Machan, no run, back of a length on off, Machan stays beside the line and knocks it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to MacLeod, 1 run, on a length close to off, MacLeod presses forward and dabs it with an angled past the diving backward point fielder, single down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[Only one slip in place..]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to MacLeod, no run, shortish and outside off, MacLeod cuts and finds Warner at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to MacLeod, no run, back of a length around off, MacLeod plays the short-arm punch to backward point, picks out the fielder there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Watson, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Machan, no run, good length ball on off, Machan turns it gently to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Machan, no run, loud shout for lbw, umpire Illingworth says not-out. That looked plumb to the naked eye. Australians contemplate a review, but decide against it. It was full and tails back in, Machan stays in the crease and goes for the flick, he might have got an inside edge, need a review to confirm that. Unless, he hit it, that was cannoning into middle and leg.]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Machan, no run, well directed short delivery, it was right at Machan, he jumps back in the crease and fends it awkwardly, the ball pops up and falls in no-man's land. There was a fielder at short mid-wicket, but he was removed and placed at cover after the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Machan, <b>wide</b>, splays it down leg, Machan shuffles across and lets it pass, easy call for the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Machan, <b>FOUR</b>, fabulous shot! It was not a bad delivery, but a top shot from Machan. On a length just outside off, Machan comes half-forward and drives it on-the-up through cover, the sweet timing takes it to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Machan, no run, back of a length on the stumps, Machan goes back and across, defends to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Machan, 2 runs, short of length and on the ribs, Machan gets inside the line and tucks it in the air wide of the square leg. That is the second time, he has chipped the ball uppishly]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to MacLeod, no run, Cummins goes short, bangs it in halfway down the wicket, MacLeod sits under it and lets it go through to Haddin]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to MacLeod, <b>FOUR</b>, MacLeod is peppering the square boundary. This is also now MacLeod's highest score in this World Cup. Full and plenty of width on offer, MacLeod throws his bat and slices it over point, the ball hurries to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to MacLeod, no run, pitched up around off, MacLeod push-drives it back to Cummins]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to MacLeod, no run, good length ball around off, MacLeod gets right behind the line and defends back down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to MacLeod, <b>FOUR</b>, MacLeod is looking in terrific touch. But, how long will it last? It was overpitched outside off, MacLeod gets a good stride forward, bends his front leg and drives it to the right of backward point for his third boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Machan, 1 run, lobbed over the fielder! Full and on the stumps, Machan stays in the crease, is early into the shot, chips it over square leg, Maxwell runs back but can't get there in time to hang onto the catch]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Machan, 1 run, first runs off Starc, welcomes the new batsman with a yorker, Machan digs it out to the unmanned cover region and opens his account]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Matt Machan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Coetzer, <b>out</b> Caught by S Smith!! Consecutive ducks for Coetzer! He never looked at ease and Starc puts an end to his misery. The umpire checks for a no-ball, but Starc is fine. It was back of a length and outside off, Coetzer goes for the slash away from the body, the outside edge goes at a good height to Smith at third slip. <b>Coetzer c S Smith b Starc 0(11)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to Coetzer, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Coetzer, no run, then comes the bouncer, Coetzer sinks under it and allows the ball to sail over him]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Coetzer, no run, edged and doesn't carry! Starc goes full and outside off, Coetzer drives it away from the body, the ball takes the outside edge and goes on the bounce to Smith at third slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Coetzer, no run, shortens the length on off, Coetzer defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Coetzer, no run, back of a length and angled across off, Coetzer looks to force it off the back foot, no footwork and the ball fizzes past the outside edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to MacLeod, <b>FOUR</b>, poor bowling from Cummins, once more goes short and wide, MacLeod makes him pay, stands tall and slaps it through the vacant cover-point region. The pace of Cummins takes it to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to MacLeod, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! This time MacLeod doesn't miss out on putting away the bad delivery, short and outside off, MacLeod cuts it in front of square, no cover fielder and the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to MacLeod, no run, <b>edged and safe!</b> It was not all that short, MacLeod goes for a cut with laden feet, the ball keeps low and takes the under edge, doesn't carry to Haddin. The Snicko shows a spike as the ball went past the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips and a gully in place...]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to MacLeod, no run, yorker aimed at the base of off-stump, MacLeod jams it down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to MacLeod, no run, plenty of room on offer, MacLeod moves forward and frees his arms, slaps it straight to backward point, Smith fields it easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to MacLeod, no run, nice juicy full toss, MacLeod misses out on that, he push-drives it back to the bowler. He could have hit it anywhere, but it straight back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pat Cummins, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Coetzer, no run, short of length on middle, Coetzer stays behind it and blocks it to the right of the bowler. Excellent over to start off by Starc]]></line><line><![CDATA[Clarke strengthens the slip cordon, he brings in another fielder..]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Coetzer, no run, another flashing short by Coetzer, short and outside off, Coetzer goes for the slash, but fails to make contact]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Coetzer, no run, toe-crushing yorker, Coetzer almost falls over as he digs it out, he does well to bring his bat down in time and squeeze it to square leg. Had he missed that, it was right on the stumps, would have been out lbw or bowled]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Coetzer, no run, back of a length on off, Coetzer gets right behind the line and defends it down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Coetzer, no run, bit of width on offer, Coetzer throws his bat at it, the ball bounces a touch extra and zips past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Coetzer, no run, starts off with a good short delivery, right on middle and leg, Coetzer ducks and evades it comfortably. Nice carry through to Haddin, who takes it head high]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Coetzer and MacLeod are at the crease. Coetzer is on strike. Starc will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players are out in the middle. The countdown begins. Starc has the bowl in hand. He has couple of slips to assist him..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Scotland</b> (Playing XI): Calum MacLeod, Kyle Coetzer, Matt Machan, Preston Mommsen(c), Freddie Coleman, Richie Berrington, Matthew Cross(w), Josh Davey, Rob Taylor, Michael Leask, Iain Wardlaw]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Australia</b> (Playing XI): Aaron Finch, David Warner, Steven Smith, Michael Clarke(c), Glenn Maxwell, Shane Watson, James Faulkner, Brad Haddin(w), Mitchell Johnson, Mitchell Starc, Pat Cummins]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mommsen:</b> 'We were going to have a bat first (if he had won the toss). It's a great wicket and we played here the other night. We want to get the runs on the board. It should play well the whole game, so we want to get first use of it and put the runs on the board (on the pitch). It's very exciting, I don't think it gets much better than this for us (on playing against Australia). There have been some really good efforts throughout the tournament, we haven't seen a full package from our team and hopefully, we can see that today. Nice to get a few runs, I think myself and Freddie (Coleman) put a nice partnership in the last game. Hopefully, we can do the same today.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Clarke:</b> 'We are going to have a <b>bowl</b>. I think it is a fantastic wicket, there is some rain forecast and that's our main reason for bowling. I think the ground is in a fantastic condition, we are in for a great game. It's a tough one, the selectors have gone for their best eleven, what they feel is the best eleven to win this game against Scotland (on getting the combination right). I think that's the right decision. It's a tough one to bat first or bowl first. Obviously, I would have liked to bat first, so our batters can get a hit, but the number one priority is to win the game. I think we have seen throughout the tournament that you can't take the team lightly. Scotland have played some really good competitive cricket and we have got to be at our best. We have gone for Cummins in for Doherty, that's our only change.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Australia have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Remember, <b>if it's a washout, Australia will finish 3rd</b> in Pool A, since both Sri Lanka and Australia will be tied on 8 points, but Sri Lanka have 4 wins and Australia will only have 3. Sri Lanka will finish higher than Australia and we will see an Australia-South Africa clash in the quarter-finals.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-Head:</b> Both Australia and Scotland have played 4 ODIs against each other, with Australia winning all those games. In fact, in their last 3 meetings, the Aussies have at least scored 334.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pitch Report:</b> 'The Scots should feel at home with the kind of weather we have today. This is a really good batting track, it is pretty hard, there is a nice covering of grass, but nothing as such to trouble the batsmen. It looks like a flat pitch, if Australia bat first they should score at least 350,' reckons <b>Mark Waugh</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Hello folks! My co-commentator <b>Akshay Maanay</b> and I, <b>Sidhant Maheshwari</b>, will be with you for the entire duration of the game. We will have the toss and teams in a short while. Stay tuned.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather report:</b> The conditions are quite overcast right now, with a <b>few showers predicted later</b> in the day. It could well turn out to be a start-stop day. Luckily, it's not raining right now and we should start right on time. The maximum temperature is expected to be around 22 degrees Celsius today.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Team News:</b> Australia have already named their playing eleven. They have made only one change to their winning combination against Sri Lanka, with <b>Xavier Doherty giving way to Pat Cummins</b>. For Scotland, there is still no place for Majid Haq, who was sent home after he claimed that his exclusion from the team was racially motivated. They could probably field an unchanged side.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Australia</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Australia have been in terrific form in the past few games. Apart from their loss against New Zealand, a game that went down right to the wire, Australia have been very dominant in their other games. Also, their game against Bangladesh was washed out without a ball being bowled. Their biggest win came against Afghanistan, where they went on to make 417 batting first, the highest score in World Cup history. In reply, Afghanistan folded for 142 and Australia won that game by a mammoth 275-run margin.]]></line><line><![CDATA[In their last match against Sri Lanka, riding on Maxwell's century and fifties from Smith, Clarke and Watson, Australia scored 376 in their 50 overs. In reply, with a ton from Sanga and fifties from Dilshan and Chandimal, Sri Lanka were well on their way to achieve the target. They were 283/4 at one stage, but the Australian bowlers came back strongly, taking 5 wickets for 29 runs and in the end, Australia won by 64 runs. Now, they will look to continue their good form and they'll be hoping that all the players have a good outing in the middle.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Scotland</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Scotland have not won a single game in this World Cup or the previous editions they have participated in. The closest they got to a World Cup win was in their game against Afghanistan, a game that Afghanistan won by a solitary wicket. They gave New Zealand a tough fight in a low-scoring encounter, but were comprehensively beaten by England and Sri Lanka. Even though they managed a total of 318 against Bangladesh, it wasn't enough as Bangladesh recorded the second highest successful run-chase in World Cup history.]]></line><line><![CDATA[With the kind of form Australia are in, it will be very difficult for them to pull off an upset here, but at least they can go out of the World Cup with a good showing against one of the best teams in the world. In their last game against Sri Lanka, their captain Preston Mommsen and Freddie Coleman, both registered fifties, but Scotland lost 6 wickets for 53 runs and were eventually bowled out for 215. Their problem has been that they haven't clicked as a unit, they have had some great individual performances but nothing to show for as a unit. Today, they will be looking to change that.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>13:15 Local Time, 02:15 GMT, 07:45 IST:</b> Australia and Scotland will lock horns in Hobart in what is going to be a dead rubber. This is the last Pool game for both the sides and for Scotland, this is going to be their last game of the World Cup. Australia would ideally want their players to spend quality time in the middle before the knockouts. On the other hand, Scotland have not won a game yet and their priority will be to put up a fight against the mighty Aussies. Let's take a look at how both the teams have done so far.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/><br/>Though a statistical mismatch, Australia's final Pool A game against Scotland at Bellerive Oval in Hobart gives them the opportunity to polish the rough edges around their campaign in the ICC Cricket World Cup 2015 so far. Still searching for their first victory in World Cups, Scotland return home irrespective of the result but will hope to put up a stronger display than they have during the course of the tournament.<br/><br/><b>Venue:</b> Bellerive Oval, Hobart<br/><br/><b>Date:</b> March 14, 2015<br/><br/><b>Time:</b> 0900 Hrs IST<br/><br/><b>Weather:</b> A maximum of 21 degrees with showers predicted in the afternoon<br/><br/><b>Team news</b><br/><br/><b>Australia</b><br/><br/>Despite putting up dominant performances against England and Sri Lanka, Australia haven't looked like their usual self yet, and their defeat to New Zealand and the rained out game with Bangladesh means some of the players haven't spent enough time in the middle. Australia captain Michael Clarke has indicated that the batting order will be shuffled around to let some of his players get a decent hit in the middle, which may see the captain himself come in at No 3, especially if Scotland decide to bat first on winning the toss.<br/><br/>Australia have already announced their XI for the game with Pat Cummins replacing left-arm spinner Xavier Doherty, who had played in the previous game against Sri Lanka in Sydney. There, however, continues to be no place for local boy George Bailey, who was left out of the side since Clarke returned to the side.<br/><br/><b>Probable XI:</b> Aaron Finch, David Warner, Michael Clarke (capt), Steven Smith, Shane Watson, James Faulkner, Glenn Maxwell, Brad Haddin, Mitchell Johnson, Mitchell Starc, Pat Cummins.<br/><br/><b>Scotland</b><br/><br/>Scotland came agonizingly close to recording their first-ever World Cup win against Afghanistan but with just one more game to be played and that too against Australia, the elusive first victory will have to wait. The last time they played Australia in the World Cup was way back in 1999 when the to-be champions had a bit of a stutter, and Scotland would seek inspiration from that game to instill some confidence in themselves.<br/><br/>Despite suffering heavy defeats, some of Scotland's players have thrived on the big stage with impressive performances. Until Trent Boult took a couple of wickets against Bangladesh on Friday, Scotland medium-pacer Josh Davey was leading the bowling charts for the tournament, which they should be proud of. Kyle Coetzer has trailed off since his 156 against Bangladesh, but will look for one last flourish in this campaign.<br/><br/>Majid Haq's controversial removal from the squad after his omission from Scotland's last game should not affect the make-up of the team, which in all likelihood will remain unchanged against Australia.<br/><br/><b>Probable XI:</b> Kyle Coetzer, Calum MacLeod, Matt Machan, Preston Mommsen (capt), Freddie Coleman, Richie Berrington, Michael Leask, Matthew Cross (wk), Rob Taylor, Josh Davey, Alasdair Evans<br/><br/><b>Watch out for</b><br/><br/><b>James Faulkner</b> has had a quiet World Cup so far, especially after missing the first few games with injury. He has been steady with the ball but hasn't had enough time in the middle with the bat and was run out first ball against Sri Lanka. A promotion up the order could be likely and it may just be the fillip Faulkner needs ahead of the knockout stages of the competition.<br/><br/>After scoring a half-century in his first World Cup game, <b>Matt Machan</b> has failed to convert the starts he has got in the subsequent matches, and against Australia he will look to correct that. Machan has looked comfortable against both pace and spin and looked solid, but the 24-year-old will hope to impress against the toughest set of bowlers he has come up against yet.<br/><br/><b>Quotes</b><br/><br/>"I think we'd be silly to pick our team today for the World Cup quarter-final. We don't know what we're going to get in Adelaide, we don't know what the wicket will be like; we still don't know who we will be playing against." - <b>Michael Clarke</b> is not looking too far ahead in the ICC Cricket World Cup.<br/><br/><b>Stats</b><br/><br/>The last time Australia and Scotland played in a World Cup was back in 1999. Australia won that game by six wickets at Worcester. Australia coach Darren Lehmann had played in that game and was out for a second ball duck.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Scotland</b> (From): Kyle Coetzer, Calum MacLeod, Matt Machan, Preston Mommsen(c), Freddie Coleman, Richie Berrington, Michael Leask, Matthew Cross(k), Rob Taylor, Josh Davey, Alasdair Evans, Hamish Gardiner, Safyaan Sharif, Iain Wardlaw]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Australia</b> (From): Aaron Finch, David Warner, Steven Smith, Michael Clarke(c), Shane Watson, Glenn Maxwell, James Faulkner, Brad Haddin(k), Mitchell Johnson, Mitchell Starc, Pat Cummins, Josh Hazlewood, George Bailey, Xavier Doherty, Mitchell Marsh]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>130</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>10</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>25.4</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Scotland">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1415</playerid>
					<name>Kyle Coetzer</name>
					<batsman-name>K Coetzer</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Coetzer</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Starc</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7710</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Steven Smith</fielder>
						<fielderId>2250</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1416</playerid>
					<name>Calum MacLeod</name>
					<batsman-name>C MacLeod</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>MacLeod</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>22</runs>
					<balls>19</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Starc</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7710</bowlerId>
						<fielder>David Warner</fielder>
						<fielderId>1739</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6565</playerid>
					<name>Matt Machan</name>
					<batsman-name>M Machan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Machan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>40</runs>
					<balls>35</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Pat Cummins</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8095</bowlerId>
						<fielder>James Faulkner</fielder>
						<fielderId>7789</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6744</playerid>
					<name>Preston Mommsen</name>
					<batsman-name>P Mommsen</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mommsen</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Watson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>158</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mitchell Starc</fielder>
						<fielderId>7710</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9318</playerid>
					<name>Freddie Coleman</name>
					<batsman-name>F Coleman</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Coleman</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Johnson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>496</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Michael Clarke</fielder>
						<fielderId>138</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1398</playerid>
					<name>Richie Berrington</name>
					<batsman-name>R Berrington</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Berrington</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Maxwell</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7662</bowlerId>
						<fielder>David Warner</fielder>
						<fielderId>1739</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9365</playerid>
					<name>Matthew Cross</name>
					<batsman-name>M Cross</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Matthew Cross</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>20</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Pat Cummins</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8095</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Brad Haddin</fielder>
						<fielderId>159</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6657</playerid>
					<name>Josh Davey</name>
					<batsman-name>J Davey</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Davey</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>26</runs>
					<balls>35</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>M Starc</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7710</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8327</playerid>
					<name>Rob Taylor</name>
					<batsman-name>R Taylor</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rob Taylor</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Pat Cummins</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8095</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Brad Haddin</fielder>
						<fielderId>159</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9383</playerid>
					<name>Michael Leask</name>
					<batsman-name>M A Leask</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M A Leask</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>23</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8423</playerid>
					<name>Iain Wardlaw</name>
					<batsman-name>Iain Wardlaw</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Iain Wardlaw</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>M Starc</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7710</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1415</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>8</runs>
				<overs>2.5</overs>
				<batsman>Kyle Coetzer</batsman>
				<batsman-name>K Coetzer</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1416</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>36</runs>
				<overs>6.6</overs>
				<batsman>Calum MacLeod</batsman>
				<batsman-name>C MacLeod</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6744</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>37</runs>
				<overs>7.3</overs>
				<batsman>Preston Mommsen</batsman>
				<batsman-name>P Mommsen</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9318</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>50</runs>
				<overs>10.1</overs>
				<batsman>Freddie Coleman</batsman>
				<batsman-name>F Coleman</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1398</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>51</runs>
				<overs>11.1</overs>
				<batsman>Richie Berrington</batsman>
				<batsman-name>R Berrington</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6565</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>78</runs>
				<overs>16.2</overs>
				<batsman>Matt Machan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Machan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9365</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>79</runs>
				<overs>16.4</overs>
				<batsman>Matthew Cross</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Cross</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8327</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>95</runs>
				<overs>20.1</overs>
				<batsman>Rob Taylor</batsman>
				<batsman-name>R Taylor</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6657</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>130</runs>
				<overs>25.2</overs>
				<batsman>Josh Davey</batsman>
				<batsman-name>J Davey</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8423</playerid>
				<nbr>10</nbr>
				<runs>130</runs>
				<overs>25.4</overs>
				<batsman>Iain Wardlaw</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Iain Wardlaw</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>8</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>9</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Australia">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7710</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
					<bowler-name>M Starc</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Starc</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4.4</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>14</runsoff>
					<wickets>4</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8095</playerid>
					<name>Pat Cummins</name>
					<bowler-name>Pat Cummins</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>P Cummins</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>42</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>158</playerid>
					<name>Shane Watson</name>
					<bowler-name>Watson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Watson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>18</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>496</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Johnson</name>
					<bowler-name>Johnson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Johnson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>16</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7662</playerid>
					<name>Glenn Maxwell</name>
					<bowler-name>Maxwell</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Maxwell</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>24</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>4</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7789</playerid>
					<name>James Faulkner</name>
					<bowler-name>Faulkner</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Faulkner</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>15</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1643</playerid>
					<name>Aaron Finch</name>
					<bowler-name>Finch</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Finch</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1739</playerid>
					<name>David Warner</name>
					<bowler-name>Warner</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Warner</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2250</playerid>
					<name>Steven Smith</name>
					<bowler-name>S Smith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Smith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>138</playerid>
					<name>Michael Clarke</name>
					<bowler-name>Clarke</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Clarke</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>159</playerid>
					<name>Brad Haddin</name>
					<bowler-name>Haddin</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Haddin</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>133</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>3</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>15.2</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Australia">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>138</playerid>
					<name>Michael Clarke</name>
					<batsman-name>Clarke</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Clarke</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>47</runs>
					<balls>47</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Iain Wardlaw</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8423</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Michael Leask</fielder>
						<fielderId>9383</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1643</playerid>
					<name>Aaron Finch</name>
					<batsman-name>Finch</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Finch</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>20</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>R Taylor</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8327</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Freddie Coleman</fielder>
						<fielderId>9318</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>158</playerid>
					<name>Shane Watson</name>
					<batsman-name>Watson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Watson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>24</runs>
					<balls>23</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>J Davey</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6657</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Matthew Cross</fielder>
						<fielderId>9365</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7789</playerid>
					<name>James Faulkner</name>
					<batsman-name>Faulkner</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Faulkner</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>16</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1739</playerid>
					<name>David Warner</name>
					<batsman-name>Warner</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Warner</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>21</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2250</playerid>
					<name>Steven Smith</name>
					<batsman-name>S Smith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Smith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7662</playerid>
					<name>Glenn Maxwell</name>
					<batsman-name>Maxwell</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Maxwell</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>159</playerid>
					<name>Brad Haddin</name>
					<batsman-name>Haddin</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Haddin</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>496</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Johnson</name>
					<batsman-name>Johnson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Johnson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7710</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
					<batsman-name>M Starc</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Starc</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8095</playerid>
					<name>Pat Cummins</name>
					<batsman-name>Pat Cummins</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>P Cummins</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1643</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>30</runs>
				<overs>3.6</overs>
				<batsman>Aaron Finch</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Finch</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>158</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>88</runs>
				<overs>12.6</overs>
				<batsman>Shane Watson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Watson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>138</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>92</runs>
				<overs>13.2</overs>
				<batsman>Michael Clarke</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Clarke</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>5</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Scotland">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8423</playerid>
					<name>Iain Wardlaw</name>
					<bowler-name>Iain Wardlaw</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Iain Wardlaw</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>57</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8327</playerid>
					<name>Rob Taylor</name>
					<bowler-name>R Taylor</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rob Taylor</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>29</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6657</playerid>
					<name>Josh Davey</name>
					<bowler-name>J Davey</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Davey</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>38</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9383</playerid>
					<name>Michael Leask</name>
					<bowler-name>M A Leask</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M A Leask</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0.2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>7</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1416</playerid>
					<name>Calum MacLeod</name>
					<bowler-name>C MacLeod</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>MacLeod</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1415</playerid>
					<name>Kyle Coetzer</name>
					<bowler-name>K Coetzer</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Coetzer</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6565</playerid>
					<name>Matt Machan</name>
					<bowler-name>M Machan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Machan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6744</playerid>
					<name>Preston Mommsen</name>
					<bowler-name>P Mommsen</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mommsen</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9318</playerid>
					<name>Freddie Coleman</name>
					<bowler-name>F Coleman</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Coleman</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1398</playerid>
					<name>Richie Berrington</name>
					<bowler-name>R Berrington</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Berrington</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9365</playerid>
					<name>Matthew Cross</name>
					<bowler-name>M Cross</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Matthew Cross</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



