<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="12898" >
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>2nd Quarter-Final</gameDesc>
		<series>WC 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Bangladesh</home>
		<away>India</away>
		<teamsabbr>BAN vs IND</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>BAN</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>IND</awayabbr>
		<homeId>6</homeId>
		<awayId>2</awayId>
		<venue>Melbourne Cricket Ground, Melbourne</venue>
		<startdate>19 03 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>19 03 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>India</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>India won by 109 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>India</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>109</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Aleem Dar</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Ian Gould</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Steve Davis</Name>
			<Country>Aus</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Roshan Mahanama</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>03:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150319112030</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>Ban</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>Ind</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>193</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>10</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>45</batteamovers>
		<status>India won by 109 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>8548</playerid>
			<name>Taskin Ahmed*</name>
			<batsman-name>Taskin Ahmed</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Taskin Ahmed</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>0</runs>
			<balls-faced>0</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
			<batsman>
				<name />
				<runs />
				<balls-faced />
				<fours />
				<sixes />
			</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>8181</playerid>
			<name>Mohit Sharma*</name>
			<bowler-name>Mohit Sharma</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Mohit Sharma</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>7</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>36</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1858</playerid>
			<name>Umesh Yadav</name>
			<bowler-name>Umesh</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>U Yadav</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>9</overs>
			<maidens>1</maidens>
			<runs>31</runs>
			<wickets>4</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>303</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>8231</playerid>
<name>Sabbir Rahman</name>
<player-runs>30</player-runs>
<player-balls>40</player-balls>
<runs>193</runs>
<wicket-nbr>10</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>1858</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Umesh</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>1</byes>
			<wides>8</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>10</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[. 4 . . . 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 B1 . 4 4 W <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 1 . 1 . W <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 . . W . W ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_WC/BAN_IND_MAR19/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[So then, two teams have punched their tickets to the semi-finals. We have a big game coming up tomorrow. It's co-hosts Australia taking on Pakistan at the Adelaide Oval and the winner will play India at the SCG in the semi-final. It's going be a cracking game. Don't miss the action. We'll be up nice and early. For now, goodbye!]]></line><line><![CDATA[India strolled into the semi-final stage of the 2015 Cricket World Cup. Here's how twitter reacted: ]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@narendramodi</b>:  Excellent game, excellent performance! Congrats yet again Team India.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@glennmcgrath11</b>: Well played @BCCI on a convincing win over @BCBtigers Both quarter finals have been one sided. Will the trend continue tomorrow? ]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@cricketaakash</b>:  70 wickets in 7 matches...India bowling has been the unlikely hero of this World Cup. Kudos.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@sanjaymanjrekar</b>:  Rohit Sharma comes of age with that 100...extremely mature innings.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@bhogleharsha</b>: 100 ODI wins for Dhoni. Time to salute him.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@fwildecricket</b>:  #Ind meanwhile are playing staggeringly good cricket, they're an awesome tournament team.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhoni</b>: "It has been good. Definitely we can't shy away from the fact that we are playing some good cricket. But also at the same time, not to forget, maybe a month back, we were struggling when it came to the ODI format also. I think a lot of credit needs to go to the bowlers and the support staff, but at the same time I think individually everyone had to lift himself up. The good thing in this tournament so far is if you see, there are not many players from our side who are in the top run-scorers list, but still we have scored runs. So I am happy with overall how we are performing. That (bowling opponents out) was an area we wanted to improve, that was a bit of a concern for us. I think in this tournament so far, the bowlers have done the job well. Even the last time when we were in South Africa or New Zealand, that was one area where we were struggling. The good thing is even if we don't get wickets with the new ball - that has happened only in a couple of games (Manjrekar interrupted him before he could complete the sentence). It's difficult. You can't just pinpoint and say this is what has really changed (in the bowling). You see batsmen who have not scored runs and in 15 minutes time, they are in the best of form. So in cricket there are a lot of abstracts, but you have to keep doing the small things and keep putting the intensity into the net sessions and everything shapes up. <b>Well, fluke happens</b> (talking about the catch he took to dismiss Soumya Sarkar)! I think it was an important catch. It was a decent partnership going at that point and they were scoring at a good pace. So it was important for us to take that wicket. I thought it was a bit away from me and I just dived and the ball came and sat into my hands more than anything else. It feels good when you take a brilliant catch, slightly different from a normal catch that you take as a wicket-keeper. I think a lot of it is because of how cricket is played (when asked what do you think is the reason for teams easily getting to 300). With the 5th fielder being inside, with the T20 coming in, the approach of the batsmen have changed. Especially when you have wickets in hand, what we have seen is, in the last few overs they can score a lot of runs. If luck is on your side and maybe if the wicket is slightly on the drier side, you may get a bit of reverse swing and it may hold on a bit. But, if there's nothing, more often than not on good wickets, you will see big runs. What really matters is, if you are able to take regular wickets in the middle overs, if not then 300 is something the opposition will definitely score."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mortaza</b>: "It could have been (when asked if toss was crucial). We would have liked to bat first as well, but can't explain. Rubel (Hossain) was bowling really well and also Shakib (Al Hasan). They had a good partnership, but we couldn't go through. 300 is always a difficult ask to chase, 280 could have been much better for the batters. I think, except today, they should be happy (on how the supporters should judge Bangladesh's performance in the World Cup). Because most of our players have played just two or three ODIs. They are starting their careers. I think the boys should be very happy with their effort. Everyone back home should be happy as well. Lot of cricket coming on, so hopefully we will carry on from here. The way we are performing at the moment, we don't have enough experience to play in these sort of conditions. But the way we played, once we go back home, we know how we have to play there. So hopefully, this year will be very exciting for us. Thanks to all the supporters. They came in and supported us throughout the tournament, so thank you."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajaraman</b> sums up India's performance in one sentence: 'It was lovely watching India batting with professionalism and not arrogance and bowling & fielding with intensity']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit</b>: "I think it (the knock) will be right up, because it came at an important situation when the team needed the most. I was determined, I wanted to bat as long as possible to put the team into a good situation and then bowlers did a fantastic job as they were doing in the league stages. Batting at the top of the order, it's always important to get big hundreds. I've been given that role to bat up the order, so I wanted to make the most out of it whenever I go in to bat. I tried to do that today and I am happy with the way we performed as a team today. Bowlers are taking wickets, batsmen are scoring runs, we just need to carry this momentum into the semis now. We have spoken a lot about how momentum plays a huge role in winning tournaments. I hope this is one-off and we have two more games to go now, hopefully we can carry the same momentum with us as we did today. We just need to do what we've been doing. We are doing the right things on the field. When it comes to batting, we are creating big partnerships and bowlers are bowling well in tandem and taking wickets, which is very important in any format."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit Sharma</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his <b>126-ball 137</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[India will take on either Australia or Pakistan in the semi-final at the SCG. On the other hand, Bangladesh played with spunk and spirit in the mega event, but it was always going to be an uphill task to take on one of the in-form sides of the tournament, India, and on expected lines, they lost the match.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Suresh Raina played his part as well by cracking some powerful shots to help India to up the ante after they found themselves in a spot of bother. For Bangladesh, Shakib Al Hasan and Rubel Hossain put up a fine show during the middle part of the innings. Rubel teasing and tempting Virat Kohli outside the off-stump before he produced the edge to snaffle his wicket has to be one of the highlights of the day. But Raina and Rohit took the game away from the grasp of Bangladesh. To make it worse for them, Rohit was caught off a no-ball for height but on replays, it was clear that the full toss was bowled below the waist.]]></line><line><![CDATA[In fact, even Ravichandran Ashwin and Ravindra Jadeja shone brightly with the ball in hand. With subtle variations of drift, Ashwin kept the batsmen in check. In this tournament, Ashwin has struck to the old maxim of using the off-spinner as the stock delivery. He has also used the drifter. The fielding too was sharp. Earlier, Rohit Sharma played with royal flourish to pierce through the minutest of gaps with surgical precision to compose a marvellous hundred. Rohit started his innings with a flurry of boundaries before he was forced to hold the innings together as a result of India losing their way in the middle overs. The sublime art and craft of Rohit's batsmanship can be encapsulated by how he expertly guided Taskin Ahmed through the third man region for a delectable boundary in the 39th over. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[It was Umesh Yadav, who produced the initial breakthrough by sending the dangerous Tamim Iqbal back to the pavilion. Shami then followed it up by taking a couple of wickets to put India in a position of strength. Interestingly, Shami has used the short ball superbly in this tournament and today, he took the wicket of Mahmudullah with it. Mushfiqur Rahim and Sabbir Rahman showed self-belief to essay decent knocks, but by then, India had all but won the game. Umesh ended up with four wickets and Shami two.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[India's bowlers put up a thoroughly professional performance to bundle out the opposition for a modest score and reach the semi-finals of the World Cup. With this victory, MS Dhoni has now captained India to 100 wins in the ODI format. Dhoni also has led his country to 11 consecutive victories in World Cups. To make it a great day for India, they have now bowled out seven teams in a row and Mohammed Shami with 17 wickets to his name, is the leading wicket-taker in this World Cup. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Indian team is very happy as they walk off the field. The Bangladeshi players come down to shake hands with their opponents.]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to S Rahman, <b>out</b> Caught by Shami!! <b>India are in the semis</b>. Short delivery on the leg stump, Rahman goes for the pull again, hits it flat and straight to fine leg. Shami fumbles the ball initially but grabs it on the second attempt. <b>India</b> become the <b>first team to bowl their opponents out in seven consecutive games in World Cups</b>. This is the <b>100th ODI win as captain for MS Dhoni</b>. It is also India's seventh successive win in this tournament. <b>S Rahman c Shami b U Yadav 30(40) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[U Yadav to S Rahman, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to S Rahman, no run, bouncer on the stumps, Rahman pulls it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Taskin Ahmed, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Rubel, <b>out</b> Caught by Ashwin!! Kohli shakes his head after Rubel was caught by Ashwin. Short delivery on the stumps, Rubel goes for the pull, but gets it on the outside half of the bat, short square leg settles under it and takes an easy catch. If you remember, earlier in the day, Rubel gave Kohli an aggressive send-off after dismissing him and now Kohli just shakes his head and sports a wry smile. <b>Rubel c Ashwin b U Yadav 0(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[U Yadav to Rubel, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Rubel, no run, short again from Yadav, Rubel is late on the pull, slices it but it doesn't carry to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Rubel, no run, short and on the stumps, Rubel ducks under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to S Rahman, 1 run, short and on the stumps, Rahman pulls, hits in the air, Dhawan runs to his left from deep backward square leg, but doesn't get there in time]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav [8.0-1-30-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rubel Hossain, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Mortaza, <b>out</b> Caught by Dhoni!! Howzzaattt is the cry from Dhoni. He was so confident and the umpire raised his finger. Full and just outside off stump, Mortaza doesn't bother to get behind the line, plays lazily at this without any feet movement and nicks it to the keeper. <b>Mortaza c Dhoni b Mohit Sharma 1(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mohit Sharma to Mortaza, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Mortaza, no run, allows the ball to come and guides it down to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to S Rahman, 1 run, goes off-side as he anticipates the short ball and pulls well to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to S Rahman, no run, slower ball outside off stump, Rahman advances and plays an ugly slog, but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Mortaza, 1 run, Mortaza stands tall and taps it to point, takes off for a sharp run, Jadeja fires a direct-hit at the bowler's end, but Mortaza was well in]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to S Rahman, 1 run, short delivery on the stumps, Rahman mistimes the pull but there is no one at mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mashrafe Mortaza, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Nasir Hossain, <b>out</b> Caught by Ashwin!! Hit well but straight to the fielder. Full and outside off stump, Hossain goes hard at the drive as he tries to go inside-out, times it very well but finds Ashwin, who takes a good low catch. Hardly any celebrations from India. Actually, Hossain struck it so hard that Ashwin took one hand off the ball as he pouched it. <b>Nasir Hossain c Ashwin b Ravindra Jadeja 35(34) [4s-6]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ravindra Jadeja to Nasir Hossain, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Nasir Hossain, <b>FOUR</b>, 'Nahi, Nahi Jad' shouts Dhoni in Hindi. Juicy flighted delivery on the stumps, Hossain plays the slog-sweep and sends it over mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Nasir Hossain, <b>FOUR</b>, down the track and tries the drive, the ball takes a thick outside edge but there is no one at slip. Raina patrols the ball all the way to the boundary from short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Nasir Hossain, no run, flatter delivery outside off stump, cut to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to S Rahman, byes, 1 run, tries the reverse sweep but misses, luckily for him it wasn't on the stumps and Dhoni fumbles to allow a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Nasir Hossain, 1 run, low full toss, gently driven to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Nasir Hossain, 1 run, good length delivery outside off stump, Hossain cuts late and sends it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Nasir Hossain, no run, 133kph on this bouncer, Hossain was just ball-watching on that occasion]]></line><line><![CDATA[How about a back-of-the-hand slower delivery now, Mohit Sharma?]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Nasir Hossain, no run, another bouncer, Nasir Hossain drops his wrists and sways out of the line at the last moment]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Nasir Hossain, no run, bouncer on the stumps, this time much quicker and Hossain ducks under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Nasir Hossain, <b>FOUR</b>, the length is too predictable. Mohit Sharma bangs one short, but it's not short enough to trouble Hossain, who rocks back and pulls over mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Nasir Hossain, no run, short of length on the off stump, turned to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma [5.0-0-28-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Nasir Hossain, 1 run, fullish, Hossain leans forward and drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Nasir Hossain, no run, no room whatsoever from Jadeja, Hossain defends off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Nasir Hossain, no run, hangs back and punches the flatter delivery back to Jadeja]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Nasir Hossain, no run, just outside off stump, pushed to point again]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Nasir Hossain, no run, flatter delivery outside off stump, Hossain cuts and picks out backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Nasir Hossain, <b>FOUR</b>, safe shot! Flighted delivery on the leg stump, Hossain steps out, gets closer to the pitch of the ball, long-on is inside the ring and Hossain just chips it over his head to pick up four]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja [6.0-0-28-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bangladesh have scored <b>30/1</b> in the batting powerplay.]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Nasir Hossain, 1 run, this time he sends this along the ground towards point and keeps strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Nasir Hossain, no run, in the airrrrr and <b>dropped</b>. Dhoni smiles! Shortish and outside off stump, Hossain cuts, doesn't keep it down, Dhawan dives forward at cover-point, gets both hands to it. It was so catchable but the ball popped out]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to S Rahman, 1 run, slider on the leg stump, Rahman glances it to long leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to S Rahman, no run, shortish from Ashwin, punched to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Nasir Hossain, 1 run, tossed up outside off stump, Hossain pushes it to point, looks at his partner and sets off]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to S Rahman, 1 run, spinning back in, Rahman guides it towards short third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin [9.0-1-26-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to S Rahman, 1 run, good length delivery on the leg stump, Rahman goes for the drive, but gets it on the inside half of the bat, the ball goes uppishly but doesn't carry to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to S Rahman, no run, the length is on the shorter side again, Rahman cuts and picks out backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to S Rahman, no run, bumper outside off stump, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Nasir Hossain, 3 runs, short and on the off stump, Hossain pulls it to deep mid-wicket, Dhawan runs across to his left and stops the ball, but while tumbling, he loses control and they take an extra run]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Nasir Hossain, no run, attempts the slower ball bumper outside off stump, Hossain goes early into the pull and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Nasir Hossain, no run, back of a length outside off stump, blocked]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to S Rahman, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Rahman tries to cut, but chops it to point as he was late on the shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Nasir Hossain, 1 run, uppishly but safe. Short and wide outside off stump, Hossain guides over gully, Dhawan collects it on the bounce at third man. Hossain wants two, but Rahman sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Nasir Hossain, no run, on a length and on the stumps, Hossain knocks it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Nasir Hossain, no run, short of length delivery and just shaping back in, Hossain tries to work it on the on-side, but gets hit on the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to S Rahman, 1 run, short enough for Rahman to hang back and guide it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to S Rahman, no run, short of length on the stumps, Rahman gets behind the line and blocks]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Nasir Hossain, no run, it's a friendly full toss and Hossain is very kind enough to tap it straight to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Nasir Hossain, <b>FOUR</b>, short and width on offer outside off stump, Hossain gets on top of the bounce, controls the cut shot very well as he hits it along the ground between backward point and cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Nasir Hossain, no run, short ball again from Shami, Hossain ducks under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Nasir Hossain, no run, good length delivery on the off stump, Hossain plays inside the line of the ball and just about manages to get a thickish outside edge that rolls to point. Maybe the ball nipped away off the deck]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to S Rahman, 1 run, short and steeply rising, Rahman hops and fends it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Nasir Hossain, 1 run, harmless back of a length delivery on the off stump, Hossain taps it towards short cover and sets off for a sharp run. A clean pick up from Jinks would have been interesting]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Nasir Hossain, <b>wide</b>, begins his new spell with a bumper, Hossain sits under it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammed Shami [6.0-1-26-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to S Rahman, <b>FOUR</b>, short of length delivery outside off stump, Rahman slashes hard, looked like it went off the toe-end of the bat, the ball rocketed past backward point and third man was way too square]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to S Rahman, <b>FOUR</b>, pulled along the ground but not convincing. Shortish ball on the stumps, Rahman plays the pull, hits it much straighter than he anticipated and sends it wide of mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Nasir Hossain, 1 run, Dhoni has a man at slip now, but Hossain guides it well wide of him to third man. The ball went off the outside half of the bat on that occasion]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Nasir Hossain, <b>FOUR</b>, edged but no one at slip. Short of a length delivery pitching around off stump and nipping away, Hossain was on the back foot to defend, but the late movement opened him up completely, luckily for him, there was no fielder at slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Nasir Hossain, no run, short of length delivery, Hossain defends and looks for a run, but Rahman isn't keen]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Nasir Hossain, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Rahim, <b>out</b> Caught by Dhoni!! Is that a wicket straightaway after the break? Yes it is! Nothing but a short of length delivery on the stumps from Umesh, Rahim had no clue about the pace on the delivery. He was so late on the pull shot and the ball flew straight up in the air after taking a top edge, Dhoni called for it, just moved a few steps to his right and swallowed it easily. In fact, Rahim was in no position to play the pull shot. India are inching closer to a big victory! <b>Rahim c Dhoni b U Yadav 27(43) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[U Yadav to Rahim, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>batting powerplay</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The <b>drinks</b> trolley arrives on the field. India are well on top. The spinners have tied one end up and the Bangladeshi batsmen have struggled to rotate the strike on a consistent basis. With the asking rate almost touching 11, it would need something heroic from these two for Bangladesh to win the game. Otherwise, India are on course to book a semi-final spot.]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, 1 run, straigher one around off, Rahim is cramped for room, but manages to ease it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to S Rahman, 1 run, low full toss just outside off, Rahman bunts it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, 1 run, well judged run, Rahim drops it in front of cover, looks at his partner who responds to his call]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to S Rahman, 1 run, tad quicker and outside off, Rahman pushes it square on the off-side, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, 1 run, fraction short and outside off, Rahim cuts it square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to S Rahman, 1 run, nicely tossed up outside off, Rahman knocks it off the front foot to the left of cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Rahim, no run, bumper on the stumps, Rahim sits under it and evades it comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[Goes back over the wicket for Rahim]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to S Rahman, 1 run, no, it is the double bluff, goes full and outside off, Rahman drives it to sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Yadav goes round the wicket. Maybe some short stuff on the menu..]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to S Rahman, 2 runs, shortish and outside off, Rahman is hurried on the cut, chops it behind point for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to S Rahman, <b>wide</b>, splays it down leg, Dhoni goes up just to put the umpire off, but still a wide is signalled]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Rahim, 1 run, Rahim showing intent now. Gives the charge to Yadav, looks to go big, but gets a thick inside edge to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to S Rahman, 1 run, knocks the back of a length delivery to the right of point, takes off for a quick single. Jadeja gets to the ball quickly and hits the timber at the non-striker's end, but Rahman had made it in]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to S Rahman, no run, short of length around off, Rahman stands tall and mistimes the punch towards point, Jadeja lets go of a bullet throw, thankfully Rahane is there to back up. It was unnecessary as Rahim was inside the crease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav [5.0-1-9-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, no run, fires it in on the stumps, Rahim digs it to the right of the bowler, Jadeja moves across and fields the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, there comes the sweep again and he gets the desired result. Jadeja gives this bit more air, Rahim kneels down and sweeps it over mid-wicket, no one protecting the rope in the deep. Bangladesh need plenty more of this]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, 2 runs, Rahim starting to use his feet now, skips out of the crease and chips it over cover for a brace. He didn't try to hit it hard]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to S Rahman, 1 run, flighted on off, Rahman opens the bat face at the last moment and knocks it to the right of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, 1 run, comes down the track, almost yorks himself, squeezes out the drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip has been employed by Dhoni]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, no run, not all that short, Rahim goes deep in the crease, cuts and finds backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to S Rahman, no run, floated up close to off, Rahman presses forward and defends to the on-side, it came off the inner part]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rahim, 1 run, tossed up around off, Rahim guides it with an angled bat to backward point, Shami runs around from short third and mopes up]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to S Rahman, 1 run, flatter and just outside off, Rahman punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rahim, 1 run, wrists it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to S Rahman, 1 run, bit of extra bounce on that occasion, Rahman rides it and taps it to point, Rahim was a bit too casual in reaching the crease, Dhoni flicks the ball onto the stumps, but the batsman had made it in. Need to be careful with Dhoni around the sticks]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rahim, 1 run, nudged with the turn to square leg, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, 1 run, taps it wide of cover and sets off immediately for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, no run, skids on after pitching, Rahim stays leg-side of the ball and drops it near his feet]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, no run, defended back down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! That is his favorite shot against the spinners and is most productive shot as well. Floated up on off, Rahim goes down on one knee and slog sweeps it wide of long-on, one bounce and into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to S Rahman, 1 run, floated up on off, Rahman stays low and nurdles it behind square, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, 1 run, tossed up on off, Rahim drives it to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to S Rahman, no run, flighted just outside off, solidly defended off the front foot. India won't mind the Bangladeshi batsmen blocking or taking the odd single]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to S Rahman, no run, throws this up invitingly outside off, Rahman lunges forward and plays it with soft hands to the off-side, Dhoni moves across and fields the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to S Rahman, no run, quicker and attacking the stumps, Rahman stays in the crease and knocks it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to S Rahman, 2 runs, tossed up on off, Rahman kneels down and sweeps it to deep square leg, Mohit runs to his right from deep mid-wicket, slides and keeps it to a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to S Rahman, no run, nice floaty delivery, Rahman presses forward and defends in front of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to S Rahman, no run, floated up outside off, Rahman drives and Rayudu swoops in on the ball, saves the single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, no run, defended with the straightest of bats back to Jadeja. Another successful over for India comes to an end]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to S Rahman, 1 run, sliding on middle and leg, Rahman leans forward and nurdles it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to S Rahman, no run, hangs on the back foot and dabs it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to S Rahman, no run, flighted on off, Rahman push-drives it towards cover, Rayudu on as a substitute dives to his right and parries it to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sabbir Rahman, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shakib, <b>out</b> Caught by Shami!! The pressure had to give something and it is the wicket of Shakib. Bangladesh in trouble now. They have lost half their side and more importantly an experienced batsman. It was short alright, but it is always dangerous to play the cut at the "G" with the extra bounce, Shakib can't control it and hits it in the air straight to short third man, where Shami takes the easiest of catches. <b>Shakib c Shami b Ravindra Jadeja 10(34)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ravindra Jadeja to Shakib, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shakib, no run, Jadeja sees the batsman advance and holds the length back, Shakib can't do much other than defend it down the wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, leg byes, 1 run, going on with the angle from round the wicket, Shakib fails to connect with the glance, takes the leg bye and keeps strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, no run, sliding onto the leg-stump, Shakib tickles it to short fine leg, the fielder is onto the ball quickly]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, no run, flatter and around off, Shakib goes back and taps it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, no run, slower and on off, defended back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rahim, 1 run, nudges it behind square, Dhoni tells Raina to chase it down from leg slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rahim, no run, comes down the track and defends off the inside part to the on-side, Rahim was not to the pitch of the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shakib, no run, slower and turning in, Shakib works it to backward short leg, finds the fielder there]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shakib, no run, stays on the back foot and taps it to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shakib, no run, Shakib is tucked for room with delivery spinning in, he works it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, 1 run, again, tad short from Jaddu, Rahim is quick to go back and cut it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, no run, plays an extended forward defence to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shakib, 1 run, shortens the length, Shakib goes deep in the crease and pulls it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rahim, no run, waits for the ball to arrive and turns it towards mid-wicket, can't get the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rahim, no run, floated up on off, Rahim lunges forward in defence]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rahim, 2 runs, Rahim was waiting to play this shot. Tossed up on off, Rahim kneels down and slog sweeps, he didn't middle it and just about cleared the mid-wicket fielder. Good enough for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rahim, 2 runs, holds the length back, Rahim goes back and cuts it past the short third man, Dhawan runs across from sweeper and keeps it to two]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rahim, no run, touch quicker and on off, Rahim dead-bats it near his feet]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, 1 run, arm-ball around off, Shakib punches it in the gap at cover, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, no run, goes straight on from round the wicket, Rahim gets inside the line and tucks it to the on-side, Dhoni runs across and saves the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shakib, 1 run, leans forward and wrists it to the left of Jaddu, he tries to stop it with his boot, but fails and the batsmen sneak in a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[A leg slip placed for Shakib]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, 1 run, slightly short and outside off, Rahim cuts it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rahim, no run, flighted on off, Rahim defends with the bat in front of his pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place..]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shakib, 1 run, drags the length back, Shakib bunts it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shakib, <b>wide</b>, turning down leg, easy call for the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shakib, no run, starts with one on leg-stump, Shakib tickles it straight to short fine]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rahim, no run, some turn there for Ash, Rahim goes hard on the drive and the ball takes the inside edge and rolls to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rahim, no run, works it with the turn towards mid-wicket, the fielder moves to his right, dives and keeps the batsmen at their respective ends]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rahim, no run, flighted on off, Rahim presses forward and defends to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[A leg slip comes in now. Raina is the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, 1 run, touch short and outside off, Shakib cuts it square of the wicket, for the <b>first run in 18 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, no run, Ashwin is giving away nothing, keeps it tight on off and middle, Shakib pushes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, no run, quicker and just outside off, Shakib mistimes the drive to cover, he went too hard at that]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Rahim, no run, targeting the stumps, Rahim stays in the crease and wrists it to mid-on. <b>Maiden</b> from Shami and that is the second consecutive maiden for the Indians]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Rahim, no run, back of a length on off, Rahim hops across and turns it to mid-wicket, no chance for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Rahim, no run, beaten! There was no movement there, but still Rahim was beaten. Fuller and just outside off, Rahim was on the move while trying to drive, the ball zips past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Rahim, no run, keeps it short and close to the off-stump, Rahim lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Rahim, no run, short of length on off, Rahim rides the bounce and drops it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[Coming back to the Sarkar wicket, Dhoni wanted to go with both hands, but he realised that he wouldn't get there. Hence, he went with one-hand. Meanwhile, Shami is stopped in his run-up as a bird flies across the turf.]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Rahim, no run, good length ball around off, Rahim pushes it to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, no run, flatter and on off, Shakib opens the bat face and guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, no run, quicker and around off, Shakib punches it to the right of Ashwin, he moves across, dives and fields the ball. There is a noticeable spring in the way the Indians are moving in the field]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, no run, fraction short, Shakib goes back and cuts, the fielder at backward point dives to his left and saves the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, no run, again, flighted on off, Shakib is half-forward and defends to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, no run, floated up on off, Shakib comes forward and blocks it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, no run, slower through the air, Shakib presses forward and taps it in front of cover, Rahim wanted the run but his partner sends him back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Rahim, no run, on a length just outside off, Rahim waves his bat and lets it go to Dhoni]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Rahim, no run, greets the new batsman with a bumper, Rahim ducks under it and lets it go through comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mushfiqur Rahim, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Soumya Sarkar, <b>out</b> Caught by Dhoni!! Terrific take from the Indian skipper. I have not seen Dhoni dive to his left to take a catch. Even he knows that is a good catch as he sports a big smile. The ploy to keep it short works for India for the umpteenth time in this World Cup. This one gets big on Sarkar, who looks to fend it away rather awkwardly, runs it off the face of the bat to the left of Dhoni, he dives and takes a brilliant one-handed take. <b>Soumya Sarkar c Dhoni b Shami 29(43) [4s-3 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shami to Soumya Sarkar, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, cleverly played! That is the second time in the innings he has played that shot. Short from Shami, Sarkar arches back and ramps it over the vacant slip cordon. The fielder at third man had no chance, it was played very fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Soumya Sarkar, no run, shortens the length around off, Sarkar is opened up a touch as he bunts it to the right of Shami]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Soumya Sarkar, no run, back of a length around off, Sarkar dabs it to backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, no run, another one that goes straight, Shakib gets inside the line and turns it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, flighted just outside off, Sarkar presses it between cover and point, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Soumya Sarkar, no run, pushed through close to off, Sarkar punches and picks out cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, 1 run, goes straight on, Shakib leans forward and glances it to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, <b>wide</b>, slides it down leg, Shakib can't get bat on that, wide given]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, no run, shortens the length, but there is some turn, Shakib goes back and across, blocked down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, no run, tossed up on off, defended back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Soumya Sarkar, no run, back of a length on off, Sarkar stays rooted to the crease and tries the steer to third man, the ball hit him on the handle and rolled to the left of Shami]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Soumya Sarkar, no run, <b>in the air and just out of reach.</b> Shami once more goes for the short ball, Sarkar is late on the pull, the ball hits the splice of the bat and lobs over leaping Shami, Rohit at mid-on dives to his right and prevents the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Shakib, 1 run, digs it short and on off, Shakib mistimes the pull to deep mid-wicket, if there was a fielder at mid-wicket, he would have gobbled that up]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Shakib, no run, shortens the length and nips back in, Shakib is tucked for room, he went for the back foot punch, the ball beats the inside edge. Hands in the air time for Shami. The ball also went over the off-stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Shakib, 2 runs, banged in halfway down the wicket, Shakib pulls it to deep mid-wicket for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Shakib, no run, back of a length around off, Shakib goes for an ugly waft, it was too close to be playing that shot and he is beaten]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Soumya Sarkar, <b>SIX</b>, fabulous shot! That spoils a good over from Ash. It was floated up on off, Sarkar gets to the pitch of the ball and plays the pick up shot against the turn, the ball has enough to clear the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Soumya Sarkar, no run, slower through the air, Sarkar prods across and pokes at it, the outside edge does not carry to the slip fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Soumya Sarkar, no run, drifting onto the pads, Sarkar fails to connect with the nudge, the ball rolls off the pads to the on-side, Dhoni tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, 1 run, leans forward and push-drives to sweeper cover, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, no run, peach! Ashwin has been simply superb when he has slowed the ball up. Flighted on middle and gets it to turn, Shakib played for the wrong angle and the ball spins past the outside edge. He was squared up and the ball goes over off-stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shakib, no run, tossed up around off, Shakib presses forward and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin [1.0-0-2-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajaraman</b> chimes in: With Mahmudullah dismissed, the Bangladesh section of the crowd has gone quiet while the Indian section has just got noisier by the minute]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Mahmudullah, <b>out</b> Caught by Dhawan!! Big wicket for India. The in-form Mahmudullah makes the long walk back to the pavilion after Ian Gould raises his finger. Once again the Indian quickies have used the short ball to good effect. Mahmudullah was hurried on the pull, top-edges it to fine leg, Dhawan initially ran too far forward, but tracked back, tried to take it over his head, but the ball popped out as he was losing balance, he did well to flick it up, go out of the rope and come back in to complete the catch. He was quite confident that he had taken it cleanly and the replays confirmed that. <b>Mahmudullah c Dhawan b Shami 21(31) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shami to Mahmudullah, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhawan is claiming a catch. Mahmudullah is the batsman. Dhawan is confident as he signals out after holding on. It has been sent upstairs. Shami's front foot is fine. Was he touching the rope? It is a very close call. The third umpire is having a look from various angles. He has a three-way screen to help him. OUT!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Mahmudullah, no run, short delivery around off, Mahmudullah arches back and allows the ball to sail through to Dhoni]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Mahmudullah, no run, good length ball on off, Mahmudullah presents the full face and defends back to Shami]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, bit of width on offer, Sarkar glides it off the face to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Soumya Sarkar, no run, banged in midway down the pitch, Sarkar looks to ramp it down towards third man, doesn't make the required connection. Shami thought it was close to taking the edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Mahmudullah, 1 run, short and on the body, Mahmudullah stays inside the line and helps it down to fine leg with a pull]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammed Shami [2.0-0-17-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[MS Dhoni then introduced the reliable Mohit Sharma into the attack. Just in the nick of time, Umesh Yadav produced the edge to dismiss Tamim and a terrible mix-up between Imrul Kayes and Soumya Sarkar saw Kayes finding himself short of the crease and he was run out. Ravichandran Ashwin bowled a tight over to put Bangladesh's batsmen under more pressure. Ashwin has used the drifter to good effect in this World Cup. Before the doosra came into play, off-spinners like Hugh Tayfield, Erapalli Prasanna, Lance Gibbs, Fred Titmus and Co. used it extensively to take wickets. While chasing down a massive target, it is imperative for the top-order to fire. Unfortunately for Bangladesh, they have lost a couple of wickets. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here is <b>Bharath Ramaraj's</b> analysis for the first 16 overs: Runs flowed smoothly from Tamim Iqbal's bat as Bangladesh made a fine start. Tamim gave a glimpse of his ability to find gaps through the off-side by cracking three sparkling boundaries off Mohammed Shami's bowling. Shami didn't help his cause by generally bowling short and wide. It is interesting to note that the outfield at the MCG is lightning quick. It wasn't the case before.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Soumya Sarkar, no run, flatter and on the stumps, Sarkar wasn't in a great position for the pull, the ball wasn't short enough as well, skidded through after pitching, ends up dragging it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Mahmudullah, 1 run, pushed through and on Mahmudullah's pads, clipped away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, Raina drops one short and well outside off, Sarkar makes room and cuts it square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, that should break the shackles, a shimmy down the track, makes room as he did so and goes over extra cover, with the turn, no chance for Shami - running across from long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Mahmudullah, 1 run, tossed up and on the stumps, driven to the left of mid-wicket. RJ gets across quickly but can't stop it cleanly, allows a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, flighted delivery and well outside off, driven to the right of extra cover for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Mahmudullah, no run, the slower ball from Mohit, Mahmudullah watches it all along and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, <b>uppish and just over short cover</b>, this was pitched up and well outside off, Sarkar was early on the drive, ends up spooning it in the air, just gets enough to clear the leaping Rohit Sharma]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Soumya Sarkar, no run, another bumper from Mohit, Sarkar went for the pull and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Soumya Sarkar, no run, the proper bouncer now, Sarkar ducks under it and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Soumya Sarkar, no run, the slower bouncer now, Sarkar was way too early on the pull and missed, Dhoni has to bend forward to take it on the full]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Mahmudullah, 1 run, Mohit slips in the slower ball, Mahmudullah nudges it towards mid-wicket. Mohit runs after the ball and keeps them down to a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Soumya Sarkar, no run, very full and just outside off, driven back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Mahmudullah, 1 run, tossed up and well outside off, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Mahmudullah, 2 runs, flighted delivery and well outside off, Mahmudullah looks to drive and gets a thick edge past short third man, back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, tossed up and just outside off, punched down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and leg-slip for the left-hander]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Mahmudullah, 1 run, another lap sweep from Mahmudullah, but Raina had shortened his length, gets an inside edge and rolls away towards short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Mahmudullah, 2 runs, very fine lap sweep from Mahmudullah, gets down on his knees, takes the ball on the full and gets it very fine for a brace]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Mahmudullah, 1 run, tad fuller and just outside off, Mahmudullah was deep inside the crease, pushes it in front of mid-on for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, punched off the back foot and past cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Mahmudullah, 1 run, Mahmudullah goes for a repeat of the previous shot, but this was a tad fuller and well outside off, gets a thick inside edge behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Mahmudullah, <b>FOUR</b>, show of intent from Mahmudullah, backs away to a full ball, gets underneath the length delivery and goes over mid-on, almost went all the way, bounced in front of the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Mahmudullah, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Mahmudullah was neither forward nor back, ends up hanging his bat and pushes it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, Mohit starts off a new spell from round the wicket, back of a length and well outside off, steered square past point for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma [3.0-0-18-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Mahmudullah, no run, Raina starts with a <b>maiden over</b>, this one's tossed up and in that corridor outside off, Mahmudullah presses forward and turns it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Mahmudullah, no run, Raina drifts one well outside off, Mahmudullah lunges forward and defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Mahmudullah, no run, pushed through and just outside off, Mahmudullah prods forward and gets an inside edge towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Mahmudullah, no run, flatter and just outside off, punched to the left of mid-wicket where Jadeja makes a tumbling stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[Raina has just one slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Mahmudullah, no run, slower and on the off-stump line, nudged towards backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Mahmudullah, no run, tossed up and on off, driven straight to the fielder at short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Soumya Sarkar, no run, this one's given more air, gets it to drift across the left-hander, defended towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Mahmudullah, 1 run, flatter and just outside off, punched down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Back over the wicket to the right-hander]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, tossed up and just outside off, dabbed past the lone slip for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Soumya Sarkar, no run, the attempted carrom ball from Ashwin, slides on after pitching, Sarkar dabs it straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Soumya Sarkar, no run, slower and just outside off, Sarkar presses forward and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Soumya Sarkar, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, some bounce for Ashwin, Sarkar goes back and blocks]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for spin and it's Ashwin, a slip and a leg slip in place. He's starting from round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, on a good length and well outside off, steered away square behind point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Soumya Sarkar, no run, appeal for LBW, but there was a big inside edge there, Sarkar was caught in his crease to one that nipped back in, the bat came down with an angle, but luckily, he got an inside edge on that]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mohit changes to round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Soumya Sarkar, no run, another slash and a miss! Sarkar backed away to a length ball, was looking to go over cover and missed, could have so easily edged it to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Soumya Sarkar, no run, tad fuller and on Sarkar's pads, turned towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Soumya Sarkar, no run, back of a length and on the off-stump channel, Sarkar stands tall and punches it straight to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, that's neatly played by Sarkar, this was short and just outside off, Sarkar waits on it, uses the pace of the ball, opens the face of the bat at the last moment and ramps it over the keeper for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Mahmudullah, no run, Yadav keeps it full and gets it to shape away from the right hander, Mahmudullah throws his hands at that and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Mahmudullah, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, back of a length and on Sarkar's pads, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Three slips in place for Umesh]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Soumya Sarkar, no run, Yadav shortens his length on off, Sarkar gets behind the line and defends it in front of point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Soumya Sarkar, no run, that's a waft from Sarkar, on a good length and angling across the left-hander, Sarkar plays away from his body and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Soumya Sarkar, no run, the bumper from Yadav, Sarkar ducks underneath and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Mahmudullah, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Mahmudullah prods across and defends it with soft hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Mahmudullah, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a nice way to get going, width on offer from Mohit, Mahmudullah throws his hands and clears point with the drive, no chance for the fielder getting across from third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Mahmudullah, <b>wide</b>, Mohit loses his line and strays this one well down leg-side, wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[Coming back to the run-out, Jadeja ran to his right, dived and stopped the ball. The throw was right next to the stumps and Yadav did well to get back in time, excellent cricket from the Indians]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Mahmudullah, no run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Mahmudullah gets well forward and blocks it towards mid-off. Soumya Sarkar was backing up and has to rush back in]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Mahmudullah, no run, that's a cracker from Mohit, pitched up in that corridor outside off and gets it to hold its line, Mahmudullah was prodding forward and is beaten on the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Mahmudullah, no run, on a good length and shaping away from well outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Mahmudullah, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Mahmudullah stays behind the line and defends it towards backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Soumya Sarkar, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Sarkar presses across and blocks it]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Soumya Sarkar, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Soumya Sarkar gets across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mahmudullah, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Soumya Sarkar, <b>out</b> Kayes Run Out!! Disaster for Bangladesh, they have lost both openers now. This was pitched up and held its line outside off, Sarkar dabbed it to the right of point, he took a step or two down the track, Kayes responded and was almost halfway down the track before being sent back. He had no chance to beat the throw, Jadeja realized it early and throws it back at the bowler. Yadav was running back towards the stumps, collects the ball and whips the bails off. Kayes was well short, despite the dive. <b>Kayes run out (Ravindra Jadeja/U Yadav) 5(14)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[U Yadav to Soumya Sarkar, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Soumya Sarkar, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Tamim, <b>out</b> Caught by Dhoni!! That's an excellent catch from Dhoni. Tamim's short burst has ended. This was pitched up and shapes away from outside off, Tamim was looking for the big drive, doesn't account for the movement. He ends up getting a thick edge on the shot, Dhoni dives forward and clasps the ball with both hands. The Indians started celebrating immediately. Tamim wasn't sure, he asked Dhoni if he took it cleanly, the Indian captain wasn't sure as well, they went up to the third umpire. <b>Tamim c Dhoni b U Yadav 25(25) [4s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[U Yadav to Tamim, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Has Tamim been <b>caught behind</b>? He asked Dhoni, the keeper wasn't 100% sure either, the umpires converge and decide to go for the third umpire. 'It's a fair delivery', says Steve Davis, they now look for the angles. He says it's clean from the front angle, but wants a few more looks, with different angles. They are zooming it now, he says 'YES, I can see that the ball has gone cleanly and the fingers are underneath it. Gunner, you can comfortably give him out, thanks', says Davis]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Kayes, 1 run, back of a length and on Kayes' hips, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Tamim, 1 run, on a length and just outside off, worked wide of mid-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kayes, no run, back of a length and on the stumps, Kayes shuffles across on the flick, misses and is hit high on the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Tamim, 1 run, just short of third man, this was full and angling across the left-hander, Tamim gave the charge and gets a thick edge towards third man, Ashwin was the fielder there, he was on his heels and doesn't go for the catch, it wasn't a catch either, dropped well in front of him]]></line><line><![CDATA[A backward short leg is in place now]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Tamim, 2 runs, now, the pull shot, Mohit bangs one short and on the stumps, Tamim swivels across and pulls it over mid-wicket. Poor running though, the batsmen are happy with just a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, Tamim is looking very positive, comes down the track to a full and wide ball, was looking to go over cover, ends up slicing it over point, the ball bounces and rolls away into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and a short cover in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kayes, 1 run, <b>uppish and safe</b>, on a good length and well outside off, Kayes was rooted to his crease as he flashed at that, the edge goes through gully and towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kayes, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Kayes prods across and turns it to the right of square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Tamim, no run, Yadav keeps it short and on the stumps, Tamim goes back in his crease and tucks it straight to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Tamim, no run, back of a length and in that channel outside off, Tamim was looking to nudge it towards the on-side, closes the face of the bat and gets a soft leading edge towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Tamim, no run, short of a length and on the stumps, Tamim presses across and turns it towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Kayes, 3 runs, not a bad way to get going, pitched up and well outside off, Kayes leans forward, opens the face of the bat at the last moment and drives it through extra cover. Jadeja gave chase from point, Ashwin ran across from mid-off but it's Jadeja who gets to the ball first and drags it back in, saves a run for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Kayes, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Kayes waits on it and steers it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Kayes, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Kayes presses across and turns it towards square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Tamim, no run, Shami bangs one short and on the stumps, Tamim rides with the bounce and nudges it in front of mid-wicket. Kayes wanted a single and is sent back, Rahane makes a direct hit at the bowler's end, but the batsman is safe]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, this is a poor over from Shami, looking for swing, he ends up pitching it up and well outside off, Tamim gets forward and caresses it through extra cover, the ball races away to the fence in a jiffy]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, width on offer from Shami, Tamim stands tall and cracks it square on the off-side, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Tamim, no run, on a good length and around off, Tamim was stuck to his crease as he prodded forward in defence, gets an inside edge and the ball rolls away towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, that's the first boundary of the innings, this was pitched up and in that zone outside off, Tamim leans forward, presents the full face of the bat and drives it past mid-off for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Tamim, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Tamim presses forward and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Tamim, <b>wide</b>, short and wide from Shami, Tamim went chasing after that and missed, called as a wide]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Kayes, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Kayes prods across, presents the full face of the bat and defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Kayes, no run, Yadav bangs one short and on the stumps, Kayes shuffles across, the ball gets big on him, he hops across awkwardly and manages to fend it away towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Kayes, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Kayes gets half forward and blocks it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Kayes, no run, rush of blood from Kayes, charges down the track, Yadav shortens his length and gets it to angle across the left-hander, he swings and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Kayes, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Kayes presses across and defends it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Kayes, no run, that's a lovely length from Yadav, tad fuller and shaping away from outside off, Kayes was lured into the drive, the balance was nowhere as he played and missed]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Tamim, no run, on a length and going away with the angle, Tamim covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Tamim, no run, fuller length delivery and a hint of nip back into Tamim, he was pushing forward and gets an inside edge towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Tamim, no run, back of a length and well outside off, Tamim rides with the bounce and steers it to the left of point. Jadeja moves across quickly and prevents a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Tamim, 2 runs, too straight from Shami, ends up drifting onto Tamim's pads, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Tamim, no run, on a good length and shaping away from outside off, Tamim plays inside the line and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Tamim, <b>wide</b>, Shami now goes across the left-hander, goes with the natural angle, but it's a bit too wide, called by the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Tamim, <b>wide</b>, Shami shortens his length and angles one well down leg-side, wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[Going back to the last ball of the previous over, there's some movement on the <b>Snicko</b> after the ball went past the bat, Dhawan went up at 1st slip, but Dhoni didn't, neither did the bowler. Raina asked Dhoni, but he just ran forward and took his position for the next over. Raina asked Kayes, who cheekily nodded yes with a smile on his face. Cheeky from both Raina and Kayes. Raina for asking and full marks to Kayes for nodding yes, he may have been just rubbing it in as the Indians didn't go for the review. Either ways it's done and let's move on]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Tamim, no run, short of a length and shaping away from outside off, Tamim drops his wrists and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammed Shami, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Kayes, no run, Raina and Dhawan were excited for a moment, but nothing from the bowler and the keeper. On a good length and shaping away from outside off, Kayes shuffles across and lets it go in extravagant fashion. Replays show that it came off the <b>bottom edge. Definite edge there.</b> Wonder how Dhoni missed that. The noise was clearly audible on the stump mic. Even the bowler didn't pick it up]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Tamim, 1 run, too short from Yadav, Tamim swivels across, rolls his wrists and pulls it past Rahane at square leg, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Tamim, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Tamim prods across and defends it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Tamim, no run, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, Tamim gets well forward in defence, the ball rolls away towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Tamim, 2 runs, Tamim is off and running! This was banged in short and just outside off, Tamim swivels across, rolls his wrists and pulls it past mid-wicket for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Tamim, no run, back of a length and in that channel outside off, Tamim rides with the bounce, plays with soft hands and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tamim and Kayes are at the crease. Tamim is on strike. U Yadav will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Right.. we are back. Umesh has the new ball with him.  Two slips in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[Had a second glance at the Mortaza-Taskin conversation. Taskin started to explain to his captain, but was quickly shot down by Mortaza. Taskin then went quiet. As Mortaza seemed to be getting out of hand, a couple of Bangladeshis quickly came across and defused the situation. As I type this, the Indians are on the field and in a huddle. We should be ready to restart. Remember since rain played a part and Bangladesh didn't bowl their overs on time, the innings break was just for a 30-minute duration.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit:</b> "It was important, big game - quarterfinal, wanted to make it count and I am glad that eventually we posted a good total. We need to come back now and bowl well. It was important for me to stay, especially knowing that we lost a couple of wickets in the middle. Before we started we knew it was going to be slow and low. We wanted to take our time, especially I wanted to take time, that's how I play my game. I knew if I stay there till 30-35th over I could make it and that's what I did, wanted to stay till the end. All the shots I played, I liked it. After the rain, I think the ball was coming on nicely. It was important to just hold the shape and play your shots and that's what exactly I did. I think so it's a decent total. We know the Bangladeshi batsmen. We can't underestimate them. They have posted 290s and 300s in the league games. We have to come and bowl really well. Fielding will be very important. We have to be very energetic on the field. Take some catches, run-outs and stuff like that. Hopefully, we can come and defend the target."]]></line><line><![CDATA[We have the man of the moment, <b>Rohit Sharma's</b> interview transcribed word-to-word:]]></line><line><![CDATA[And I had previously mentioned that I will keep an eye on Mortaza's reactions on the field. After Taskin bowled Rohit, Mortaza was right in the youngster's face. The captain instead of congratulating the bowler for the wicket, was angrily gesturing and asking him why he didn't execute the yorker earlier in the over. He was unhappy with the two short balls that went for boundaries. Mortaza's reaction was very aggressive and there were some cuss words spoken as well. Poor, Taskin just bore the brunt of his captain's reaction and sportingly shrugged his shoulders. Taskin finished off with a smile, without even saying a word. Extreme from Mortaza, but shows the passion and commitment he plays the game. Depends on which way you want to take it, I suppose.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The target should prove to be difficult for Bangladesh as it is not easy to bat under lights at the MCG. Remember, <b>no side has scored 300 while batting second at the MCG in ODIs</b>. However, one expects them to put up a spirited performance and give their fancied opponents a run for their money.]]></line><line><![CDATA[With Shakib and Rubel keeping the opposition in check, Ajinkya Rahane had a rare moment of indiscretion as he looked to play on the up and Taskin picked up a wicket. At that time, Bangladesh seemed to have gained the upper hand, but Raina and Rohit came to India's rescue. Bangladesh didn't help their cause by allowing both the batsmen to take easy singles. The story could have been different for them, as Rohit was caught in the deep off Rubel's bowling, but the on-field umpire, Aleem Dar, adjudged a full toss that was clearly below the waist as a no ball for height.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, after Shikhar Dhawan and Rohit stitched a useful partnership for the first wicket, Bangladesh's bowlers bowled with diligence and discipline to pull the batting side back. After Shakib provided the crucial breakthrough by taking the wicket of Dhawan, it was Rubel, who bowled an inspired spell and was rewarded for his efforts with the wicket of Virat Kohli. Rubel preyed on Kohli's inclination to poke at deliveries on a fourth or fifth stump line and it bore fruit as he produced the edge to send Kohli back to the pavilion. Rubel also surprised Kohli with the odd bouncer. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rohit started on a great note by essaying fine drives, imperious pull shots and lofted strokes. However, as India lost a slew of wickets in the middle overs, he looked to play the anchor role before opening up his shoulders in the slog overs. He showed his class by using soft hands to steer Taskin Ahmed through the third-man region for a boundary in the 39th over. He also played a sweetly timed shot down the ground to thump Rubel Hossain for a six and collect 15 runs in the 46th over. One has to give credit to Suresh Raina as well as it was Raina's offensive that helped India to up the tempo. He launched Shakib Al Hasan over the long-on region for a stunning six and smacked a low full toss from Rubel for a boundary to give the innings the much needed impetus. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rohit Sharma played with unruffled elegance to compose a memorable ton and take India to a massive total on the board. In fact, Bangladesh came across as a highly-motivated side and put India under immense pressure by picking up wickets at regular intervals, but it was Rohit, who steered them to safe waters. For most part of his innings, Rohit looked in sublime touch and picked the length very early. Rohit's feet, his bat and body seemed to be instinctively aligned, as he waited for the ball to arrive and for him to find the gaps in the field with his graceful game.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here is something that interested me. Rohit becomes the second Indian after Sourav Ganguly to <b>score a WC hundred in a knockout game</b>. That is an unbelievable stat. I cannot fathom the fact that only one Indian has scored a hundred before today. And India have won two World Cups! Ganguly got his hundred against Kenya in the 2003 WC semi-final. The likes of Sachin, Azhar, Dravid, Sehwag and Co. haven't got a hundred in a knockout game. That's staggering stuff.]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, well bowled Rubel! Yorker on off, dug out to cover, only a single results and India end on 302. Just the <b>6 singles</b> came off the final over. Excellent one from Rubel under the circumstances]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Ashwin, 1 run, very full and on the stumps, Ashwin's bat turns and he gets a single to long-on. Rubel hasn't given the batters anything to get under]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, low full toss, clipped to mid-wicket. 300 is up for India. Mild cheer goes up at the 'G'. Rubel has done well so far in this over]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Ashwin, 1 run, Rubel is doing a good job. In the blockhole, Ashwin deep in the crease and wristing it to mid-on. Again just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, very full and on off, no timing on the big hit, single to extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Ashwin, 1 run, Mortaza applauds that effort from Taskin. That's good to see. The youngster has just finished his spell and he cannot run and take the catch at third man. It was ramped by Ashwin and a quicker fielder would've got there, the ball bounces in front of Taskin as he stumbles and slips while running forward. They are happy with just a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rubel Hossain [9.0-0-50-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Dhoni, <b>out</b> Caught by Nasir Hossain!! Nasir keeps his head as others are losing theirs in the field. Short and cramping Dhoni for room, he swivelled for a big pull, the ball went off the thick outside half, more of a slice and point running back takes it well. Kept his eyes on the ball and took it comfortably. <b>Dhoni c Nasir Hossain b Taskin Ahmed 6(11)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Taskin Ahmed to Dhoni, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Dhoni, 2 runs, very full and on the stumps, Dhoni went for a big hoick, but it ran off the inside half, maybe he was looking for the helicopter as well, he was deep in the crease and he gets two to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, slower delivery from Taskin Ahmed, heaved away to deep mid-wicket, Kayes this time has an easier job and keeps it to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Ravindra Jadeja, <b>FOUR</b>, Imrul Kayes, better win it for Bangaldesh with the bat. That won't make Mortaza happy. It will make him mad. Already Mortaza is seething with rage. It was a simple slide and stop, but Kayes after getting across to his right from deep mid-wicket, allowed the ball to slip under his body. Got the slide right, but incomprehensibly allowed the ball to escape. Retrieves the ball and throws it back. The camera pans to Mortaza, but I didn't pick up anything from him]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Ravindra Jadeja, <b>FOUR</b>, Ravindra Jadeja now gets four. Taskin Ahmed did well to follow the batsman, who was backing away, but bowled it full, which was the mistake, allowed Jadeja to clip it wide of backward square leg, inside the ring, beats deep square leg running to his left. Taskin Ahmed wears a disappointed look as he walks back]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Ravindra Jadeja, 2 runs, Taskin Ahmed shakes his head and the Bangladeshi fielding has gone to pieces. Chipped in front of mid-off, the fielder didn't need to shy as Ravindra Jadeja was well in, does so and ends up giving away an extra run, as there was no-one backing up. Very poor from Bangladesh]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[47.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, yorker length outside off, jammed out to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Ravindra Jadeja, <b>FOUR</b>, that is thumped by Ravindra Jadeja. Down the track and he belts the length ball wide of the diving cover, no chance for long-off, running across. The fielder at cover could've done a much better job at the edge of the circle]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Ravindra Jadeja, <b>FOUR</b>, Shakib has beaten Ravindra Jadeja, but the batsman has got a boundary. Jadeja was looking to come down the track, it was fraction short, so he went back and edged the cut, deflected off Rahim's pad and raced away past the short third inside the ring. Shakib has a wry smile on his face]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Dhoni, 1 run, yorker length outside off, Dhoni took two steps forward and his ugly hack across the line, sees him get a thick inside half to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Dhoni, no run, again well bowled Shakib. Sees Dhoni charging and drags the length back, Dhoni has to adjust and hits it straight back at Shakib]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Dhoni, no run, slower and well bowled by Shakib, Dhoni has to adjust and pushes it softly to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan [9.0-0-48-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Taskin Ahmed finally gets some solace. He gets Rohit. In the blockhole, Rohit was trying to jam it out, with an angled bat, Rohit jammed it out, but the ball hit the turf and then the stumps. Taskin Ahmed does a Akhtar as he unveils his aeroplane celebration with both arms stretched out wide. <b>Rohit b Taskin Ahmed 137(126) [4s-14 6s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, no run, makes room to go over cover, but hits it uppishly, mistimed and it falls in front of Shakib at cover, who got his body behind the ball and stopped it. Rohit sends Dhoni back]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, Rohit is just toying with a young Taskin Ahmed. He is reading him like a book. Anticipates that the bowler may bowl the slower delivery, shuffles across and then picks the back-of-the-hand slower delivery, it sits up short for him to pull over square leg, no-one there and it dribbles away. Taskin Ahmed under huge pressure now]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, <b>SIX</b>, how well is Rohit hitting them? Very well. Just a forward press and then slams it across the line over wide long-on, caught in the crowd by a young Sardar. Taskin Ahmed guilty of bowling too short and Rohit was waiting for it. The bat may have turned on impact, but enough timing on the shot to clear the long boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, <b>wide</b>, banged in very short and Rohit leaves. Wide called for height and the right call too as it was way over the head]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, no run, Rohit missed out there, slower delivery outside off, width outside off, short too, Rohit cuts and picks out point]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Dhoni, 1 run, short and hurried onto Dhoni, who mistimes the pull to deep mid-wicket, wants two, but Rohit sends him back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[45.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, 'save your legs Rohit Sharma, don't run' says Nasser on air! So effortlessly played and perfect description from Nasser. It was on a good length and outside off, may have been the slower delivery as well, Rohit just lazily punched it wide of cover and split mid-off too. Both were inside the ring and Rohit continues to churn out boundaries]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Dhoni, 1 run, short and down leg, Dhoni swivel-pulls, but finds fine leg, single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, 1 run, slower delivery outside off, Rohit calmly knocks it wide of point, takes the single on offer]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, now pulls through mid-wicket. Knew Rubel will bowl short after getting hit for a six and murders a short-arm pull, sat back and hammered it]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, <b>SIX</b>, fabulous shot! Rubel misses his length and Rohit hits the bowler for a six over long-off. Rubel failed to find the yorker, Rohit went deep in his crease and lofted it beautifully over long-off. Sweet timing and it went all the way. Dhoni walks up to him and punches gloves]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, no run, Rubel starts off well, right up there, Rohit drills it straight to the fielder at mid-off, inside the ring]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rubel Hossain [8.0-0-34-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Lots of hand waving was going on just before Taskin Ahmed bowled that final delivery of the over. There were too many people in the Bangladeshi team trying to set the field. That confused the bowler, but he held his nerve to finish the over with a dot]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Dhoni, no run, dug in short outside off, Dhoni reaches out and tries to upper cut, but can't connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, 1 run, slower, shortish delivery outside off, Rohit delays the cut and hits it to the right of short third, Dhoni told Rohit in Hindi - 'aa jaa, aa jaa' and Rohit makes it to the other end without any trouble at all]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, 2 runs, Dhoni is so quick. He races across for the second, the call was two right from the moment Rohit pulled it, wide of deep mid-wicket, the fielder did a good job but couldn't beat Dhoni. Two taken with ease in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Dhoni, 1 run, full and on the pads, clipped to deep square leg, only a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Dhoni, no run, width outside off, Dhoni went too hard on the cut and bottom-edged it back to Taskin Ahmed's left. Fielded by the bowler. Those two dots should help Bangaldesh]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Dhoni, no run, short of length on the pads, turned to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Taskin Ahmed [7.0-0-40-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, more class from Rohit. Just a back foot punch and he gets four. Past the diving cover to his left, once it beat the fielder inside the ring, had to beat long-off to his left as well, the distance that the fielder had to cover made it hard and the ball trickled into the ad-cushions. Didn't hit it hard, just timed it superbly and the outfield did the rest]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>MS Dhoni, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Raina, <b>out</b> Caught by Rahim!! Raina goes. Top-edged straight up in the air and a good catch by Rahim, slower off-cutter on the stumps, Raina looked for the big slog and got a heavy edge. Not easy to grab swirlers like that, but Rahim kept his cool and went back, got those big gloves around the ball and grabbed it. There were insects and debris flying around, but he didn't allow that to distract him. <b>Raina c Rahim b Mortaza 65(57) [4s-7 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mortaza to Raina, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Raina, no run, on a length and outside off, Raina wants to go over cover, but mistimes it to the right of the bowler. That came off the bottom of the bat. Mortaza fields]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Raina, 2 runs, just short of long-on charging forward. Raina uses his feet and mishits, but gets away as the ball didn't carry. The fielder didn't put in the dive, instead offered his body and it ricocheted away. They take two]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, 1 run, that will make Mortaza unhappy. And angry even more. Sarkar with the fumble after Rohit punched that towards mid-off, Sarkar got across and Rohit had said no for the single. But the fumble allows the single, what's more he throws to the wrong end, when a throw to the keeper could've produced something for Raina was running blind]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Raina, 1 run, slower delivery on leg stump, Raina makes room, but Mortaza follows him, clipped to deep square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Raina, 1 run, Raina comes down the track and takes it on the full, clipped to long-on. Good over from Shakib, just the four off it]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, 1 run, Rohit makes room and drives hard and straight to deep cover, only a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Raina, 1 run, pre-meditates the paddle, but Shakib bowls a low full toss, Raina early into the shot and off the toe-end of the bat and down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Raina, no run, Raina gets inside the line and goes for a big hoick, but misses, no appeal from the Bangladeshis, but it would've been sliding down]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, driven hard and straight to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, no run, Shakib beats Rohit with a ball that turns away a little, the turn beats the outside edge as Rohit went for the drive, Rahim whipped the bails off, but Rohit had gone nowhere, not even referred to the third umpire]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, 1 run, calmly knocks the ball to long-on and retains the strike with that run]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, <b>no ball</b>, 2 runs, there it is! Punches it through cover and gets there. Takes two and then after finishing the second, he leaps and punches the air. Removes the helmet, raises his bat to all corners of the 'G'. Takes in all the applause from the Indians. What is worse is that Mortaza only had four inside the circle. Basic error that and it's a <b>no-ball</b>. Well spotted by Gould. The fielder at sweeper charged at the ball and misfielded. The Indian contingent were on their feet as soon as Rohit reached his 100. Well played, in a pressure game]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit gets his 100!</b> He is punching the air in delight]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rohit is on 99. Crowd know that and cheer. What is the field that Mortaza has? Four inside the circle all on the off-side.]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Raina, 1 run, Raina makes room and looks for the big hit, but Mortaza slips in a slower delivery, pushed past the bowler's left]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, 1 run, Rohit is willing to be patient. He defends this in front of cover and sets off. Raina responds in kind and makes it easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Raina, 1 run, on a good length and on the pads, nudged through mid-wicket for a single, brings Rohit on strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, class from Raina. Shuffles across a bit and then goes over backward square leg in the ring. Controlled flick, even though it was in the air, no-one in the deep at deep square leg and Raina will get a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mortaza is again not happy with his fielders. He was moving one of them and didn't like that the fielder wasn't in the exact position he wanted him to be. Waves his hand angrily]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, 1 run, short and wide outside off, cut square of the wicket, just a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mashrafe Mortaza [8.0-0-49-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Forgot to add that India scored <b>50 in the batting powerplay</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, rubbish ball and Raina puts Shakib away. Down leg and short, Raina had all the time to rock back and choose his spot, he did so, sending the ball to the deep fine leg fence, over the man inside the ring at short fine. Shakib grimaces at the end of the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, 1 run, gets forward and softly pushes the tossed up delivery outside off into the gap at cover, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, now all the luck is with Rohit and India. A thick outside edge runs through the vacant slip and beats short third, fraction short outside off, Rohit cuts and gets lucky. Just a hit away now to get to his hundred]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Raina, 1 run, short and pulled straight to the fielder at deep backward square leg, <b>fifty</b> for Raina and he raises his bat to all corners of the ground. Another nice innings from the left-hander]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, 1 run, Rohit gets forward and eases a single to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[My apologies to Gould. It was Aleem Dar who signalled no-ball from square leg. He had the hand up straightaway and that prompted Gould to signal no-ball. Dar seems to have lost all his confidence in recent times. Did the wasp bite have something to do with it? He could've waited a bit longer and then referred it upstairs, if he wasn't sure. Anyway let's move on]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Raina, 1 run, sliding on, nudged to backward square leg, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan [7.0-0-32-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Raina, 1 run, good length on the stumps, tucked to mid-wicket, retains the strike with that run]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, Raina rubs more salt into the wound. This was overpitched outside off and Raina leant forward to drive wide of mid-off, got it in the gap and the quick outfield does the rest]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Raina, 2 runs, short outside off, Raina pulls and top-edges it, mid-on running back cannot get back in time and catch it. Shakib didn't dive, he just watched the ball lob over him. Raina now gets away. No luck for Rubel]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, <b>no ball</b>, 1 run, <b>caught and it's a no-ball!</b> That is a shocking decision from Ian Gould. Well below the waist. Gould has got that wrong. Roar from the Indians in the crowd. They saw the hand stretched from Gould and went ballistic. Rubel is a disappointed man. He takes a deep breath at the top of his mark. Low full toss, swung straight to the fielder at deep square leg, Rohit lost his shape and one hand came off the bat handle as he swung. Luckily he gets away with one. Bangladesh <b>don't have a review left</b> too, to challenge that call. Could still prove to be a big moment, and a turning point come the end of the game]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, no run, back of a length outside off, Rohit opens the face of the bat and guides it to the left of point, who dives and fields. Good stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Raina, 1 run, short of length outside off, Raina punches it to the left of mid-off for another single]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Rohit gets forward and drives to the left of mid-off, moves into the nineties]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, 1 run, Rohit gets forward and then dabs that good length delivery outside off, into the vacant cover region for an easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Raina, 1 run, on the pads, nudged to the right of short fine running across]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, 1 run, short of length outside off, Rohit opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now a slip is brought in]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, well played by Rohit. It bounced from a back of a length and straightened too, Rohit adjusted well and didn't jab at it, controlled stroke through vacant slip, beats third man and leaves Taskin Ahmed disappointed]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Raina, 1 run, on the pads, worked away to deep backward square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players are back on the field. The Bangladeshis are stretching and doing a bit of warming up. Taskin and Mortaza have a chat. And there come the batsmen. They are slowly walking in. Ian Gould has to go back inside and call them in. Mortaza looks unhappy with that. Tardy from Raina and Rohit. They should've been there along with the Bangladeshis. Team director, Ravi Shastri looks a bit nervy. He is twiddling his thumbs. As soon as he sees the camera is on him, he puts on a more cool face.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nice to see a Bangladeshi player walk up to Raina and check on him while he was walking back. Raina was gesturing that everything was fine. <b>Harsha</b> had this to say when he saw the physio on air: 'The physio can stay there, the patient is coming to him.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>17:31 Local Time, 06:31 GMT, 12:01 IST:</b> The lights are on at the 'G' and the clouds are passing. As I type this, the umpires are back out there and the news is that they are restarting in four minutes time. A cheer goes up on the ground after the umpires are seen on the ground. 'They should've listened to you Warnie' says Harsha on air.]]></line><line><![CDATA[What has happened here? Raina isn't happy. He is grimacing. Hoho! It has started to <b>rain</b> as well. Shane Warne reckons it will be a five-ten minute stop. Doesn't think it will rain for a long time. The physio was waiting to come in and check on Raina, but he was stopped by the rain. The batsmen are walking back and the square has been covered now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Raina, 2 runs, Raina patted that with soft hands in front of long-on and wide of deep mid-wicket. Two was the call and they complete two easily. Rohit was the one running to the danger end and he made it in time]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Taskin Ahmed [6.0-0-30-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Raina, 1 run, Raina went for a big hoick over mid-wicket, but failed to time it properly, gets a single though to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, 1 run, short outside off, Rohit slashes and gets it wide of backward point, a single to square third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bangladesh seem to have lost the plot after the second drinks break. They are leaking runs, the fielding has been sloppy. The body language too isn't good as fingers are being pointed in all directions]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Raina, 1 run, turns the strike over with a nudge to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, gift for Raina and he won't miss out. Low full toss down leg, it needed bat and Raina provided that with a clip, beating short fine inside the ring. Lots of hand-waving going on at the moment from the Bangladeshis]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Rohit gets forward to drive to mid-off, Shakib is standing at the edge of the circle and it's an easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Raina, 1 run, full and on the stumps, Raina went for a big drive and inside-edged it through backward square leg, there were thoughts of a second, but that was sniffed out quickly by the fielder running across]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rubel Hossain [6.0-0-14-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, calculated hit and Rohit gets a boundary. Knows that he has to get it over the men inside behind square and opts for the sweep, kneels down and hits it well, that will be 11 runs off the over. India getting a move on now]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, no run, pushed back to the bowler as Rohit lunged forward to meet the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, no run, angling in and extra bounce for Shakib, but down leg, Rohit is hit on the body as he failed to turn it to leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shakib from round the wicket to Rohit]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Raina, 1 run, flicked through mid-wicket, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Raina, no run, softly taps it beside his feet as Shakib slows it up]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Raina, <b>SIX</b>, Raina goes over long-on. On the boundary. Comes down the track and lofts Shakib all the way. The fielder is there with the Indians in the crowd behind him, but he watched it sail over his head. Once again Raina targetting the bowler off the first delivery of the over. Connected well and had to as it was a big boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan [6.0-0-21-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, no run, on the pads, clipped to square leg, didn't hit the gap there]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rohit is having a look at the field as Mortaza takes his time to bowl this final delivery]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Raina, 1 run, another cutter from Mortaza, that stopped on Raina who adjusts and dabs it with soft hands, in front of short third]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Raina, no run, short of length on the pads, whipped straight to the fielder at backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, Mortaza is a frustrated man. He wants to know how that has gone to the boundary. He stretches his arms wide and wants an answer. It was a slower delivery outside off, Raina opens the face of the bat and splits backward point and short third, right in the gap as the former dived across, while the latter ran after the ball, but couldn't stop it. The quick outfield takes it all the way. The fielders are on the ground and don't want to look at Mortaza]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Raina, no run, slower delivery from Mortaza, defended to the left of Mortaza]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely way to begin the powerplay. Raina shimmies down the wicket and goes for his favorite inside-out shot over cover, everyone are in on the off-side and Raina knew that. Beautifully played and deliberately hit over the infield. The Indian dug-out applaud that shot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Batting powerplay time!</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Raina, 1 run, tossed up outside off and Raina gets forward to drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Raina, no run, down leg, Raina can't glance it away, Rohit doesn't want the leg bye as Rahim moves quickly to his right]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, 1 run, Rohit lunges out and push-drives to the right of cover diving across, single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Raina, 1 run, shortish down leg, whipped off the back foot to deep mid-wicket, Rohit wants two, but Raina sends him back now]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Raina, no run, Raina comes down the track and pushes it to the left of Nasir Hossain who runs around and makes a half-stop, recovers well, Raina wanted the single, but then seeing Nasir field, he decided against it]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Raina, no run, sliding on, Raina defends off the back foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, no run, on a good length and outside off, Rohit dabs straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, delicate stuff from Rohit. There was no width on that at all from Mortaza, but he opens the face of the bat and plays a cute tap to the right of the diving Rahim, played ever so late and that's a boundary of the highest class]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Raina, 1 run, Raina opens the face of the bat and angles the bat to run it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Raina, no run, now Mortaza beats Raina on the drive, full and outside off, Raina went for a big drive and missed. Carries nicely to Rahim]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Raina, no run, that pitched just a millimetre outside leg and that saves Raina who had shuffled way too across and got struck right in front. The bat came around the front pad and the ball pinged the pad. Gould if he has given it for pitching outside leg, then fab decision for him. The decision left the Bangladeshis and Mortaza stunned. Disappointment shown too]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mortaza goes up for a review against Raina. For a lbw. Raina shuffled across a long way and missed. Gould didn't give it out. No bat. 'Definitely no bat involved in that, bat seems to have hit pad,' says the third umpire. '<b>Pitching outside leg</b>, so you can stay with your original decision Ian, I will let you know when the camera is on you. You are on camera now and you can make the signal now,' signs off the third umpire. So Raina will survive. Loud roar from the Indians in the crowd. Just a millimetre outside leg. Mortaza can't believe it. As do the Bangladeshis in the crowd. So close!]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Raina, no run, good length on middle and leg, turned to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Raina, 1 run, that was just a defensive stroke, but it races past Nasir Hossain's right and beats his dive]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, 1 run, down leg, nurdled to backward square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Raina, 1 run, full on the pads, flicked to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Raina, no run, angled in from round the wicket, Raina nudges it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Raina, no run, tossed up outside off, Raina softly taps to cover after reaching out]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, 1 run, Rohit gets forward and eases a drive to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Rohit gets forward to drive and plays it to square third man, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, no run, on a good length and outside off, Rohit opens the face of the bat and defends to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, 2 runs, back of a length outside off, turned in front of deep square leg, Rohit slipped while turning back, but made it. The throw came to the other end and a <b>direct hit</b> would've made things interesting for Raina was struggling to make it]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Raina, leg byes, 1 run, Raina shuffles across and misses the leg-side clip, off the pad and Rahim diving to his right, can't stop it cleanly]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, 3 runs, sloppy from Bangladesh. It was wristed to mid-on's right, it was always a single, the throw came to Rahim on the bounce, who failed to collect and there was no one backing up as well, they take two more. Mortaza isn't pleased]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, very poor delivery from Mortaza, short and wide outside off, Rohit rocks back and cuts hard, over point, who leapt high to his right, but it was always going over his hand. Sweeper can't get there too. Good start after the break for India. That was a nothing ball and duly dispatched]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mashrafe Mortaza [5.0-0-25-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[At the other end, Shakib Al Hasan also bowled a few tight overs and was rewarded with the wicket of Shikhar Dhawan. To make it even better for Bangladesh, Taskin Ahmed sent Ajinkya Rahane back to the pavilion. It has been a superb comeback from them. For India, Rohit Sharma looked to hold the innings together and notched up a fine fifty.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here is <b>Bharath Ramaraj's</b> analysis for the last 15 overs: Rubel Hossain bowled with fire and aggression to snare the key wicket of Virat Kohli. Kohli has a habit of playing away from the body and poking at deliveries bowled on a fourth or fifth stump line. Today too he paid the price for playing away from the body. However, the credit has to go to Rubel for pushing Kohli back and then pitching it up to produce the edge. Rubel is skiddy through the air and on a drop-in pitch, he is proving to be effective. Rubel has looked to attack the stumps and surprise the batsman with the odd bouncer. Interestingly, Rubel didn't bowl with the new ball. Maybe it was due to the fact that he doesn't like to bowl with the white new ball. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> again]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, 1 run, Rohit hits that to long-on, and takes a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Raina, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Raina pushes it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, 1 run, Nasir Hossain was going to his right and Rohit played it to his left, the bowler moved to his left and dived, but cannot stop the ball, single given away]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, <b>wide</b>, fired down leg, called wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Raina, 1 run, Raina makes room slightly and dabs that softly in front of short cover, quick single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Raina, no run, Raina lunges forward and gets forward to drive back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, 1 run, Rohit plays for the spin and closes the face of the bat early, but it goes straight on and the ball goes off a thick leading edge, along the ground to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged</b> and through where a second slip would've been. Raina going hard on the cover drive and edging it. Played well away from the body and the angle across him made it difficult for him to control the stroke. Taskin Ahmed hides his face with his hand in disappointment]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, 1 run, slower delivery outside off, well outside off in fact and Rohit reaches out to squeeze it wide of the backward point fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[Backward point, point, cover and mid-off all in the ring for Rohit]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, no run, pitched up outside off, Rohit drills that well, but picks out mid-off, either side of the man and it would've been a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rohit has done well to hang in there and grit a fifty out. He hasn't been in the greatest of nicks in the tournament, but in a knockout game, with his team under pressure, has got a start. India badly need him to kick on and if he does so, he has the capability to go big, once he is set. With Rahane too gone, it is imperative for Rohit to stay till the end and anchor India to a defendable total]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, no run, back of a length outside off, Rohit is on the hop and mistimes the cut, chopped to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Raina, 1 run, short and down leg, pulled straight to the fielder at fine leg, Raina swivelled on the shot and missed out]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place for the left-handed Raina]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Raina, no run, on a good length and outside off, Raina opens the face of the bat and defends to the right of point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Coming back to the celebrations after the Rahane wicket, there was one chest-bump between Taskin and Mortaza, before Mortaza wanted a reprise of the act. That's when it got too exciting for the both of them and actually both fell to ground. Nothing serious though. No damage done too]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, no run, Rohit shows the full face of the bat and drives it back to Nasir Hossain]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Raina, 1 run, gets forward and looks to drive, off the inside edge and goes to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dar is clearly troubled by that wasp bite. He goes up to Gould and shows him the back of his neck area. Stoppage in play as Dar seeks some medical attention. Will the reserve umpire come out? No. Dar is set to continue]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Raina, byes, <b>FOUR</b>, Dar has made a mistake there. Down leg, Raina got a faint tickle on the leg-side glance and it hit the pad of Rahim before running away. Raina pointed out to Dar that he got bat on that, but Dar has more important things on his mind at the moment]]></line><line><![CDATA[Looks like an insect has bitten Aleem Dar. Slight stoppage in play. He gets it checked from the bowler. Dar is grimacing and looks uncomfortable out there. For now he allows the bowler to bowl]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Raina, no run, driven back to the bowler, that's three dots in a row]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Raina, no run, down leg and swept straight to the fielder at short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Raina, no run, gets forward and pushes it to mid-on, no chance of a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Nasir Hossain [5.0-0-21-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Look at those celebrations from Taskin Ahmed and Mortaza. Taskin Ahmed couldn't contain his excitement after getting the wicket and ran up to his skipper to celebrate. There were a couple of chest-bumps between the two and off the second, Taskin Ahmed went to ground. Funny! But he has a smile on his face even as he goes to ground. That chest-bumping reminded me of the <b>Leander Paes-Mahesh Bhupathi duo</b> who perfected that for India]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rahane, <b>out</b> Caught by Shakib!! Rahane has thrown it away. Wanted to go over mid-off, tried to play on-the-up and the bat face turned on impact, the ball lobs to the left of mid-off, where Shakib runs and then takes it, before tumbling over. Rahane never looked at ease today and the pressure got to him eventually. Bangladesh chip away. <b>Rahane c Shakib b Taskin Ahmed 19(37) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Taskin Ahmed to Rahane, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, 1 run, shortish outside off, pulled to deep mid-wicket, Rohit controlled the shot and kept it down with a roll of the wrists]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rahane, 1 run, back-of-the-hand slower delivery outside off, Rahane stands tall and punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rahane, no run, pitched up outside off, Rahane's one hand comes off the bat handle as he tamely drives to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in again for Taskin Ahmed against Rahane]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, 1 run, short outside off, pulled to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely flick. It was a tad too straight and on off and middle, Rohit played a delightful flick through mid-wicket, beat the chasing fielder easily, timing, balance and head position perfect on that shot. Breaks the shackles a bit with that boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rahane, no run, on the back foot and punched back to the bowler who fields on his followthrough]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rahane, no run, nurdled to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, 1 run, Rohit raises his bat and punches the gloves with Rahane, who pats him as well. <b>26th fifty for Rohit</b>. Gets there with a back foot punch to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rahane, 1 run, half-tracker from Shakib and Rahane has hit that straight to the fielder at deep square leg, on the bounce, he could've hit it anywhere, but chose the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, 1 run, comes down the track and goes inside out, uppishly hit, but in the gap to deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, no run, Rohit gets forward and pushes it to the right of Shakib who fields]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>first boundary in 66 balls!</b> And it has come via a thick outside edge. Taskin Ahmed had a slip stationed all over, but in order to protect the over, Mortaza moves the man and it has gone right through where a second slip would've been. Thick outside edge as Rahane punched and third man had no chance. Taskin Ahmed is a disappointed man, with a double-teapot pose]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rahane, 2 runs, the 100 has come up in the 26th over, Rahane gets forward and clips it to the left of deep mid-wicket, easy two. The Indians in the crowd cheer, but not too loudly]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rahane, no run, he still can't get the ball in the gap, wristed from outside off, straight to the fielder at square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[I sense Rahane is getting a bit itchy out there]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rahane, no run, full and on off and middle, clipped straight to the fielder at mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[Something's gotta give, I feel]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rahane, no run, on a good length and outside off, Rahane gets forward and pushes it to mid-off, no chance of a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rahane, no run, Rahane was lining up for the big hit, but saw the length and punched it back to Taskin Ahmed]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, no run, more good fielding by short fine, diving to his left, keeps Rohit at his end. Swept to the fielder's left and he did well. Rahane sent Rohit back. Another tidy over comes to an end]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, no run, Rohit skips out and has to defend it back to Shakib as he isn't to the pitch of the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, no run, tossed up outside off, Rohit goes for a big drive and the ball comes off the inside edge, rolls to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rahane, 1 run, turned softly and wide of backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, 1 run, soft hands and into the gap wide of short cover, single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rahane, leg byes, 1 run, Rahane comes down the track and can't get bat on the clip, the ball rolls off the pads to the right of Rahim, quick single taken]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Here's <b>Rajaraman</b> with more about the present weather in MCG: Medium (60%) chance of showers, most likely during the afternoon and early evening. There is a chance of a thunderstorm during the afternoon and early evening. Winds northerly 25 to 35 km/h increasing to 35 to 50 km/h in the morning then shifting cooler south to southwesterly 25 to 35 km/h in the late afternoon. It is grey all over and the floodlights are on.]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, no run, Rohit gets forward and wrists that well, but hasn't hit the gap, straight to the fielder at mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, no run, short of length on off, Rohit defends it back to Taskin Ahmed]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rahane, 1 run, angling in, Rahane gets forward and wrists it in the gap at short mid-wicket, easy single that time]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rahane, no run, Rahane gets an inside edge onto the pads, as he flicks, the ball goes to the right of square leg. Rohit isn't switched on and sends Rahane back]]></line><line><![CDATA[Attacking captaincy by Mortaza. He is not giving the easy singles away. Kept fielders inside the ring. Has given Taskin Ahmed a slip. Pressure building slightly on India]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rahane, no run, back of a length outside off, Rahane rolls his wrists and turns it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rahane, no run, on a good length and outside off, Rahane gets forward and plays a nice-looking drive, but straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Taskin Ahmed [2.0-0-10-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rahane, 1 run, Rahane gets forward to flick and misses, Rahim tries to grab the ball, but can't and they take a single to short third man. Did Rahane get a slight inside edge onto the pads? Aleem Dar makes no signal, so it will be runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rahane, no run, turned to short mid-wicket's right, there was a single there, but Rohit isn't interested. He sends back Rahane who took a few steps out of his crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, 1 run, Rohit opens the face of the bat and taps the ball into the gap at cover-point, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rahane, 1 run, had Rahane missed the sweep, that would've been close, he knelt down and got a thin edge onto thigh pad, gets a single to short fine. There was an appeal, but Aleem Dar spotted the edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rahane, 2 runs, driven past the diving short cover's left, two to deep extra cover, by the time the sweeper comes around]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Rohit gets forward and drives to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, 1 run, angling in, worked away to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, no run, too close to play the dab to third man, also point has moved to almost a gully now, played to that man]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rahane, 1 run, short of length outside off, punched well off the back foot to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rahane, no run, on a good length and outside off, Rahane shows the full face of the bat and gets forward to defend it back to Rubel]]></line><line><![CDATA[I had a look again at Rubel's reaction after getting Kohli out. He moved towards Kohli and it was Taskin and Rahim who surrounded him and calmed him down, not Mortaza. Apologies for the initial mistake]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rahane, no run, short of length on the middle and leg, turned to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, 1 run, short of length outside off, dabbed to the left of backward point, quick single taken]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, 1 run, shortish on the stumps, Rohit goes back and punches it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, no run, Rohit wants to push that in the gap on the off-side, but can't do so. Shakib keeping it on a string this over]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, no run, slower and on the stumps, calmly defended]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rahane, 1 run, well tossed up on the stumps, Rahane gets forward and eases it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rahane, no run, angling in, Rahane softly nudges it to the short backward square fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rahane, no run, tossed up outside off, pushed back to Shakib]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[It has gotten a bit more dark and dull at the 'G'. For the uninitiated I'm referring to the MCG as the 'G'. Basically saving time and my fingers as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rahane, 1 run, angling in, on a fuller length, flicked to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rahane, no run, nearly dragged on! Rubel has his hands on his head. Rahane done in by the low bounce, trying to cut and gets a bottom-edge that bounces into the ground and misses the stumps. So easily could've chopped it back on]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, 1 run, short outside off, Rohit lifts one leg up in the air and controls the pull to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rahane, 1 run, short of length on the hips, nudged off the hips to the right of square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now Mortaza has given Rubel two slips. Again pro-active captaincy. Bangladesh sense an opening here. They know that India would like to rebuild and this is the time to pile on the pressure and grab a few more wickets. Importantly, Rubel is bowling well, giving nothing away]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rahane, no run, pitched up on the stumps, Rahane drives without any timing to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rahane, no run, Rahane shuffles across and then presents the full face of the bat before defending to mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Coming back to the Kohli wicket, Mortaza roared and ran up to Rubel to congratulate him. As Kohli was walking off, Rubel wanted to continue his celebrations and moved towards the batsman, looking to give the departing Kohli more lip, but Mortaza came across and stopped his bowler. Sensible thing from Mortaza for Kohli could well have reacted angrily had Rubel met him]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, no run, lunges forward and pushes it back to Shakib]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, no run, only Rahim appealed there, Rohit down the track and pad-batted that as he wasn't to the pitch of it. Well down the track, highly optimistic from Rahim]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rahane, 1 run, shortish outside off, punched off the back foot wide of the diving short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rahane, no run, Rahane wants to get forward, but has to go back as the ball skids on, blocked]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rahane, no run, tossed up and sliding on from round the wicket, Rahane gets forward and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, 1 run, on middle and leg, turned to deep backward square leg, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Good set-up by Rubel for he tempted Kohli with that outswinger. Early on Kohli is suspect to the full one outside off, his technique isn't tight to the outswinger as one saw on the England tour where James Anderson relentlessly exploited that flaw in his game. Also good captaincy by Mortaza, keeping a slip in place and backing his bowler. The Bangladeshis in the crowd went wild when Kohli got out.]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rahane, no run, short of length outside off, Rahane shoulders arms and lets it go. A sighter first up for him]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ajinkya Rahane, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Kohli, <b>out</b> Caught by Rahim!! Rubel is pumped and is giving Kohli a send-off. Big moment in the game. After bowling short and back of a length all over, he pitches the ball up and outside off, gets a bit of movement away, tempts Kohli to play away from the body and the outside edge is nicely held by Rahim diving to his right. Rubel running forward pumped his fists and looked at the departing batsman. Kohli just put his head down and walked off. <b>Kohli c Rahim b Rubel 3(8)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rubel to Kohli, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Kohli, no run, short of length outside off, nips back in a tad and cramps Kohli for room, he defends in front of point, looks for a quick single, but it isn't there]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Kohli, no run, punched off the front foot, but straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Kohli, no run, on a good length and outside off, Kohli gets forward and defends to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Kohli, no run, short of length outside off, Kohli gets right behind the line and defends it back to Rubel]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Kohli, <b>wide</b>, very short and Kohli ducks under that, called a wide]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Kohli, 1 run, gets forward and drives to long-off, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Kohli, no run, glanced to short fine, sent back by Rohit]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Kohli, 2 runs, very full outside off, Kohli places a cover drive to deep extra cover, hurries back for the second, is off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Virat Kohli, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Dhawan, <b>out</b> Stumped!! Dhawan overbalanced on the drive and is stumped. Went for a big drive to a tossed up delivery outside off and missed. The back foot is outside the line and Rahim is quick to whip the bails off. Replays show that Dhawan made room and actually one hand came off the bat handle as he went for the big drive. Good work by Rahim too. <b>Dhawan st Rahim b Shakib 30(50) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shakib to Dhawan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Stumped!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rahim has gone up for a stumping appeal against Dhawan. He is confident. Pats Shakib and looks like Dhawan's foot is on the line. No problems with the front foot. 'It's a fair delivery' says the third umpire. Dhawan is out. 'I'm happy with that picture and I'm going to give the batsman out, thank you' reckons the third umpire. Dhawan is gone and cue for wild roaring from the Bangladeshis at the 'G']]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Dhawan, 2 runs, tossed up outside off, Dhawan opens the face of the bat and square drives to deep point, easy two]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, 1 run, floated up on middle and leg, Rohit gets forward and eases a drive to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[If India pile up a massive total, it won't be easy for Bangladesh to chase down the target under lights. Even in the 1990s, there was a feeling that under lights at the MCG, the ball tends to zip through the wicket and batsmen find it difficult to stamp their authority on the proceedings.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here is <b>Bharath Ramaraj's</b> analysis for the first 16 overs: On a good track for batting, Bangladesh's pacers bowled on both sides of the wicket and the openers duly took advantage of it by unfurling a series of boundaries. Rohit Sharma, in particular, essayed some imperious drives and forceful pull shots. Rohit also played with soft hands and handled the pacers with aplomb. On the other hand, Shikhar Dhawan looked to play strokes square of the wicket through the off-side. With Taskin Ahmed extracting a bit of bounce,  Bangladesh perhaps missed a trick by not positioning a fielder at gully for Dhawan. Interestingly, Mortaza introduced Nasir Hossain into the attack in the sixth over of the innings. Nasir was able to join the dots and build a bit of pressure on the batsmen.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are called for at the 'G']]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, 1 run, on a good length and outside off, Rohit stylishly opens the face of the bat and steers it down to third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Dhawan, 1 run, full on the pads, flicked to deep mid-wicket, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Dhawan, no run, Mortaza is walking up to Rahim and asks his keeper whether Dhawan had nicked it. Rahim says no and Mortaza walks back. It was down leg and short, Dhawan swivelled on the hook and missed. <b>Snicko doesn't show any spike</b>. Rahim went up immediately and Rubel followed suit. Ian Gould shook his head and he was proved right eventually. The ball was close to the bat, but <b>no edge</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Dhawan, no run, short ball outside off, Dhawan arches back and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third time that Dhawan has pulled out. Boos echo around the 'G'. Dhawan apologised immediately and it was the debris flying around that caused the distraction. Rubel though isn't pleased]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Dhawan, no run, good short ball, catches Dhawan by surprise, Dhawan wanted to pull, but the ball caught up with him very quickly, in the end he jabs it and softly, the ball hits the splice and goes down instantly]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Dhawan, no run, short of length on off, defended to backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, <b>SIX</b>, the pressure has been released. Rohit choosing the right time to go after Nasir Hossain, use of the feet and to the pitch, before smashing it straight back over the bowler's head. A flat hit and it goes all the way, into the sightscreen. That wakes the Indian crowd up, who had gone a bit silent of late]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, no run, turned to that short mid-wicket fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pressure building on India, just a bit. Good bowling by Bangladesh. Also it has gone a bit cloudy and gloomy at the 'G'. Breeze blowing too, flags are fluttering everywhere]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Dhawan, 1 run, skips out and takes it on the full, slammed to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Dhawan, no run, again down the track and pushed back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Dhawan, no run, uses his feet and flicks to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Dhawan, no run, pushed through, Dhawan defends to the left of Nasir Hossain]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Dhawan, 1 run, on the pads, softly nudged into the gap at mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Dhawan, no run, short of length on the stumps, defended to the left of Rubel]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhawan pulls out as Rubel runs in and that makes the bowler unhappy. He was about to hurl the ball into the ground in disgust. But doesn't do so. Some movement behind the bowler's arm and that irritates Dhawan.]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, 1 run, short of length outside off, Rohit opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Dhawan, 1 run, short on the hips, doesn't rise too high, Dhawan short-arm jabs a pull to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, 1 run, angling in, Rohit's bat face closes as he turns it in front of mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, no run, back of a length and outside off, tucks Rohit for room slightly, defended to point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Dhawan, no run, slower and Dhawan had to wait for it, punched to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, 1 run, punched off the back foot, past the dive of the short mid-wicket fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[Long-off back for Rohit. As is long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, no run, flighted outside off, defended to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Dhawan, 1 run, Dhawan uses his feet and push-drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Rohit lunges out to push to long-off, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, no run, that kept low, not good signs for the Bangladeshis later on, but Rohit got his bat down and defended it to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Nasir Hossain [3.0-0-11-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Dhawan, no run, solidly defended as he gets right behind the line. Rubel has a stare at Dhawan who doesnt't back down]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Dhawan, no run, Dhawan is crouching low, suggesting the ball kept low and beat him. The feet were stuck in lead as he went for a wooshy cut, but the ball skidded on and beat him. Wanted to play it late too, which meant the pace on the ball worked against him]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, 1 run, a huge grunt from Rubel as he delivers the ball, it is short outside off, pulled to deep mid-wicket, played with control]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, no run, Rubel hits the bat hard as Rohit presses forward to defend, off the splice and down to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, no run, pitched up outside off, Rohit wanted that to turn to leg, but didn't close the bat face, the ball ran off the toe-end to point, has a look at the end of the bat and grimaces]]></line><line><![CDATA[Slip in for Rubel]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rohit, no run, short of length outside off, Rohit plays beside the line of the ball and dabs that to backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rubel Hossain, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Rohit, 1 run, gets forward and eases a single to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Rohit, 2 runs, short on the stumps, Rohit pulls and the fielder from deep backward square leg runs to his left, dives and pulls it back to the other fielder. Lot of effort put in and the batsmen are happy with just two. Three was possible, but poor running]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Rohit, no run, Rohit is early into the push and the ball goes off a thick leading edge, but goes down quickly, fielded by the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Dhawan, 1 run, shortish on the stumps, whipped off the back foot to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mahmudullah is bowling from round the wicket with no-one catching behind the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Dhawan, no run, driven straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Dhawan, no run, high full toss and it's been driven straight back to the bowler. Dhawan missed out there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mahmudullah, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, no run, turned to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Dhawan, 1 run, gets forward and finds long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Dhawan, no run, driven to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, 1 run, half-tracker outside off and Rohit nearly gives Nasir Hossain a <b>caught and bowled chance.</b> Very lazy from Rohit as he flat-bats it softly, the ball carries in the air and to the right of the diving Nasir Hossain, who couldn't grab it one-handed, went for the catch, but the ball dipped and hit the turf. They take a single to long-on. Can't really call that a chance, but if Nasir Hossain had been a bit more athletic and anticipated, he could've had a chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Dhawan, 1 run, uses his feet and pushes it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, 1 run, Rohit pushes it to the right of the diving Nasir Hossain, the bowler can't stop it cleanly and it's a single to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Dhawan, no run, Dhawan gets forward and shows the full face of the bat to drive, but it is too well-timed and straight to the fielder at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Dhawan, no run, turned to the short mid-wicket fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[No slips now. A short mid-wicket and a short cover catching. Mortaza isn't running in. He is ambling in and looking to hit a good length. Also bowling a lot of cutters]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Dhawan, no run, short of length on the stumps, defended with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Dhawan, no run, short outside off, Dhawan went hard on the cut and bottom-edges it to Rahim, on the bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, that is well-timed! Another off-pace delivery, Dhawan waits for it and clips that in the air, through mid-wicket, Nasir runs after it and puts in the head-first dive, but the hands don't go in the right position, can't pull it back and the ball touches the ad-cushions]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Dhawan, 2 runs, looked like the cross-seam cutter from Mortaza, it stopped and bounced on Dhawan, who had decided to pull, irrespective of the length, shovels it over the man at mid-wicket running back, the ball clears him and they take a couple]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, Rohit goes over mid-off now. Down the track and goes a bit inside-out over the man, once he cleared the man it was four. Rohit was itching to get at Nasir Hossain and chose the right moment]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, no run, softly nudged to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Dhawan, 1 run, flatter and on the pads, turned to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Dhawan, no run, comes down the track and drives well, but finds cover once more]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Dhawan, no run, finds cover now]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Dhawan, no run, Dhawan gets an inside edge that goes between his legs and misses leg stump by a distance, Nasir Hossain and the close-in Bangladeshis were interested for a bit. Dhawan played that with an angled bat looking to defend to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Dhawan, 1 run, looked like the cutter, Dhawan waits on the shot and opens the face of the bat to steer it to third man, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhawan pulls away as Mortaza runs in. Not happy with movement behind the bowler's arm. That is sorted and we are ready to roll once again]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Dhawan, 2 runs, another back foot punch, wide of short cover and beats cover to his left. A couple it is as it is not so well-timed to reach the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Dhawan, no run, that stopped on Dhawan a tad, he ensures he doesn't punch too hard and hits that to the short cover fielder on the bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, Dhawan was cramped slightly on the cut, but he created his own room and punched it past the vacant short point position. It was on a back of a length and Dhawan timed the shot really well. Not sure why Mortaza moved that short point fielder to a short cover. It would've been fielded by that fielder, anyway Dhawan gets a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, 1 run, back of a length outside off, Rohit opens the face of the bat and dabs that down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[Interesting to see Mortaza give the ball to Nasir ahead of Shakib, that too in the powerplay. Even Rubel hasn't bowled till now. One plausible explanation for giving Nasir the ball, could be the left-handed Dhawan at the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, no run, full outside off, Rohit plays a solid front foot defence to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Dhawan, no run, short of length from round the wicket, punched to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, 1 run, Nasir Hossain runs to his right and dives, but cannot stop the single as the ball passes him]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, no run, Rohit is content to have a look at Nasir Hossain, pushed to the bowler's right]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, no run, pushed through outside off, Rohit comes on the front foot to defend it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Rohit, no run, tossed up outside off, Rohit gets forward to defend]]></line><line><![CDATA[Slip and a leg slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Dhawan, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Dhawan gets forward and drives to long-off, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Nasir Hossain, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Dhawan, 1 run, good running by Dhawan, just defended that well in front of mid-off and immediately said yes for the quick single. Easily done in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, 1 run, Dhawan has a smile and a thumbs up to Rohit. Dhawan slipped as the ball passed Mortaza, would've been in danger had Shakib from mid-on, had the presence of mind to see Dhawan slipping and thrown to the keeper, but Shakib fires in a meek throw to Mortaza, who too didn't realise that there was a chance of a run-out. By the time the throw came to the keeper, Dhawan was well home. <b>Half-chance gone for Bangladesh</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, no run, middle and leg line, on a good length, turned softly to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Dhawan, leg byes, 1 run, down leg, runs off the thigh pad as Dhawan misses out on the flick, they take a leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Dhawan, no run, short of length outside off, punched well, but straight to the fielder at short point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Dhawan, no run, gets a bit of indip and cramps Dhawan for room, defended back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Just a lone slip now for Mortaza. He has brought in a short point for Dhawan, removing the 2nd slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, no run, wayward but Taskin Ahmed gets away. Short and well outside off, Rohit didn't have anything to do with that, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, 2 runs, and he drifts onto leg, easy pickings for Rohit who clips the bowler through backward square leg, for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, no run, that's well bowled! Taskin Ahmed has pitched it up and got some late movement to beat Rohit's lazy drive. The feet didn't move and the ball beat the outside edge, not by much. That's where he should target more often, especially if he is getting swing and seam]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, no run, back of a length outside off, defended easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, Rohit is quick to pull! Was on the front foot and played it awkwardly, but got it to the deep backward square fence. The weight wasn't fully forward, but he somehow swivelled around and played it in the gap, beats the fielder at long leg easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rohit, no run, in the air, but doesn't carry to Taskin Ahmed on his followthrough. Rohit got forward to push and checked his shot, softened the defensive shot and the ball was fielded by Taskin Ahmed on the bounce]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Will keep an eye on Mortaza's reactions. He can get quite hot under the collar. We have seen that happening in this tournament earlier. Especially against Sri Lanka here when the red mist came out of his eyes]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, 1 run, well played by Rohit in the end. This delivery reared up on him from a back of a length and he did well to play with soft hands. Took the bottom hand out of the handle and kept it down, the ball bounces in front of 2nd slip and goes through the fielder's hands. Mortaza isn't impressed, but third man keeps it to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, no run, Mortaza has pulled his length back nicely after being a tad full off the first delivery, pushed towards mid-off off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, no run, on a good length and outside off, Rohit gets forward and defends to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, no run, back of a length outside off, Rohit punches to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, no run, short of length outside off, Rohit rises tall and defends it back to Mortaza]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, shot! Picture-perfect from Rohit. Got half-forward and offered the full face of the bat, the ball met the bat and off it went past the umpire, gave no chance to the chasing fielders. The Indian contingent clap with Rayudu leading the way]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, Taskin Ahmed spoils all the good work he had done in the over, by bowling a half-volley, Dhawan needed to middle that and put it in the gap and he did so with just a push-drive, into the gap at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Dhawan, no run, Taskin Ahmed gets away with a leg-side delivery, it swung for him and at pace, but went down leg, Dhawan failed to nail the flick and it rolled off the pad to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Dhawan, no run, back of a length outside off and Dhawan steers it from the crease to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Dhawan, no run, short of length outside off, good lines these from Taskin Ahmed, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Dhawan, no run, short of length and cramping Dhawan for room, who defends in front of point and looks for a quick single, not there]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Dhawan, no run, good start by Taskin Ahmed, he lets the short ball go, dug in outside off, Dhawan watches it, arches back slightly and lets it go. Carried well to Rahim]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Taskin Ahmed, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, no run, turned straight to the fielder at mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, leg byes, <b>FOUR</b>, a diving Rahim doesn't get there. Wrong line, down leg, brushes the pad of Rohit and beats the keeper to his left. All it needed was a faint tickle which came via the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, no run, Rohit is right in behind that, defended to cover from the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now Mortaza asks his keeper and the slip cordon to come up a bit]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, no run, Mortaza beats Rohit, but it doesn't carry to Rahim. Rohit played close to his body, but still the inswinger beat Rohit on the forward defensive. No pace from Mortaza, so it meant the ball bounced on the way to Rahim]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, no run, on a length and outside off, Rohit gets forward to defend to cover, looks for a quick single, but Dhawan isn't interested]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, super start for India! Long half-volley outside off from Mortaza, Rohit had to reach out and did so, bending his right-knee and creaming a square drive wide of point. Went all along the ground and raced away. The outfield looks in good condition too]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit and Dhawan are at the crease. Rohit is on strike. Mortaza will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhawan scored a hundred the last time he batted here. He is a big match player and Rohit would be looking to get his touch back. Sunny and very bright now. The countdown begins and ends quickly. Mortaza is warming up and is ready to go. What a game we have on hand. Two slips in place. Here we go then!]]></line><line><![CDATA[The two anthems are done. Magnificent atmosphere at the 'G' today. Even spread of Bangladeshi and Indian supporters in. Green vs Blue. Huge flags in their hands. Dhawan straps his gloves on and walks out along with Rohit. The Bangladeshis are in a team huddle and they break out of it with a spring in their step.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>India</b> (Playing XI): Shikhar Dhawan, Rohit Sharma, Virat Kohli, Ajinkya Rahane, Suresh Raina, MS Dhoni(w/c), Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Mohammed Shami, Umesh Yadav, Mohit Sharma]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangladesh</b> (Playing XI): Tamim Iqbal, Imrul Kayes, Soumya Sarkar, Mahmudullah, Shakib Al Hasan, Mushfiqur Rahim(w), Sabbir Rahman, Nasir Hossain, Mashrafe Mortaza(c), Rubel Hossain, Taskin Ahmed]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>India have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhoni:</b> "I think it just gets harder and harder. But the thing that makes it easy is, to make some good plans and execute them well because that makes life slightly easy. Other than that I don't think it gets easier. We will bat first. Big match, good wicket, put the runs on the board and look to defend it. Everyone is fit, that's one good thing and that is one thing that we emphasise a lot upon. We want all the players available for selection, fortunately we have been able to keep everyone fit. It's not really in our Indian fast bowling, to keep looking to bowl in the right areas. We have bowlers who have been brilliant, but in between they would try something and give loose deliveries to the batsmen. What this unit has done different from others is that they have kept it in the same area. Even if it's doing a bit, they want to hit the right area. That's a big development for us, not only in this format, it's something that we really need in Test venues also because it makes life a lot easier when you are playing outside the sub-continent. There is scope of improvement everywhere. You may be a good side, you may be playing good cricket, but there are still areas we can improve. If we can manage to do what we have been doing, we will be quite pleased. Not really (when asked if India were taking Bangladesh lightly), every team that has reached the quarter-final is a good side. Every team that participates in the World Cup is a good team. So we have to have that respect. But at the same time you have to be confident about your strengths and where you need to work on. So I feel every team is a good team."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mashrafe Mortaza</b>: "Definitely we are proud. This is the first time we are playing a quarter-final, so we are very positive and hopefully we will give our best today. We would have liked to bat first as well. Only one change, I am coming in place of Taijul (Islam). I am okay to go, hopefully I will give my best today. We have to stop twos and threes and we have to field well. We couldn't field well against Sri Lanka here, so hopefully we will do well today. Rubel (Hossain) and Taskin (Ahmed) are bowling over 142kph, so hopefully they will come with a good plan and deliver."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Toss time!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajaraman</b> adds that it's fine on the weather front for now, but there's some showers predicted later. Will it influence the decision of the captain winning the toss? The ground is filling up fast and there's plenty of support for Bangladesh as well. Should be a cracking atmosphere.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pitch report</b> by Dean Jones: 'This pitch was used recently for the Sri Lanka and Bangladesh game. Even covering of grass.' Except the pitch, stats, stats and more stats from Deano. Also praising the MCG rather than concentrating on the actual square. Lots of random babble and at the end he signs off with: 'bat first, no doubt for me.' Thanks Deano!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Our man <b>G Rajaraman</b> is at the ground and he says that both teams are warming up. It's a big match for Bangladesh, their 300th ODI and the first time they will be featuring in a knock-out match in the World Cup.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina</b> is quietly confident: "All World Cup games are very important. All matches are going in a pressure situation. We need to just go in there and play to our potential."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Quotes now. <b>Mashrafe Mortaza</b> isn't bothered by the past and wants to concentrate on the present: "2007 is a long way in the past. Thinking of it is not going to help us."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sourav Ganguly</b> feels that rain may help Bangladesh. "Rain is Bangladesh's best chance. The shorter the game the more competitive Bangladesh will be. In a curtailed match they will not need to sustain the momentum for 100 overs and that will help them."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather update:</b> There is a 70% chance of showers predicted in the afternoon/evening. A high of 32C is predicted but rain is expected to make an appearance in the afternoon and evening. Melbourne has been rainy and grey for a couple of days as well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangladesh:</b> Mortaza who missed the last game against New Zealand, will be back to lead the side. The rest of the side pick themselves except for one bowling spot. Arafat Sunny, Taijul Islam and Nasir Hossain are fighting for the one spot. It will be interesting to see whether Bangladesh go for a genuine bowler or stick with Nasir Hossain as he can bat as well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pre-match</b> team news, <b>India</b>: India aren't going to tinker with the winning combination, barring injury.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shakib is hoping there will be a strong Bangladeshi contingent in the crowd as well. "I have played in front of large crowds before but I think this will be different in the sense that the majority will be supporting the other team," he said. "However, this will be an occasion to treasure for the fans and I call upon every cricket follower to make it to the MCG on Thursday."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mortaza said it didn't matter who the fans would support. "The atmosphere will be electric and it will be a thoroughly enjoyable experience for everyone present," he said. "If you are in Melbourne, you should not miss getting a seat at the MCG on Thursday. This could be the last chance for some to become a part of the World Cup legacy. Fan support is important to every team and I believe the Bangladesh fans will come in numbers to cheer us."]]></line><line><![CDATA["The crowds have been outstanding and very supportive, and we look forward to similar encouragement when the Melbourne quarterfinal takes place," Dhoni was quoted as saying in an ICC release. "There are some excellent players on either side and I will encourage people to fill the MCG and enjoy what I think will be an excellent contest."]]></line><line><![CDATA[In a move to bring the crowds to watch the quarter-finals, after a disappointing turnout in the first quarter-final at the SCG, the ICC have roped in the services of India and Bangladesh captains Mahendra Singh Dhoni and Mashrafe Mortaza as well as Bangladesh allrounder Shakib Al Hasan to ask their fans to fill the Melbourne Cricket Ground for the ICC Cricket World Cup knockout quarter-final clash on Thursday.]]></line><line><![CDATA["It depends on the day, we need to start well. Whatever we do and if we keep doing that and we keep the momentum in our favour then anything is possible," he said.]]></line><line><![CDATA["And, so far in this World Cup, I think we're doing it. If we do exactly what we did against England or New Zealand, I think we'll have a very good game."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Meanwhile, Shakib Al Hasan has called for 'fearless cricket' against India. "I think we played fearless cricket (when Bangladesh beat India eight years ago) and we all want to play that brand of cricket that we played," Shakib told a media conference.]]></line><line><![CDATA["I'm not saying India will take Bangladesh lightly. In fact, India should not take Bangladesh lightly because at the end of the day, it's a game between two teams and anything can happen. Bangladesh surprised England and went right till the end against New Zealand where better captaincy could have forced a result in their favour. So India should not take them lightly, although on paper and just by statistics India are a far better side than Bangladesh."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sourav Ganguly</b>, writing exclusively on our site warned India not to take the Asian side lightly. "India play Bangladesh tomorrow in the second quarter-final of this World Cup and a lot of people might say that India are 'lucky' to have Bangladesh in the quarters. I would rather go the extra mile and say that India have earned their right to play Bangladesh in the quarter-finals, especially with the way they have played in the group stages. Six games out of six and they have got past every side convincingly, and they deserve to play Bangladesh in the quarter-finals."]]></line><line><![CDATA["We've played a Test Match here and faced Australia and South Africa in ODIs," Raina said of the MCG. "We've spent a lot of time in Australia over four and a half months now. We're used to the conditions more than other teams but we need to go there and play positive cricket. That's it. Keep it simple."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now let us turn our attention on all the talk ahead of the big quarter-final. News from the Indian camp first. "India will keep it simple against Bangladesh." Says Suresh Raina ahead of the game. "As a team, we have done really well in all departments. We took 60 wickets. The fast bowlers have done a lot of disciplined work. I think the credit goes to the staff. They've been doing a great job for us. When it comes to World Cup, you need to just play yourself in and look to have belief in yourself and you can win in any situation," Raina said.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Their batting still revolves around Shakib and Rahim, but it has been Mahmudullah who has been a revelation. His back-to-back hundreds against England and New Zealand showed his class and he will be a key man for them in the quarter-final too. Mashrafe Mortaza, Rubel Hossain and Taskin Ahmed have bowled well throughout the World Cup, barring the odd game and if the pitch helps them a bit, they could pose a few problems. Shakib with the ball is looked at to provide control and get the odd wicket or two. Mahmudullah will chip in with the ball too and would be the fifth bowler, should Bangladesh go in with only four bowlers.]]></line><line><![CDATA[That win confirmed their place in the quarter-finals and they played New Zealand next. Mahmudullah's second consecutive ton helped them recover after early blows and they fought all the way till the end. Only the ice-coolness of Daniel Vettori carried New Zealand over the line. Bangladesh finished fourth in the group and that meant a quarter-final at the 'G' against India.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangladesh:</b> Bangladesh started off their campaign on a winning note against Afghanistan, avenging their loss to the same side in the Asia Cup. Then they got a point as their game against Australia was washed out. That point was a bonus as they were up against a very strong Australian side. Sri Lanka brought them back to earth with a thumping win at the 'G' where the bowling and fielding of the Tigers went to pieces. But Bangladesh got their campaign back on track with a win against Scotland where they chased over 300. It was a superb chase and they carried that confidence into their next game against England. It was a winner-takes-it-all battle and Bangladesh held their nerve at the end to come out on top. Rubel Hossain was the star as he yorked James Anderson which sparked off wild celebrations.]]></line><line><![CDATA[There is a certain intensity and aggressiveness in the Indian bowling which was clearly missing in the Test and Tri-series in Australia. Ashwin is bowling as well as he has done in his career and with the fielding backing up the bowling, India have all the boxes ticked. They are riding high on momentum and it would take something special to stop them.]]></line><line><![CDATA[India look like a side at the top of their game. Dhawan has led from the front at the top with two hundreds and there have been hundreds too for Kohli and Raina. Rahane impressed against South Africa, while MS batted like he always does in a chase against Zimbabwe. Rohit Sharma is the one who needs some runs and the quarter-final might just be the day he gets the big runs. The bowling has been the major plus for India with the line-up taking all the 60 wickets on offer in the league stages.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Road to the quarter-final:</b> Played 6. Won 6. 100% record. That is India's record in this World Cup. It all began with a comprehensive win at Adelaide over Pakistan, followed by one more big win against South Africa at the 'G'. UAE were blown away at Perth, while they edged past West Indies at the same venue. Once the top spot was confirmed, India looked to end the group stages unbeaten and they completed that with wins over Ireland and Zimbabwe respectively. While Ireland was handled easily, the Zimbabwe game tested India. They were in trouble chasing, but Suresh Raina's ton and MS Dhoni's calmness ensured a win as the African side flagged at the end.]]></line><line><![CDATA[So we wrap the recap segment there and look at how both sides have got to the quarter-finals. Let's start with India.]]></line><line><![CDATA[He further continued with more gems flowing from his mouth: "Everyone did well, other than Sreesanth." Sehwag was the first to admit that this was a grudge match after the 2007 defeat. And he finished off with this: "They (Bangladesh) can compete in ODIs, but today they could not."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Redemption came in 2011 when India crushed Bangladesh in front of their home crowd at the Sher-e-Bangla National Stadium. It was the opening game of the 2011 World Cup and some termed it the game of Bangladeshi cricketers' lives. Sehwag and Kohli - on his World Cup debut hit hundreds as India racked up 370. Once such a total was put up, it was a no-contest. Sehwag was the star with the bat as he made 175 and his reaction was typical Sehwag - "I am happy that at least once in my career I have batted 47 overs."]]></line><line><![CDATA[When someone of the stature of Sachin Tendulkar is so deeply affected by a loss, then you can imagine the impact it has on the psyche. That is where Bangladesh's win ranks in terms of World Cup upsets. It made the entire country go wild with joy, while the reverse was true in India. The loss effectively knocked India's stuffing out. And it marked the slow, but sure end of two of India's finest batsmen - Sourav Ganguly and Rahul Dravid. The early exit set alarm bells ringing in India and the slow, but steady rebuilding of the ODI side began after the doomed campaign.]]></line><line><![CDATA["The game has been cruel to us and I want to stop. That was when he said, 'can you imagine in 2011 you are here at Wankhede stadium holding that beautiful trophy. That is when you should think of retiring'. That conversation really helped and it motivated me to go out and play with a purpose," the Mumbai-born cricketer said.]]></line><line><![CDATA["I still remember (after) 2007 (World Cup) when I came back home, I was so depressed and so upset with the way we had performed. I actually thought of retiring then. I called my brother over, Ajit, and told him that I do not want to continue," Tendulkar said.]]></line><line><![CDATA[While the Indian fan's reaction was to be expected. One man who was most affected by the untimely exit of his side was the legendary Sachin Tendulkar. Recently he revealed that he had been heartbroken by India's exit and wanted to quit the game altogether. Sachin was singled out for harsh criticism as he scored just seven and zero against Bangladesh and Sri Lanka respectively. But only his brother's persuasion forced Sachin to continue playing on.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Not only was Dhoni targetted but as were Dravid, Tendulkar, Sehwag and others. Posters, effigies and placards were burnt as a mark of protest at India's poor performance. Some even alleged that players spent more time appearing in advertisements than preparing for the World Cup. Typical Indian fan's overreaction!]]></line><line><![CDATA["They raised slogans and asked the Government to take back the plot allotted to Dhoni, who was out for a nought in Saturday's game in the West Indies. The police stepped up vigil at the site and Dhoni's home at Mecon in Ranchi."]]></line><line><![CDATA["In wicketkeeper M.S. Dhoni's hometown Ranchi, about two dozen people gathered near a house being built on a plot given to him by the Jharkhand Government and set afire an effigy to which the player's poster was pasted."]]></line><line><![CDATA[So we have seen how Bangladesh reacted. What about India then? This may shock you all. But this is a fact. MS Dhoni may have won everything that there is to win in ODI cricket, but the 2007 game against Bangladesh was one of his lowest points in his career. He was out for a 3-ball duck and saw his house vandalised after the defeat. Security cover was provided to Dhoni's parents after the incident. This is what The Hindu had to say about the incident.]]></line><line><![CDATA[So how did Bangladesh as a nation celebrate this win? Bangladesh had been under a state of emergency since January but that was all forgotten as thousands of jubilant fans celebrated into the wee hours, partying and shouting slogans in praise of their nation. Millions of Bangladeshis too had stayed up into the wee hours of Sunday morning to watch the match being shown live from the Caribbean. There were victory processions in Narail - hometown of Mashrafe Mortaza and Chittagong - the place where Tamim Iqbal comes from.]]></line><line><![CDATA["We'd beaten India before, but never in a World Cup. We sensed victory once we stopped them at 191. The celebration still rings in my ears. Nobody was coming out of the dressing room. After that day, our respect for each other reached an all new pedestal," says Bashar, who retired from all forms in 2008.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Former captain <b>Habibul Bashar</b>, under whose leadership the Tigers defeated India had this to say to the Hyderabad Chronicle. He was asked to recall that famous win and pointed out that they never had a plan against India in 2007. "When we beat India in 2007, we never had a plan. We knew they were a strong unit but we were more concerned about putting up our best performance. That worked for us. But once it happened, it took a long time for the feeling to sink in," recalls Bashar.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Khaled Mahmud</b>, the former allrounder loved the way Bangladesh played the game. "The cricket we played in the first game is simply outstanding. The confident cricket from the young breed actually makes the difference. I always love to see Tamim playing that way."]]></line><line><![CDATA[We still have loads of time, so let us look back at that 2007 triumph by Bangladesh. Let us see how former players from Bangladesh reacted to their side's shock win. Former captain, <b>Raqibul Hasan told The Daily Star</b> that Bangladesh's win was the most comprehensive he had seen. "I got emotional not only because Bangladesh won a match against a formidable side but the way they achieved it was incredible. It was truly a professional performance by the boys. I feel fortunate as a former captain that I could see my team playing the game in such a fashion."]]></line><line><![CDATA[But take nothing away from Bangladesh's win that day. They were the better side and definitely out-thought, out-batted, out-bowled and out-played India in all three departments. 8 years later, they meet their rivals once again - this time in a knockout game. It's the second quarter-final of the 2015 World Cup and we welcome one and all to our coverage of this game. Sit tight and enjoy whatever we serve up. It's going to be long, lengthy but one thing is guaranteed. We will leave no stone unturned to bring you the best coverage possible. Ready for the ride then? Then chug along with us.]]></line><line><![CDATA[India's loss in their opening game upset all plans and eventually they bowed out of the competition in the league stage, after another defeat to Sri Lanka. This for a side that had Rahul Dravid as captain, with the likes of Sachin Tendulkar, Sourav Ganguly, Virender Sehwag, Yuvraj Singh, MS Dhoni, Zaheer Khan and Harbhajan Singh. The side was coached by Greg Chappell - considered to be one of the most astute of cricketing brains. No-one could point a finger as to what went wrong. It was certainly the lowest point of Dravid, Sachin and Ganguly's ODI careers. That exit caused a lot of introspection and led to soul-searching.]]></line><line><![CDATA[But Cricket has a way of surprising people. It throws up the most unexpected of results. Catching everyone unawares. That's what happened on 17th March as Bangladesh registered one of the great upsets in World Cup history, beating a much fancied Indian side. On a slow wicket, India were bundled out for 191 and the score chased down with 9 balls to spare. Zaheer Khan was made to look like a novice as the 18-year old Tamim Iqbal treated with utter contempt. It was a performance worthy and deserving of a win. Bangladesh had come to win and not make up the numbers. They had made a statement. And that statement echoed around the whole of India.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>12:30 Local Time, 01:30 GMT, 07:00 IST:</b> <b>March 17, 2007.</b> The venue: Queen's Park Oval, Port of Spain, Trinidad. The occasion: A World Cup encounter between India and Bangladesh. Sourav Ganguly vs Tamim Iqbal. Virender Sehwag vs Shahriar Nafees. Rahul Dravid vs Mushfiqur Rahim. Sachin Tendulkar vs Shakib Al Hasan. Zaheer Khan vs Mashrafe Mortaza. Harbhajan Singh vs Abdur Razzak. World beaters vs hopefuls. Heavyweights vs lightweights. Any way you want to look at it, it was a no-contest. At least on paper. India were expected to have a smooth ride against their neighbors from Asia. No-one was even contemplating an upset.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/><br/>India's intensity, determination and allround skills can combine to overpower a fearless Bangladesh in the quarterfinals of the ICC Cricket World Cup 2015 at the Melbourne Cricket Ground on Thursday. But only if they embrace the right emotions and not complacency that can creep in at the thought of facing the 'easiest' of the opponents in the round of eight.<br/><br/>India return to the scene of one of their most memorable wins in this World Cup taming South Africa after beating Pakistan in their opening game in Adelaide. India have managed their recovery and training, including backroom preparation, well. They can add another victory on Thursday if they approach the match with due respect.<br/><br/>That India are playing with immense confidence rather than arrogance was shown when they slipped past tricky situations against West Indies and Zimbabwe, thanks to Mahendra Singh Dhoni's calming influence. They will be hoping that the top-order batsmen will not make the mistake of treating Bangladesh's bowlers with a complacent demeanour.<br/><br/>There have been attempts to evoke memories of 2007 World Cup when India were surprised by a pack of left-arm spinners and lost to Bangladesh in Port of Spain. But the focus on that would dilute as soon as freeze frames of India's whipping of Bangladesh on their home ground surface.<br/><br/>India's bowling attack has acquitted itself admirably, with the team being the only one to claim all 60 wickets in the league phase. In the run-up to this game, the players have found the right mix of intensity and joy.<br/><br/>Well as Bangladesh themselves have batted in the World Cup, Mahmudullah scoring back-to-back hundreds against England and New Zealand, their only 300-plus score came against lowly Scotland. Unless their pace bowlers step up the plate, they will find it hard to stop India from making it to the Sydney semifinal against Australia or Pakistan.<br/><br/>Undoubtedly, Thursday will be among Bangladesh cricket's biggest days, not because they will be playing their 300th ODI but more since they have put themselves in line for a semifinal spot for the first time. With fearlessness as their accomplice, they will be primed to give it their best shot just as they attempted in their last game against New Zealand.<br/><br/>They were fortunate to share points with Australia after rain in Brisbane washed their Group A game off but they showed they had kept in touch with the modern game during their 15-run victory over England in Adelaide. The fast-medium bowling trio of skipper Mashrafe Mortaza, Rubel Hossain and Taskin Ahmed have 19 wickets but can be a handful.<br/><br/>Bangladesh coach, Chandika Hathurusingha has often pointed out that the team was not afraid to fail. "If we are paralysed by failure, we are not pushing ourselves, that's what we have talked about throughout this World Cup. I think the freedom to do things and believing in ourselves has been the key. We are backing ourselves to do well," he said.<br/><br/>Cricketers and coaches, irrespective of nationality or teams they are attached to, also keep reminding us that the past does not matter as much as what a team does on a given day. Bangladesh will be bidding fair to make Thursday count as their own while India, carrying committed heavyweight performers in their ranks, will seek to extend their winning run.<br/><br/><b>Teams:</b><br/><br/>India (from): Mahendra Singh Dhoni (captain, wicketkeeper), Shikhar Dhawan, Rohit Sharma, Virat Kohli, Suresh Raina, Ajinkya Rahane, Ravindra Jadeja, R Ashwin, Mohammed Shami, Mohit Sharma Umesh Yadav, Ambati Rayudu, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Axar Patel and Stuart Binny.<br/><br/>Bangladesh (from): Mashrafe Mortaza (captain), Tamim Iqbal, Imrul Kayes, Soumya Sarkar, Mahmuddullah, Shakib Al Hasan, Mushfiqur Rahim (wicketkeeper), Sabbir Rahman, Nasir Hossain, Rubel Hossain, Anamul Haque, Taskin Ahmed, Arafat Sunny, Taijul Islam and Mominul Haque.<br/><br/>Umpires: Ian Gould (England) and Aleem Dar (Pakistan); TV umpire: Steve Davis (Australia); Match referee: Roshan Mahanama (Sri Lanka).]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>India</b> (From): Shikhar Dhawan, Rohit Sharma, Virat Kohli, Ajinkya Rahane, Suresh Raina, MS Dhoni(c/w), Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Mohammed Shami, Umesh Yadav, Mohit Sharma, Axar Patel, Stuart Binny, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Ambati Rayudu]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangladesh</b> (From): Tamim Iqbal, Imrul Kayes, Soumya Sarkar, Mahmudullah, Shakib Al Hasan, Mushfiqur Rahim(w), Sabbir Rahman, Nasir Hossain, Mashrafe Mortaza(c), Rubel Hossain, Taskin Ahmed, Shafiul Islam, Arafat Sunny, Mominul Haque, Taijul Islam]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>302</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>6</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>50</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="India">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>576</playerid>
					<name>Rohit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Rohit</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rohit</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>137</runs>
					<balls>126</balls>
					<fours>14</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Taskin Ahmed</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8548</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1446</playerid>
					<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhawan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhawan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>30</runs>
					<balls>50</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[stumped]]></status>
					<bowler>Shakib</bowler>
					<bowlerId>544</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mushfiqur Rahim</fielder>
						<fielderId>394</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Kohli</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>8</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Rubel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1736</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mushfiqur Rahim</fielder>
						<fielderId>394</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1447</playerid>
					<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
					<batsman-name>A Rahane</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rahane</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>19</runs>
					<balls>37</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Taskin Ahmed</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8548</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Shakib Al Hasan</fielder>
						<fielderId>544</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Raina</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>65</runs>
					<balls>57</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mortaza</bowler>
					<bowlerId>323</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mushfiqur Rahim</fielder>
						<fielderId>394</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhoni</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Taskin Ahmed</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8548</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Nasir Hossain</fielder>
						<fielderId>8018</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<batsman-name>R Jadeja</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>23</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<batsman-name>Ashwin</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ashwin</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7909</playerid>
					<name>Mohammed Shami</name>
					<batsman-name>Shami</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shami</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1858</playerid>
					<name>Umesh Yadav</name>
					<batsman-name>Umesh</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>U Yadav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Mohit Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mohit Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1446</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>75</runs>
				<overs>16.3</overs>
				<batsman>Shikhar Dhawan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dhawan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1413</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>79</runs>
				<overs>17.5</overs>
				<batsman>Virat Kohli</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1447</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>115</runs>
				<overs>27.6</overs>
				<batsman>Ajinkya Rahane</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Rahane</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>413</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>237</runs>
				<overs>43.5</overs>
				<batsman>Suresh Raina</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>576</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>273</runs>
				<overs>46.6</overs>
				<batsman>Rohit Sharma</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rohit</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>265</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>296</runs>
				<overs>48.6</overs>
				<batsman>MS Dhoni</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>4</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>2</noballs>
			<legbyes>7</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>16</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Bangladesh">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>323</playerid>
					<name>Mashrafe Mortaza</name>
					<bowler-name>Mortaza</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mortaza</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>69</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8548</playerid>
					<name>Taskin Ahmed</name>
					<bowler-name>Taskin Ahmed</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Taskin Ahmed</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>69</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8018</playerid>
					<name>Nasir Hossain</name>
					<bowler-name>Nasir Hossain</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nasir Hossain</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1121</playerid>
					<name>Mahmudullah</name>
					<bowler-name>Mahmudullah</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mahmudullah</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>4</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1736</playerid>
					<name>Rubel Hossain</name>
					<bowler-name>Rubel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rubel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>56</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>544</playerid>
					<name>Shakib Al Hasan</name>
					<bowler-name>Shakib</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shakib</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>58</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>612</playerid>
					<name>Tamim Iqbal</name>
					<bowler-name>Tamim</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Tamim</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1583</playerid>
					<name>Imrul Kayes</name>
					<bowler-name>I Kayes</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Kayes</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8233</playerid>
					<name>Soumya Sarkar</name>
					<bowler-name>Soumya Sarkar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Soumya Sarkar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>394</playerid>
					<name>Mushfiqur Rahim</name>
					<bowler-name>Rahim</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rahim</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8231</playerid>
					<name>Sabbir Rahman</name>
					<bowler-name>S Rahman</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Rahman</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>193</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>10</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>45</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Bangladesh">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>612</playerid>
					<name>Tamim Iqbal</name>
					<batsman-name>Tamim</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Tamim</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>25</runs>
					<balls>25</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Umesh</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1858</bowlerId>
						<fielder>MS Dhoni</fielder>
						<fielderId>265</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1583</playerid>
					<name>Imrul Kayes</name>
					<batsman-name>I Kayes</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Kayes</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>5</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ravindra Jadeja</fielder>
						<fielderId>587</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Umesh Yadav</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>1858</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8233</playerid>
					<name>Soumya Sarkar</name>
					<batsman-name>Soumya Sarkar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Soumya Sarkar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>29</runs>
					<balls>43</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Shami</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7909</bowlerId>
						<fielder>MS Dhoni</fielder>
						<fielderId>265</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1121</playerid>
					<name>Mahmudullah</name>
					<batsman-name>Mahmudullah</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mahmudullah</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>21</runs>
					<balls>31</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Shami</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7909</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Shikhar Dhawan</fielder>
						<fielderId>1446</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>544</playerid>
					<name>Shakib Al Hasan</name>
					<batsman-name>Shakib</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shakib</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>10</runs>
					<balls>34</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>R Jadeja</bowler>
					<bowlerId>587</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mohammed Shami</fielder>
						<fielderId>7909</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>394</playerid>
					<name>Mushfiqur Rahim</name>
					<batsman-name>Rahim</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rahim</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>27</runs>
					<balls>43</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Umesh</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1858</bowlerId>
						<fielder>MS Dhoni</fielder>
						<fielderId>265</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8231</playerid>
					<name>Sabbir Rahman</name>
					<batsman-name>S Rahman</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Rahman</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>30</runs>
					<balls>40</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Umesh</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1858</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mohammed Shami</fielder>
						<fielderId>7909</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8018</playerid>
					<name>Nasir Hossain</name>
					<batsman-name>Nasir Hossain</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nasir Hossain</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>35</runs>
					<balls>34</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>R Jadeja</bowler>
					<bowlerId>587</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ravichandran Ashwin</fielder>
						<fielderId>1593</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>323</playerid>
					<name>Mashrafe Mortaza</name>
					<batsman-name>Mortaza</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mortaza</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mohit Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8181</bowlerId>
						<fielder>MS Dhoni</fielder>
						<fielderId>265</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1736</playerid>
					<name>Rubel Hossain</name>
					<batsman-name>Rubel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rubel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Umesh</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1858</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ravichandran Ashwin</fielder>
						<fielderId>1593</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8548</playerid>
					<name>Taskin Ahmed</name>
					<batsman-name>Taskin Ahmed</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Taskin Ahmed</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>612</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>33</runs>
				<overs>6.3</overs>
				<batsman>Tamim Iqbal</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Tamim</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1583</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>33</runs>
				<overs>6.4</overs>
				<batsman>Imrul Kayes</batsman>
				<batsman-name>I Kayes</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1121</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>73</runs>
				<overs>16.6</overs>
				<batsman>Mahmudullah</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mahmudullah</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8233</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>90</runs>
				<overs>20.4</overs>
				<batsman>Soumya Sarkar</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Soumya Sarkar</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>544</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>104</runs>
				<overs>28.2</overs>
				<batsman>Shakib Al Hasan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Shakib</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>394</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>139</runs>
				<overs>35.1</overs>
				<batsman>Mushfiqur Rahim</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rahim</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8018</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>189</runs>
				<overs>42.6</overs>
				<batsman>Nasir Hossain</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Nasir Hossain</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>323</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>192</runs>
				<overs>43.6</overs>
				<batsman>Mashrafe Mortaza</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mortaza</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1736</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>193</runs>
				<overs>44.4</overs>
				<batsman>Rubel Hossain</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rubel</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8231</playerid>
				<nbr>10</nbr>
				<runs>193</runs>
				<overs>44.6</overs>
				<batsman>Sabbir Rahman</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Rahman</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>1</byes>
			<wides>8</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>10</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="India">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1858</playerid>
					<name>Umesh Yadav</name>
					<bowler-name>Umesh</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>U Yadav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>31</runsoff>
					<wickets>4</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7909</playerid>
					<name>Mohammed Shami</name>
					<bowler-name>Shami</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shami</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>37</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>4</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Mohit Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mohit Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<bowler-name>Ashwin</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ashwin</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>30</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<bowler-name>Raina</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Raina</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>15</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<bowler-name>R Jadeja</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>42</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1446</playerid>
					<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhawan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhawan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>576</playerid>
					<name>Rohit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Rohit</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rohit</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<bowler-name>Kohli</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Kohli</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1447</playerid>
					<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
					<bowler-name>A Rahane</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rahane</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhoni</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhoni</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



