<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="12882" >
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>28th Match, Pool B</gameDesc>
		<series>WC 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>India</home>
		<away>West Indies</away>
		<teamsabbr>IND vs WI</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>IND</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>WI</awayabbr>
		<homeId>2</homeId>
		<awayId>10</awayId>
		<venue>W.A.C.A. Ground, Perth</venue>
		<startdate>06 03 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>06 03 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>West Indies</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>India won by 4 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>India</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>4</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Kumar Dharmasena</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Nigel Llong</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Billy Bowden</Name>
			<Country>NZ</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Ranjan Madugalle</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>06:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150306134610</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>Ind</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>WI</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>185</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>6</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>39.1</batteamovers>
		<status>India won by 4 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>265</playerid>
			<name>MS Dhoni*</name>
			<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Dhoni</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>45</runs>
			<balls-faced>56</balls-faced>
			<fours>3</fours>
			<sixes>1</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>1593</playerid>
			<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
			<batsman-name>Ashwin</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Ashwin</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>16</runs>
			<balls-faced>32</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>356</playerid>
			<name>Marlon Samuels*</name>
			<bowler-name>Samuels</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Samuels</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>3.1</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>10</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>255</playerid>
			<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
			<bowler-name>Dwayne Smith</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Smith</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>5</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>22</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>183</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>587</playerid>
<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
<player-runs>13</player-runs>
<player-balls>23</player-balls>
<runs>134</runs>
<wicket-nbr>6</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>7736</bowlerid>
<bowlername>A Russell</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>1</byes>
			<wides>19</wides>
			<noballs>3</noballs>
			<legbyes>3</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>26</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[Wd . . 1 1 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. 1 1 . . . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 1 . 1 4 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_WC/IND_WI_MAR06/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[That's it from us. We have a double-header tomorrow. The first one is a big game in Auckland, where Pakistan and South Africa lock horns with each other. In the other game, Ireland take on Zimbabwe in Hobart. Looking forward to your company then. Goodbye!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Let's glance through some of the <b>tweets</b> pertaining to this game:]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@glennmcgrath11:</b> Congrats to @BCCI winning their match over @westindies quite comfortably in the end. This will ensure they finish top of their pool ]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@mohanstatsman:</b> MS Dhoni now most ODI wins in "away" games for India - 59 now! He went past Saurav Ganguly's 58 wins]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@fwildecricket:</b> The support for India at the grounds at this WC has been incredible. Conditions aside, they’re playing at home. #CWC15]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@ShaneWarne:</b> Besides @MClarke23 Brendan Mcullum & Dhoni the Captaincy in this World Cup has been ordinary & really disappointing.....]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@G_Rajaraman:</b> MS Dhoni deserves all the credit for shepherding the team to a win and ensuring that the bowlers' effort would not go in vain #CWC15 #WIvIND]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@cricketaakash:</b> A mild wake up call for Indian batting...not a bad thing to happen before the knockouts.]]></line><line><![CDATA["Quite a few dropped catches, but I think there must be something wrong. It must be difficult because all our best fielders dropped catches. We'll just brush it under the carpet with a bit of thought as to what really happened. It is always a difficult target. You don't really know whether you want to play your big shots. Also our lower middle-order hasn't been tested so far. So it was a good opportunity against a good bowling line-up. I feel Ashwin batted really well, Jadeja will have to step up. I feel his slot is very important if he starts scoring runs consistently for us, it will be a very difficult line-up to contain. Also the fact that we have to accept, lower down the innings we won't be able to clear the boundaries out here if the short pitched deliveries are bowled to us. So we'll have to method ways as to how to get runs out of them. Use a bit of innovation to get plenty out of the bowlers. That's one area where we'll have to improve, but a few more games, hopefully we will. The last time when we were in New Zealand I felt the wickets were very good. True wickets, not a lot of turn for the spinners, but we'll have to see again what kind of wicket is provided, but generally the wickets are good over there. It comes on nicely to the bat, there is a bit of bounce for the fast bowlers, the boundaries are not very big. That's one area where we can exploit if the short pitched deliveries are bowled to us, we can start looking to play our big shots. Overall, we will have to adjust our lengths slightly because there will be a bit more swing for a bit longer. You can bowl your fast bowlers till the 20th over maybe and look to reverse which we found difficult in New Zealand."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhoni</b>: "I think it was a difficult wicket, even when we were bowling initially with the new ball, there was variable bounce and there was extra bounce for the fast bowlers. There was something for the fast bowlers. I think it settled down later, but there was a bit of swing for the West Indian bowlers also when they were bowling. I don't think it misbehaved as much as it did in the first innings, especially in the first 10 overs. I felt our bowlers did a very good job, they didn't try too much. At times when there is help, you start thinking okay let's swing it from the middle stump maybe, lets do this lets do that. But they stuck to their line and length. Yes, it had a bit more bounce, so we have quite a few wides bowling bouncers, but overall the bouncer was good. A lot of batsmen, they did get out on the short pitched deliveries. Overall I was very happy with the performance, the spinners also bowled well."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Holder</b>: "No regrets about batting first. Always thought the wicket was gonna be a good wicket. The bounce is pretty much true on this wicket. I just thought that batsmen didn't hang in long enough on this wicket. We just lost the momentum early in the innings and we just never really recovered. I think it wasn't difficult, we just didn't apply ourselves well enough today. When we batted, we never really caught up in the game. I think going forward, just need to assess conditions as quickly as possible and just make the adjustment necessary. That was my plan initially, to bat out the overs. I still thought we needed runs to help out net run rate. Tried to get a partnership going in the latter half of the innings, but unfortunately just gave away my hand in the end. I am quite pleased with my form at the moment, but it's a team effort. We just need to win some more games. We just definitely have to string together a complete game, because we have been lacking that in the previous games. So once I think we can string together a complete game, we'll be good enough to go well in the last game."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammed Shami</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b>. Unfortunately Shami couldn't talk to Ian Bishop apparently because of his poor English speaking skills. Maybe there should have been an interpreter along with him.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Indian camp will be happy with the win. But the think-tank would perhaps be concerned with the fact that they dropped four catches. India will next face Ireland in Hamilton. On the other hand, the West Indies will take on UAE in Napier. After this loss, the game against UAE will turn out to be a key encounter for the West Indies.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Andre Russell and Kemar Roach backed up Taylor's fine effort by taking the wickets of Virat Kohli and Ajinkya Rahane, respectively. Suresh Raina, who was welcomed to the crease with a barrage of short stuff then was dismissed by Dwayne Smith. Russell used the short ball to snare the wicket of Ravindra Jadeja as well. Dhoni though, yet again played with a level head on his shoulders to soothe the jangling nerves in the Indian set-up. Holder perhaps missed a trick by not bringing Taylor earlier into the attack for his second spell. When India needed about 20 runs to win, Holder surprisingly used the part-timers. The West Indies also allowed the batsmen to take easy singles. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Just when everyone thought that India would cruise towards victory, the West Indies' pacers bowled with fire to give the Indian camp jitters. In particular, Jerome Taylor, bursting forth with athletic brilliance and immense self-belief, caused the batsmen problems. Taylor zipped through the crease quickly and generated prodigious swing to snare the wickets of Shikhar Dhawan and Rohit Sharma. He bowled a superb length and that resulted in Rohit and Dhawan getting caught in the crease. In fact, it swung for around 20 overs for the West Indies. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[It was Jason Holder and Darren Sammy, who looked to steady West Indies' innings. Holder even landed a few meaty blows and compiled a fine fifty. But despite Holder's gutsy knock, West Indies ended up with a below par total on the board. For India, all the bowlers gave a good account of themselves. Shami took three wickets and Umesh, who bowled with good pace took two. Even Ravichandran Ashwin bowled tidily. The Indian seamers also executed the plans to near perfection. They used the short ball to great effect to pick up wickets.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Smith's opening partner, Gayle, looked to play himself in. However, in the eighth over of the innings, Gayle tried to break the shackles by thwacking Umesh Yadav all over the ground. But once he was dismissed by a fine short delivery from Shami, the West Indies fell like a pack of cards. To make it worse for them, Gayle and Marlon Samuels were involved in a terrible mix up and Samuels was run out. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, the Indian bowlers put up a marvellous show to bowl out the West Indies for a paltry score. It was Mohammed Shami, who bowled with supreme control and generated swing to trouble the West Indies' batsmen. Initially, with the wind blowing from left to right, Shami used the inswinger to keep the openers, Chris Gayle and Dwayne Smith in check. He then produced the breakthrough by sending Smith back to the pavilion with a nip-backer. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Despite West Indies' pacers putting up a sterling performance with the ball in hand, MS Dhoni held his nerve to take India to victory. When India were 134 for 6, they found themselves in a precarious position, but in the end, the Windies were perhaps 30-40 runs short of a par score. With this win, <b>India have qualified for the quarter-finals of the World Cup</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Dhoni, <b>FOUR</b>, India remain unbeaten in the 2015 World Cup and this is a good workout for them before the knockouts. Flatter delivery outside off stump, Dhoni pushes away from the body and gets a thick edge, the ball goes wide of Gayle at slip, the fielder gives chase and tries to stop it with his boot, but the ball touches the rope. This is <b>India's 8th consecutive win in World Cups</b>, equalling their previous best streak in 2003]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>India have won</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Dhoni, 1 run, full toss on the leg stump, Dhoni flicks it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Dhoni, <b>FOUR</b>, short and wide and Smith is not quick enough to trouble Dhoni. The Indian captain rocks back and cuts it in front of square, the ball rolls through cover and escapes to the fence. India are just one hit away now]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ashwin, 1 run, outside off stump, guided to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ashwin, no run, short of length delivery on the off stump, Ashwin defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Dhoni, 1 run, outside edge but there is no second slip. Short of a length outside off stump, Dhoni tries to guide it to third man but gets a thickish edge that goes wide of Gayle at first slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ashwin, 1 run, short ball, pulled to fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Dhoni, no run, on the leg stump, turned to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Dhoni, no run, pushed back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Dhoni, no run, defended into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ashwin, 1 run, oh what's happened there! Both Ashwin and Dhoni collide midway and the Indian captain is not impressed. Flatter delivery outside off stump, punched off the back foot to short third man. Ashwin was running straight into Dhoni even as the latter moved to his right and he collided into Dhoni. Thankfully, no harm done]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Dhoni, 1 run, short enough to hang back and punch it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Dhoni, no run, tossed up on the off stump, Dhoni leans forward and defends it into the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[This is India's game to lose now. Just 12 runs needed and West Indies need a Malinga in their ranks.]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Dhoni, 1 run, pulls the short ball nicely, but hits it straight to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ashwin, 1 run, friendly ball. Down the leg-side, Ashwin glances it along the ground to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Dhoni, 1 run, back of a length delivery outside off stump, Dhoni knocks it to mid-on for an easy run]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ashwin, 1 run, gets across the sticks and turns the good length delivery to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ashwin, no run, full and outside off stump, Ashwin softly drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ashwin, no run, short ball on the stumps, Ashwin looks to pull but misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ashwin, <b>wide</b>, another wide, Curtly Ambrose will be an unhappy man in the dressing room]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Smith [3.0-0-9-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ashwin, 1 run, on the off stump, Ashwin leans forward and works it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ashwin, no run, shortish, Ashwin defends easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ashwin, no run, on the off stump, defended]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ashwin, no run, slower through the air, Ashwin looks to defend, but misses. Ramdin takes the bails off, but Ashwin had his back foot grounded]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ashwin, no run, flatter ball on the leg stump, punched back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[By the way, the 5-over batting powerplay has been enforced.]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Dhoni, 1 run, tossed up just outside off stump, Dhoni flicks it to deep mid-wicket, Ashwin looks for two but the fielder got to the ball very quickly. Dhoni is not happy with Ashwin and asks him to wait for his call before attempting the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Ashwin, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, defended off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Ashwin, <b>wide</b>, that is the 18th wide from West Indies. Have to be disciplined defending a low total. Attempts a short ball but it bounces well over the batsman]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Dhoni, 3 runs, short and outside off stump, Dhoni rocks back and cuts, doesn't get it from the middle of the bat because of the bounce, sends it through cover-point. Johnson Charles, the substitute, gives chase and saves one with a slide]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Ashwin, 1 run, easily done. A move across the stumps and then a gentle glance along the ground to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Ashwin, <b>wide</b>, short ball just down the leg-side, Ashwin misses the pull. The umpire wants Roach to rebowl that ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Dhoni, 1 run, Dhoni hops and tucks the short of length delivery to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Ashwin, 1 run, Ash opts to play the pull shot as Roach bangs this short, he hits it along the ground and sends it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Dhoni, 1 run, short of length delivery just outside off stump, Dhoni pulls it to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tanmoy</b> is as apprehensive as the Indian supporters at the WACA - 'Tense but hopeful and patient,' he says. Still some way to go for India]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ashwin, no run, flighted delivery on the off stump, defended off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ashwin, no run, slower through the air this time, Ashwin looks to defend off the front foot, the ball hits the splice of the bat as it bounces extra and goes in the air for while, before rolling to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ashwin, no run, punched off the back foot to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Dhoni, 1 run, quicker through the air, Dhoni hangs back and pushes it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Dhoni, no run, short and slow outside off stump, Dhoni looks to punch hard off the back foot, but mistimes it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ashwin, 1 run, short and down the leg-side, Ashwin flicks it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Marlon Samuels, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[This is interesting. Samuels is coming on! Not sure if this is the right ploy against two right-handers. But you never know... One slip in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Dhoni, no run, 'nooo' says Dhoni after defending this length delivery off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Dhoni, no run, much better line from Roach and he hits Dhoni on the stomach. Extra bounce on this short of length delivery, Dhoni hops and looks to turn it on the on-side, but gets hit on the body]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Dhoni, <b>wide</b>, poor line from Roach. Sprays this down the leg-side and that's an extra run for India. West Indies need to be more tighter]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Ashwin, 1 run, this time a controlled flick shot from Ash and it rolls along the ground to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Ashwin, 2 runs, flicked in the air but wide of the man at short mid-wicket. Fullish and angling into the right-hander, Ashwin turns his wrist and flicks, plays it in the air but the fielder had no chance. The 150 comes up for India]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Ashwin, no run, a confident back foot defence from Ash as Roach bowls a length ball outside off stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Dhoni, 1 run, short ball on the off stump, Dhoni plays the Nataraja pull shot with one leg in the air, but hits it straight to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kemar Roach [6.0-1-30-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Alright, India need 35 runs now. Can West Indies nip out a wicket here?]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Ashwin, no run, short ball on the stumps, Ashwin sits under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, 1 run, in the airrr but safe! Dhoni hops and chips the steeply rising short ball as he looks to play on the on-side, but the ball doesn't carry to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, <b>SIX</b>, the Indian captain has hit a timely six and that gets the crowd going. Short and wide outside off stump, the pitch has enough bounce for the batsmen to execute the upper-cut, Dhoni hits it very fine and it flies over the slip cordon]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Ashwin, 1 run, extra bounce on this short of length delivery, Ashwin tries to work it on the on-side, the ball goes off the glove towards fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, 1 run, fullish and on the leg stump, Dhoni flicks it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, no run, low full toss and Dhoni is caught at mid-on, but it won't count. Dhoni swings hard, but gets it on the bottom of the bat, mid-on runs to his left and takes the catch. Dhoni is unhappy that he missed out on the free-hit]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Free-hit</b> coming up and that was a big no ball.]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, <b>no ball</b>, Russell oversteps as he delivers this full ball, Dhoni drives it to mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Ashwin, no run, good short ball around the off stump, Ashwin drops his wrists and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Ashwin, no run, harmless back of a length ball on the off stump, Ashwin defends off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Ashwin, no run, optimistic shout for LBW. This full ball just swinging back in and beats Ashwin's attempted flick, the ball hits him on the front pad, but was clearly going down the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Ashwin, 2 runs, short enough for Ashwin to hang back and punch it through point for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Ashwin, no run, very full as he tries the yorker, Ashwin digs it out to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Ashwin, <b>wide</b>, short and down the leg-side, Ashwin lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[Russell is seen stretching his legs. Is he cramping? The physio has a chat with him at the boundary.]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Ashwin, no run, Ashwin gets right behind the line of this good length delivery and defends well]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, no run, back of a length delivery, Dhoni defends off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, no run, full and outside off stump, Dhoni drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Ashwin, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Ashwin steers it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Ravindra Jadeja, <b>out</b> Caught by Samuels!! In the air and oh he's juggled that one before holding onto it again. It was a short ball around the off stump, Jadeja doesn't control the pull shot because of the bounce on this pitch, the ball went off a top edge and straight to deep backward square leg, where Samuels was too casual. He almost dropped the ball, but palmed it with his right hand and recovered quickly to grab it with both hands again. This is just the start West Indies wanted after the break. <b>Ravindra Jadeja c Samuels b A Russell 13(23) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A Russell to Ravindra Jadeja, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, an ugly slash outside off stump from Jadeja. He was not 100% committed to the shot, just threw his bat at it at the last moment and got beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, 1 run, short of length delivery just nipping away outside off stump, Dhoni adjusts well and guides it to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, <b>wide</b>, it's too short and the umpire doesn't like the height on that one. Ramdin jumps to collect the ball. "Even another Dhoni, on top of himself, may not have hit that," says Hayden on air]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Once Rahane was dismissed, West Indies looked to target Suresh Raina with short pitched stuff. On occasions, Raina got into awkward positions, but he seemed to have got through the difficult period. However, he then threw his wicket away to an innocuous delivery from Dwayne Smith. The ball is still swinging for the West Indies, but they need to snare the wicket of MS Dhoni to have any chance of winning the game.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here is <b>Bharath Ramaraj's</b> analysis of the last 14 overs: The West Indies' pacers continued to trouble India's batsmen and Kemar Roach was rewarded with the wicket of Ajinkya Rahane. Rahane, who was given out as caught behind by the on-field umpire, Nigel Llong, went for the review. On the review, the snicko showed a small spike and the decision was upheld.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, Jadeja is livid with himself for not hitting it from the middle of the bat. Short of a length and on the leg stump, Jadeja tries to flick, but gets an inside edge onto pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Dhoni, 1 run, bit of shape back into the right-hander on this fullish ball, but it goes down the leg-side and Dhoni easily flicked it away through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, very full, Jadeja digs it out to extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Dhoni, 1 run, full and on the pads, easily glanced away to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, good fielding at third man by Russell. Fullish and outside off stump, Jadeja guides it to third man, Russell moves like a rocket to his right, gets down low and collects it cleanly in one motion]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, false shot from Jadeja! Scrambled seam length ball outside off stump, Jadeja feels for the ball and gets beaten as the ball nips away off the deck]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jerome Taylor [6.0-0-26-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, that's a good bumper. Steeply rising, Jadeja hops and looks to defend, the ball goes off the glove and rolls towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Ravindra Jadeja, <b>FOUR</b>, in the air and just over the man at widish mid-on. In the end, you would have to say, that is a calculated risk from Jaddu. This short ball doesn't rise much, Jadeja pulls off the front foot, hits it in the air and just evades the fielder's outstretched right hand]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhoni signals for a change of bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, leg byes, 1 run, fullish and down the leg-side, Dhoni misses the flick, the ball hits Dhoni on the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, no run, oh Dhoni looks to cut with no feet movement, he only manages to chop it towards cover-point. He could have easily dragged that back onto the sticks]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, no run, a gentle nudge from Dhoni to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, no run, short of length delivery just nips back in, Dhoni looks to punch off the back foot, the ball hits him on the inside half of the bat and rolls towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell [5.0-0-25-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, short and wide outside off stump, Jadeja is happy to let that go]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, Smith changes to round the wicket, but it's not close enough to make Jadeja play]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, covers the off stump and allows the length ball to go through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, bit of extra bounce on this length ball, Jadeja defends, the ball takes a thickish edge and rolls to the right of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, short of length delivery angling away from the left-hander, Jadeja defends it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[Team Director Ravi Shastri is a relaxed man in the dressing room and he wears a big smile on his face.]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ravindra Jadeja, <b>FOUR</b>, that releases all the pressure. Full and wide outside off stump, Jadeja leans forward and crashes the drive to the left of the man at cover. Good start to the over for India]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[The match is still in the balance. India need 65 runs and West Indies need to get one or two quick wickets to gain the upper hand.]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Dhoni, no run, easily blocked off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Dhoni, no run, Dhoni deliberately moves across the stumps every ball and this time he taps this back of a length softly into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, short and down the leg-side, Jadeja pulls it to deep backward square leg, where Samuels tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Dhoni, 1 run, Dhoni is late to take off for the run but he gets home safely. He defends this short of length delivery off the back foot towards short cover, looks at his partner, Jadeja responds and Dhoni charges to the non-striker's end]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Dhoni, no run, goes across the sticks again and works this length delivery towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Dhoni, 2 runs, Dhoni hops across the stumps and carefully pushes this short of length delivery off the back foot, the fielder at backward point dives to his right but couldn't stop the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, on a good length and well outside off, punched towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, this is exceptional bowling from Smith, tad fuller and shaping away from outside off, lures Jadeja into the drive and misses by a long way. There was a massive noise before that though, but it wasn't bat hitting ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, that's nicely bowled by Smith, tad fuller and going away with the angle, drags Jadeja forward and beats his outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, on a good length and well outside off, Jadeja doesn't need to play those, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, on a good length and slanting across the left-hander, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, fuller length delivery and on Jadeja's pads, flicked straight to the fielder at square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ravindra Jadeja, <b>wide</b>, full and swinging down leg-side, wide called]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Dhoni, no run, another good bumper from Holder, Dhoni sways inside the line and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Dhoni, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Dhoni gets well forward and defends it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Dhoni, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>top-edge and four</b>, this was a well directed short ball from Holder, Dhoni was looking to help it on its way, gets a top edge that loops over the keeper and into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, dabbed away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Holder changes to round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Dhoni, 1 run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, pushed to the left of mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Dhoni, no run, short of a length and well outside off, Dhoni cuts it to the right of point where the fielder makes a tumbling stop]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, on a good length and a hint of nip back into Jadeja, defended with an open face towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Raina, <b>out</b> Caught by Ramdin!! That's a big wicket for West Indies! Innocuous looking delivery from Smith, short and wide outside off, Raina went chasing after that, gets a thick edge through to the keeper. India have lost half their side now and are still some way towards getting to their target. <b>Raina c Ramdin b Dwayne Smith 22(25) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dwayne Smith to Raina, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Dhoni, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, Dhoni hops across and tucks it past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Dhoni, <b>wide</b>, wayward stuff from Smith, short and well down leg-side, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Raina, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, worked wide of cover-point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Raina, no run, on a good length and just outside off, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Dhoni, 1 run, short of a length and on Dhoni's hips, tucked away towards fine leg for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Smith, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, Raina is living dangerously! This was short and on the stumps, Raina swivelled across on the pull, was clearly late on the shot, the ball hits the gloves and races away wide of the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Raina, no run, back of a length and just outside off, dabbed away with an angled bat towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Raina, <b>wide</b>, another short ball from Holder, Raina lets it go, called as a wide for height]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Raina, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Raina hops across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Raina, no run, <b>almost carried to mid-wicket</b>, Raina and the short ball! He was cramped for room, the ball hurried onto him, doesn't get hold of the shot, goes to the fielder on the half-volley, Roach was the fielder there]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Raina, no run, short and angling into the left-hander, Raina was looking to pull and missed, went pretty close to the gloves]]></line><line><![CDATA[Holder changes to round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Dhoni, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Dhoni shuffles a long way across and nudges it to the right of mid-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jason Holder [4.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Raina, no run, short and well outside off, Raina throws the kitchen sink at that and misses, aahs and oohs in the Windies camp]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Raina, no run, another bumper from Russell, Raina ducks underneath it and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Raina, no run, tad fuller and on off, Raina gets behind the line and blocks it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, 1 run, tad fuller and just outside off, Dhoni was rooted to his crease as he pushed forward, gets an inside edge past mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Raina, 1 run, Raina wasn't in control over this pull, but the top-edge dropped well in front of the fielder at deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Raina, 2 runs, short and on the stumps, not much bounce to hassle Raina, he pulls it behind square on the on-side, almost bisected the two fielders in the deep, Roach gets across from fine leg, puts in the dive and saves a couple of runs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Our man at the ground, <b>Tanmoy</b>, has this to say. "West Indies' bowlers replicating the lines and lengths Indians bowled earlier and reaping the rewards."]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Dhoni, no run, short of a length and well outside off, Dhoni stays back and punches it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Raina, 1 run, short and on the stumps, Raina swivels across, rolls his wrists and pulls it down towards long leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, Raina is looking in exquisite touch here! Tad overpitched and just outside off, Raina presents the full face of the bat and punches it back past Dhoni for a boundary, that was sweetly struck]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Dhoni, 1 run, fuller length delivery and on Dhoni's pads, he gets an inside edge onto the pads, the ball rolls away towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Raina, 3 runs, nicely played by Raina, pitched up and just outside off, Raina leans forward, meets the ball on top of the bounce and caresses it through extra cover, back for the third run]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Raina, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Raina prods forward and gets an inside edge towards short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, no run, short of a length and on the stumps, Dhoni hops across and nudges it to the right of the bowler, on his followthrough]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, no run, back of a length and coming back with the angle, Dhoni gets his gloves and bat out of the way as he let it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, no run, once again in that channel outside off and holding its line, Dhoni plays inside the line and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, no run, Russell keeps it short and well outside off, Dhoni doesn't need to play at those, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, no run, short of a length and well outside off, Dhoni watches it go through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, <b>5 wides</b>, that's bonus runs for India, Russell banged one short and on the stumps, went sailing over Dhoni, no chance for Ramdin as well, five runs added to the total]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Raina, 1 run, short and on the stumps, Raina swivels across, rolls his wrists and pulls it past square leg for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Dhoni, no run, on a good length and angling into Dhoni's pads, he stays in his crease and turns it towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>MS Dhoni, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, <b>out</b> Caught by Ramdin!! India are in some trouble now! This was pitched up and held its line outside off, Rahane was playing with an open face as he looked to run it down towards third man, was there an edge on that? The replays weren't conclusive, umpire Llong gave it as OUT. The third umpire has a few looks and decides there's nothing conclusive to overrule the original call. Might be a bit harsh on the batsman, but he has to go. <b>Rahane c Ramdin b Roach 14(34) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Roach to Rahane, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rahane has been given out <b>caught behind</b>. He wants a <b>review</b>. It was almost an instantaneous call by the batsman, he looked a bit puzzled when the umpire's finger went up. Is there an edge on that? There's a spike on the snicko, but it looks like the bat brushed the pads, there's definitely no bat on ball though. Will the decision be overturned? NO, the original call stays, Rahane has to go]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, width on offer from Roach, Rahane gets well forward and slaps it over extra cover, didn't get hold of the shot, but has enough to race away to the ropes for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, no run, short of a length and just outside off, defended towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, no run, and Rahane misses out once again, a waist high full toss from Roach, Rahane was backing away on the swing and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Raina, <b>no ball</b>, 3 runs, sloppy from West Indies, Roach oversteps and offers a long half-volley outside off, driven straight to cover-point. Russell is done in by some extra bounce, ends up allowing another three runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Raina, no run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Raina leans forward and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Rahane, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Rahane hops across and dabs it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Rahane, <b>wide</b>, another nasty bouncer from Russell, followed Rahane as he swayed away from the line, too high though, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Rahane, no run, short and just outside off, Rahane drops his wrists and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Rahane, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Rahane rides with the bounce and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Raina, 1 run, width on offer from Russell, Raina gets on top of the bounce and cuts it square behind point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Raina, no run, short and just outside off, effort ball from Russell, Raina slashes at that and is beaten by the bounce, he was looking to help it over the slip cordon]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Raina, no run, short of a length and shaping away from outside off, Raina went for the sliced cut and missed]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Raina, 1 run, Roach keeps it short and on the stumps, Raina presses across, rolls his wrists and pulls it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, byes, 1 run, whoa! What happended there? This was full and in that channel outside off, Rahane let it go though, Ramdin can't collect it cleanly, the ball almost went all the way to the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, no run, Rahane loses concentration! Goes chasing after a full and wide ball outside off, misses by a small margin]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Raina, leg byes, 1 run, short and on the stumps, Raina was shuffling across on the flick, the ball thuds into his thigh pad and rolls away past the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place for Raina]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, 1 run, on a good length and on Rahane's pads, tucked to the right of square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, no run, that's very well bowled by Roach, goes full and well outside off, Rahane was backing away, gets a toe-end on the drive towards cover, looks like the bat broke on impact as well. Rahane gets a new bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Free-Hit</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, <b>no ball</b>, on a good length and just outside off, defended towards point, but Roach has overstepped]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[In fact, historically, the Windies pacers have been lethal at the WACA. The current bowling consultant of West Indies, Curtly Ambrose's awe-inspiring spell of 7 for 25 in a Test match played against Australia in 1993 is still rekindled fondly by fans. Ian Bishop too took a 6-for in the second innings of that Test. As Mark Waugh later in his biography said: "It was going to be almost impossible getting runs against 6'7" blokes [Ambrose, Bishop and Courtney Walsh] on that pitch. And it was." West Indies certainly need their pacers to fire on all cylinders today to win the game. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Initially, when Taylor bowled it a touch short, Shikhar Dhawan took advantage of it by collecting four runs in the third over of the innings. It was Taylor, who then provided the crucial breakthrough by bowling from around the wicket to induce Dhawan to edge the delivery and was caught by Darren Sammy in the slips. The length was bang on the money and that resulted in Dhawan getting caught in the crease. Taylor followed it up with another superb delivery to send Rohit back to the pavilion. Rohit too was caught in the crease. Taylor also got the ball to hurry off the surface and that caused Indian batsmen a few problems. Andre Russell then got the vital wicket of Kohli with a short delivery.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here is <b>Bharath Ramaraj's</b> analysis of the first 15 overs: The West Indies pacers, Jerome Taylor and Jason Holder bowled well with the new ball. Taylor generated prodigious swing too and snared two wickets. However, the Indian batsmen rotated the strike well and Virat Kohli played some glorious shots through the on-side to keep the scorecard ticking. The West Indies' fielders need to be agile, as the Indian batsmen are looking to steal a single at every given opportunity. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Kohli, <b>out</b> Caught by Samuels at deep backward square leg!! Kohli has fallen to the trap! This was banged in short and just outside off, Kohli swivelled across on the pull, hits it pretty well but can't keep it down. There's a man in the deep, and he holds onto the chance. That's a huge wicket at this stage. Kohli is gutted as he walks away, Russell was chuffed to bits. The umpire checks for a no-ball, but the bowler is fine on that count as well. <b>Kohli c Samuels b A Russell 33(36) [4s-5]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A Russell to Kohli, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Rahane, 1 run, short and on Rahane's hips, he shuffles across and helps it down towards fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Rahane, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Rahane drops it with soft hands, the ball rolls away towards point, he wants a single and is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Rahane, no run, short of a length and angling into Rahane, he looks to tuck it towards the on-side and is struck on the right arm]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Rahane, <b>wide</b>, another bumper from Russell, but it's too short and sails over Rahane's head, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a cracking shot, fraction too short from Russell, Rahane is quick to rock back and pulls it over square leg, almost went all the way, bounces just in front of the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Kohli, 1 run, back of a length and on Kohli's hips, turned to the right of mid-wicket for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, no run, short of a length and on the stumps, Rahane stays behind the line and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Rahane plays with an open face and drives it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, no run, short of a length and on Rahane's pads, turned past square leg, he wants a single but is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, no run, that's loose from Rahane, went sparring at one that nipped away off the surface, nearly edged it through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, no run, fuller length delivery and in that channel outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, no run, short of a length and just outside off, defended towards the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Rahane, 1 run, tad fuller and on the stumps, Rahane watches it all along, closes the face of the bat and nudges it backward of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Kohli, 1 run, length ball and on Kohli's pads, flicked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Kohli, <b>wide</b>, another short ball from Russell, it's angled down leg-side as well, Kohli went for the pull and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Kohli, no run, back of a length and in that channel outside off, defended with an angled bat and towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Rahane, 1 run, short from Russell, Rahane swivels across, rolls his wrists and pulls it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Kohli, 1 run, short of a length and on Kohli's pads, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Rahane, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, dabbed away in front of backward point, Kohli calls for a quick single and beats the direct hit from the fielder]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Kohli, no run, the bumper from Roach, Kohli ducks under it and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, 1 run, back of a length and on Rahane's hips, he hops across and nudges it off the gloves, the ball rolls away past the keeper, Rahane is off the mark with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, no run, Roach shortens his length and gets it to hold its line outside off, another easy leave for Rahane]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, no run, tad fuller and shaping away from outside off, another easy leave for the batsman]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, no run, back of a length and swinging away from outside off, Rahane watches it go through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Rahane, no run, on a good length and shaping away from outside off, left alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Rahane is on strike now, for the first time since the end of the 8th over]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, this is pure timing from Kohli, he's on a roll here, tad too straight from Taylor, Kohli hops across, brings his wrists to good effect and flicks it past mid-wicket for another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, can't bowl anything too straight, full and on the middle stump line, Kohli shuffles across and whips it through mid-wicket, the timing is sublime and the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, no run, Taylor keeps it full and well outside off, Kohli covers for the movement and drives it crisply, can't get it past cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, Kohli closes the face of the bat and drives it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, no run, loud shout for LBW, and West Indies <b>do not have a review</b>. Was the height an issue? This was full and nipped back into Kohli, beats his attempted clip and hits him on the back thigh, Hawk-Eye suggests that the ball was going over, the WACA bounce has saved Kohli here]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, no run, on a good length and on the stumps, Kohli presses across and defends it with a straight bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Kohli, 3 runs, poor ball from Roach, once again slips a length ball on Kohli's pads, he prods across and clips it in front of square on the on-side, big chase for Holder from mid-on, the batsmen run hard and get back for the third run]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Kohli, <b>wide</b>, Roach loses his line and sprays this one miles outside off, left alone, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a poor ball from Roach, he's released all the pressure, too straight and drifting onto Kohli's pads, flicked away past mid-wicket for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Kohli, no run, Ramdin wasn't convinced one bit, so was Gayle at 1st slip. Only Roach and Sammy at 2nd slip went up and managed to convince Holder into asking for the <b>review</b>. Nothing on the Snicko and West Indies have lost their only review. Coming back to the ball, it was a lovely outswinger from Roach, full and jagging away from outside off, Kohli is lured into the drive and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[Loud shout for a <b>caught behind</b>. West Indies want a <b>review</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Kohli, no run, Roach shortens his length and gets this one to jag away from outside off, Kohli was thinking about playing it, lets it go at the last moment]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Kohli, no run, that's much better from Roach, goes fuller and wider outside off, Kohli is lured into driving away from his body, almost found the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Kohli, <b>wide</b>, Roach goes short and well down leg-side, wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Kohli, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, Kohli almost overbalances as he drives it towards mid-on, closed the face of the bat at the last instant]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kemar Roach, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, 1 run, once again Taylor drifts onto Kohli's pads, flicked away towards long leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, 2 runs, too straight from Taylor, ends up drifting onto Kohli's pads, worked past mid-wicket for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a cracking shot, Kohli is looking in excellent touch, this was a touch fuller and on the middle stump line, Kohli presses half forward, presents the full face of the bat and drives it past mid-on, classy as it gets, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, no run, another yorker from Taylor, this was well outside off, Kohli was looking to squeeze it towards third man and misses, the bat hit the ground and the ball bounces through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, no run, yorker length delivery and just outside off, Kohli jams it out and the ball rolls away to the right of second slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from off, Kohli arrests his front foot movement and defends it with the full face of the bat, the ball rolls away towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Rahane, no run, fuller length delivery and on Rahane's pads, he shuffles across and clips it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Rahane, no run, tad fuller and on the stumps, Rahane presses across and defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Rahane, no run, on a length and shaping away from outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Rahane, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Rahane watches it all along and defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Kohli, 1 run, back of a length and well outside off, Kohli rides with the bounce and dabs it down towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, much better from Kohli, this is how you play the cover drive, tad fuller and just outside off, Kohli gets well forward, covers for the movement and drives it past extra cover for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ajinkya Rahane, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Rohit, <b>out</b> Caught by Ramdin!! India have lost both openers now! Taylor is in the middle of an excellent spell, this was pitched up and in that corridor outside off, Rohit pressed forward on the drive, doesn't cover for the movement off the deck, ends up throwing his hands at that. The outside edge is found and Ramdin gleefully collects the offering. India find themselves in some trouble, for the first time this World Cup. <b>Rohit c Ramdin b Jerome Taylor 7(18) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Jerome Taylor to Rohit, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Rohit, no run, back of a length and just outside off, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, 1 run, short of a length and on Kohli's hips, he looks to flick and gets an inside edge onto the thigh-pad, gets a single behind square]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, Kohli closes the face of the bat and drives it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Rohit, 1 run, this is poor from West Indies, this time it's Samuels at gully, on a good length and just outside off, Rohit defended with soft hands, gets an edge that goes right through Samuels' hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, 1 run, that's sloppy from Russell at cover, this was full and nips away at the last moment, Kohli was shaping for the flick, closed the face of the bat and gets a soft leading edge, Russell allows the ball to go through him and concedes a run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tanmoy</b> has this to say. 'This wicket is going to suit the West Indies bowlers. Holder's 57 may have made their total of 182 look better than it actually is.']]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Rohit, no run, Holder shortens his length and gets it to hold its line outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>gorgeous from Rohit</b>, too full and too wide from Holder, Rohit gets a good stride forward and drives it with a straight bat, beats mid-off and races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Rohit, no run, fuller length delivery and holding its line outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Kohli, leg byes, 1 run, aborted appeal for LBW, but the angle was taking it down leg, Kohli shuffled across a long way on the flick and missed, the ball rolls away to the left of the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Kohli, no run, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, Kohli doesn't need to play at those, gets well forward and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Kohli, no run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, Kohli gets a big stride forward, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Rohit, no run, full and a hint of late outswing, Rohit prods across and gets his bat behind the line]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, 1 run, fraction too short and on Kohli's hips, he gets inside the line and tucks it behind square, off the mark with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, no run, that's a searing yorker, very full and just outside off, Kohli watches it all along and blocks it]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, no run, back of a length and a hint of shape away from off, Kohli gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Kohli, no run, on a good length and on the stumps, <b>144 kmph from Taylor</b>, Kohli shuffles across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Virat Kohli, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Dhawan, <b>out</b> Caught by Sammy!! Edged and caught! That's perfect from Taylor, he came from round the wicket, pushes one across Dhawan and gets it to straighten. Dhawan could have let it go, instead, he pokes half-heartedly, gets a thick edge and to the right of second slip. Sammy moves across and holds onto a good catch. Just the start West Indies wanted, India have lost an early wicket. <b>Dhawan c Sammy b Jerome Taylor 9(14) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Jerome Taylor to Dhawan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Dhawan, 1 run, excellent running! Tad fuller and just outside off, Dhawan drops it in front of cover-point and calls for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Dhawan, no run, short and well outside off, went sailing over Dhawan's head, not called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Dhawan, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Dhawan dabs it in front of backward point, thinks about a single but decides against it]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Rohit, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, Rohit rides with the bounce and nudges it in front of short mid-wicket, another easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Rohit, no run, on a length and shaping back in, Rohit presses across and defends it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Dhawan, 1 run, on a good length and coming back with the angle, tucked in front of mid-wicket for a quick single. Holder isn't happy, felt a single was given away far too easily]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Rohit, no run, much fuller to Rohit, the line is just outside off, he gets half-forward and defends it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Dhawan, 1 run, short and wide from Taylor, Dhawan limply pokes at that, gets a thick edge that goes to the fielder at third man, on a bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Dhawan, no run, that's much better from Taylor, tad fuller and swinging back in late, Dhawan just about gets his bat down, plays with an angled bat and blocks it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, you can't bowl short and wide to Dhawan, width on offer from Taylor, Dhawan gets on top of the bounce and cracks it square past point, the fast outfield takes care of the rest]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Dhawan, no run, too short and too wide from Taylor, left alone. Umpire Dharmasena lets the bowler get away with this one]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Dhawan, no run, short of a length and well outside off, good pace from Taylor, Dhawan sways away from the line and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Rohit, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Rohit rides with the bounce and defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Rohit, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Rohit gets a big stride forward and blocks it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Rohit, no run, Holder has hit a good line and length, tad fuller and just outside off, nips away after pitching, Rohit isn't tempted at playing those, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Rohit, no run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, shapes away after pitching, Rohit gets a good stride forward and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Rohit, no run, tad fuller and shaping away from that channel outside off, Rohit covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Dhawan, 1 run, more good running between the two batsmen, Dhawan drops a length ball in front of cover-point and calls Rohit through for a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jason Holder, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Rohit, no run, Taylor keeps it short of a length and on the stumps, Rohit presses across and turns it towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Dhawan, 1 run, back of a length and in that channel outside off, Dhawan was caught in two minds, decides to let it go at the last moment, the ball runs off the face of the bat and goes towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Dhawan, no run, tad fuller and a hint of nip back into Dhawan, he covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Dhawan, no run, good pace and bounce for Taylor, shortens his length and gets it to hold its line outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[Taylor switches to round the wicket for Dhawan]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Rohit, 1 run, Rohit is off and running! This was a short of a length delivery and just outside off, Rohit dropped it in front of the popping crease, calls Dhawan through for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Rohit, no run, short of a length and a hint of shape away from outside off, Rohit covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit and Dhawan are at the crease. Rohit is on strike. Jerome Taylor will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place for Taylor]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back. Can West Indies defend their below-par score?]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jadeja:</b> "We are very happy. We did well, the bowlers did their job and now we need to just bat well, initially first 10-15 overs. There is a little bit slow grip on the wicket but very good batting wicket. Initially the ball was moving around a little bit. I don't think so, our batsmen are doing their job very well. They are scoring some runs so I think we need to just look for 10-15 overs initially and then we can get through the total (when asked if 182 was a challenge to the Indian batsmen). We all are doing fielding practice. It happens, it's a part of the game. We need to pull up our socks and just be focussed more. First thing it's a lucky charm for team. We have won the three out of three and secondly <b>I don't look good without the beard, so I always keep growing beard </b>(when asked about how his beard is going)."]]></line><line><![CDATA[At the other end of the spectrum, despite Holder and Sammy taking the West Indies to a score of some respectability, they were disappointing. None of the batsmen looked to get used to the pace and bounce on offer at the WACA and hardly played the ball late. Their running between the wickets was poor too. For the West Indies to have any chance of winning this game, their pacers need to strike with the new ball. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ashwin too showed his worth by using the strong breeze to get a bit of shape away from the batsmen and snaffle one wicket. Ashwin has now taken eight wickets in just three ODIs at the WACA. In fact, in the past too, finger spinners have harnessed the breeze to their advantage to take wickets at the WACA. To illustrate the point, Daniel Vettori, the slow left-arm orthodox, used it brilliantly to take a 6-for against Australia in a Test match that was played in 2001. In short, the think-tank have drawn some well thought-out plans and the bowlers have executed it superbly by testing every crevice of a batsman’s defence in this tournament. The only cause for concern for the Indian set-up would be they dropped four catches today.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[After Gayle and Samuels were dismissed, West Indies continued to wallow in mediocrity. Darren Sammy, who was dropped by Ravindra Jadeja, and Jason Holder tried to hold the innings together. Holder even struck some meaty blows and amassed a fine fifty. But it has to be said that the West Indies ended up with a below par score. For India, Shami took three wickets. Umesh, who bowled a good burst of pace snared two wickets.The Indian coaching staff would be gladdened by the near perfect execution of the short ball tactic. The pacers have rarely wasted the short ball in this World Cup, as they have usually bowled it head high and outside the off-stump.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shami started on a good note by keeping West Indies' opening batsmen, Dwayne Smith and Chris Gayle in check. Smith looked to play a slew of pull shots, but he couldn't connect any of them. Smith's tendency to premeditate didn't help his cause. Shami eventually, bowled a nip-backer to produce the edge and dismiss Smith. Smith's opening partner, Gayle, looked to play himself in before playing a few shots. In particular, Gayle took a heavy toll off Umesh's bowling by clobbering him for a four and a six in the eighth over of the innings. Gayle though, gifted his wicket away, as Shami dismissed him with a short delivery. He also was involved in a terrible mix up with Marlon Samuels and unfortunately for the Windies, Samuels was run out. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Indian bowlers put up an inspired show to land crucial blows at regular intervals and skittle out the opposition ranks for a modest total. It was Mohammed Shami, who bowled with unremitting control and used the breeze that was blowing from left to right to generate a bit of inswing and take wickets upfront. Once Shami gave India a rousing start, the likes of Umesh Yadav, Mohit Sharma and Ravichandran Ashwin followed up his efforts by bowling with diligence and discipline to put India in a position of strength.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, <b>out</b> Caught by Kohli!! All over. Holder had to go for it and sliced the loft, completely mistimed and Kohli takes an easy skier at long-off. He throws the ball away after catching it and that's the end of the innings. It may have turned a little and that forced the mishit. Ravindra Jadeja does a double fist pump and then <b>blows a cheeky little kiss to Kohli</b>. <b>J Holder c Kohli b Ravindra Jadeja 57(64) [4s-4 6s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, no run, Holder gets forward and defends to cover. The single is there, but he doesn't take it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja [8.0-0-27-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Holder, 1 run, another slower delivery outside off, forced down to long-on, retains the strike with that run]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Holder, <b>FOUR</b>, how well played is that? It was a middle stump yorker length delivery from Mohit Sharma, Holder made room and squeezed it with an open face, to the deep point fence. The rich timing takes it all the way]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Holder, no run, back of the hand slower delivery, Holder waits for it and runs it down to short third]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Roach, leg byes, 1 run, Roach ducks very early and takes one on the arm, before it deflects onto the helmet and runs away to third man. They take a leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Holder, 1 run, pushed to long-on, 'two, two' was the call, but it was just a single as the ball was timed a bit too well]]></line><line><![CDATA[Taylor swivelled to pull, but was in an awful position as he played the shot. He completed 360 degrees and at the end of the rotation had seen Umesh take the catch. Pretty poor batting and cricketing sense from such a senior member of the team. But then, I have said that previously too, today. Haven't I?]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Holder, no run, short of length on the stumps, defended calmly to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma [8.0-2-29-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kemar Roach, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Jerome Taylor, <b>out</b> Caught&Bowled!! Taylor is the latest to be afflicted by the top-edge syndrome. He is in no position to play the pull and can only lob a tame catch to Umesh who runs to his right and accepts the invitation. He strikes with the last ball of his spell. Why not defend the last ball, Jerome? When you have Holder doing all the hitting at the other end. <b>Jerome Taylor c and b U Yadav 11(18) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[U Yadav to Jerome Taylor, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught&Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, 1 run, Jinks at deep extra cover, does a great job by running to his right at full pelt and stop that, concedes just a single. Holder drove that full toss very hard through cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Jerome Taylor, 1 run, now gets the pull going, short-arm jabbed to deep mid-wicket, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Jerome Taylor, no run, hurries onto Taylor who awkwardly pokes out to mid-on. He was lining up for the pull and had to adjust]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, 1 run, back of a length on off, wristed wide of mid-on, that's <b>fifty for Holder</b>. Back-to-back ones too. The West Indians in the crowd have something to cheer about. Raise of the bat and a handshake with Taylor. Richie Richardson applauds that effort]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, no run, short of length and on the stumps, bounce for Yadav, Holder pulls and misses, off the thigh pad and sent back by Holder as Taylor looks for a leg bye]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, 1 run, Holder keeps strike with a wristed bottom-handed shot to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mid-wicket is up now, preventing the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, no run, flatter and outside off, steered straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Jerome Taylor, 1 run, Jerome Taylor can't help himself. Another slog and a thick inside edge runs to Shami's right at long-on, fielded]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Jerome Taylor, 2 runs, tossed up outside off, pre-meditated paddle and Jerome Taylor gets a couple to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Jerome Taylor, no run, and again]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Jerome Taylor, no run, shortish outside off, punched to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja [7.0-0-23-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, no run, dabbed to the left of backward point, Jadeja dives to his left and keeps Holder off strike. Holder slams his bat into the turf in disgust]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Jerome Taylor, 1 run, now <b>Rohit drops one at mid-on.</b> Taylor lofting and skying it, Rohit goes to his right and seemed to have it covered, but as it did with Jaddu earlier, the ball slips through his hands and hits his thigh, before going down. Rohit too was scrambling to pounce on the rebound. A let-off for Taylor]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, 1 run, short down leg, short-arm whipped to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, no run, Holder makes room, too much in fact and is lucky that the attempted low full toss, doesn't hit the off stump. Yadav missed the yorker there]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, <b>FOUR</b>, just over mid-off now! The fielder came in and then had to go back, he leapt and dived backwards, but the ball eluded his fingers. Raina was the fielder. Holder slicing a loft and getting fortunate. Yadav thought he had his man and was disapppointed]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, no run, on a length and on the stumps, Holder plays a back foot defence to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>42</b> from the powerplay for the loss of Sammy. West Indies will take it, considering the situation they are in]]></line><line><![CDATA[Our man, <b>Tanmoy</b> is impressed with what he has seen so far from Holder - "The captain from No. 9 is showing sense with the bat. Hits a six then changes strike next ball," he says.]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Holder, 1 run, in the air, but just wide of the man at short mid-wicket, Holder early into the leg-side clip and gets lucky]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Jerome Taylor, 1 run, Taylor looks to come forward and then goes back to punch with an open face wide of backward point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Holder, 1 run, Holder was backing away to go big again, but Ashwin held his length back a bit, pushed into the gap at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Jerome Taylor, 1 run, shortish outside off, punched square of the wicket, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Slip and a leg slip in place for Taylor. Holder has a word with Taylor]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Holder, 1 run, wide of the crease and on the middle and leg line, clipped to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Holder, <b>SIX</b>, Holder welcomes Ashwin with a six. Dances down the track and goes slightly inside out over wide long-off. Made room and lofted it cleanly, superbly struck and the white Kookaburra flies a long way]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin [8.0-0-27-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Jerome Taylor, no run, leaves the final delivery all alone, as it was outside off]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Jerome Taylor, no run, length and on the stumps, Taylor makes room to muscle it straight down the ground, but completely mistimes it to Umesh's left]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Jerome Taylor, <b>wide</b>, short down leg, Jerome Taylor pulls and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Jerome Taylor, <b>FOUR</b>, this time he connects! Goes deep in his crease and gave some room, slashed away past backward point, third man had no chance. Yadav got this to bounce as well, but Taylor played that well]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Jerome Taylor, no run, too close to cut as Jerome Taylor aims for the shot. It cramps him for room. Bounces past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Jerome Taylor, no run, back of a length outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, 1 run, short on the stumps, Holder is late on the pull, but manages to get a single to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav [7.0-1-27-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Jerome Taylor, no run, Taylor looks at the square leg umpire after a short ball from Shami, but he gets nothing after leaving that. He thought about pulling, but he couldn't reach it. Shami may have got away with one there]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to J Holder, 1 run, back of a length outside off, Holder rides the bounce and drops it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to J Holder, <b>SIX</b>, looked like a mishit when Holder played that, but it has carried all the way over long-off. The cutter from Shami, Holder makes room and lofts over the man inside the ring at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to J Holder, <b>FOUR</b>, Crunch! That made a beautiful sound as Holder pulled with power. Short one from Shami, but it sits up nicely for the tall lad to muscle it over mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[In the batting powerplay, West Indies are looking to survive. That's how bad the batting earlier on has been]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to J Holder, no run, slower delivery outside off, eased off the front foot to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to J Holder, no run, short outside off, Holder doesn't offer a shot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, 1 run, pushed into the gap at cover, retains the strike with that run]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, 2 runs, driven hard into the ground and wide of the leaping cover fielder, wide of long-off for two]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, no run, Ravindra Jadeja holds this one back, beats Holder's ugly mow across the line, the ball turns away past the shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, <b>SIX</b>, Holder has no other option now. Dances down the track and slices the loft, the long-off was there, but he was a mere spectator. Power of Holder on show]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, no run, fired in flat, defended back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in for Ravindra Jadeja]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, no run, tossed up outside off, Holder gets forward and drives, but finds cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Jerome Taylor, no run, dug in short from wide of the crease, Jerome Taylor hops to ride the bounce, but the ball climbs and beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sammy's bottom-hand came off as he completed the stroke. Was completely done in by the bounce. After a horror swipe which resulted in him being dropped, he knuckled down and was willing to show patience. But a good ball got him finally. Credit to Shami. He changed the angle by going wide of the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Jerome Taylor, no run, back of a length outside off, pushed to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Jerome Taylor, <b>wide</b>, short and wide outside off, Jerome Taylor throws his bat at the cut and doesn't connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jerome Taylor, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Sammy, <b>out</b> Caught by Dhoni!! Shami strikes with a good delivery. Went wide of the crease and got this to rear on Sammy, Sammy couldn't ride the bounce and edged it with an open face, was trying to run it down, but healthy nick and caught by Dhoni. Shami celebrates with the finger pointed upwards. <b>Sammy c Dhoni b Shami 26(55) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shami to Sammy, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Sammy, <b>FOUR</b>, the inside edge goes Sammy's way. Full and outside off, Sammy went for the big drive and the edge missed leg stump and ran away, beating fine leg. Shami has his hands on his head]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Sammy, no run, slower short ball outside off, Sammy lets it go, stopped on the bounce by Dhoni. Shami smiles]]></line><line><![CDATA[No need to remind, but the batting powerplay is now enforced]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Sammy, no run, back of a length outside off, punched well, but cover-point fields]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammed Shami [6.0-2-19-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, 1 run, gets to the pitch and drives to long-off, to get a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, no run, another front foot defence to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, no run, fired in on the stumps, defended to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, no run, driven to Ravindra Jadeja's right, he stops it with his boot]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, no run, driven back to Ravindra Jadeja]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, no run, inside-edged to short mid-wicket, Sammy sent Holder back late and the throw hit Holder's bat and came slowly to the bowler, Holder with a dive made it back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Has Holder made it back? Run-out check upstairs. Sammy sending Holder back and the ball hit the bat of Holder, that saved him. Or else he was gone]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Holder, no run, Mohit Sharma keeps it on a back of a length outside off, defended to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Sammy, 1 run, back of a length outside off, punched to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Holder, 1 run, slower delivery outside off, eased off the front foot to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Holder, no run, back of a length outside off, defended in front of point]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Holder, no run, short and on the stumps, Holder pulls and misses, loops to Dhoni]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Holder, no run, short of length outside off, Holder opens the face of the bat and finds point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, no run, Ravindra Jadeja is running through his overs, defended to short mid-wicket now]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, no run, defended back to the bowler as Ravindra Jadeja fires in another dart]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, no run, flatter outside off, Sammy defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, 1 run, driven inside out to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, no run, skidding on, on the stumps, turned to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, 1 run, drifting in on middle and leg, clipped to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Holder, no run, Holder is frustrated that he hasn't found the gap on that, wanted to open the face and get it wide of point, but plays it straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Holder, no run, pitched up outside off, sweetly driven, but straight to the fielder at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Sammy, 1 run, back of a length outside off, punched square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Holder, 1 run, defended wide of cover and to the left of the fielder, easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Holder, <b>FOUR</b>, he shuffled across to middle and had he missed that, he would've been dead plumb. But Holder clipped that beautifully through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Holder, no run, back of a length outside off, dabbed straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma [6.0-2-21-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks are on the field now</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, 2 runs, chipped uppishly and over the leaping Ravindra Jadeja. Sammy would've had his heart in his mouth for a fraction of a second. Too early into the flick, but he gets away eventually. Would've been a miracle catch had he taken that for he was airborne and at full stretch to his right]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, no run, wide of off, the sucker ball, Sammy shoulders arms to that]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, no run, skidding on on off, Sammy smothers that]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, 1 run, uses his feet and drives to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, no run, pushed off the front foot to Ravindra Jadeja's left]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, <b>wide</b>, down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, no run, angling in on off, Holder defends off the front foot to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, 1 run, short on the stumps, pulled without any timing to fine leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Sammy, 1 run, nips back in and Sammy gets an inside edge onto the pads, the ball rolls to short cover, quick single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[Very glum faces in the Windies camp]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Sammy, <b>wide</b>, dug in very short, Sammy ducks under that, wide called for height]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Sammy, no run, pitched up on the stumps, Sammy defends to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, 1 run, short of length outside off, punched to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, no run, fullish on off and middle, wristed straight to the fielder at mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, no run, nips back in and catches Holder on the pads, above the kneeroll. Too high and also sliding down]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, 1 run, flighted delivery outside off, Holder drives to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, no run, flicked straight to the fielder at short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, no run, pushed firmly to Jinks' left at cover-point, fielded with a dive]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, no run, very full on the stumps, driven straight back to Ravindra Jadeja]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, no run, targetting middle, Holder gets forward and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, no run, pushed to short cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, 1 run, back of a length outside off, Holder rises onto his toes and punches, gets a single to third man, 100 is up now]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, no run, nice shot for no runs. Crisp front foot drive, but intercepted at cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, no run, now Yadav beats Holder. Angling in on a short of length and then holds its line outside off, Holder was on the back foot looking to defend and is comprehensively beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, no run, pitched up outside off, little movement away, Holder shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, <b>wide</b>, now slips one down leg as he tries the inswinger]]></line><line><![CDATA[As soon as Russell top-edged the hoick, he started walking towards the pavilion. Sammy forced him to cross, so that he could he be on strike. The reactions of the West Indians in the crowd best describes that shot. They were too shocked to react. It has been happening with every wicket that falls]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Holder, <b>wide</b>, short and wide outside off, Holder throws the bat at it and doesn't connect. Called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Sammy, leg byes, 1 run, short of length on the pads, Sammy misses the whip and it runs off the pad behind square for a leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Sammy, no run, short of length outside off, shaping away a tad, left alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav [5.0-1-20-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, 1 run, on the stumps, a bottom-handed drive to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Holder gets forward and drives to sweeper cover, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, 1 run, Sammy reaches out and deliberately drives in the air, but over cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, no run, the tempter outside off, turn and bounce, Sammy shoulders arms to that]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, no run, fired in on the pads, flicked straight to the fielder at short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, no run, tossed up outside off, Sammy gets forward and pushes to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Sammy, 1 run, to cover, pushed off the back foot wide of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Sammy, <b>FOUR</b>, first piece of slack fielding from India. Short and wide outside off, Sammy rocks back and cuts hard in the air, wide of backward point, Shami allows the ball to bounce in front of him and hangs his left-hand out, but the ball turns away and beats him to the fence. Should've got the body behind it]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Sammy, no run, turned straight to the fielder at short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Sammy, no run, gets forward and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Sammy, no run, punched to Ashwin's right, he holds Holder and deflects the ball to short mid-wicket. He held Holder with his hands to get to the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Sammy, no run, turns in a bit and beats Sammy's forward defence, struck on the pads. Did Sammy get outside the line? A mild appeal from Ashwin, nothing more]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to J Holder, no run, defended off the front foot to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, 1 run, Sammy looks to drive to long-off, but the thick inside half runs down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, no run, Sammy gets forward and pushes it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, 2 runs, flighted delivery outside off, a sliced drive square of the wicket, for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sammy, no run, driven back to Ravindra Jadeja who fields]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jason Holder, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to A Russell, <b>out</b> Caught by Kohli!! 'Awful shot, terrible shot' from <b>Ian Bishop</b> on air. From Bish that is. From the ever-diplomatic Bish. The West Indians are playing this like a T20 game and are simply gifting their wickets away. Russell knew as soon as he hit it, that he was gone. Went for a big slog to a tossed up delivery from Jadeja and finds long-off. Kohli comes forward and accepts the catch. <b>A Russell c Kohli b Ravindra Jadeja 8(8) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Ravindra Jadeja to A Russell, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Jadeja tried to take it the Indian way and the ball slipped out of his hands. It hit the thigh and went to ground as he desperately tried to hang on, on the rebound]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Sammy, no run, shortish outside off, Sammy opens the face of the bat and cuts, but Shami goes to his left at backward point and fields]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Sammy, no run, Sammy was aiming for the big hit again, but then arrested his stroke and defends to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Sammy, no run, tossed up outside off, Sammy gets forward and defends to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to A Russell, 1 run, patted wide of short leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to A Russell, no run, turned to short leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to A Russell, no run, pushed back to Ashwin]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Sammy, no run, <b>dropped by Jaddu at point.</b> Horrible stroke from Sammy, he wound up and skied the length delivery outside off straight up in the air, it was a regulation take for Jadeja but let it slip out of his grasp, despite getting both hands. A couple of his team-mates come up and console him. Sammy gets away with one]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Sammy, 2 runs, Sammy doesn't time the pull well, but gets it wide and over mid-on. They take a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Sammy, <b>wide</b>, too many short balls and Mohit Sharma is getting carried away. Called wide for height]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Sammy, <b>wide</b>, down leg, Sammy can't connect with the flick]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to A Russell, 1 run, Rohit at mid-off does well to stop a cracking drive from Russell. He dives and then stops the ball. Keeps the batsmen to just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to A Russell, no run, this now is mindless slogging. The back-of-the-hand slower delivery, outside off, Russell swings and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to A Russell, <b>wide</b>, short and down leg, called wide for height]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to A Russell, <b>SIX</b>, Russell has nailed that. Backs away and knows the length will be short, muscled way over deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to A Russell, no run, short and outside off, Russell drops his wrists, hops and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[The reaction from Ashwin after the wicket suggested that Shami had misjudged the take and overran the ball. Once Shami caught it, Ash broke into a smile as did Dhoni. Carter was very aghast with himself and showed his displeasure, with disappointment writ large over his face]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Sammy, no run, backs away and cuts with an open face, but finds point]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Sammy, <b>wide</b>, the carrom ball goes wrong, down leg, Sammy gets inside the line to let go]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, <b>out</b> Caught by Shami!! Top edge and gone. Good catch by Shami at deep backward square leg. Sweeping against Ashwin on this WACA track is invitation for disaster and Carter now finds out why. Down leg, he connected the sweep well, albeit off a top edge, the ball was swirling away from Shami, with the sun distracting him as well. But he keeps his composure and takes it with both hands over his head. After taking it, he rubs his eyes, suggesting the sun was right in his eyes. <b>J Carter c Shami b Ashwin 21(43) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ashwin to J Carter, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, no run, beautiful bowling. Ashwin gets this to turn away a little and has an unsure Carter prodding. So close to the outside edge as Carter went back to defend, Dhoni collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, no run, rocks back and cuts hard, but finds Jaddu at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, no run, went for the pre-meditated big sweep, but the ball bounces and turns past his attempted shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, no run, angling in from round the wicket, Carter defends to silly point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Sammy, no run, another <b>maiden</b> for Mohit Sharma, his 2nd in this spell. Length delivery outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Sammy, no run, once he knows that he can't bowl anymore of the short stuff this over, he switches to a back of a length on the stumps, pushed to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Sammy, no run, Mohit Sharma is relying a lot on the short ball. That's the second one for the over as Sammy ducks once more]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Sammy, no run, another short delivery, on the stumps, Sammy ducks under that]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Sammy, no run, length delivery outside off, Sammy shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Sammy, no run, short and wide outside off, Sammy sees that and leaves. Called one for the over]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, no run, tossed up on the stumps, Carter defends to silly point]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Sammy, 1 run, shortish and that allows Sammy to go back and punch through cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Sammy, no run, pushed wide of slip with an open face, wants a single, sent back by Carter]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Sammy, no run, spins in and bounces, going down leg, Sammy offers the body and the ball drops down after hitting the body]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Sammy, 2 runs, this one held its line outside off, Sammy opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man, for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Sammy, no run, tossed up outside off, Sammy uses his long reach and smothers the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Carter, no run, pitched up outside off, Carter opens the face of the bat and drives well, but finds cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Carter, <b>wide</b>, that is inside the guideline but called wide by Dharma. Poor stroke from Carter though as he saw the full and wide delivery and went after it. So nearly could've edged that]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Carter, no run, that is a tight and good leave from Carter. Carter left that on length and trusting the bounce. It was close to the off stump, but it didn't nip back in]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Carter, no run, a loud call of 'wait' as Carter flicks and finds mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Carter, no run, pitched up outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Carter, no run, dug in short outside off, Carter sways away from the line and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Darren Sammy, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Simmons, <b>out</b> Caught by U Yadav!! West Indies are five down now. Once again a batsman falls to the short ball. It was outside off and Simmons had to fetch it from there, couldn't control the pull and top-edged it straight to the fielder at long leg. Umesh reverse-cups it to his chest as Sharma claps the wicket. <b>Simmons c U Yadav b Mohit Sharma 9(22)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Mohit Sharma to Simmons, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, no run, spin and bounce for Ashwin, floated outside off, Carter gets forward and leaves that]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, <b>FOUR</b>, way too wide and short outside off, Carter throws his bat and gets a thick bottom edge, races away past the lone slip. Beating third man inside the ring]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, 1 run, comes down the track and flicks that to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, no run, shortish outside off, cut straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, no run, spins in and beats Simmons' defensive push, strikes him on the pad, but was going down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[Jinks is coming in to field at short leg now. There is a fielder at a very deep slip. Very unconventional field that. <b>Dhoni has given his pads</b> to Jinks. <b>He is is keeping without his pads</b>. The things Dhoni does!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, 1 run, gets forward and wrists that to long-on, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Simmons, no run, short of length outside off, a tight maiden over from Sharma as Simmons shuffles across to cover off and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Simmons, no run, back of a length outside off, Simmons pushes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Simmons, no run, dug in short and over the head of Simmons who just turns his head away from the line of the ball. Called one short delivery for the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Simmons, no run, width was there that time, but the length was on a back of a length outside off, so Simmons sees that and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Simmons, no run, short of length outside off, Simmons plays a copybook back foot defensive stroke to the left of Sharma. Held the pose too]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Simmons, no run, back of a length outside off, left alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, no run, Carter was shaping to to go back initially but then saw the fuller length and came half-forward to push to cover. Ashwin nearly did him with the length]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, <b>FOUR</b>, that is pre-meditated but well hit. Gets the sweep going and rolls his wrists to beat deep square leg, scatters a few birds away as the ball races away into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, 1 run, gets forward and flicks to the right of short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, no run, tossed up outside off, pushed to point with an open face]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, 1 run, drifts in once more to the left-handed Carter, who is late on the back foot defence, the inside edge though runs to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, 1 run, tossed up outside off and spins in, Simmons presses forward to defend, but it takes the inside edge and runs to the right of short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Once Gayle got set though, he thwacked Umesh Yadav for a four and a six.  However, after surviving a couple of dropped chances, Gayle then threw his wicket away, as he was dismissed by a short delivery from Shami. The Indian seamers have certainly used the short ball cleverly in this World Cup. Gayle was also involved in a terrible mix up with Marlon Samuels and unfortunately for the West Indies, Samuels was run out. To make it worse for the Windies, Denesh Ramdin's lack of footwork yet again cost him his wicket as he dragged one back onto the stumps off Umesh's bowling. Even when Ramdin played his first Test series back in 2005 in Sri Lanka, the likes of Chaminda Vaas and Gayan Wijekoon took advantage of Ramdin's lack of footwork. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shami eventually, dismissed Smith with a nip-backer to produce the edge and for MS Dhoni to take the catch. With the wind blowing from left to right, Shami also generated a bit of inswing. On the other hand, Smith's opening partner, Chris Gayle, looked to play himself in. With his lack of footwork and tendency to go hard at the ball, the pacers concentrated on shaping it away from the left-handed batsman.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here is <b>Bharath Ramaraj's</b> analysis of the first 15 overs: Barring the odd short and wide delivery, Indian pacers were impressive with the new ball. It was Dwayne Smith, who looked to be the aggressor for the West Indies by trying to play a slew of pull shots against Mohammed Shami. However, he struggled to connect any of those pull shots. It was clear that Smith was premeditating most of his strokes. Now, batsmen who have succeeded at the WACA watch the ball right onto the bat and use the pace and bounce to their advantage. Damien Martyn, who scored tons of runs for Western Australia and Australia at the WACA, was well known for it.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks are on the field now</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Simmons, 1 run, nudged in front of mid-on, Sharma can't get across and they take a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Carter, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Carter slashes and gets a thick outside edge to square third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Carter, no run, back of a length on the stumps, Carter hops back and wrists it straight to the fielder at mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Carter, no run, loose shot from Carter. Full and wide outside off, Carter went for a big drive and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Carter, no run, pitched up outside off, Carter shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Simmons, 1 run, pushed to the right of cover, quick single taken]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, no run, now kneels to sweep and misses, is hit on the body]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, no run, the skidder! Pushed from the front of the hand, with just a flick of the finger and Carter is eons late on that. Goes back to cut and is trapped on the thigh pad, but the bounce of the WACA pitch means that it would've gone over. Dhoni and Ash look at each other, but don't go for the review. That drifted in appreciably]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, no run, shortish and spinning away, cut straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, no run, Carter gets forward and defends solidly to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[Slip and a short cover now]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, 2 runs, Carter kneels down and then drags the sweep to deep backward square leg, Shami has some work to do and does it well]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, no run, well tossed up outside off, Carter goes for a big drive and is beaten. Turned away too]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Simmons, no run, back of a length outside off, pushed wide of the diving cover, but point mops up]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Carter, 1 run, on the pads, whipped away to deep square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Carter, no run, pitched up outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Carter, <b>FOUR</b>, nice back foot punch. Carter going deep into his crease and punching it to the left of short point, races away]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place for Sharma]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Carter, no run, back of a length outside off, defended to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to J Carter, no run, short and down leg, hurries onto Carter who pulls and misses. Hit on the thigh pad and the ball falls near his feet]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, no run, punched back to Ashwin, who sticks his right boot out and deflects it to short mid-wicket. Nifty footwork from Ashwin]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, 1 run, gets forward and drives uppishly but straight to the fielder at long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, no run, defended with an open face to slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to J Carter, no run, tossed up on off, Carter presses forward and defends to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[From round the wicket with a slip and a leg slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, 1 run, stops on Simmons who flicks and gets an inside edge to deep backward square leg, gets off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, no run, tossed up on the stumps, driven back to Ashwin]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to J Carter, no run, pitched up outside off, sweet drive off the front foot, but straight to the fielder at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to J Carter, no run, full outside off, Carter watches it well and then shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to J Carter, no run, short of length outside off, pushed off the back foot to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to J Carter, 2 runs, down leg, whipped to deep backward square leg, for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Simmons, leg byes, 1 run, angling in, down leg, off the pad as Simmons misses the flick, they take a leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Simmons, no run, back of a length outside off, left alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Simmons, <b>wide</b>, dug in short outside off, Simmons sways away from the line of the delivery, square leg ump signals wide and Shami isn't impressed at all. That didn't look wide]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Carter, no run, pitched up outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Carter, no run, that hits the splice again, but doesn't carry to third slip. Yadav getting the ball to angle across and producing the outside edge. Carter didn't push out hard too, which ensured that it didn't carry]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Carter, no run, pitched up outside off, Carter drives well, but picks out cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to J Carter, no run, short of length outside off, dabbed to the right of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[Apalling batting by West Indies. Gayle was at fault for Samuels' wicket and then in a needless show of bravado he threw his wicket away. The need of the hour was to see off the new ball, especially when the wicket was doing so much and the Indians were bowling superbly. But Gayle wanted to show who the boss was and predictably left his team in hot water. Poor stuff from one of the most experienced campaigners in the team. With Ramdin gone first ball, West Indies have a task to bat out the 50 overs]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Simmons, 3 runs, full and on middle and leg, Simmons shuffles across a little and clips through mid-wicket. Mohit gives chase and prevents the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Lendl Simmons, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Ramdin, <b>out</b> Bowled!! West Indies are falling apart now. Ramdin gets out like this a lot of times. Pitched up outside off, Ramdin's feet are stuck in lead and his cover drive finds the inside edge and clatters into leg stump. The Indians in the crowd are jubilant as Ramdin begins the long walk back. <b>Ramdin b U Yadav 0(1)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[U Yadav to Ramdin, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Denesh Ramdin, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Gayle, <b>out</b> Caught by Mohit Sharma!! Gayle's over-aggressive instincts costs him. The short ball does the trick for Shami. Gayle went for the pull and top-edged it to the only man at deep square leg. Mohit settles under it and takes it despite the sun right in his eyes. Shami can't believe his luck and has a nervous smile. The West Indians in the crowd are a shell-shocked lot. <b>Gayle c Mohit Sharma b Shami 21(27) [4s-2 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shami to Gayle, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Gayle, no run, some defence now from Gayle. Gets right behind the line and defends to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Gayle, <b>wide</b>, a late call for wide as Shami slips in the shorter ball, just over the head of Gayle and rising further, square leg ump calls that a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Gayle, no run, wild shot and beaten. Gayle charges Shami and tries to slog to leg, the ball beats the bat and goes over the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Gayle, 2 runs, short of length on the ribs, nudged to deep backward square leg, for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now over the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[Coming back to the Samuels run out, Gayle was just ball-watching. Samuels completed the run and then came back, so a run and a half there. He was very upset at getting out. Gayle just stood there and didn't react at all. He was more worried about the fact that whether Mohit will take the catch or not]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Gayle, <b>FOUR</b>, pitched up and angling in, Gayle stands deep in his crease and hoicks it over mid-on. Opened the front leg and swung well. Gayle is in the mood now]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Gayle, no run, angled in and then moves away a shade to beat Gayle who was pushing forward. Cracker from Shami from round the wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Gayle, 1 run, now round the wicket for the last delivery, dug in short and on the ribs, pulled to deep backward square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Gayle, <b>SIX</b>, take that Yadav! Gayle wants to show who the boss is. A length ball and Gayle has swung that miles over mid-wicket. The ball carries into the stands. Stood there and whacked the leather off that]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Gayle, 2 runs, Gayle is angry and nearly gets out. <b>Shami drops a tough, tough chance at third man</b>. It was slashed to his left and despite running a long way, and stretching to get both hands, the ball spilled out. They come back for the couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Gayle, <b>FOUR</b>, Gayle hits that right off the middle of the bat, pitched up outside off, Gayle lofts over mid-off. Clean hit]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jonathan Carter, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Gayle, <b>out</b> Samuels Run Out!! Hara-kiri from the West Indians. Nearly a catch to mid-on as Gayle spliced the pull, fabulous effort from Mohit, he came charging in and took it on the bounce, after diving forward, he saw that Samuels was halfway and near Gayle. Threw the ball at the non-striker's end, Kohli ran in to collect the throw and effected a simple run-out with Samuels nowhere. That's a gift of a wicket for India. <b>Samuels run out (Mohit Sharma/Kohli) 2(7)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[U Yadav to Gayle, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Samuels has been run out!</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Samuels, 1 run, Samuels pre-meditates the big shot and almost gets out. He made room to a middle stump yorker and just about got the bat down on the ball, quick single taken in front of mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Samuels, 1 run, opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Gayle, 1 run, <b>almost a great catch by Umesh at third man!</b> Gayle threw the bat at a full and wide delivery outside off, a thick outside edge was flying to Umesh's right. He ran and dived full length, had the ball in his grasp, till the moment the hands hit the ground. It still was lodged in his chest as he rolled, but popped out. Nevertheless, a magnificent effort and Dhoni applauds that piece of fielding from Umesh. Would've gone down as one of the catches of the tournament]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Gayle, no run, now outside off and no need for Gayle to play at that, he leaves]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Gayle, <b>wide</b>, down leg as Shami loses his radar]]></line><line><![CDATA[Great reaction from Gayle after getting beaten by that ripper. He just opened his eyes and made it as large as possible. Nodded at Shami and acknowledged the fact that he couldn't do anything against such a kind of delivery. Gayle ever the cool dude!]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Gayle, no run, well wide of off, Gayle leaves]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shami is now coming round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Gayle, no run, superb delivery. Pitches middle and then squares up Gayle completely, great bounce as the ball flies past the outside edge. Dhoni leaps to collect]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Gayle, no run, the pressure is getting to Gayle. He charges Shami and wants to deposit him out the park, swings across the line and is beaten by a long way. Shami has a wry smile on his face]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Gayle, <b>wide</b>, well wide of off, Gayle threw his bat at that and had no chance of connecting]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Our man, <b>Tanmoy</b>, has this to say: 'Crowd getting firmly behind Umesh and Shami, both generating good pace off the deck']]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Samuels, no run, plays inside the line to this full delivery outside off and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Samuels, no run, Samuels' feet are going nowhere, he just pushed out and then the ball was miles away from the bat, can't call that beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Samuels, <b>wide</b>, down leg as Yadav attempts the inswinger, called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Samuels, no run, Samuels is deep in his crease and then watches the outswinger, before leaving it alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Samuels, no run, pitched up outside off, swinging away, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Gayle, 1 run, first runs off the bat for <b>West Indies in 21 balls.</b> Short of a length and on the hips, nudged wide of backward square leg. They are happy with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Gayle, no run, full outside off, Gayle pushes forward and then lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Samuels, no run, dug in short and that's a good short ball, Samuels did well to sway away from the line despite the ball being outside off. Dhoni leaps to collect]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Marlon Samuels, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Dwayne Smith, <b>out</b> Caught by Dhoni!! Shami puts Dwayne Smith out of his misery. Dharmasena had the finger up in a flash. It wasn't there for the cut, it nipped back in and was on a fuller length to be playing the shot, was too close to his body too and Smith just feathered an edge through to Dhoni. Smith's sorry WC continues. <b>Dwayne Smith c Dhoni b Shami 6(20) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shami to Dwayne Smith, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Dwayne Smith, no run, Dwayne Smith has played that well, didn't pull that as he softly pushed it in front of mid-on, they thought about the single, Gayle even took a few steps out, but they decided against it in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Dwayne Smith, no run, Shami is moving the ball both ways and now pings Dwayne Smith high on the thigh pad, this one moved back in appreciably]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Dwayne Smith, no run, when Shami pitches it up outside off and on a fuller length, Dwayne Smith has no clue. He tries to steer that to third man with the slip cordon waiting and predictably gets beaten. Nothing shot!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Dwayne Smith, leg byes, 2 runs, down leg, off the pad and they take two leg byes]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Gayle, no run, a diving stop to his right by Rahane at backward square leg prevents any runs and gives Yadav a deserved <b>maiden over</b>. Gayle with one leg up in the air, controlled the pull but Jinks pulled out a fine save]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Gayle, no run, this time Yadav beats Gayle, despite the batsman playing inside the line, Gayle tried his best to cover the line, but the ball kept following him and nearly got the snick. Not far from the off stump too, Yadav is generating good steam out there]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Gayle, no run, plays inside the line to the rising short of length delivery outside off, and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Gayle, no run, further wide of off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Gayle, no run, look at that ball carry to Dhoni. Gayle was hopping back, feet in the air and the ball flew over the head of Dhoni who leapt and collected. Yadav has a wry smile on his face after delivering that]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Gayle, no run, softly nudged to mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Dwayne Smith, no run, Dwayne Smith is all at sea against Shami. Tries to manufacture something out of nowhere, to deny Shami a maiden. Walks down the track and attempts a slash, but the sharp inswinger beats his shot and flies over the stumps. The true bounce of the WACA on show]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Dwayne Smith, no run, nips back in sharply, Dwayne Smith pushes it towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Dwayne Smith, no run, another pull attempted and again missed. This time it was down leg and it rolls off the pads after Dwayne Smith missed the shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Dwayne Smith, no run, Dwayne Smith is in all sorts of trouble against the short ball and now gets hit on the stomach. This one hurries him for pace and he looks very ungainly when he is playing those kind of strokes. That has hurt him and he walks away to regain his composure]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Dwayne Smith, no run, back of a length and on the stumps, tucked to the right of square leg, they don't take the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Dwayne Smith, no run, pitched up outside off, Dwayne Smith goes hard on the drive, on-the-up too but finds Rohit at cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Gayle, no run, short of length and on the stumps, Gayle hops a little and defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[A leg slip in place now for Gayle]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, back of a length outside off, Dwayne Smith opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Three slips</b> in place for Yadav]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dwayne Smith, no run, pitched up and moving away, Yadav getting the ball to shape away, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dwayne Smith, no run, another poor stroke. Short and rising outside off, Dwayne Smith slashes without any footwork and gets beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dwayne Smith, no run, second time that Dwayne Smith has pulled and nearly pops a catch. This one too is quick onto him and in the end he plays a half-hearted short-arm jab, that doesn't carry to mid-on. The length wasn't there to be playing that kind of a stroke]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dwayne Smith, no run, pitched up outside off, swinging away, Smith sees that and then shoulders arms]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Our man, <b>Tanmoy Mookherjee</b>, is at the ground and he says that the atmosphere is electric at the WACA. This is the last match on this ground and it's already buzzing, despite being a very hot day.]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Gayle, no run, well outside off, easily left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Gayle, no run, loud shout for caught behind from Shami. But nothing from Dharmasena. He shakes his head and says no. Short of a length and rising, angling across Gayle, who poked out to defend, the ball missed the edge, just though and carried nicely to Dhoni. There is a <b>slight movement on Snicko</b>, but India don't take the review]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, full and down leg, clipped straight to the fielder at fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, Dwayne Smith comes back well with a nice cut shot. Shami going short and wide outside off, Smith cuts and to the left of point, third man had no chance. Smith and West Indies are off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Dwayne Smith, no run, Shami hurries Dwayne Smith on the pull, it came back in and Smith was late on the shot. Hit the splice of the bat and nearly carried to Rahane at square leg. Promising signs for Shami though]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Dwayne Smith, no run, back of a length and angling in, Dwayne Smith tucks it to square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Smith and Gayle are at the crease. Dwayne Smith is on strike. Shami will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Before the players came out for the anthems, Sammy gave a thumbs up to Dhawan. The anthems are done and out walk the openers onto the field. The Indians are in a huddle and break out of it. Shami to start. Smith to face. Here we go.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>India</b> (Playing XI): Shikhar Dhawan, Rohit Sharma, Virat Kohli, Ajinkya Rahane, Suresh Raina, MS Dhoni(w/c), Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Mohammed Shami, Umesh Yadav, Mohit Sharma]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>West Indies</b> (Playing XI): Chris Gayle, Dwayne Smith, Marlon Samuels, Jonathan Carter, Denesh Ramdin(w), Lendl Simmons, Darren Sammy, Andre Russell, Jason Holder(c), Jerome Taylor, Kemar Roach]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>West Indies have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhoni:</b> "We've kept it simple. The only big change that has happened is that the guys are believing more in the process. They have understood the fact that when we are bowling, we have to rely on bowling in specific areas and not to look for wickets, just keep bowling in the right areas and you will get wickets. Same with the batting. Pick your shots when you want to play it rather than putting too much pressure of looking to explode. I am not too disappointed to lose the toss, it looks like a wicket that won't change much. Also I felt there was a bit of swing when we bowled in the other game. I don't think it changes too much, hopefully it will be the same. It just gives us good exposure. If we are needed to chase later on in the tournament we'll be more ready for it. It's a bit of an advantage in the sense that we know how the wicket behaves here. Maybe their batsmen or bowlers will take that extra few overs to know what's the kind of bounce you can encounter over here and what is the right length that you have to bowl as a bowler. Apart from that, I feel with the videos and everything available, most of the international cricketers know they need to alter their batting style or a bit in the bowling length. One change, <b>Shami</b> is fit, he comes back and so <b>Bhuvi</b> has to make space for him."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Holder</b>: "We just have to start well in this game against India, it's a must win game for us. I am very confident coming into this game that we can execute. We are going to bat first. Looks to be a good wicket, we want to put runs on the board and then defend it. I wouldn't say there is a specific comfort zone, the wickets have been very good here and we just feel comfortable putting runs on the board. It's just upto us now to defend them. We have to execute our death bowling a lot better than we did in the previous game, but I am confident today that everything will come together. Just one change, Kemar Roach in for Sulieman Benn. We just feel that Kemar is more suited to the conditions."]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's <b>toss time</b> folks.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pitch Report:</b> "It's another warm day at WACA, Perth. It is the same pitch that was used for the Afghanistan-Australia game. It is a bit dry and hard. The ball will carry through. There will be bounce and pace. The more you pitch the ball up the more success you will get. If you bowl slower, the spinners will extract some turn. The wicket has something in it for everyone. The team winning the toss will bat first and look to put the runs on the board," reckon <b>Sourav Ganguly</b> and <b>Ian Bishop</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here is <b>Ashwin</b> talking about how the rule changes in ODI cricket have made bowlers like him 'feel very little'. "I think it's huge in the sense if you get a couple of wickets up front, then the entire game turns on its head," Ashwin said ahead of India's fourth group game against the West Indies at the WACA ground. "As far as the spinner is concerned, when I come in, I've got that little bit more freedom. Having said that, I just made up my mind that I'm going to bowl this way the entire tournament. Come what may, I'll try to execute it, and that is one of the reasons that I've come out to express myself in any of these major tournaments. I like the big stage, and I like to assume I do it my own way."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Darren Sammy</b> said that his team needs to bring out their best game against India. "It's another cricket match but India is playing well at the moment. You give each and every opponent the respect that they deserve. We have always had good matches against India and we have to bring out our 'A' game to beat India."]]></line><line><![CDATA[On being asked about MS Dhoni, Holder said he has learnt a lot from the Indian skipper. "I've picked up a lot from Dhoni. He's a good leader. He's a guy who is respected in the dressing room. Going about my career I tend to look at a few players and look at a few things people do, not particularly MS Dhoni, but successful players who have played cricket before. I just try to take bits and pieces from everybody and try to put it together into one."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Some quotes from both camps before the game. First up is <b>Jason Holder</b>. "I back my bowlers to execute their plans, putting them back and setting them on the back foot," said Holder during the media briefing on the eve of the game. "But they have a pretty good line-up and some good quality players. We've planned for them and we're just looking to execute our plans tomorrow."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>West Indies</b>: West Indies may have been badly beaten by South Africa, but in all likelihood they will go in with the same side that lost to South Africa, meaning still no place for Kemar Roach.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pre-match team news, <b>India</b>: Mohammed Shami who didn't play in the last game due to a minor knee issue is fit and bowled in the nets prior to the game. He may come in for Bhuvneshwar Kumar in the only likely change for this game.]]></line><line><![CDATA[It later turned out that Kohli had intended it for a different journalist. He then apologized through another journalist and the team management chose to play down the incident as a case of 'misunderstanding'.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Kohli's emotions had come to a boil at the scenic Murdoch University ground on Tuesday after the team's training session had ended. Before heading towards the nets, the Indian vice-captain confronted a journalist and went on an expletive-filled tirade in full public view.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The release also added: "The BCCI has been in touch with the Indian team management on this issue, and has advised that this kind of incident should not be repeated."]]></line><line><![CDATA[A bit of controversy and Virat Kohli never go out of place. The Indian vice-captain was reprimanded for losing his cool at a senior journalist just before India's game against the West Indies. His behaviour was reported both to the BCCI and the ICC. "The player in question has been told to maintain the dignity of the Indian team at all times, and avoid any such behaviour in the future. The BCCI would like to request the concerned parties to move on, and focus on the Indian cricket team's campaign in the ongoing ICC CWC 2015," stated the BCCI release.]]></line><line><![CDATA[West Indies were on a high coming into their clash against South Africa. They had beaten Pakistan soundly and were up for the clash against the Proteas. They started well with the ball too, keeping things tight till the 20th over. All that changed, once AB de Villiers came out to the middle. Runs flowed like a rampaging river from his bat as he broke one record after another. The white Kookaburra flew to all corners of the SCG as he made the fastest 150 in ODIs. South Africa made 408 and once Gayle was out cheaply, it was the margin of victory that everyone were guessing. West Indies were shot out for 151 giving South Africa a 257-run win. It was the joint highest victory margin in World Cups in terms of runs and severely dented West Indies' NRAJ.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Let's now have a look at how India and West Indies respectively performed in their last outing in this tournament. Starting with India. India simply blew the hapless UAE side, bowling them out for 102 in just 31.3 overs. The UAE batsmen had no clue against India's bowling and it was a stroll in the park for India's batsmen. Rohit Sharma helped himself to a fifty as he sought some form going into the business end of the tournament. That crushing win made it three wins in a row for India and kept their winning momentum going.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The relations between the boards might not be the greatest, but the players from both sides get along very well. Thanks largely in part to the IPL. The likes of Gayle, Sammy, Russell and Holder in this current West Indian team are pals with a number of the Indian players. In fact Gayle and Kohli got along like a house on fire when they both played together for the Bangalore. So don't expect any tension or verbal jousts during the clash at the WACA on Friday.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Also the BCCI suspended all bilateral cricket tours with the WICB after the pull-out. "At the moment, it looks unlikely that the bilateral series would resume anytime soon. It will be up to the legal cell now to see if and when a settlement takes place," revealed an insider.]]></line><line><![CDATA["The BCCI holds the WICB responsible and liable for all such consequences and intends to enforce its rights to seek compensation from the WICB to the fullest extent permissible in law."]]></line><line><![CDATA["Diwali in India is a monumental disaster for the BCCI. It is during this season that our partners derive the most value from their rights. Our broadcaster had committed to its advertisers during this season and on account of your actions, is facing a severe crisis the effects of which are felt by the BCCI."]]></line><line><![CDATA["The BCCI is faced with huge revenue losses, a loss of reputation and is at risk of losing valuable commercial partners. The consequences of cancellation of a committed home tour during the biggest festival season."]]></line><line><![CDATA[That move by the Dwayne Bravo led West Indian side severely upset the BCCI who slapped a $42 million lawsuit, claiming damages stemming from the abandoned tour. "The consequences on the BCCI of not delivering a scheduled home tour to its members, sponsors, broadcasters and the fans are multi-fold and crippling," the BCCI letter said.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Gone are the days when a West Indian side evoked fear and awe in equal measure, in an opposition side. Going into today's clash at Perth it's the Indians who are considered favorites to come out on top. Relations between the two cricket boards haven't been cordial ever since West Indies pulled out of India's tour last year due to payment dispute with the WICB.]]></line><line><![CDATA[So that is that then on the 1983 triumph. The reason we brought that up today was to put into context what India did to West Indies in a World Cup. It's India versus West Indies again, but how times have changed. Back then West Indies were the all-conquering, mighty power. India were just a another team. Now in 2015, West Indies are a shadow of their former self. Infighting, lack of inspirational leaders, indiscipline, constant squabbling, a farce of a cricket board, lack of interest in the youngsters back home have relegated cricket to the background in the Caribbean.]]></line><line><![CDATA[So, why a movie on the 1983 World Cup? "Not many know that India were the underdogs. It was the biggest thing to happen to us in sports. After the win everyone started looking up to us; so it is a good idea to showcase the facts and the reality," says  Sanjay.]]></line><line><![CDATA[In honor of India's win, a movie is being made on the historic event by Vishnu Vardhan Induri and national award-winning director Sanjay Puran Singh. "It's surprising that no one ever thought of this. Our film is going to be an official biography of the 1983 match," says Vishnu.]]></line><line><![CDATA[One more from <b>Shastri</b>: "Being the youngest man in that party, all I'll tell you is that day at Lord's changed my life. June 25, 1983 changed the face of Indian cricket. And when I say that I don't only mean the cricket lovers. The corporate got behind the team, the media started to give the Indian cricket team the recognition they deserve."]]></line><line><![CDATA[More from <b>Kapil</b>: "We felt that the 1983 World Cup changed the entire sport in our country and gave a new dimension to Indian cricket."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Joel Garner</b>: "For a long time, two or three months, I wouldn't talk to any of my team-mates," he admits. "I would say that the World Cup 1983 was the biggest disappointment in terms of my cricket career."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sunny Gavaskar</b>: "It's something that brings goosebumps even after so many years. At times it is difficult to believe that you were once a part of a World Cup winning team. It is the best moment of your cricketing career to see your captain lift the World Cup up in the air with massive reaction and reception from the huge crowd gathered at Lord's. It was a moment to savour."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravi Shastri</b>: "We just said, 'let's go out there and enjoy ourselves'. There was no thought of winning or losing. We had played damn good cricket to reach the final and now let's go and enjoy."]]></line><line><![CDATA[What did Kapil and his team have to say after their win? First up is Kapil. "We were just a bunch of young boys who wanted to have fun. Winning was more fun in the evening and that's what we started to look out for  how we can enjoy more. The first match itself (against West Indies) gave us a little hope. After that our aim was to make the top four. Every match became more and more serious after that."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Clive Lloyd</b>, the losing captain gave full credit to Kapil's inspirational leadership. "He's been able to rally the entire team behind him," said Lloyd admiringly, adding: "He's really done a marvellous job." Also Lloyd had this to say at the end of the final: "Indian cricket has arrived. And it's here to stay."]]></line><line><![CDATA[A warm welcome to one and all as we begin our coverage of India's clash with West Indies at Perth. Having started off with the 1983 triumph, let's dwell on it for some more time. This is how the newspapers responded to India's giant-killing win. "Kapil's men turn world upside down" screamed the London Times headline while the report went on to term India as "cannonfodder turned cannon".]]></line><line><![CDATA[India may have subsequently gone on to win many trophies, including World Cup wins in 2007 and 2011, but till date the 1983 World Cup win is considered to be their finest achievement on a cricket field. Why? Because no-one expected them to win and against one of the all-time great sides in history. Also before that win, cricket wasn't the crazy, popular and all-encompassing sport in the country that it is now. The win gave birth to future legends like Sachin Tendulkar who was inspired to take up the game after watching India win. So one cannot equate the enormity of Kapil Dev's side's triumph.]]></line><line><![CDATA[A tremendous explosion of interest since that epic day has seen Indian cricket grow immeasurably and fast forward to 2015, India is the cricketing superpower. One may never know how Indian cricket may have shaped up, had India not won that day, but it can be said that, that triumph inspired millions of Indians to believe and hope that they can achieve great things, not only in the sporting arena but in life too.]]></line><line><![CDATA[So what happened then on 25th June 1983? India - against all odds pulled off one of the greatest upsets in sporting history when they defended 183 against West Indies. It was a historic day in the annals of Indian cricket and 'Kapil's Devils' wrote their names into the record books. After that day, cricket in India was never the same and one can safely surmise that Indian cricket can be split into two halves. Before 25th June 1983 and after 25th June 1983.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The bookies were offering odds at 50:1 for an Indian win. No-one gave them a chance. Here is an interesting anecdote that encapsulates how even Kapil Dev's wife didn't give her husband's side a chance. Since they had a low score, even the family members, of the cricketers, including Kapil's wife didn't expect them to win. So when the match was going on, Kapil's wife had gone shopping and missed the match. But no one told Kapil about this and he got to know about it only after the match!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>12:30 Local Time, 04:30 GMT, 10:00 IST:</b> Twice World Champions and red-hot favorites to make it three in a row. Gordon Greenidge. Vivian Richards. Clive Lloyd. Jeff Dujon. Andy Roberts. Michael Holding. Joel Garner and Malcolm Marshall. Versus - Krish Srikkanth. Sunny Gavaskar. Mohinder Amarnath. Syed Kirmani. Kapil Dev. Roger Binny. Madan Lal and Balwinder Sandhu. It was a no-contest at least if you look at the head-to-heads individually. A galaxy of stars versus a bunch of hard-working, honest triers. The fearsome West Indies' side of 1983 led by Clive Lloyd were expected to steamroll India in the final at Lord's.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/>Events over the last two days relating to a tiff between vice-captain Virat Kohli and a senior Indian journalist have dominated news space, but Friday's Group B fixture against the West Indies presents India with an opportunity to shut out the distractions and continue their unbeaten run in the tournament.<br/><br/>It was expected that whatever transpired in Perth over the past two days would be the talking point when an Indian player attended the media interaction ahead of their game at the WACA ground. But as has been the practice, India sent out to the Man of the Match from their previous match, R Ashwin, for the pre-match press conference.<br/><br/>Ashwin's pragmatic interaction with the media meant the conversation largely focused on the game at hand and his performance in the previous game against UAE here, where he took career-best figures of 4 for 25. The offspinner's improving form in the tournament has given India more control in the middle overs where he has flourished by attacking the batsmen.<br/><br/>Pace bowler Mohammad Shami, who was rested for the previous game against the UAE continued to bowl at the nets, suggesting that he may return to take his place, but whether India would sacrifice Bhuvneshwar Kumar, who had returned from an injury to feature in the game last Saturday, remains to be seen. Bhuvneshwar boasts of a strong record against the West Indies, particularly Chris Gayle, whose threat continues to linger with the big Jamaican having recently smashed the first double century in World Cup history.<br/><br/>Predictably, it should be the only area of selection where the Indian team management may have a long discussion about, as the rest of the bowling as well as the batting has impressed in the last three matches. While the top order have been amongst the runs consistently, the likes of MS Dhoni and Ravindra Jadeja in the lower middle order haven't spent enough time in the middle, and against Pakistan and South Africa they were unable to kick on after the top order had set it up for them. But with head coach Duncan Fletcher having rejoined the team, India would look to him as they hope to improve on that aspect of their game.<br/><br/>The West Indies, on the other hand, have enjoyed a long rest since their arrival in the city, and save for the odd practice session, have been limited to watching the action from their Group. A heavy defeat to South Africa has meant the West Indies can't afford any more lapses to stay in contention for a spot in the quarter-finals and the game against India will put them under extra pressure.<br/><br/>Gayle's back troubles have meant the batsman takes limited part in the team's practice sessions and after a light hit in the nets at the Murdoch University ground on Tuesday, he was seen having a long conversation with chairman of selectors Clive Lloyd, away from the rest of the team. Having given an interview about reconsidering his Test career, he may have been picking Lloyd's brains on reinforcing his belief after the mauling his team received at the hands of South Africa.<br/><br/>West Indies captain Jason Holder has fond memories of the WACA ground since he made his international debut here, but knows an opposition like India could easily trip them up. Holder was taken apart by AB de Villiers in the game at the SCG, and how the captain comes back after giving away 104 runs from his 10 overs will speak volumes about his character at the end of Friday's match.<br/><br/>Kemar Roach was rested for the previous game but the conditions at the WACA may prompt the West Indies to include him in the side. On both days of the West Indies training, their bowlers were seen practicing death bowling with diligence with the likes of Roach, Jerome Taylor and Andre Russell sending down numerous deliveries to get their yorkers right.<br/><br/>The West Indies have crossed the 300-mark in three out of their four matches but their bowlers have also consistently given away runs to make matters tough, and against India on Friday, they would be guarding against a repeat of their SCG performance. India would be mindful of that, and will look to target their bowlers, particularly their 23-year-old captain.<br/><br/><b>Probable XIs:</b><br/><br/><b>India:</b> 1. Rohit Sharma, 2. Shikhar Dhawan, 3. Virat Kohli, 4. Ajinkya Rahane , 5. Suresh Raina, 6. MS Dhoni (capt and wk), 7. Ravindra Jadeja, 8. R Ashwin, 9. Bhuvneshwar Kumar/Mohammed Shami, 10. Umesh Yadav, 11. Mohit Sharma.<br/><br/><b>West Indies:</b> 1. Chris Gayle, 2. Dwayne Smith, 3. Jonathan Carter, 4. Marlon Samuels, 5. Denesh Ramdin (wk), 6. Lendl Simmons, 7. Andre Russell, 8. Darren Sammy, 9. Jason Holder (capt), 10. Sulieman Benn, 11. Jerome Taylor/Kemar Roach.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>West Indies</b> (From): Chris Gayle, Dwayne Smith, Marlon Samuels, Jonathan Carter, Denesh Ramdin(w), Lendl Simmons, Darren Sammy, Andre Russell, Jason Holder(c), Jerome Taylor, Nikita Miller, Kemar Roach, Sheldon Cottrell, Sulieman Benn, Johnson Charles]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>India</b> (From): Shikhar Dhawan, Rohit Sharma, Virat Kohli, Ajinkya Rahane, Suresh Raina, MS Dhoni(c/w), Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Mohammed Shami, Umesh Yadav, Mohit Sharma, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Stuart Binny, Axar Patel, Ambati Rayudu]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>182</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>10</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>44.2</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="West Indies">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Smith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>20</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Shami</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7909</bowlerId>
						<fielder>MS Dhoni</fielder>
						<fielderId>265</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>247</playerid>
					<name>Chris Gayle</name>
					<batsman-name>Gayle</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Gayle</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>21</runs>
					<balls>27</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Shami</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7909</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mohit Sharma</fielder>
						<fielderId>8181</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>356</playerid>
					<name>Marlon Samuels</name>
					<batsman-name>Samuels</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Samuels</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mohit Sharma</fielder>
						<fielderId>8181</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Virat Kohli</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>1413</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8314</playerid>
					<name>Jonathan Carter</name>
					<batsman-name>J Carter</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>J Carter</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>21</runs>
					<balls>43</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Ashwin</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1593</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mohammed Shami</fielder>
						<fielderId>7909</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>399</playerid>
					<name>Denesh Ramdin</name>
					<batsman-name>Ramdin</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ramdin</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Umesh</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1858</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>599</playerid>
					<name>Lendl Simmons</name>
					<batsman-name>L Simmons</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Simmons</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>22</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mohit Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8181</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Umesh Yadav</fielder>
						<fielderId>1858</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>253</playerid>
					<name>Darren Sammy</name>
					<batsman-name>Sammy</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sammy</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>26</runs>
					<balls>55</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Shami</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7909</bowlerId>
						<fielder>MS Dhoni</fielder>
						<fielderId>265</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7736</playerid>
					<name>Andre Russell</name>
					<batsman-name>A Russell</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>A Russell</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>8</runs>
					<balls>8</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>R Jadeja</bowler>
					<bowlerId>587</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Virat Kohli</fielder>
						<fielderId>1413</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8313</playerid>
					<name>Jason Holder</name>
					<batsman-name>J Holder</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>J Holder</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>57</runs>
					<balls>64</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>R Jadeja</bowler>
					<bowlerId>587</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Virat Kohli</fielder>
						<fielderId>1413</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>379</playerid>
					<name>Jerome Taylor</name>
					<batsman-name>Jerome Taylor</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Jerome Taylor</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>11</runs>
					<balls>18</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Umesh</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1858</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Umesh</fielder>
						<fielderId>1858</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1359</playerid>
					<name>Kemar Roach</name>
					<batsman-name>Roach</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Roach</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>255</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>8</runs>
				<overs>4.5</overs>
				<batsman>Dwayne Smith</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>356</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>15</runs>
				<overs>7.2</overs>
				<batsman>Marlon Samuels</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Samuels</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>247</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>35</runs>
				<overs>8.6</overs>
				<batsman>Chris Gayle</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Gayle</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>399</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>35</runs>
				<overs>9.1</overs>
				<batsman>Denesh Ramdin</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Ramdin</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>599</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>67</runs>
				<overs>18.1</overs>
				<batsman>Lendl Simmons</batsman>
				<batsman-name>L Simmons</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8314</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>71</runs>
				<overs>21.5</overs>
				<batsman>Jonathan Carter</batsman>
				<batsman-name>J Carter</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7736</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>85</runs>
				<overs>24.1</overs>
				<batsman>Andre Russell</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Russell</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>253</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>124</runs>
				<overs>35.4</overs>
				<batsman>Darren Sammy</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Sammy</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>379</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>175</runs>
				<overs>42.6</overs>
				<batsman>Jerome Taylor</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Jerome Taylor</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8313</playerid>
				<nbr>10</nbr>
				<runs>182</runs>
				<overs>44.2</overs>
				<batsman>Jason Holder</batsman>
				<batsman-name>J Holder</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>16</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>5</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>21</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="India">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7909</playerid>
					<name>Mohammed Shami</name>
					<bowler-name>Shami</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shami</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>2</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>5</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1858</playerid>
					<name>Umesh Yadav</name>
					<bowler-name>Umesh</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>U Yadav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>42</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>5</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<bowler-name>Ashwin</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ashwin</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>38</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Mohit Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mohit Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>2</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>4</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<bowler-name>R Jadeja</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8.2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>27</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1446</playerid>
					<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhawan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhawan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>576</playerid>
					<name>Rohit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Rohit</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rohit</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<bowler-name>Kohli</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Kohli</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1447</playerid>
					<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
					<bowler-name>A Rahane</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rahane</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<bowler-name>Raina</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Raina</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhoni</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhoni</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>185</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>6</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>39.1</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="India">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>576</playerid>
					<name>Rohit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Rohit</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rohit</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>7</runs>
					<balls>18</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Jerome Taylor</bowler>
					<bowlerId>379</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Denesh Ramdin</fielder>
						<fielderId>399</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1446</playerid>
					<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhawan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhawan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Jerome Taylor</bowler>
					<bowlerId>379</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Darren Sammy</fielder>
						<fielderId>253</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Kohli</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>33</runs>
					<balls>36</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>A Russell</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7736</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Marlon Samuels</fielder>
						<fielderId>356</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1447</playerid>
					<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
					<batsman-name>A Rahane</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rahane</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>14</runs>
					<balls>34</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Roach</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1359</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Denesh Ramdin</fielder>
						<fielderId>399</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Raina</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>22</runs>
					<balls>25</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Dwayne Smith</bowler>
					<bowlerId>255</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Denesh Ramdin</fielder>
						<fielderId>399</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhoni</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>45</runs>
					<balls>56</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<batsman-name>R Jadeja</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>13</runs>
					<balls>23</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>A Russell</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7736</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Marlon Samuels</fielder>
						<fielderId>356</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<batsman-name>Ashwin</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ashwin</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>16</runs>
					<balls>32</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7909</playerid>
					<name>Mohammed Shami</name>
					<batsman-name>Shami</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shami</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1858</playerid>
					<name>Umesh Yadav</name>
					<batsman-name>Umesh</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>U Yadav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Mohit Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mohit Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1446</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>11</runs>
				<overs>4.1</overs>
				<batsman>Shikhar Dhawan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dhawan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>576</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>20</runs>
				<overs>6.6</overs>
				<batsman>Rohit Sharma</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rohit</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1413</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>63</runs>
				<overs>14.6</overs>
				<batsman>Virat Kohli</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1447</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>78</runs>
				<overs>17.5</overs>
				<batsman>Ajinkya Rahane</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Rahane</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>413</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>107</runs>
				<overs>22.5</overs>
				<batsman>Suresh Raina</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>587</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>134</runs>
				<overs>29.3</overs>
				<batsman>Ravindra Jadeja</batsman>
				<batsman-name>R Jadeja</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>1</byes>
			<wides>19</wides>
			<noballs>3</noballs>
			<legbyes>3</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>26</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="West Indies">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>379</playerid>
					<name>Jerome Taylor</name>
					<bowler-name>Jerome Taylor</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Jerome Taylor</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>33</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8313</playerid>
					<name>Jason Holder</name>
					<bowler-name>J Holder</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>J Holder</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>29</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1359</playerid>
					<name>Kemar Roach</name>
					<bowler-name>Roach</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Roach</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>44</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>5</wides>
					<noballs>2</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7736</playerid>
					<name>Andre Russell</name>
					<bowler-name>A Russell</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>A Russell</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>43</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>9</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<bowler-name>Dwayne Smith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Smith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>22</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>356</playerid>
					<name>Marlon Samuels</name>
					<bowler-name>Samuels</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Samuels</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3.1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>10</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>247</playerid>
					<name>Chris Gayle</name>
					<bowler-name>Gayle</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Gayle</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8314</playerid>
					<name>Jonathan Carter</name>
					<bowler-name>J Carter</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>J Carter</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>399</playerid>
					<name>Denesh Ramdin</name>
					<bowler-name>Ramdin</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ramdin</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>599</playerid>
					<name>Lendl Simmons</name>
					<bowler-name>L Simmons</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Simmons</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>253</playerid>
					<name>Darren Sammy</name>
					<bowler-name>Sammy</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sammy</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



