<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="12903" >
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>Final</gameDesc>
		<series>WC 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>New Zealand</home>
		<away>Australia</away>
		<teamsabbr>NZ vs AUS</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>NZ</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>AUS</awayabbr>
		<homeId>13</homeId>
		<awayId>4</awayId>
		<venue>Melbourne Cricket Ground, Melbourne</venue>
		<startdate>29 03 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>29 03 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>New Zealand</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Australia won by 7 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Australia</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>7</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries>Mitchell Starc</manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Kumar Dharmasena</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Richard Kettleborough</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Marais Erasmus</Name>
			<Country>RSA</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Ranjan Madugalle</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>03:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150329100601</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>Aus</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>NZ</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>186</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>3</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>33.1</batteamovers>
		<status>Australia won by 7 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>2250</playerid>
			<name>Steven Smith*</name>
			<batsman-name>S Smith</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>S Smith</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>56</runs>
			<balls-faced>71</balls-faced>
			<fours>3</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>158</playerid>
			<name>Shane Watson</name>
			<batsman-name>Watson</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Watson</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>2</runs>
			<balls-faced>5</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>9067</playerid>
			<name>Matt Henry*</name>
			<bowler-name>M Henry</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Matt Henry</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>9.1</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>46</runs>
			<wickets>2</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1057</playerid>
			<name>Tim Southee</name>
			<bowler-name>Southee</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Southee</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>8</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>65</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>184</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>138</playerid>
<name>Michael Clarke</name>
<player-runs>74</player-runs>
<player-balls>72</player-balls>
<runs>175</runs>
<wicket-nbr>3</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>9067</bowlerid>
<bowlername>M Henry</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>6</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>3</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>9</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[4 4 4 4 1 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>Wd W . 1 2 2 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. . 1 . . 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_WC/NZ_AUS_MAR29/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[This has been a great World Cup and we enjoyed bringing every bit of it to you. Hope you enjoyed our coverage as well. Looking forward to your company on April 8 for the start of the T20 extravaganza. On behalf of <b>Srivathsa</b>, <b>Pradeep</b>, <b>Akshay</b>, <b>Sidhant</b>, <b>Raju</b>, <b>Krishna</b>, <b>Sriram</b> and <b>Bharath</b>, this is <b>Ramakrishnan</b> saying goodbye for one final time. Take care!]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's a great day for Player of the Series Mitchell Starc and Player of the Match James Faulkner in their young careers.]]></line><line><![CDATA[David Warner's 178. Pakistan's inspiring victory against the Proteas. Bangladesh stunning England and knocking them out at Adelaide. Teams failing to keep the Indian bowlers at bay. Brendan Taylor's goodbye to Zimbabwe. JP Duminy's hat-trick against Sri Lanka. Mahela Jayawardene and Kumar Sangakkara bowing out on a sad note. Wahab Riaz's jaw-dropping spell against Australia. Grant Elliott denying his country of birth in the semi-final. Steven Smith's love affair with India. Daniel Vettori calling time on his international career. These are some of the moments that I could recollect. Phew! What a treat we had.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Let's relive some more moments for one last time. Steven Finn's hat-trick. James Taylor denied a hundred because of an umpiring blunder. A high-profile clash between India and Pakistan. Ireland thumping West Indies and proving that it was right to include the Associates. Tim Southee rattling England. Afghanistan scaring Sri Lanka. Chris Gayle's double-hundred. Samiullah Shenwari's brilliance with the bat. The AB de Villiers assault at the SCG. That insane game at the Eden Park between the Trans-Tasman rivals. Kumar Sangakkara scoring hundreds at will. South Africa becoming the first team to score 400 in successive games.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Although Australia weren't as ruthless as they were before in this World Cup, they managed to grab key moments, which was key to their successful journey. The fact that they managed to win the title despite not playing their perfect game in the entire tournament speaks volumes of the depth they have in their outfit. Mitchell Starc outclassing Mitchell Johnson was a sight to watch. Overall, the Australian boys have given a perfect farewell gift for their captain Michael Clarke, who has hung up his ODI boots.]]></line><line><![CDATA[There were so many moments to savour in this World Cup. Let's begin with today and the two teams that were on show today. Brendon McCullum's courageous captaincy - he was not afraid to have four slips and leave the off-side field open looking for wickets early on. His field placings gave a lot of confidence to Boult and Southee, who were exceptional with the new ball throughout the tournament. Baz himself led from the front in the field with his acrobatic efforts. New Zealand's confidence as a whole unit even under pressure was good to see.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Inside the Australian dressing room, Barry 'Nugget' Rees, a former South Australian player, a close friend of coach Darren Lehmann and an inspirational figure in the Australian team for a number of years, pours beer on the World Cup trophy and kisses the cup. He makes a speech to the team. The Australian players then have a beer.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Let's take a look at some of the best <b>tweets</b> from this game: ]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@gauravkalra75:</b> australia have now won world cups in asia, europe, africa, north america & australia. only south america & antarctica remain! #CWC15Final]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@BrianLara:</b> Well played Australia you were the best team by far and your wins from the quarterfinals onwards were clinical and showed your superiority!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@cricket_U:</b> Back to back World Cup Final wins for the home team. Before 2011, no home team had ever won it. #CWC15Final]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@JimmyNeesh:</b> It seems strange to say this in the face of a loss but I've never been prouder to be a New Zealander and a New Zealand cricketer.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@mohanstatsman:</b> In World Cup winning sides, GEOFF MARSH Player 1987 Coach 1999]]></line><line><![CDATA[Darren Lehmann Player 1999 & 2003 Coach #CWC15 #AusvNZ]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@bhogleharsha:</b> The best team at the World Cup, the favourites, the most fancied win another World Cup. #Australia #champions]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@glennmcgrath11:</b> Congratulations to @MClarke23 & @CricketAus on winning the @cricketworldcup Great win boys, very well deserved #CWC15]]></line><line><![CDATA[The ecstatic Australian players celebrated long and hard after winning the World Cup. As the curtains fell on the mega event, we leave you with all the <b>records</b> that were broken and landmarks that were achieved during the course of the tournament: ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Martin Guptill was in supreme touch during the later part of the World Cup and ended up as the highest run-scorer of the tournament with <b>547 runs.</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Kumar Sangakkara, the fulcrum of Sri Lanka's batting line-up, became the first cricketer to notch up <b>four back-to-back tons in ODIs.</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mitchell Starc and Trent Boult were consistently amongst the wickets and ended up as the highest wicket-takers of the tournament with <b>22 wickets.</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Martin Guptill went on to post the <b>highest individual score</b> in World Cups with a rousing innings of <b>237</b> not out against the West Indies. Interestingly, Chris Gayle had earlier become the first cricketer to crack a double ton in World Cups, when he achieved that feat against Zimbabwe in Canberra. Guptill now also has the second highest individual score in ODIs to his name.]]></line><line><![CDATA[While compiling a splendid innings of 162 not out against the West Indies in Sydney, AB de Villiers became the fastest to reach 150 in ODIs. He reached that feat in a mere <b>64 balls.</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[New Zealand's captain, Brendon McCullum, played with a dash of adventurism against England in Wellington to register the fastest fifty in World Cups. He completed his fifty in just <b>18 balls.</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Australia's monstrous score of <b>417 for 6</b> against Afghanistan at the WACA was the highest total in World Cups.]]></line><line><![CDATA[With <b>37 sixes,</b> Chris Gayle and AB de Villiers now have thwacked most number of sixes in World Cups. Now, <b>26</b> of those Gayle's sixes came in this World Cup and that turned out to be a record for most number of sixes smashed in a single World Cup.]]></line><line><![CDATA[By clobbering Zimbabwe's bowlers for <b>16 sixes</b> in Canberra, Chris Gayle equalled Rohit Sharma's record for most number sixes in an ODI innings.]]></line><line><![CDATA[With as many as <b>31 sixes</b> being hammered, the quarter-final match between New Zealand and West Indies in Wellington saw the most sixes smashed in a World Cup match.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Maxwell runs behind the advertisement boards near the boundary and does high-fives with the crowd. The Australian players now sing the team song as they walk across the outfield.]]></line><line><![CDATA[ICC Chairman N Srinivasan hands over the World Cup trophy to Michael Clarke and the celebrations begin. They now pose for the cameras. Woo hoos are heard all over. Big smile on every single player of the Australian team and why not. David Warner pours champagne on Shane Watson and Steven Smith. The Australians do a lap of honour with the trophy in their hands. Clarke is seen clapping his hands to the fans. Clarke gets a bit emotional as well. Ah! Darren Lehmann remembered 1999 I guess. He takes the trophy and holds it high. Clarke now poses with the cup as photographers try to capture the moment.]]></line><line><![CDATA["I might give it back to Warnie (when asked if he would hand his No. 23 jersey to anybody). I haven't thought too much about it to be honest. It's been an honour and a privilege to represent my country in Tests, ODIs and T20Is. The time is right for me to walk away from one-day cricket, but I'll keep playing Test cricket. I don't know I have to think about the number 23 (jersey), but I am honoured to have received it from Shane Warne. I am very proud to wear it and tonight has been extra special.  As you can see it has got PH on it (when Mark Nicholas asked him about the black armband he was wearing). I will wear it every game I play for Australia. For everybody in Australian cricket it's been a really tough few months and I am sure I don't speak just for myself. I am sure everybody standing on the stage tonight will say that we played this World Cup with 16 players and tonight is certainly dedicated to Phil Hughes. Hughesy used to party as good as any of them, so we'll make sure that we drink two at a time tonight. One for Hughesy and one for us. We are really proud and it's a wonderful achievement. It's a great thing just to make the World Cup final, but to be able to win in your own backyard in front of your family and friends is extremely special. I can guarantee, we'll celebrate hard tonight."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Clarke</b>: "Obviously I am over the moon. What a tournament. Firstly, to Brendon (McCullum) and the New Zealand team, they deserve a lot of credit there. They are always a tough team to beat. It seems in any sporting event, Australia v New Zealand is always an exciting contest and tonight was no different. So to Baz and his team, congratulations on a wonderful tournament mate and well done. Especially personally, you were outstanding throughout the whole tournament. To the Australian fans, to all the fans of the game of cricket, I think it's been an amazing turnout for this tournament. People watching at home on TV and people coming to all the games, to the support that we had throughout the tournament, thanks to every Australian and every cricket supporter out there. Most importantly to our amazing team including support staff that stands over there, I couldn't have asked for anything more. The support I've received since coming back into the team, the way they have stood up and played, they deserve to certainly stand here tonight and hold that trophy up. We have played really well tonight. I said after the semi-final I think the guys were certainly ready for this final mentally. We had to recover physically and it's a great strength of our team. The support staff we have, the medical staff do a great job in getting everybody fit and healthy and the guys were ready for tonight and they played really well once again."]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's now time for the Australian team to collect their medallions. Big roar from the crowd as Mark Nicholas reads out Michael Clarke's name.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Starc</b>: "I don't know what words to use. It was an amazing tournament, some outstanding performances, but today to cap it off (was amazing). New Zealand have been a great team throughout the whole tournament. They really set the benchmark, but I think we came hard today and really led to this performance. I wouldn't say that (when asked if he was the best fast bowler in the world at the moment). I've worked really hard at it for a number of months now with Craig McDermott (the bowling coach) in the background. I think a few series ago we sat down and penned down a little plan. To see it come to fruition tonight or through the whole tournament, it's been phenomenal. There was a lot of luck involved I think (referring to the ball to dismiss Brendon McCullum). There was a little plan that Craig and I had going a couple of days ago, to see it get executed really but Brendon has been fantastic throughout the tournament, so I think there was luck involved and I am just happy to get that one. The support from the Australian public and the crowd here has been fantastic through the whole tournament for us. So thank you all. To play in front of this crowd, in front of these many people, is nothing like it. I would like to (when asked if he can go on and produce something like this in all formats), but I am just going to enjoy this one for now."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc</b> is the <b>Player of the Tournament</b>. He picked up <b>22 wickets at an average of 10.18 in 8 innings,</b> Tendulkar gives him the award.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Faulkner</b>: "It's an amazing feeling, to play in front of 93,000 fans here at the MCG and win a World Cup is amazing. I will try and chip in and play my role for the team but what a performance today. It's been an amazing couple of years as an Australian one-day outfit. We brought our A game today. I suppose I get tossed the ball when the skipper wants me to bowl. Normally it's in the powerplay and I love that job. Today it worked out for us, but it can be tough sometimes. Definitely, I would be lying if I said there wasn't a moment when I thought I wouldn't be here today. But the physios looked after me and amazing, I am here today and it's an amazing feeling. I am not sure, you have to ask the senior members of the team (smiles, when asked what will happen tonight)."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner</b> is the <b>Man of the Final</b> for his <b>3/36</b> and he receives the award from Sachin Tendulkar.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>McCullum</b>: "It's been one hell of a ride for us. Right throughout the way, we have played some outstanding cricket and we ran into an outstanding Australian team tonight, who continue to set the way in international cricket and full credit to them. They are deserved champions. Michael Clarke as well deserves to bow out as a World Cup champion too. All the best to them. They were outstanding in this World Cup and they thoroughly deserved to win. It was a quick one (referring to the ball Starc bowled to get rid of him). It all sort of unfolded probably not as we had planned, but I still thought we had got ourselves back in the game. 3/150, but as Australia do,  they came back at us again and to take 7/33 at the end, obviously put us under a lot of pressure. Still thought 180 we dared to dream. If we had a couple of things go our way, who knows what would have ended up. In the end, we were the second best team on the day. Again, credit to Australia. No regrets. This is the greatest stage that you can ask for as a cricketer. This is what you do your hard work for all the time, avail all the sacrifices that you make. We know we've had the opportunity as a group of guys to go on this ride and we have forged some memories and friendships which will last forever. Obviously we weren't able to lift the trophy, but the brand of cricket and the entertainment that we've been able to give people throughout our country but also throughout the world is something we are immensely proud of. We have no regrets and we walk away from this tournament with our heads held high. It is the greatest time of your life. To be able to represent your country on the international stage with a group of friends and then pit your skills against the world's best, it is the greatest time of our lives and that's how we have tried to play the game. Play with a free spirit and plenty of heart all the way along. It took us so far in this tournament, but obviously we weren't able to get past the final hurdle. As I said, I am immensely proud of all the guys within the team, all the management group and all those who have been a part of this team over the last few years and helped build us into what we are. We've still got some work to do, but I still think we can be very proud of our achievements in this tournament."]]></line><line><![CDATA[First up, the match officials receive their mementos. The New Zealand players now receive their medallions.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Presentation time!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Marsh:</b> "It probably hasn't quite sunk in yet, but what a feeling. Although, we had a few blokes running on with the drinks, I am sure all of us will celebrate like we have made hundred and took 5-fers."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Cummins:</b> "It's been great. We both (him and Marsh) got a couple of games, but just being part of the 15, we had a lot of fun in the past five-six weeks. Good to be part of a bit of history. Even though we weren't playing, we still got the nerves the night before. It still feels like we are really part of it. The crowd today was fantastic."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hazlewood:</b> "Starcy has been outstanding the whole tournament and to have Mitchell Johnson in the team and just see him leading the team, having that experience to talk to him and ask him stuff, is just outstanding."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Watson:</b> "It's what I have always dreamt of and it is to be involved in a World Cup final like this at the MCG, so impressed with the way we did it, it's just incredible. Absolutely, they have been the form side in world cricket for the last six months, especially in one-day cricket. Brendon McCullum has done an incredible job leading that team. They have got match-winners all the way through the whole team. We knew we had to be at our absolute best, lucky enough we were. What do you reckon? (when asked how long the celebrations will last, one night or one week)."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Maxwell</b>: "That was incredible. Was just hoping that we don't lose another wicket because I would have happened to walk out there and I was pretty nervous. That was as good as it gets. Home final, MCG, 93,000, it doesn't get better than that. It has been a lot of fun and it has been a lot of fun while we were having success as well. Riding on the back of our wins has been great and tonight to not do a thing during this final has been even better. Watched the boys go about their business. Oh! you are right I did get a run-out (on being told he took a wicket)."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bailey</b>: "Unreal. That was as special as it gets. A really big build-up and playing in front of a crowd like that, it must have been absolutely phenomenal. The build-up during the whole six weeks, then for the guys to put on such a wonderful performance tonight, that's one of the best feeling I ever had. You prefer to be playing no doubt about that, but to be part of the group has been so special and the whole journey has been amazing. I couldn't think of a better team to sit on the sidelines and watch, it has been the best seat in the house. It has been phenomenal. The players have been so outstanding, it's been an absolute privilege."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Starc</b>: "I had plenty of nerves. It was a little plan we had been working on, Craig McDermott and I for a couple of days, it's just nice to see it come off in front of a packed MCG. It was an amazing, amazing feeling during this World Cup and we just finished it off, it's just been amazing. All 15 guys, we were outstanding through the tri-series leading up to this World Cup. Right throughout, the staff have been fantastic, support of the Australian public, everyone in tonight has been an amazing feeling. It just really topped off the summer for everyone really."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Smith</b>: "Unbelievable feeling you know. We said that we wanted to play our best game towards the end of the tournament. To win this three down in the final, the boys were outstanding tonight. The bowlers really set it up for us. 180 on that wicket, they have done it all tournament. Thanks for all the fans for coming out tonight in front of 90,000 odd, what a better occasion, it was unbelievable. I would imagine so (on being thirsty tonight). It is not every day you win a World Cup. I know you (Shane Warne) have been part of one and it's a special feeling. I thought it was a very fitting farewell for Pup (Michael Clarke). He has been a terrific one-day player over a long period of time. I just wish he was out there with me at the end there. I was saying Pup, stay with me, stay with me and unfortunately he got out, but what a fitting farewell."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Finch:</b> "It's amazing. You always dream this as a kid and for it to finally happen, specially at home, at the MCG is an amazing feeling. When you get in a tournament, it is all about peaking at the right time. I think the way we played today, credit to everyone involved in that, to be able to restrict such a great side to around 180 and knock them off is unbelievable." ]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Lehmann</b>: "They just keep coming up, front up for you day in and day out. They have been fantastic over these six weeks. The support we have had around Australia has been unbelievable. We thank everyone for coming out at the MCG to see two quality sides. It was a great result for us tonight. That's why I love them (when Haddin and Bailey threw a bucket of drinks on the coach). It was a great crowd. Obviously, supported both sides and that spirit lives on today in this ground. It's been fantastic for everyone that have come along and have enjoyed some good cricket. More than that I would think and why not? (on being asked whether the celebrations will last more than a week)."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Haddin:</b> "It was special. We had not played a perfect game throughout the tournament and we delivered on the biggest stage. It's just a great feeling at the moment. We'll try and have a beer with every Aussie spectator in the building. So. it's going to be good fun tonight. It's been an amazing four weeks. We have enjoyed every minute. The support we have got all around Australia and even the little bit we got in New Zealand was good as well. The crowd support we got and how much all Australia appreciates this effort, it has been an enjoyable four weeks. I am thirsty as we speak. I want to try and have a beer with everyone in the place."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Warner:</b> "I have already lost my voice mate. It's a magical feeling. Credit to the guys, the bowlers did their job early on and gave us a good total to chase. We were pretty clinical there. You got to be positive and every game we have gone in, we have been a 100%, we have done all the right things. Today we came here and we expected a big crowd and thanks to everyone who came out and supported us throughout the tournament. Credit to you guys."]]></line><line><![CDATA[There are a lot of player interviews being conducted. We will have everything word by word. They will be up in a short while.]]></line><line><![CDATA[This victory certainly will be the crowning glory of those Australian cricketers, who lifted the glittering trophy. New Zealand too can be proud of their performance as they played with a positive mindset throughout the tournament to reach their first final. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Australia rode on the brilliance of Starc, Mitchell Johnson and Josh Hazlewood, with the new ball. If Starc swung it at pace, then Johnson and Hazlewood bowled back of a length and hit the bat hard. Faulkner with his box of tricks ran through the middle-order and took three scalps. Their fielding too was sharp. In short, Australia didn't put a foot wrong in the big game.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[It was Mitchell Starc, who gave them a perfect start by shattering Brendon McCullum's stumps to send the jam-packed crowd at the MCG into paroxysms of delight. Martin Guptill and Kane Williamson followed him back to the pavilion. Grant Elliott and Ross Taylor then stitched a century stand to resurrect their fortunes. It was James Faulkner, who put Australia in pole position by taking the wickets of Taylor and Corey Anderson in quick succession. Even though, Elliott continued to play a sterling knock, New Zealand's innings sloped towards a modest score.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[After being bundled out for a paltry score, Trent Boult gave New Zealand a glimmer of hope by snaffling Aaron Finch's wicket. However, once Smith and Clarke forged a superb partnership, the door was shut on their dream of winning the mega event for the first time. In fact, the credit also has to go to the bowlers, as they scythed through the New Zealand batting line-up.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Match summary:</b> Australia put their stamp on what was an authoritative show by chasing down the target with plenty of overs to spare. It was for the fifth time that they won the World Cup. Emotions were on full view, as on one side, the New Zealand players had a dejected look on their faces. At the other end of the spectrum, it turned out to be a red letter day for the opposition. It was an amazing performance from Australia and they deservedly got the chance to taste the glory of success. It also has to be remembered that this was Michael Clarke's last ODI and he signed off from the abridged version of the game in style by notching up a half-century. Steven Smith too scored a fine fifty.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Australian players rush onto the field to join Smith and Watson in their celebrations. The MCG goes berserk. The New Zealand players shake hands. McCullum hugs Vettori, who is retiring from international cricket. The Australians congratulate and hug each other. Coach Darren Lehmann is elated and is seen hugging every single player of the Australian team.]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>Australia win the World Cup for the fifth time</b>. 1987 - Eden Gardens, 1999 - Lord's, 2003 - Wanderers, 2007 - Kensington Oval, but winning at the MCG at home must be really special. India did it four years ago chasing at the Wankhede in a final and today, Australia have done it at the MCG. Michael Clarke's won a World Cup in his first attempt as captain and what a way to end your ODI career. Shortish slower delivery just outside off stump, Smith rocks back and pulls it behind square on the on-side, the ball runs away to the fence. Smith punches the air in delight, has his hands aloft as he runs, takes off his helmet and gloves, jumps and hugs Watson]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to S Smith, 1 run, very full from Southee, Smith drives it straight down the ground, mid-on dives to his left and half-stops the ball, Baz, who was at mid-off tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[The entire Australian team is on the sidelines, waiting to run onto the field and celebrate. Clarke is a bit emotional. Has a tear or two in his eye.]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to S Smith, no run, excellent inswinging yorker on the stumps, Smith keeps it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to S Smith, no run, not given a wide as Smith went across the stumps. Southee fired in a yorker and it almost shaved the leg stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[Just three needed now for Australia]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Watson, 1 run, low full toss from Southee, Watson looks to drive, gets a thickish inside edge that goes wide of mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Watson, no run, just a bit of shape back into the right-hander on this good length delivery, Watson defends and gets an inside edge onto pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Watson, no run, good length delivery on the off stump, Watson defends off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to S Smith, no run, defends this easily from the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to S Smith, 2 runs, full delivery outside off stump, Smith drives it past backward point and returns for the second. That's another <b>fifty</b> for Smith - fifth in a row]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to S Smith, 2 runs, full toss and Smith pushed it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Watson, 1 run, short ball from Henry, Watson pulls it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Watson, no run, good length delivery on the off stump, Watson defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Watson, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Ohhh he's dragged that on! He can't believe it. The MCG is on its feet to applaud Michael Clarke as he walks off the field for one last time in ODIs. Brendon McCullum runs up to Clarke and congratulates him. Tim Southee joins in as well. Clarke raises his bat to the crowd and gets a bit emotional as well. Now he points the bat up towards the sky, probably in remembrance of Phil Hughes. Off-cutting slower delivery just outside off stump, Clarke tries to run this down to third man, but gets an inside edge that crashes into the leg stump. The Australian skipper has played an exceptional innings in the final. <b>Clarke b Matt Henry 74(72) [4s-10 6s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Matt Henry to Clarke, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, <b>wide</b>, tries the slower ball, but sprays it down the leg-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Matt Henry [8.0-0-36-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to S Smith, no run, pitched up around off, Smith drives crisply but straight to the fielder at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Clarke, 1 run, it is not five boundaries in a row, banged in midway down the wicket, Clarke helps it on the way to fine leg with a pull]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, Clarke wants to get it done with it. He is improvising. Shortish and outside off, Clarke backs away and cuts it in the air to the right of backward point, no one protecting the boundary on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, hat-trick of boundaries for Clarke, short and outside off, Clarke goes back and cuts it fiercely past the diving backward point fielder, the power on that took it to the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, fabulous shot! Australia inch closer to the target. A long half volley outside off, Clarke reaches out and drives it through the diving cover fielder, looked like he didn't middle it, but the ball raced away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, Clarke wants to get his hands on the trophy in a hurry. Length delivery on off, Clarke clears his front leg and heaves it wide of long-on, it almost carried the distance. One bounce and into the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, no run, ends his spell with a yorker, Smith stays in the crease and jams it to the left of the bowler. His figures read: <b>10-1-40-1</b> and he ends the tournament as the joint highest wicket-taker along with Starc]]></line><line><![CDATA[Goes back over the wicket for his last delivery..]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Clarke, 1 run, takes the pace off the ball, Clarke stays in the crease and guides it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, Australia coasting along now. It was a nice juicy full toss from Boult, Clarke needed to hit in the gap, he did that with ease, driven to the left of cover, even a spirited chase from Baz can't stop the ball from reaching the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Clarke, no run, short of length around off, Clarke knocks it gently to short cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[Short cover and short cover-point in place..]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, 1 run, yorker around off, Smith digs it out to third man, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, no run, Boult continues round the wicket, fullish and on off, Smith pushes it to mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Clarke, 2 runs, another full toss from Southee, Clarke wanted to lift it over McCullum at mid-off, mistimes it completely, but has enough to clear the New Zealand skipper, two more added to the total]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to S Smith, 1 run, the attempted yorker goes wrong, ends up being a full toss on leg-stump, Smith flicks it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two short mid-wickets in place. Baz still attacking..]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to S Smith, no run, on a length just outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to S Smith, 2 runs, this might have been the slower one from Southee, Smith was winding up for a big mow towards cow corner, the inside edge just misses the off-stump and trickles down to fine leg. He has rode his luck today has Smith]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, short, wide and four. There was plenty of width on offer, Smith threw the kitchen sink at it, the ball takes the outside edge over the slip fielder, no chance for Boult at third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to S Smith, 2 runs, good length ball outside off, Smith square drives it through cover-point, he opened the bat face at the last instant to get the placement right]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tim Southee [5.0-0-35-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Clarke, no run, back of a length on leg-stump, Clarke fails to connect with the flick, wears it on the pads. No appeal for lbw, it pitched outside leg and was going down as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[Goes back over the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Clarke, no run, short of length on off, Clarke goes back and across, defends to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Clarke, no run, bouncer angled in towards the batsman, Clarke sits under it and allows it to sail over him]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Clarke, no run, and Clarke picks out one of them, he stands tall and punches the short of length delivery]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two short covers in place..]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, 1 run, back of a length on off, Smith moves across and wrists it towards mid-on, easily single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, no run, short of length on off, Smith goes up on his toes and blocks it towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Clarke, no run, stays on the back foot and punches it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Clarke, no run, flatter around off, Clarke dabs it to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to S Smith, 1 run, gives this bit more air outside off, Smith comes down the track and drives it uppishly to mid-off, the ball lands just in front of Southee, who dived forward and got his body behind the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Clarke, 1 run, Michael Clarke notches up his <b>58th ODI fifty</b>, in his last ODI innings. The whole of MCG is on their feet applauding the effort. He waves his bat around and acknowledges the applause. Slower and on the stumps, Clarke works it to backward square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Clarke, 2 runs, tossed up on off, Clarke shimmies down the wicket and whips it to deep mid-wicket, super shot against the turn]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to S Smith, 1 run, flighted on off, Smith comes down the track and eases it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, "that is glorious", says Ian Smith. He couldn't have put it better. Pitched up on off, Clarke drives through the line, it was in the air but straight down the ground. Almost took the umpire with him]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Clarke, no run, change of pace from Boult, bowled at <b>114.4kph</b>, Clarke presses forward and blocks it to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Clarke, no run, too full and outside off, Clarke toe-ends it to Ronchi, it was a bump ball. He looks at the bat soon after playing that]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Clarke, no run, shortens the length on off, Clarke gets behind the line and defends to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Clarke, no run, trifle short and around off, Clarke mistimes the cut to short cover, it was too close to him to play that shot. He is disappointed with himself as he hits bat onto the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Clarke, no run, Boult starts from round the wicket, keeps it back of a length, Clarke stays back and knocks it to short cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Trent Boult [7.0-0-29-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Clarke, 1 run, shortish and outside off, Clarke cuts square of the wicket and retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Clarke, <b>SIX</b>, fabulous shot! Clarke is now putting on an exhibition in his last ODI innings for the packed MCG crowd. Skips out of the crease, gets to the pitch of the ball and lofts it beautifully over long-off for a maximum. Great use of the feet from the Australian skipper]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Clarke, 2 runs, Clarke comes down the track and almost yorks himself, but somehow manages to squeeze the flick to deep mid-wicket, Elliott is not able to prevent the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Clarke, no run, goes on with the arm, Clarke stays back and punches it to cover, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to S Smith, 1 run, flatter and just outside off, Smith punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Clarke, 1 run, Vettori sees the batsman, drags the length back, Clarke adjusts and cuts it behind point, Boult keeps it to a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Daniel Vettori [3.0-0-9-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to S Smith, no run, slanted across the batsman, Smith has nothing to do with it]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to S Smith, no run, touch too full and outside off, Smith squeezes the drive to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to S Smith, 2 runs, easily done by Smith, just a shuffle across, gets inside the line to the back of a length delivery and nurdles it behind square leg, calls for two and gets it comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to S Smith, no run, on a length close to off, Smith defends to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Clarke, 3 runs, Clarke looking more and more confident now. It was not all that full, he comes forward and drives it on-the-up to the left of cover, Elliott and Baz combine to save a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[Anderson and McCullum have a chat]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to S Smith, 1 run, too straight from Anderson, Smith nudges it to backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to S Smith, <b>wide</b>, Anderson starts with a wide, bouncer down leg, called wide for height. That extra also brings the <b>50-run</b> partnership between these two]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Corey Anderson, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, top shot! That is Michael Clarke showing his authority. It was a length delivery on off, Clarke doesn't bother to get behind the line, stands and tonks it over mid-on, ball bounces once before reaching the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, there comes the full delivery, but tad overpitched, Clarke drives but can't beat Baz at mid-off, who dives to his left and stops]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, again, the length is short, Clarke hangs back and punches it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to S Smith, 1 run, banged in short, not much venom in that delivery, Smith has all the time to pull it in front of square]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, 3 runs, back of a length well wide of off, Clarke stands tall and punches it through the vacant cover region, Baz runs behind the ball, dives head first and hauls the ball in just before the rope. Saved a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[Still no third man for Clarke. Three slips and a gully in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to S Smith, 1 run, short from Henry, Smith takes from an off-stump line and pulls it to fine leg, all along the ground]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Clarke, no run, once more Clarke can't beat the man at mid-off, times the drive, sweetly finds the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Clarke, no run, quicker and on off, Clarke drives and picks out mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to S Smith, 1 run, punched to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Clarke, 1 run, Ronchi shouted "catch" but fell short of the fielder, Clarke advanced down the wicket and chips it to long-on, he almost hit it too well, the ball went on the bounce to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to S Smith, 1 run, fraction short and outside off, Smith cuts square of the wicket, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to S Smith, no run, tossed up outside off, Smith comes down the track and drives it towards cover, Baz dives to his left and saves a run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Clarke calls for a new pair of gloves.]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, back of a length around off, Clarke plays the short-arm pull, mistimes it towards mid-on, where Boult dives to his left and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to S Smith, 1 run, short of length on middle and leg, Smith nurdles it behind square leg to bring up the <b>100</b> for Australia]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to S Smith, no run, bumper angled in, Smith gets his head out of the way and lets it go. Umpire Dharmasena signals one for the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[Only one slip for Smith]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, 1 run, Henry pulls the length back just outside off, Clarke punches it past the man at point, who dived in vain]]></line><line><![CDATA[Three slips in place now]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, good length ball close to off, Clarke defends solidly and shouts "no" for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, starts the over with a yorker, right on the base of off-stump, Clarke brings his bat down and jams it in front of cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[It was the Australian skipper, Michael Clarke, playing in his last ODI, who replaced Warner at the crease. Clarke, definitely would look to sign off from ODI cricket in style by playing a fine hand. From New Zealand's perspective, Henry could have banged it short from around the wicket and tested Clarke's defence.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Trent Boult continued to swing the ball, but it was Matt Henry, who provided the crucial breakthrough by dismissing David Warner. Henry has that uncanny ability to surprise the batsman for a bit of pace. After Warner pulled Henry for a crunching boundary, he came back well by hitting the bat hard to take the prized scalp. Henry could have also taken the wicket of Steven Smith, but an inside edge rolled onto the stumps and the bails didn't come off. It isn't the first time that it has happened in this World Cup. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Clarke, 1 run, steps out of the crease and clips this fullish delivery on the pads to long-on, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Clarke, no run, slows this one just outside off, Clarke puts in a good stride forward and defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Clarke, no run, gives the charge this time and drives this tossed up delivery to the right of short cover, who dives and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Clarke, no run, quicker one from Vettori and on the stumps, Clarke defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to S Smith, 1 run, Smith advances down the track and clips this flighted delivery through square leg, the batsmen take a single as the fielder from backward square runs to his left and hunts the ball down]]></line><line><![CDATA[Just a slip in place for Vettori]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Clarke, 1 run, floated up on off and middle, Clarke leans forward and eases it down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Daniel Vettori [1.0-0-3-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, 1 run, overcompensates his length this time and bowls it on middle and leg, Clarke works it through mid-wicket and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, enough width on offer on this delivery and Clarke frees his arms, he slashes hard and it was uppish, but well wide of the gully fielder who was diving to his right, the ball runs away to the fence as there was no third man in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, banged in short and slightly wide outside off, Clarke waits for it inside the crease, goes for the upper cut and gets it very fine. Clarke was looking to go squarer there, but he wouldn't mind these runs one bit]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Clarke was looking to run it down to third man, but ends up chopping it behind square on the off-side, can't get the single either]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, just short of a good length and around off, Clarke punches it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to S Smith, 3 runs, on a good length and outside off, Smith leans forward, gets to the pitch of the ball and drives it through the covers, the batsmen take three even though McCullum from mid-off gave chase]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Clarke, 2 runs, short delivery from Southee and Clarke plays the short-arm pull this time, the ball goes behind square on the on-side and the batsmen take two before Boult from fine leg runs to his left, slides and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Clarke, no run, yorker from Southee this time, Clarke squeezes it out into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four!</b> There was no third man there for Southee, it was fuller and slightly wide outside off, Clarke is lured into the drive, who goes hard at it. The ball flies off the outside edge and goes over the slip cordon, goes on the bounce and crashes into the third man boundary. It would have been a regulation catch if there was a third man fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Clarke, no run, almost a yorker on off and middle, Clarke jams out the drive to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to S Smith, 1 run, banged in short this time and Smith goes across and pulls it behind square on the on-side, the batsmen change ends]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to S Smith, no run, fuller in length and just outside off, Smith drives it to mid-off off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Southee comes round the wicket now]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, touch fuller and on middle stump line, Clarke bunts it towards mid-on off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, back of a length delivery that was rising towards Clarke, who is up to the task as he jumps and drops his wrists on it, negotiates it comfortably in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, length delivery just outside off, Clarke opens the face of the bat and guides it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, angling in on middle, Clarke pushes at it off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, <b>wide</b>, bumper from Henry but it's too high for the umpire, who calls it a wide as Clarke leaves it alone outside off, Ronchi leapt high and could only collect it after outstretching his right hand]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, on a length this time and slightly wide outside off, Clarke is not lured into the drive and watches it go into the keeper's mitts]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to S Smith, 1 run, Smith shuffles across once again and works this just short of a good length delivery to deep square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now. Australia are moving along nicely. However, the runs have dried up to an extent after Warner's wicket. Smith is the key here and if the Kiwis can snare his wicket quickly after the drinks break, this match could well turn out to be a thriller. But for now, Australia are in front by a big margin.]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to S Smith, 1 run, length delivery outside off, Smith opens the face of the bat and was looking to run it down to third man, he gets a thickish outside edge and the batsmen cross over as the ball rolls away towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to S Smith, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Smith opens the face of the bat and pushes it towards the cover point region, where the point fielder runs to his right, slides and prevents the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to S Smith, no run, fuller and just outside off, Smith leans forward and drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Clarke, 1 run, on a good length and angles it in on middle, Clarke bunts it past the non-striker, the batsmen take a single before McCullum from mid-off runs across to his right and slides to collect the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Clarke, <b>wide</b>, another wide called but this time it's for height, it was the bumper from Southee and Clarke ducked under it comfortably, the square leg umpire though signalled a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Clarke, <b>wide</b>, Southee bowls this just outside the tramline as Clarke was backing away to play it through the off-side, he doesn't offer a shot in the end and the umpire calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Clarke, no run, fullish delivery outside off, Clarke comes on the front foot and drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to S Smith, 1 run, slightly back of a length and just outside off, Smith goes across and clips it through mid-wicket for another single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tim Southee [3.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, another back of a length delivery just outside off, Clarke hangs back and punches it towards shortish point, he didn't time it well at all]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, just short of a good length and just outside off, Clarke punches it to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, goes fuller this time and bowls this in the channel outside off, Clarke lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to S Smith, 1 run, angles this in on the pads, Smith hangs back and tucks it away to deep square leg to get off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to S Smith, no run, fullish delivery outside off, Smith leans forward and drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to S Smith, no run, ohh dear! <b>How lucky is Smith there?</b> He was shuffling across as he went for the forward push, gets an inside edge and the ball rolls back onto the stumps, but the lights didn't light up and the bails didn't even move an inch. Both the bowler and the batsman had their hands on their head. Henry can't believe his luck there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Clarke, no run, yorker from Boult and it was just outside off, Clarke jams it out into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, 1 run, back of a length delivery on off and middle, Smith goes back and across and tucks it away behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[Remember, Boult got Clarke caught at short cover in the group game at Auckland]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Clarke, 3 runs, fullish delivery on the stumps, Clarke was early into the flick, gets a leading edge that goes to the left of short cover, the ball rolls away towards the sweeper cover region and the batsmen take three]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Clarke, no run, fullish delivery angling away outside off, Clarke is happy to leave it for the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips, a gully, a short cover, a short mid-wicket and a shortish backward point in place for Clarke]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, 1 run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Smith shuffles across and works it past mid-wicket for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, no run, Boult angles this one across off, Smith was on the walk as he tried to tuck it away into the on-side, gets an inside edge onto the pad and the ball rolls back on the pitch]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, fullish delivery that shapes back in from outside off, Clarke leaves it alone, but the ball wasn't that far away from the off stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, angling in on off from a good length, Clarke defends and shouts 'No' for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, touch fuller this time and with a hint of shape back in, but Clarke reads it well and defends it with the full face of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[There are two slips, deepish short leg and a short point in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[Clarke, meanwhile, got a standing ovation from the crowd as he was coming in to bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Clarke, no run, back of a length delivery on off, Clarke hops in the crease and defends it solidly]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Michael Clarke, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Is this the wicket New Zealand needed to put the Aussies under some pressure? Only time will tell.]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Warner, <b>out</b> Caught by Elliott!! Finally, New Zealand get the crucial breakthrough and it's Warner who is gone. It was again short of length from Henry but this time Warner didn't have enough room to free his arms. He was also in two minds there whether to go through with the pull or not, he goes for it but ends up hitting it half-heartedly. McCullum had placed the fielder there after the previous ball and Elliott runs in from deep square leg and takes a good low catch. <b>Warner c Elliott b Matt Henry 45(46) [4s-7]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Matt Henry to Warner, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>smashed!</b> You just can't bowl to Warner there, it was short and just outside off, Warner had all the time in the world to rock back and he muscles the pull to the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, no run, short of length delivery angling away outside off, Smith opens the face of the bat and knocks it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, 1 run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Warner punches it to the right of short cover and sets off, makes it to the other end even though the fielder fires in the throw]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, no run, loud shout for lbw! Just short of a good length and on middle and leg, Warner misses the push and is hit on the back pad, but the angle was taking it down leg, New Zealand don't review either]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, no run, ohh! <b>Almost drags it back on!</b> It was on a good length and outside off, Warner went for the cut, but the length was not there. He ends up chopping it and the ball bounces over the off stump, it was very close to the stumps there]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, no run, back of a length delivery on top of off, Warner was looking to work it through the on-side, but closes the bat face a little too early, gets a soft leading edge that rolls away back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[Three slips in place for Boult]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, no run, on the stumps, Warner stays back and punches it hard to mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Warner, 1 run, on middle stump line this time, Warner shuffles across just a touch and clips it in front of mid-on, the batsmen take a quick single and Warner will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Warner, no run, touch fuller and on off, Warner drives it back to the bowler, who puts his left hand out to pluck it]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Warner, no run, angling away outside off, Warner hangs back and punches it to short cover, who fires in the throw at the non-striker's end, but Smith was well in]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to S Smith, 1 run, Henry goes full again in the channel outside off, Smith goes for the drive once again, but mistimes it off the inside half of the bat to mid-on, the batsmen sneak in a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to S Smith, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Smith looks to force it through the off-side, gets an inside edge that rolls away into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to S Smith, no run, fullish delivery just outside off, Smith leans forward and drives it to mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[It was David Warner, who then broke the shackles with cracking shots through the off-side. Once Warner played with a positive intent, Tim Southee, in particular, lost the plot and started bowling short. It also resulted in Brendon McCullum pushing the field back and Warner edged through the vacant second slip for a boundary. New Zealand can win this game only by bowling out Australia, so they need to look for wickets. McCullum also introduced Daniel Vettori into the attack, but he was struggling to pivot his left leg and the troublesome Achilles tendon seemed to be affecting him. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Trent Boult bowled it full and swung the new ball to trouble the openers up front. Boult was rewarded for his effort with the wicket of Aaron Finch. The Kookaburra doesn't swing for long and from New Zealand's perspective, they made good use of the new ball for the first few overs.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Warner gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, 2 runs, short and wide from Boult, Warner hops across, gets on top of the bounce and cuts it over point. The fielder at third man gets across and keeps them down to a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, no run, on a length and nipping back into Warner, he was caught on the shuffle as he looked to flick, gets struck in front of leg-stump, that would have been going down]]></line><line><![CDATA[Loud shout for LBW, but Kettleborough says NO and NZ don't review]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, that's creamed! Very full and just outside off, Warner took half-a-step forward, plays with a slightly open face and drills it through extra cover for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, 1 run, Boult keeps it full and well outside off, Smith plays with an open face and runs it down towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, no run, on a good length and coming back with the angle, Smith watches it all along and blocks it towards cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Warner, no run, tad fuller and on off, Warner watches it carefully and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Warner, no run, that one spat from a length, Warner was taken by surprise as he lunged at the ball, does well to play with soft hands and the ball rolls back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Warner, no run, Henry keeps it on a good length and just outside off, Warner leans forward and defends it towards short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Warner, no run, tad fuller and on off, driven towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Warner, no run, on a good length and well outside off, Warner nailed the drive but hits it straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, almost a wicket! Did Anderson misjudge it? This was short and on the stumps, Warner swivelled across on the pull, didn't bother to keep the ball down. Anderson ran in and then had to go sideways, the ball bounces wide of him and races away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Matt Henry, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, no run, tad fuller and coming back with the angle, Smith was on the move, plays with an open face and defends it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, 1 run, very full and on Warner's pads, worked to the left of mid-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Three slips in place for Warner]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, no run, tad fuller and on the stumps, Warner presses across and defends it towards short extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, blocked towards extra cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, 2 runs, Smith is in exquisite touch at the moment! Overpitched and well outside off, Smith gets a big stride forward and eases it past mid-off. McCullum gives chase, puts in the slide and saves a run for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Smith gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Boult changes to round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Warner, no run, pushed through and going away with the angle, driven towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Warner, no run, flatter and well down leg-side, Warner goes down on his knees and finds the man at backward square leg with the sweep]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Warner, no run, Vettori fires one on Warner's pads as he came down the track, he adjusts, bends low and sweeps it towards backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to S Smith, 3 runs, nicely played by Smith, Vettori dropped this one marginally short, Smith is quick to go back and slices it square past point. Two men give chase and keep the batsmen down to three runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to S Smith, no run, Vettori drops one slightly short, Smith goes back and works it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to S Smith, no run, Smith shimmies down the track to a well flighted delivery and drives it towards mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[A slip and a leg-slip for Dan]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Daniel Vettori, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, 1 run, on a good length and well outside off, Smith leans forward and pushes it wide of mid-off for a single. McCullum dived across and saves a run or two]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, Smith's too good on the short ball, this wasn't a bad delivery by any means, perhaps, fractionally short, Smith is quick to swivel back and pulls it to the left of square leg, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, no run, short of a good length and going away with the angle, Smith stays behind the line and pushes it towards short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, Smith gets behind the line and defends it back at the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, no run, fuller length delivery and holding its line outside off, Smith is drawn into the drive, the bat turned on impact and the ball rolls away towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, no run, yorker length delivery and just outside off, Smith watches it all along and jams it down towards mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to S Smith, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, worked towards the vacant mid-wicket region for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to S Smith, no run, tad fuller and shaping away from outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to S Smith, <b>wide</b>, Southee sprays this one miles outside off, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Warner, 1 run, on a good length and well outside off, blocked in front of mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, where are the slips? Just one slip and the ball grazes past Taylor at 1st slip, this was pitched up and nipped away from outside off, draws Warner into the drive, the edge is found, it flies to the left of first slip, Taylor dives in vain, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, that looked like a mistimed pull, but it almost went all the way! This was dug in short by Southee, Warner rocks back and flat-bats it, over the bowler's head, one bounce and over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, too short and too wide from Southee, Warner waits on it and cracks it square past mid-off, the ball whistles away to the fence in a jiffy]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, leg byes, 3 runs, wrong line from Boult, ends up offering a half-volley on Warner's pads, he looks to flick and misses, the ball runs away fine and past the keeper. Henry gets across from the deep, puts in the slide and saves a run for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, no run, just short of a yorker length delivery from Boult, Warner watches it all along and defends it back at the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, no run, full and on Warner's pads, he gets his bat in front of the pads and blocks it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, that's lovely placement from Warner, tad fuller and well outside off, Warner gets a good stride forward and caresses it sweetly through extra cover, the fielder gives chase but the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, no run, Boult shortens his length outside off, cramps Warner for room as he went for the short-arm jab, the ball rolls away towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, 2 runs, short of a length and on Warner's hips, he hops across and tucks it to the left of mid-on for another couple of runs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Warner, 1 run, tad fuller and just outside off, Warner presses across and nudges it in front of mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Warner, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Warner once again goes hard on the shot and mistimes it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Warner, 2 runs, on a good length and just outside off, Warner defends from the crease, presents the full face of the bat and pushes it past mid-off for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[Oh ho! Looks like Vettori is in trouble, he limped across from fine leg, didn't attack the ball, allowed the second run with ease and walks back not looking 100% alright]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Warner, 2 runs, too straight from Southee, ends up drifting onto Warner's pads, clipped away behind square on the on-side for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Warner, 2 runs, width on offer from Southee, Warner went hard on the chop, the ball bounces off the turf and goes past cover-point, the batsmen get back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Warner, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, Warner prods across and tucks it towards mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, no run, very full and just outside off, Smith leans into the drive and hits it firmly, straight to the fielder at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, no run, full and a hint of nip back into Smith, he shuffles across and defends it with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Steven Smith, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Finch, <b>out</b> Caught&Bowled!! New Zealand and Boult have struck early! He has been NZ's answer to Mitchell Starc. This was full and swings back in late, Finch was shuffling across on the flick, closed the face of the bat and gets an inside edge, the ball lobs off the pads and it's a simple return catch to the bowler. Boult accepts it gleefully and is immediately mobbed by his captain and the rest of the team. Excellent start for New Zealand. <b>Finch c and b Boult 0(5)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Boult to Finch, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught&Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Just two slips and a short mid-wicket for Finch]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, 1 run, full and on the stumps, Warner presses across and nudges it with soft hands, the ball rolls away in front of mid-on, Warner calls for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[A fourth slip is in place now]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, no run, another flash and a miss from Warner, width on offer from Boult, gets it to nip away further, Warner throws his bat at that and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Warner, no run, loose from Warner, Boult kept his length short and gets it to shape away from outside off, Warner threw his bat at that and is lucky not to have edged it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Three slips for Boult]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Trent Boult, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Finch, no run, excellent start from Southee, shortens his length a fraction and gets this one to nip away from outside off, Finch is drawn towards the ball, does well to withdraw his bat at the last moment]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Finch, no run, that's very well bowled by Southee, tad fuller and shaping away from outside off, Finch is lured forward into the tentative push, he ends up playing away from his body and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Finch, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Finch prods forward and blocks it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[Three slips in place for Finch]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Finch, no run, Southee shortens his length and gets this one to shape away from outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Warner, 1 run, fraction too straight and on Warner's pads, flicked away towards long leg for a single. Warner is off and running]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Warner, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Warner gets behind the line and punches it towards mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Warner and Finch are at the crease. Warner is on strike. Southee will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips and a gully in place as Southee steams in]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players are out in the middle.. Australia are on the cusp of their fifth World Cup title. Only an inspired burst from New Zealand's bowlers can stop them..]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. New Zealand dismissed Australia for 151 during their league phase match in Auckland. But that was a match with very little pressure, not so today. Can Boult & Co. repeat their pyrotechnics at the MCG? They need early wickets, else this will be all over in a hurry]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Faulkner:</b> "Obviously pretty good start by the boys. It's in our hands to chase the runs and if we start well there is no reason why we can't (chase this down). Pretty good MCG wicket really. I thought it was a little bit slow than we are used to, but pretty good all-round wicket. One aspect we have been working hard on is our fielding, another strong performance and hopefully like I said we can start well with the bat and chase this total down. The outfield is pretty standard, maybe a little bit quicker than normal, but the ground is in fantastic condition. It is in our hands now."]]></line><line><![CDATA[It has never been easy to chase down targets at the MCG under lights as it tends to zip through the wicket. However, New Zealand have to play out of their skins to lift the glittering trophy from here.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The battle-hardened cricketer, Elliott continued to play with a singular aim to succeed before he eventually got out for a tenacious innings of 83. For Australia, it wasn't just about the trio of Starc, Johnson and Hazlewood, who shone brightly. Faulkner too teased and tempted the batsmen to their downfall with his variations and picked up three crucial wickets.]]></line><line><![CDATA[It was left to Elliott and Taylor to stand up to the trial by fire. Both the batsmen farmed the strike in a clinical manner. Initially, they found runs hard to come by, but Elliott frustrated Australia with cheeky shots through the third man region. Elliott certainly played with unhurried swagger at the crease. Taylor struggled to find gaps with needlepoint precision, but he showed the resolve to forge a century stand with Elliott. It was in the 36th over when the game turned on its head. It was James Faulkner, who landed decisive blows by picking up the scalps of Taylor and Corey Anderson. With Luke Ronchi too losing his wicket, Australia just took a vice-like on the proceedings.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, with 91,112 fans at the stadium, it drummed up an electric atmosphere.  It was Mitchell Starc, who breathed fire by generating swing to knock over the dangerman, Brendon McCullum, in the first over of the innings. Josh Hazlewood and Mitchell Johnson backed it up by bristling with energy and untiring discipline. After playing with poise and balance against the pacers, Martin Guptill threw his wicket away by getting out to the part-timer, Glenn Maxwell. Kane Williamson, known for his ice-cool temperament, then lobbed it back to Johnson. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Australian bowlers put up a thoroughly professional show to bundle out the opposition for a below par total. In fact, after losing early wickets, Ross Taylor and Grant Elliott soothed the jangling nerves in the New Zealand camp with confident strides and the pair looked set to take them to a competitive total. However, they lost a slew of wickets in the slog overs and ended up with a modest score.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[What a performance by Australia. Thoroughly professional and come the big day - in a World Cup final, they are a different beast. A powerful beast that runs over all opposition. We have seen that in 1999. In 2003. In 2007 and again now in 2015. Just need to finish it off with the bat. Wouldn't be surprised if they chase this down in 35 overs, trying to make a statement. Wouldn't put it past Australia to do anything in a World Cup final. Truly great sides come to the party when the heat is on and the Aussies are the best in doing that. Coming back to the final dismissal, Clarke gave a big beaming smile and seemed quite happy as well as stunned with that athletic effort from Maxi.]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Boult, <b>out</b> Southee Run Out!! Fab from Maxi and he has just produced a spark from nowhere to extinguish this innings. It was pushed to him at a short mid-wicket position, he fielded and realised that Southee was out of his crease, rifled in a throw and hit direct. Southee was trying to get the bat in, then tried with his foot, both failed as Maxi was too quick. Maxi knew it as soon as he hit, the third umpire was needed as the fielder was very quick. No way the umpire would've known. <b>Southee run out (Maxwell) 11(11) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Johnson to Boult, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Has Big Show run Southee out? Southee didn't get the bat down. He was trying to. But <b>replays show that he is gone.</b> The big screen confirms the same. Loud cheer greets the fall of that wicket. The 'G' is a cacophony of noise at the moment.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now round the wicket for the final delivery]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Boult, <b>wide</b>, back over the wicket and pacy short delivery, down leg, Boult is ducking under that. Didn't know much about that delivery. Has a smile on his face]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Trent Boult, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Matt Henry, <b>out</b> Caught by Starc!! Low full toss outside off, Matt Henry has somehow sliced that to cover-point. A very soft dismissal that. Johnson pumps his fist. Matt Henry is cursing himself as he walks back. That should've been put away, with all in on the off-side. <b>Matt Henry c Starc b Johnson 0(7)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Johnson to Matt Henry, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now round the wicket. Four in on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Matt Henry, no run, Johnson looks frustrated. Length angled across, Matt Henry slogs and misses after clearing his front leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Southee, 1 run, slower delivery cutter, Southee is early into the slog, drags it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Southee, no run, goes back to his ploy of making room to go over cover, drilled straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Southee, no run, now Southee gets inside the line to go leg-side, it is bowled short and Southee swings and misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Matt Henry, no run, back of a length outside off, Matt Henry stands tall and thumps it straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Southee, 3 runs, hat-trick of slower deliveries, Southee finally gets bat on one and goes over cover. Clarke and Watson are the ones chasing and it is Clarke who pulls it back. Faulkner applauds that effort from his skipper]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Southee, no run, back of the hand slower delivery again, Southee making room doesn't connect. Not far away from leg stump that one]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Southee, no run, back of the hand slower delivery, Southee hops and goes back a little to cut to point. 'Wait on' is the call from Southee]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Southee, no run, Southee is making room to go over cover, Faulkner though keeps the batsman honest with a back of a length delivery on the stumps, defended to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Southee, no run, nips back in from round the wicket, cramps Southee for room, the batsman cuts and misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Matt Henry, no run, another fast short delivery, dug in and before Matt Henry could think about playing a shot, the ball fleew past his bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Matt Henry, no run, and Johnson produces that, but it's not quite a yorker, Matt Henry makes room and drives to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[Matt Henry and Southee have a chat with the former having a smile on his face. Expect the full fast yorker now]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Matt Henry, no run, too quick and too fast for Matt Henry, he tries to back away and pull, misses the short ball by a long way. That short delivery had some gas from Johnson]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Southee, 1 run, makes room and eyes long-on again. But drags this without any timing]]></line><line><![CDATA[New Zealand in danger of being bowled out here. First priority should be to bat the 50 overs and get whatever they can]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Southee, no run, shuffles across to off and defends as Johnson angles a length ball across the right-hander]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Southee, <b>SIX</b>, Southee welcomes Johnson with a six over long-on. Made room and cleared his front leg, before lofting it into the crowd. Connected it off the middle of the bat and is a bit surprised by his hit. Punches gloves with Matt Henry]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Matt Henry, no run, full and on off from round the wicket, driven well, but straight to the fielder at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Matt Henry, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, <b>out</b> Caught by Haddin!! Faulkner and Haddin give Elliott a send-off. Not needed I guess. Elliott looks at them and doesn't respond at all. Just keeps walking back. Before he goes off, raises the bat and goes in. It was a brilliantly disguised back of the hand slower delivery, Elliott early into the leg-side swipe and the thick outside edge looped to Haddin. He did all he could, but his lack of partners at the other end meant he had to go for it. <b>Elliott c Haddin b Faulkner 83(82) [4s-7 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Faulkner to Elliott, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, no run, looked like the slower delivery, Elliott is on the front foot and drives straight to the fielder at cover. No timing on that at all]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, no run, on a good length and on off, pushed with an open face to point, off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, no run, looks to clip to leg and gets an inside edge onto the pads, the ball dies down near his feet. Faulkner runs forward and prevents any runs being taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, <b>FOUR</b>, Elliott meanwhile continues to impress. Fraction short outside off, Elliott short-arm jabs a pull over mid-wicket, a couple of bounces and into the deep mid-wicket fence. Strong wrists from Elliott on display]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tim Southee, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Vettori, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Johnson yorks Vettori. Well almost as replays show that the attempted yorker was a foot short. Full and sliding down, but tail involved, Vettori as is his wont, looks to clip to leg, all the time, this time the ball brushes the pad and goes onto hit the stumps. Vettori nods in appreciation at that delivery from Johnson and walks off head bowed. Johnson roars in delight. <b>The last batting stint for Vettori in New Zealand colors.</b> <b>Vettori b Johnson 9(21) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Johnson to Vettori, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Elliott, 1 run, Smith is gesturing that he didn't see that from the shadows. Square driven to his left at backward point and he dives, gets a hand but cannot stop the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Elliott, no run, short of length outside off, looked like it stopped on Elliott a touch who punches and finds mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Elliott, no run, and he fields that to his right at slip after Elliott opens the face of the bat and guides it. Elliott has been playing that shot really well and getting runs, not that time. Clarke has a smile at the end of it all]]></line><line><![CDATA[Clarke has kept himself at slip for Elliott]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Vettori, 1 run, shuffles across and works the back of a length delivery in front of mid-on, quick single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Vettori, no run, Vettori has failed to connect with the late dab. He rarely fails to do so, but did there. The width was there but he couldn't lay bat on ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Johnson [6.0-0-19-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[New Zealand have scored <b>just 15 off the batting powerplay and lost three wickets</b>. Not a good one for them]]></line><line><![CDATA[It is a big game, but for New Zealand to put the opposition under any kind of pressure, they need a score of around 240-250. On their part, Australia stuck to the basics of not giving any room for the batsmen and that paid them rich dividends.]]></line><line><![CDATA[With Ross Taylor and Grant Elliott stitching a century stand, it seemed like they had laid the platform for New Zealand to notch up a competitive total. Elliott's ability to open the bat face and play cheeky shots through the third man region frustrated the opposition. However, just in the nick of time, James Faulkner struck twice in one over and Mitchell Starc dismissed Luke Ronchi to leave New Zealand in trouble.  <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Vettori, 1 run, Vettori gets forward and pushes it to mid-on, calls for the quick single and gets it]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Vettori, no run, full and on the stumps, once again Vettori flicks and finds mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Vettori, no run, Vettori finds short mid-wicket with a clip]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, 1 run, length and angling in, Elliott gets forward and eases a drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, <b>FOUR</b>, delicately played. Saw the width outside off, opens the face of the bat and runs it down, beats the diving short third to his right. Needed to hit the gap and did so]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, no run, nips back in and catches Elliott on the back thigh, wasn't forward and missed the defensive shot. Clarke relcuctantly went for a review, he was forced to by Haddin and Faulkner. It was umpire's call as it was just clipping]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Australia are going for a lbw review against Elliott. Not-out was the original call. 'Fair delivery, spin vision, front on and then RTS to follow. Just rock and roll that for me please. No bat involved. Ball-tracking if you have it ready. Ball-tracking coming now. Pitching outside. Impact in-line. It's umpire's call and you can stay with your decision. You are on camera now, you can make your decision, thank you.' <b>Elliott survives!</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Vettori, no run, Vettori shuffled across well outside off there, but Starc bowled a high full toss that caught the batsman unawares, pushed to mid-on in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Vettori, no run, bouncer, Vettori ducks under that. Not too high for a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Vettori, no run, in the air, but just in front of Starc on his followthrough, Vettori early into the push and gets lucky]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Vettori, no run, short of length outside off, rising, Vettori arches back to ramp and doesn't connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Vettori, 2 runs, full and angling in, clipped to deep backward square leg, Vettori is struggling a bit on the second, but makes it easily in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Vettori, no run, Vettori is backing away to leg, Starc goes for the attempted yorker, low full toss, patted to mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Here's <b>Jamie</b>, with an update as Australia slowly begin to take control over their neighbours:  'The crowd really behind Australia after those three wickets. A sea of yellow' - he says.]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Vettori, 1 run, dug in short, Vettori keeps the hook down to deep backward square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Vettori, no run, driven off the front foot wide of cover, Maxi fumbles and despite that they don't go for the single. Sensible as Maxi recovered quickly]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Vettori, <b>FOUR</b>, brilliant on-drive. Vettori showed the full face of the bat and punched it past Finch at mid-on. He couldn't get across and Vettori gets a pressure-releasing boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Vettori, no run, full and on the stumps, clipped straight to the fielder at mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Vettori, no run, Vettori plays all around a back of a length delivery outside off and completely plays down the wrong line, the ball misses the inside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[Vettori stops Faulkner midway as he isn't happy with movement behind the bowler's arm. Faulkner goes up and sorts things out near the sightscreen. A beach ball is the issue, distracting Vettori. <b>'It had to be yellow' chirps Ian Smith</b> on air, who is on fire today - after seeing the color of the beach ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sachin is seen at the 'G'. All suited and booted. Mark Waugh on air reckons he looks like a rockstar after initially pretending not to know him]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, leg byes, 1 run, nips back in and catches Elliott on the pad, it was going over and Vettori pushes Elliott through for the leg bye. No real appeal for lbw as the Aussies knew it was going over]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Vettori, no run, dug in short, Vettori ducks under that]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Vettori, no run, tailing back in, very late, Vettori digs it out to Starc]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Vettori, no run, pitched up outside off, driven to the left of mid-off, where the fielder slides and fields]]></line><line><![CDATA[Elliott walks up to Vettori and has a chat. They punch gloves at the end of the chat]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Vettori, no run, Vettori has come out and he too is nervy. Tries to dab that with a slip in place and nearly feathers an edge. Poor from the experienced Dan]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Daniel Vettori, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Ronchi, <b>out</b> Caught by Clarke!! Ronchi goes for a duck. Good catch at slip to his left by Clarke. He catches and then throws the ball up in the air in delight. Pitched up outside off, Ronchi went for a big drive and edged it, the ball was travelling and safely pouched by Clarke. New Zealand threatening to come apart here in the batting powerplay. <b>Ronchi c Clarke b Starc 0(4)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to Ronchi, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Elliott, 1 run, <b>had Smith hit Elliott was gone!</b> It was dabbed to the left of Smith at point, Ronchi was halfway down and that pushed Elliott to go for the run. He had no option, ran and gave up. Smith had all three stumps to aim and missed. Lucky escape for Elliott]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc [6.0-0-17-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Ronchi, no run, pitched up outside off, width was there, Ronchi completely mistimes the drive to short cover. <b>A double-wicket maiden</b> from Faulkner to start the powerplay]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now over the wicket for the last ball. A slip in now]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Ronchi, no run, length delivery on off, angling in, Ronchi defends awkwardly to mid-off, was in the air for a while, but falls well short of anyone]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Ronchi, no run, from round the wicket and the attempted yorker, Ronchi wrists it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Luke Ronchi, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Corey Anderson, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Look at that roar from Faulkner. He has knocked over Corey Anderson. Full fast and straight on middle, Corey Anderson like McCullum was slow in bringing the bat down. Was he expecting a short one? The weight was on the back foot, the feet didn't move, the bat came down slow and the ball found its way through. Australia come storming back after a hundred run stand. <b>Corey Anderson b Faulkner 0(2)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Faulkner to Corey Anderson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Corey Anderson, no run, full and on the stumps, wristed straight to the fielder at mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Corey Anderson, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Ross Taylor, <b>out</b> Caught by Haddin!! If he had left that, would've been close to a wide. But Ross Taylor reached out and jammed at the fuller length back of the hand slower delivery, it wasn't a bump ball, went straight off the edge and Haddin diving took it one-handed to his right. The ball got stuck in the webbing and he was sure initially, that he took it, but then seemed unsure. Strange. It was referred and the third umpire made the right decision. <b>Ross Taylor c Haddin b Faulkner 40(72) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Faulkner to Ross Taylor, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner [4.0-0-18-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Haddin and Faulkner are going up for a caught behind appeal. Dharma and Kettleborough are conferring. They go upstairs. 'We are checking for bump ball first and then clean catch' says Erasmus. 'It's not a bump ball, so we are checking for the catch. Just rock and roll that from me please, maybe one from square on the off-side, you can zoom that as well for me please. Excellent, can you rock and roll that. To the big screen, please put out. Thank you!' <b>Ross Taylor is gone</b>. That is a huge wicket off the first ball of the <b>batting powerplay</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Elliott, no run, Elliott charges Watson and drags the hoick, mid-wicket dives to his right and keeps it to a dot. Aggression from Elliott]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Elliott, <b>FOUR</b>, just out of the the reach of the diving Haddin. Elliott opens the face of the bat and delicately guides that, Haddin dived with one hand to his right, but didn't even get a finger on it. Watson has his hands on his head]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Ross Taylor, 1 run, good length outside off, wristed to mid-on, for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Ross Taylor, no run, Smith is brilliant at point. He goes acrobatically to his right to keep the shot down, recovers and then shies at Elliott's end. Elliott makes it back again. The shot was hit hard by Ross Taylor, but Smith is so good that he anticipated it well]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Ross Taylor, 2 runs, short outside off, Ross Taylor pulls and gets a top edge to fine leg, the fielder runs and then slides to keep it to a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Ross Taylor, no run, almost a huge mix-up. Ross Taylor though sent Elliott back in the nick of time. Pushed to Clarke at short mid-wicket and he was in quickly, under-arms the throw, but Elliott has plonked his bat in. That was a nervy moment for the Kiwis]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Ross Taylor, <b>wide</b>, full and down leg, wide called]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Ross Taylor, 1 run, nips back in and Ross Taylor is into the push, doesn't know where the ball is for a moment, until Elliott calls him through. The ball has just gone beside the pitch]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Ross Taylor, no run, short of length outside off, Ross Taylor defends it back to Hazlewood]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Elliott, 1 run, another ramp from Elliott, but he has played that almost straight to the fielder at third man, Johnson runs in but doesn't get there]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Ross Taylor, 1 run, fraction short outside off, Ross Taylor cuts to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Elliott, 1 run, width on offer, but Elliott has mistimed the front foot slash, but gets it wide of Smith at point, takes a quick single. The <b>100-run stand</b> is up]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Elliott, <b>FOUR</b>, well played! Short outside off, Elliott just ramps it over the vacant slip cordon. Beats third man with ease. Controlled shot that]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Josh Hazlewood [7.0-2-22-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Another <b>drinks</b> break. This final has followed an eerily similar script to the 92 one. These two are doing a Miandad and Imran. Just need a Wasim Akram with the bat and the ball. Who will be New Zealand's Wasim Akram with bat? Corey Anderson? With ball? Trent Boult? Let's see.]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Elliott, 1 run, short of length on the stumps, Elliott stays beside the line, gives himself some room and dabs that to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Ross Taylor, 1 run, too straight from Watson, Ross Taylor nudges it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Ross Taylor, no run, dug in short, Ross Taylor ducks under it, four dots in a row]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Ross Taylor, no run, short of length outside off, Ross Taylor can't get it away, dabbed straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Ross Taylor, no run, no room to dab that length ball wide of point, Ross Taylor is cramped for room, finds point]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Ross Taylor, no run, good length and a hint of nip back in, Ross Taylor works it to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Watson [2.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, 1 run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Ross Taylor bottom-hands a wristy stroke to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Elliott wrists it to long-on, keeps the strike rotating]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, 1 run, gets forward and pushes it to long-on, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, no run, shuffles across and works it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, 1 run, flatter and well outside off, Elliott opens the face of the bat and dabs that to the left of short third man, Mitch slides to keep it to one]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, 2 runs, Elliott comes down the track and deliberately goes over cover, who is inside the ring and gets a couple]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Elliott, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Elliott plays a drive in the air but where a cover-point would've been]]></line><line><![CDATA[So many strokes have gone through that gully, point and backward point region in the air. From this duo especially. Meanwhile, Johnson is coming round the wicket for the final delivery]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Ross Taylor, 1 run, full and wide of off, Ross Taylor reaches out and slices it in the air, but in the gap to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Ross Taylor, no run, another cutter from Johnson, it is outside off, Ross Taylor shoulders arms. Doesn't carry to Haddin]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Elliott, 1 run, on a good length and on off, Elliott opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Ross Taylor, 1 run, short of length on the hips, Ross Taylor hops and nudges it to the vacant square leg area]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Elliott, 1 run, dug in short on the stumps, Elliott rolls his wrists and pulls it through mid-wicket, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Mitchell Starc bowled a slew of yorkers, but Elliott seemed to have shortened his back-lift a touch to face up to Starc and dug out those yorkers quite well. Elliott then played a fine inside-out shot off James Faulkner in the 24th over for a boundary. Elliott is certainly good at essaying lofted shots through the off-side. More importantly for New Zealand, Taylor and Elliott farmed the strike well and eventually, Elliott reached a well-measured fifty. For Australia, their fielders have backed up the bowlers superbly.]]></line><line><![CDATA[After losing early wickets, Grant Elliott and Ross Taylor shored up New Zealand's innings. Elliott was given out lbw off Glenn Maxwell, but he went for the review and the decision was overturned as it was missing. Australian bowlers though, kept up the intensity by bowling with good control. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, no run, the line is well wide of off, Ross Taylor pushes it back to Maxwell]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, no run, wristed straight to the fielder at short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, 1 run, very full on off, driven to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, no run, Maxwell isn't a happy man. Lets a load of abuse at no-one in particular. Tossed up outside off, again it doesn't turn, beats Elliott on the drive, Haddin is quick, but Elliott is there in his crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, 2 runs, comes down the track and works it wide of Smith at mid-wicket, placed expertly and they come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, no run, tossed up outside off, Elliott gets forward and drives straight to the fielder at cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Elliott, 1 run, full and wide of off, Elliott plays another airy drive, but through the vacant gully region to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Ross Taylor, 1 run, good length outside off, Ross Taylor gets forward and pushes with an open face to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Ross Taylor, no run, fullish and nips back in a tad, Ross Taylor defends to the right of Johnson, mid-on is there]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Ross Taylor, no run, angled across Ross Taylor who shoulders arms, doesn't carry to Haddin. May have been the cutter]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Ross Taylor, no run, back of a length on the stumps, nudged back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Elliott, leg byes, 1 run, down leg, Elliott fails to work it away, off the thigh pad and they take a leg bye]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Johnson [4.0-0-12-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, 1 run, the Kiwis in the crowd are up on their feet, applauding that <b>fifty from Elliott.</b> Who would've thought that it would be Elliott who would play the match-winning innings in a semi and now in a final get a fifty. I didn't see that coming, honestly. Gets there with a mistimed loft, was early into the shot and luckily for him it landed in front of the fielder at long-off. Elliott has a wry smile after reaching the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Ross Taylor gets forward and drives to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, <b>wide</b>, fired down leg, was Maxwell looking for the leg-side stumping? Or did the ball slip out?]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, 1 run, 'down' shouted Haddin to short mid-wicket, but the fielder had no chance as the ball is pushed to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, 1 run, very full on the stumps, wristed with a strong bottom-hand to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, 1 run, opens the face of the bat and guides it to short third man, Ross Taylor calls Elliott through for the quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[How many times has Ross Taylor paddled Maxwell today?]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Ross Taylor takes it on the full and paddles to fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Glenn Maxwell [4.0-0-21-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Elliott, 2 runs, 'oh Australia you have been brilliant in the deep' says Ian Smith with that lovely voice of his. Can't agree more. This was four all the way as Elliott slashed and got a thick outside edge, Hazlewood ran to his left from third man and dived, stopped it with one hand and kept it to two. Watson has a puzzled look on his face but that is more in frustration at how the over has gone, rather than anything else]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Ross Taylor, 1 run, back of a length outside off, dabbed away to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Ross Taylor, <b>wide</b>, dug in very short and called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Ross Taylor, no run, shuffles across slightly and calmly defends the length ball back to Watson]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Ross Taylor, <b>FOUR</b>, that is a genuine outside edge and no slips means four for Ross Taylor. Ross Taylor was pushing out and got an edge that beat Haddin, third man had no chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Elliott, 1 run, good length outside off, Elliott opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man, 100 up for New Zealand]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Elliott, no run, good length on off, driven uppishly but in front of Watson on his followthrough]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Ross Taylor, no run, shortish outside off, Ross Taylor goes hard on the cut and mistimes it to Smith at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, 1 run, this time he waits for it and then angles the bat to run it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, no run, tennis ball bounce for Faulkner, gets it to rise and beats Elliott's attempted steer. That was a poor shot and so easily could've nicked that]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, <b>FOUR</b>, last over off Faulkner he went over the fielder, now wide of the fielder. Hit all along the ground as well as Faulkner overpitched. Drilled wide of cover and splits mid-off too. Clarke has a worried expression while a couple of Kiwis fist pump in the crowd]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, no run, good length outside off, Elliott opens the face of the bat and drives but finds backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Ross Taylor, 1 run, on a good length and outside off, driven off the front foot to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Elliott, 2 runs, shortish outside off, Elliott delays the cut and sends it over the leaping Smith. Smith was airborne at backward point but the shot had too much power and he didn't even get a finger on it. Two it is as third man comes around]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Elliott, no run, stump to stump line, Elliott defends to backward point, but can't get it in the gap for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Elliott, 2 runs, fraction short outside off, Elliott cuts and it goes to the right of backward point, Starc runs around and slides to keep it to a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Elliott, no run, on a good length and outside off, Elliott shuffles across slightly and works it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Elliott, no run, pitched further up on off, Elliott defends solidly to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Elliott, no run, on a good length on the stumps, Elliott defends to point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Watson, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[These two at the crease are doing a fine replica job of what Miandad/Imran Khan did in the 1992 World Cup final]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Ross Taylor, no run, Haddin again saves some runs as he goes quickly and stops it to his left. Faulkner was appealing for an lbw after Ross Taylor had got a thin inside edge onto the pads, the ball deflected away, but Haddin was there]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, 1 run, on a good length and outside off, Elliott opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[Elliott looks so calm as well. A good sign for New Zealand]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, <b>FOUR</b>, Elliott is a confident man. Picks the slower delivery and goes over mid-off. Lofted cleanly and beats the man inside the ring. The width was there and he used it beautifully]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, no run, back of a length on off, defended to short point]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Ross Taylor, 1 run, Ross Taylor is on the walk and pushes in front of mid-off, quick single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Ross Taylor, no run, length ball on middle and leg, Ross Taylor defends to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner [2.0-0-6-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Elliott, no run, on a good length and outside off, going with the angle, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Elliott, no run, was there any words spoken there? Looked like it as Elliott dug out the yorker, pinpoint yorker from Starc, on off, Elliott dug it out and wanted to help the Aussies by picking up the ball near his feet, Warner and the man from cover race forward and pick the ball themselves. A word or two said as Elliott has a look at Warner]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Elliott, <b>SIX</b>, second top edge that has gone for a six today. Down leg and Elliott swivelling on the shot got a biggie. Carried all the way into the crowd]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Elliott, no run, the attempted yorker on off, dug out to mid-off. The bat came down straight from Elliott that time]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Elliott, no run, Haddin does magnificently well. Clarke pats him on the back for that effort. A bottom-edge from Elliott and Haddin, who was wrong-footed went acrobatically to his left and snaffled the take on the bounce, one-handed. That is a photographer's delight to see Haddin airborne. <b>Anyone remember him catching Salman Butt down leg-side at Sydney in a Test?</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Elliott, no run, short of length on off, defended with an open face to point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, 1 run, worked to the right of short mid-wicket, for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Ross Taylor kneels down and paddles to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, no run, going straight on, Ross Taylor defends to the right of Maxwell]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, no run, shuffles across and finds short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, 1 run, uses his feet and drives to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, <b>FOUR</b>, shortish outside off, very short and Elliott rocks back to cut to deep backward point, beats the cover-point fielder and races away]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Ross Taylor, no run, Ross Taylor played that a bit uppishly, but it falls in front of mid-off. Got forward to drive and the batsman checked his shot which ensured it didn't carry]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Elliott, 3 runs, now drives wide of the diving mid-off, to the fielder's left. Played well right off the middle of the bat and it's three runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Elliott, no run, a big slash and a miss. Elliott went after it with no feet and missed the sharp back of a length delivery outside off which was rising]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Elliott, no run, full on off, defended to cover off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Ross Taylor, leg byes, 1 run, nips back in and Ross Taylor is forward to defend, misses, off the thigh pad and Elliott calls him through for a leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Ross Taylor, no run, short of length on the stumps, defended]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc [4.0-0-8-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[If we turn back the pages, in the 1996 World Cup Quarter-Final played in Chennai, New Zealand had found themselves in a similar position against Australia at 44 for 3, with Glenn McGrath, Damien Fleming and Paul Reiffel working well in tandem. However, Chris Harris' awe-inspiring innings of 130 lifted their sagging spirits. They certainly need someone to stand up to the challenge today too.  In short, Ross Taylor has to perform on the big stage from New Zealand's perspective. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[After looking assured against the pacers, Martin Guptill lost his concentration and Glenn Maxwell picked up his wicket. It just shows that a part-timer can always provide a crucial breakthrough or two. Mitchell Johnson, on the other hand, bowled cross-seam. He has been successful, especially in the shorter forms of the game by using the cross-seam delivery. To make it a perfect start for Australia, Kane Williamson then just lobbed it back to the bowler, Johnson. New Zealand's batsmen seem to have been hit by a bout of nerves.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, no run, Elliott knelt down to sweep and was struck in line, missed the sweep and the ball struck him pretty low down. Dharmasena thought about it for a while and lifted his finger. Elliott and Ross Taylor had a chat and the former went for it. Reviews show that it was missing. After the decision came, Elliott and Ross Taylor punched gloves. A big moment in the game]]></line><line><![CDATA[Elliott has reviewed that. He has been given out lbw by Dharmasena. Did Elliott get outside the line of off? 'Getting spin vision now Kumar. Can I get the RTS? Front on there looks like no bat Kumar. Just rock and roll that please. Keep rock and rolling it for me. No bat. Can I have the ball-tracking please? Kumar, it is missing. I will tell you to reverse this decision Kumar. I will tell you when you are on screen.' <b>Elliott survives!</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, 1 run, Ross Taylor kneels down and paddles that fine to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, no run, softly played to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, 1 run, short of length outside off, Elliott is late on the dab, gets a bit of bottom edge to short third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, no run, gets forward and clips to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, 2 runs, Elliott reverse laps Maxwell and played that <b>off the back of the bat.</b> Down to third man, Mitch keeps it to two]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Ross Taylor, no run, Ross Taylor times that off-drive well, but Starc goes quickly to his right at mid-off to keep it to a dot]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Ross Taylor, no run, gets forward and on-drives, but mid-on is there]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Ross Taylor, no run, on a good length and outside off, defended to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, 1 run, drives to mid-off and sets off. Makes it even as the throw misses. Would've been in with a direct hit as well. Well-run]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, 2 runs, pitched up outside off, Elliott square drives and gets it right in between the two men at point, runs two to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, no run, pitched up outside off, Elliott plays a hard drive, but finds Smith at short cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, 1 run, pushes it to cover-point and takes the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, no run, well bowled Maxwell, pulled the length back and it went straight on, Elliott was forward to push and was expecting the ball to turn, it didn't and beat the outside edge. Haddin had the bails off in a flash, but Elliott went nowhere]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, 1 run, very full and a bottom-handed drive to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, no run, stays back to punch to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, 2 runs, takes it on the full and paddles to fine leg, two it is]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Elliott, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Elliott gets forward and drives to sweeper cover, wants two, but Ross Taylor sends him back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Glenn Maxwell [1.0-0-5-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Ross Taylor, no run, low full toss on the stumps, driven back to Faulkner who tumbles and stops it. Good stop and saved a few runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Ross Taylor, no run, on a good length and outside off, pushed back to Faulkner]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, 1 run, good length on middle, Elliott clips to deep square leg, wants two, but the fielder is in quickly]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Ross Taylor, 1 run, back of a length on the stumps, Ross Taylor gets inside the line and nudges to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Ross Taylor, no run, back of a length outside off, Ross Taylor shuffles across and defends to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Elliott, 1 run, back of a length outside off, Elliott opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks time</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Ross Taylor, no run, nips back in and cramps Ross Taylor for room, who was looking to play it to leg. Adjusts and finds mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Ross Taylor, no run, good length outside off, Ross Taylor knocks it to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Elliott, 1 run, on a good length and outside off, Elliott runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Ross Taylor, 3 runs, shuffles across to off and clips an off stump delivery wide of the diving square leg, huge boundaries these and it's a comfortable three]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Ross Taylor, no run, Ross Taylor wasn't ready there, was half-forward in looking to defend and the ball runs off a thickish outside half to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Ross Taylor, no run, back of a length outside off, Ross Taylor hangs back and defends to mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Elliott, 2 runs, pitched up outside off, now Elliott gets the gap at cover. More work for Starc to do]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Elliott, no run, short and down leg, Elliott half-ducks and watches the ball fly past his left-shoulder]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Ross Taylor, 3 runs, pitched up outside off, Ross Taylor gets forward to drive and doesn't get it off the middle of the bat, wide of mid-off. Starc chases and keeps it to three]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Elliott, 1 run, full on off, defended into the space at cover, easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Elliott, no run, pitched up outside off, Elliott is late in bringing the bat down, but opens the face of the bat to defend it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips and a short leg in]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Elliott, no run, dug in short outside off, Elliott arches back and drops everything in his way and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Ross Taylor, no run, nearly another wicket. Ross Taylor on the walk and lucky not to have edged that behind. Full and wide of off, lured Taylor into the stroke and since he was on the move, got into an awkward position. Another <b>maiden over</b> from the relentless Hazlewood]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Ross Taylor, no run, back of a length outside off, Ross Taylor shuffles across and defends it back to Hazlewood]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Ross Taylor, no run]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Ross Taylor, no run, pitched up outside off, Ross Taylor gets forward to drive and the ball runs off the outer half to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Ross Taylor, no run, short of length outside off, punched to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Ross Taylor, no run, short of length outside off, defended to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Ross Taylor, no run, full and nips back in, Ross Taylor plays around his front pad a little, but manages to work it to mid-on who comes around, slides and fields]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Josh Hazlewood [5.0-1-18-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Elliott, no run, pitched up outside off, went with the angle, Elliott went towards the ball looking to defend with an open face. Nearly feathers an edge to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[Johnson has a short leg in place for Elliott]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Ross Taylor, 1 run, Warner misfields! That's a rare sight. Full and outside off, square driven to Warner, straight to him at point and he fumbles]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Ross Taylor, no run, short of length on the stumps, Ross Taylor hops and defends it back to Johnson]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Elliott, 1 run, short of length on middle, run down with an open face to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Grant Elliott, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Williamson, <b>out</b> Caught&Bowled!! Now Williamson chips one back to Johnson. Johnson points at someone in the dressing room and pumps his fist. The Aussies surround the bowler. Was it a cutter? Looked like it, on a length and on middle and off, Williamson was early into the flick and lobbed a dolly back to Mitch. He won't drop those and the nervy Williamson walks back. Australia well on top at the 'G'. <b>Williamson c and b Johnson 12(33) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Johnson to Williamson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught&Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Ross Taylor, 1 run, short of length on the hips, Ross Taylor gets inside the line to clip to fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[After having done all the hard work against Starc, Johnson and Hazlewood and surviving, Guptill has fallen to Maxi. Loss of concentration perhaps or was it a mental error?]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Williamson, no run, Clarke dives to his left at cover and stops a powerful drive from Williamson. Saved some runs there]]></line><line><![CDATA[Maxwell and Clarke have a chat about the field]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, 1 run, shuffles across and gently clips to square leg, played with the turn]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, no run, driven straight to the fielder at cover now]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Ross Taylor, <b>FOUR</b>, 'that is very friendly from the Australians to start Ross Taylor's innings off' says AB on air. Full toss outside off, a gift for Ross Taylor and he doesn't miss out. Drives hard and wide of cover. Gets off the mark with a four]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ross Taylor, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Guptill, <b>out</b> Bowled!! How has Guptill missed that? Haddin gives him a send-off. Clapping right in front of the batsman. It spun back in from a short of length and cramped Guptill for room, on the punch, Guptill made room to play the stroke and the ball somehow escaped to hit the outside half of off. Guptill stood there disbelieving, before Haddin's celebrations woke him up. Maxwell strikes 2nd ball. <b>Guptill b Maxwell 15(34) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Maxwell to Guptill, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Guptill, no run, short and wide outside off, Guptill nearly holes out to cover-point, cut in the air, but in front of Faulkner]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Glenn Maxwell, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Guptill, 1 run, down leg, nudged to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Williamson, 1 run, very full outside off, Williamson drives to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Williamson, no run, another peach. Similar to the last delivery, a bit wide of off this one, Williamson is beaten on the defence. Once again Johnson stares. So easily could've had a wicket with either one of those on a another day]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Williamson, no run, that is a beauty. Rolled his fingers across the ball and the ball spits off the surface, Williamson covered the line and did all the could to defend that, but it just moved away a fraction to beat the outside edge. Johnson has a stare at Kane. Clarke has his hands on his head]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Williamson, no run, pushed softly to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Williamson, no run, dug in short down leg, Williamson got inside the line to pull and then realised he was better off not playing, pulls out of the stroke]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[So far this match has gone the 1992 World Cup final route. Sedate start as the bowlers are on top. Played at the same ground too. Let's see if the rest of the innings follows a similar pattern]]></line><line><![CDATA[Historically, McCullum has had his problems against left-arm pacers, who have swung it with the new ball due to his lack of footwork. For instance, Zaheer Khan has dismissed him six times in ODIs. Interestingly, he has been dismissed three times lbw and once bowled by Zaheer. However, the credit has to go to Starc for bowling it full and generating enough swing to castle the dangerous McCullum. It was Martin Guptill, who soothed the nerves in the New Zealand camp with a fine cover-drive. Guptill, who has worked hard on his footwork with his mentor Martin Crowe, seems to have improved his game. New Zealand certainly need Guptill and Kane Williamson to steer them to safety.]]></line><line><![CDATA[As the summit clash between Trans-Tasman rivals, Australia and New Zealand got underway, the  fans were buzzing with excitement in anticipation of a riveting contest. Mitchell Starc started on a great note by swinging it in the air to knock over Brendon McCullum for a duck in the first over. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Guptill, no run, back of a length and rising from that length, Guptill plays back and hops to keep it down. Did well there]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Guptill, no run, pitched up outside off, driven hard and straight back at Hazlewood, who half-stops the ball, mid-off is there though]]></line><line><![CDATA[Just a lone slip now. Second slip is now at short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, 1 run, good length outside off, Williamson opens the face of the bat and plays it wide of the diving backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, 2 runs, short on the stumps, Williamson gets inside the line and pulls to deep backward square leg, Starc runs around and keeps it to two]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely off-drive from Williamson. Just relied on timing and timed it on-the-up, past mid-off. Even Hazlewood is impressed, just has a look and walks back]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, no run, pitched up on the stumps, Williamson gets forward and plays a nice straight drive back at Hazlewood, who deflects the ball into Guptill]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Guptill, no run, short of length on off, punched to mid-off, played well, but straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Guptill, no run, back of a length on the stumps, Guptill is rock-solid in his defence, played to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Guptill, <b>wide</b>, down leg and that nearly went to Haddin on the bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Guptill, no run, short of length outside off, punched straight to the fielder at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Guptill, no run, on a good length and on middle and leg, defended solidly to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Guptill, no run, short of length outside off, defended to point with an open face]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Guptill, no run, Johnson comes on and hits Guptill on the glove. Dug in short and had Guptill on the hop, the ball hit glove and fell safely. Nasty first delivery from Johnson]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Johnson, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, no run, a fine <b>maiden over</b> from Hazlewood, gets this to nip back in and catches Williamson on the thigh pad. The batsman failing to work it away. Practices the shot after missing]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, no run, pitched up on off, Williamson gets forward and pushes it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, no run, that is a rip-snorter from Hazlewood, Williamson was in the air as he swayed back, looking to leave, the bat was hung up like a periscope but managed to leave that in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, no run, now Faulkner at mid-on, dives to his right and saves some runs. It was clipped nicely by Williamson, but Faulkner was there]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, no run, that one kept a bit low, on off stump, Williamson defends to cover. Adjusted well to the low bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, no run, Williamson doesn't look confident. Another tentative poke at a short of length delivery outside off, played outside the line and missed by a long way. Was late in covering the line too]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Guptill, no run, very high bouncer and Haddin had to leap acrobatically to gather that. Did well as he gloved the ball. Was a bit too high but the umpires were happy with the height on that one]]></line><line><![CDATA[Guptill has gone past Sanga to move into the top of the run-getter's list in this World Cup. Starc now has 21 wickets and is joint level with Boult for the most wickets.]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Guptill, no run, short of length outside off, Guptill lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Guptill, no run, Mitch at mid-on does well, dives to his right and stops the flick from Guptill, saved a couple at least]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Guptill, no run, third delivery that Starc has pushed it across Guptill, is that a set-up? Could well be. Guptill lifts his bat and lets it go as the ball was well outside off]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Guptill, no run, another of those tempters from Starc, but this time Guptill gets forward and shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Guptill, no run, that's the variation. Starc beats Guptill with a full delivery outside off, he didn't try to swing it back in, pushed it with the angle. Guptill fell for it and was lucky that he didn't edge it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Guptill, <b>wide</b>, dug in very short, Guptill sits under it and called wide]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, 2 runs, full on the pads, even though Williamson has played slightly around the front pad, he flicks it wide of Maxi at square leg, for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Guptill, 1 run, back of a length on the stumps, Guptill looks to punch and gets a thick outside edge to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Guptill, no run, short of length on the stumps, Guptill defends to the right of Maxi at square leg and the first call was 'wait']]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, 1 run, short of length outside off, Williamson looks to defend and gets a thick outside edge to third man, went to ground quickly]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, no run, nips back in and raps Williamson on the pads. He was trying to flick and missed. The ball would've gone over as it hit Williamson high on the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, no run, well outside off, left alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Williamson, 1 run, Williamson is off the mark, in a streaky fashion. Gets forward to drive and the square drive produces a thick outside edge, but it doesn't carry straight to the fielder at point. Wide of that fielder, Starc has a wry smile]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Williamson, no run, that's much better. Sees the short delivery outside off and gets down quickly and then sways out of the line]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Williamson, no run, now Starc beats with one that is close to off, Williamson pushes out with feet stuck and is beaten. Tried to pull the bat inside the line, but the ball had already gone past the edge by then]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Williamson, no run, Williamson isn't off the mark and plays a nervy shot outside off. It was on a back of a length and outside off, rising, Williamson looked to punch with a horizontal bat and the ball flew over the edge. Was a half-hearted attempt to play which meant he was always going to miss]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Williamson, no run, on middle and leg, pushed in front of mid-on. Played with soft hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Williamson, no run, back of a length outside off, pushed wide of cover, mid-off is there too]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Guptill, no run, short of length on the stumps, Guptill is early into the flick, closes the face of the bat too early and the leading edge rolls to cover. Was in the air for a while, but died down very quickly]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Guptill, no run, on a good length and outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Guptill, <b>SIX</b>, Haddin running back signals six. It was dug in short and Guptill top-edges the pull, it was a big top edge too and it carried all the way. These aren't short boundaries at the 'G' and to have carried for six shows how thick the edges of the bat are]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Guptill, no run, nips back in a tad and Guptill is forward to defend, gets it off the inside half to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Guptill, no run, almost a collision at point between Warner and Smith. Both went for the ball in trying to field and eventually they manage to get out of each other's way. Warner manages a smile. It was short and wide outside off, Guptill mistimed the cut]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Guptill, no run, in the channel outside off, lifting too, Guptill shoulders arms. Haddin collects]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jamie</b> chirps in from the ground: The match has been sold out, but it's not a full-house as of now. Big queues outside the gates and there are some vacant spaces in the stands - as of now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Guptill, 1 run, on the hips, nudged to fine leg, to retain strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Guptill, no run, well played again. Dug in short at <b>149.4kph.</b> Guptill sways back and then gets out of the line of that delivery. Johnson liked that and claps]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Guptill, <b>FOUR</b>, Guptill will get a lot of confidence from that shot. Very full and outside off, with the angle, Guptill bends his knee a little and laces a drive to sweeper cover, two fielders give chase, but the ball wins the race]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Guptill, no run, back of a length on the stumps, solidly defended that time to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Guptill, no run, short of length on the hips, Guptill rises tall and keeps it down near his legs]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Guptill, no run, Australia ponder a review. Clarke and Haddin have a chat, decide against it. They thought it was pad first, but replays show that it was an inside edge onto the pads. The bat first as Guptill played around his front pad, in trying to flick. Shape for Starc as he brought this back in. No short leg too. Starc shook his head as he knew it was bat first]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, no run, Hazlewood is getting swing early on, but Williamson is content to leave that outswinger early on. Saw it early and left it without any trouble]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, no run, pitched up outside off, Williamson is solidly forward and defends to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, leg byes, <b>FOUR</b>, second time that Hazlewood has drifted down leg this over. Williamson doesn't get bat, but gets thigh pad and it runs away to the fine leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, no run, dug in short outside off, Williamson wants to spar at it and then pulls his bat inside the line, just in time. Did well not to thrust the gloves out at that]]></line><line><![CDATA[Replays show that Baz played slightly outside the line as he tried to drive. The ball was too quick and it had a nice shape back in as well. Brilliant bowling from Starc. On the big day, he has come to the party]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Williamson, no run, lovely outswinger, just inside the guideline, Williamson shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hazlewood to Guptill, 1 run, down leg, Guptill nurdles a single to fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Josh Hazlewood, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Williamson, no run, swinging down leg, Williamson fails to flick. A token appeal for lbw, but that was comfortably going down]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kane Williamson, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Brendon McCullum, <b>out</b> Bowled!! <b>Gone! Got 'im!</b> Starc has the early wicket and that too of Brendon McCullum. Superb bowling this from the left-armer. The 'G' stand up and applaud the Aussie. Starc runs with his finger pointed upwards. Inswinging fuller length delivery, nearly a yorker, but just a few inches short of that length, Brendon McCullum stood rooted to the crease and was beaten for pace. The ball cannonned into the base of off after the batsman couldn't bring his bat down in time. What a start that is for Australia. Disaster for New Zealand. <b>Brendon McCullum b Starc 0(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to Brendon McCullum, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Brendon McCullum, no run, hello, hello! Brendon McCullum charges Starc and misses. The bowler followed McCullum as he came out of the track, but the ball went in between drive and the legs, missed leg. Good take by Haddin too. McCullum nervy early on]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Brendon McCullum, no run, ohhh! That was so close to the off stump. Look at the cheek of Brendon McCullum, he has a wry smile at Starc who has his hands on his head. It nipped in from a fuller length and went through the drive of McCullum, the batsman was forward to play an ambitious drive and the ball nearly shaved off. A coat of paint!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Right, it is Brendon McCullum vs Starc. What a battle this is! Two slips and two men right at point, close to each other. What will Baz do first up?]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Guptill, 1 run, short of length outside off, Guptill softly dabs that wide of the diving backward point fielder, single and off the mark with that run]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Guptill, no run, nice shape and carry through to Haddin, Guptill gets forward and sees the good length delivery outside off, it holds its line and he shoulders arms]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Guptill and Brendon McCullum are at the crease. Guptill is on strike. Starc will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Aussies are out there first. McCullum and Guptill do a bit of stretching before they walk out together. The countdown begins and we are all ready to go. Game on! The biggest game of the year! Starc has the new ball. Two slips in place. Let's go then...]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players are making their way out for the anthems. Oops! Just as the teams were getting ready for the anthems, an intruder ran onto the field. The security guards get rid of him quickly. New Zealand's anthem is followed by Australia's "<b>Advance Australia Fair</b>."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pitch report by Shane Warne:</b> Average score here is 290. Whoever wins the toss will definitely bat first. At night the grass stands up and the quick bowlers get it to zip through. Few little cracks but it is absolutely rock-hard. Someone like a Dan Vettori may get a bit of spin.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Australia</b> (Playing XI): Aaron Finch, David Warner, Steven Smith, Michael Clarke(c), Shane Watson, Glenn Maxwell, Brad Haddin(w), James Faulkner, Mitchell Johnson, Mitchell Starc, Josh Hazlewood]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>New Zealand</b> (Playing XI): Brendon McCullum(c), Martin Guptill, Kane Williamson, Ross Taylor, Grant Elliott, Corey Anderson, Luke Ronchi(w), Daniel Vettori, Tim Southee, Matt Henry, Trent Boult]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>New Zealand have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>McCullum</b>: "It (the build-up) has been great, tremendous semi-final and it's been a great World Cup for us so far. We've earned the right now to play against the Australians in their own backyard in the final. It's going to be a great game and sure both teams will play outstanding cricket. It's a shame that one team will have to win and one team will have to lose I guess. We are going to have <b>bat</b> first. The wicket looks outstanding, I think give ourselves great opportunity to put the runs on the board. We've got the same team. The guys were outstanding against a very good South African team. So we've given the opportunity in the final as well. We are really happy with the way the guys are. We know we will play well today, but it doesn't guarantee us success. But we know that we will be tough to beat. We have worked on this for a long time. We know that the game has its ups and downs, so we need to remain pretty stable emotionally. The guys are excited about today and certainly not fearful. We will go out there and display our skills the best we can and hopefully they will be good enough come the end of  the day. We've been very fortunate to have a lot of support from back home. Reading some of the articles, we had support from all around the world for us as well. It's going to be a great final. We are very privileged to be here and we just can't wait to get out and get amongst it."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Clarke</b>: "It's a special game. I think for both Brendon (McCullum) and I and for both the teams it is special to have made the finals. I know the Australian boys are extremely excited. It's an honour to be here and have this opportunity to try and win it. I would have batted first as well. The wicket looks fantastic so I don't think it (toss) matters too much. Same XI for us. Continue to play consistent cricket. We haven't done too much over the last couple of days. It was about recovery, making sure everybody was as fresh as possible for today. I said after the semi-final that the boys were mentally ready to go. Physically we've been able to get ourselves right and we are looking forward to today. It (support) is great. The Australian public have been so supportive. Even in the semi-final there was a lot of Indians there but the Aussies turned up and I know there are plenty at home watching on TV as well. Hopefully we can play some really good entertaining cricket for them today."]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's <b>toss time</b> folks!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Our man, <b>Jamie</b> at the ground has this update: "There are many fans lining up, buying souvenirs, merchandise, getting faces painted, eating snacks and such. And a lot of fans in Black Caps jerseys with New Zealand flags."]]></line><line><![CDATA[The whole of New Zealand would be hoping that McCullum and Co. do it for Marty! Do it for Marty, Baz!]]></line><line><![CDATA["He seems to have really found peace with himself and the game as well, and he's been instrumental in helping some of our guys on the team peel back their games and really focus on being able to develop individually but also buy into the team collectively. So he's been a really big asset, and there are many others as well who have assisted guys individually which has helped the team collectively. So it was really sad what he's going through, and we just hope that he's able to find some peace in the time that he's got left."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Asked by a reporter if he had read Crowe's letter, McCullum on Friday replied in the affirmative before speaking from the heart. "I read the article. I think he's a fantastic writer," he said. "I think what he's going through at the moment is incredibly difficult. We had him involved in the group, and not long ago as well, he came and spent time with the team and it was great."]]></line><line><![CDATA[In his letter, the New Zealand great paid a touching tribute to two particular members of the Black Caps squad, terming <b>Ross Taylor and Martin Guptill as "the two sons I never had".</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A pretty poignant moment on TV as Martin Crowe is seen chatting to Brendon McCullum. Just then, Martin Guptill walks in and shakes Crowe's hand. Crowe gives him a hug and suddenly becomes emotional. Crowe earlier had written a heartfelt letter to the Black Caps. Ian Smith hopes that it isn't Crowe's last game that he watches live. We all hope the same. For the uninitiated Crowe is battling with lymphoma and his health is deteriorating.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Michael Clarke:</b> "You know, tomorrow will be exactly the same as it's been every single time I've walked out onto the field to play cricket for Australia. Extremely special."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Quotes: <b>McCullum</b>: "It's been a great ride so far. I guess this is the ultimate game for us to be able to play in everyone's theory."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather update:</b> No rain is predicted for today. It is a warm and sunny day and it will stay that way. So a perfect day and a perfect forecast for the World Cup final.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pre-match team news, <b>Australia</b>: They are likely to go in unchanged. <b>New Zealand:</b> Same as Australia. They too are most likely to not make any changes to their winning XI]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-head record:</b> Australia lead that stat in World Cups, winning 6 and losing 3. But they lost the last game, in this World Cup at Eden Park. New Zealand haven't played at the MCG since 2012, but they won the last encounter they played against Australia in 2009. Australia, meanwhile haven't lost at the MCG since 2012, winning all their last six games.]]></line><line><![CDATA["It's an exciting side. Lehmann has been working on this side for two years and put together a really good squad. When you look at the depth in this side, both with our bowling and batting, and with the allrounders, it is a strong unit. Full credit to Lehmann for that, for fostering that sort of environment and spotting talent," said the 56-year-old.]]></line><line><![CDATA[In an exclusive interview former Aussie opener, <b>Geoff Marsh</b> believes the influence of coach Darren Lehmann has been huge in the Australian cricket team's resurgence. "From the time that Lehmann took over, the team has become a real family again," he said. "He's gone out of the way to make sure of that. He's picked the right players and they are playing for the right reason. Lehmann has brought it all together. Along with Michael, and now Smith, they've made sure that there is a terrific atmosphere in the team and that everybody has been able to relax. I think that Boof (Lehmann) has also been very big on family, making sure that players are not away for a long period of time without support. He's just been able to make players relax and enjoy their cricket, and that is massive for a coach."]]></line><line><![CDATA["I've got a wonderful group of talented and gifted players, but more importantly, I've got a team of 15 guys that have an amazing attitude and want to have success. That's what drives you every day to get out of bed and try and become better. I hope we can train well today and then go and get that reward we're after tomorrow."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Michael Clarke</b> had already said his team would have to play its best cricket to beat New Zealand, the form team of the competition. "Once we walk out onto that field, we know it's going to be an extremely tough battle and we're going to be up for that, but off the field, both teams get on really well," he said. "I think there's always that great rivalry between Australia and New Zealand. There's a great mutual respect between both teams."]]></line><line><![CDATA["Even though deep within I know that Australia start as favourites, they are a good team backed by a 90,000-strong MCG ground backing their team. Brendon McCullum has urged New Zealand fans to chime in and they are doing their bit to salvage whatever tickets that remain, but my question remains, can New Zealand win it? I can tell you this much: I will be happy if Australia win, but I will be happier if New Zealand win it."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sourav Ganguly</b> writing exclusively on our site doesn't agree with the fact that since New Zealand are playing for the first time in Australia in the tournament, they will find it difficult. He writes: "Everyone here is saying Australia will win, and the reason they say is because New Zealand haven't played in Australia so far, which I don't agree with. They say the ball swung in New Zealand and it won't in Australia - I don't believe that either. The quality of Tim Southee and Trent Boult is much more than just conditions, and I think if they bowl in the right areas, they will get some swing and movement against Australia at the MCG. Don't forget though, that if the ball comes back into Aaron Finch and Steven Smith, who has been in outstanding form, they have been in trouble and Boult will look to do exactly that."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Southee said New Zealand were not too worried about having to play at the large MCG. "We've got guys who have played a lot of cricket around the world, on big grounds, on small grounds, we've got enough experience on big grounds. A lot of the grounds in New Zealand are small but Hagley Oval is reasonably big. A lot of the guys have played in front of big crowds in India. It's going to be a great occasion, the guys are excited and we'll embrace the occasion," he said.]]></line><line><![CDATA["I think that's been a strength of ours, the level-headedness that comes in the team. We don't get ahead of ourselves and we stay in the moment and just worry about the job at hand. The occasion is bigger but I'm sure the lead-up, the way we train, the way we go about it, it doesn't change from any other game," Southee said.]]></line><line><![CDATA[New Zealand bowling spearhead <b>Tim Southee</b> reckons that the Black Caps will not be overawed by the occasion when they play Australia in the final. "We (Black Caps) would have no issues with any potential hangover from Tuesday's epic semifinal win against South Africa in Auckland. The guys enjoyed and celebrated the success and we've had to park that and move onto Sunday, and we have," he told the media.]]></line><line><![CDATA[One thing is for sure, McCullum is a very clever man and also the Indian fan would surely be pleased to have received an offer from the Kiwi captain and will be certainly rooting for them after the Aussies knocked the Indians out in the semi-final. The Indians certainly don't warm up to the Aussies as much as they would do for the Kiwis. McCullum can definitely expect a lot of support from the Indians who would come to the 'G' on Sunday.]]></line><line><![CDATA["I think, it's probably no secret that most of the other teams around the world would probably want New Zealand to win against Australia. So hopefully, we'll get a good smattering of support tomorrow, and I'm sure the Indian guys will certainly be rooting for us."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>McCullum also reached out to a billion Indian fans</b> for support ahead of the final against Australia at the Melbourne Cricket Ground. In a heart-warming letter addressed to 'every cricket fan in India', McCullum said he'd already seen a wave of support from the Indian fans already and requested their support through every ball in the final.]]></line><line><![CDATA["No, we're not intimidated, I don't think," he said. "We're excited. I guess right through the week there's been a healthy sort of chat about those things externally. But from our point of view we're just going about our work in the same way. We know if we play well we'll be tough to beat, and, yeah, that's pretty much our preparation. I reckon we might have the home crowd tomorrow actually. I think it's probably no secret that most of the other teams around the world would probably fair New Zealand to win in Australia. So hopefully we'll get a good smattering of support tomorrow, and I'm sure the Indian guys will certainly be rooting for us."]]></line><line><![CDATA[The MCG will test them, maybe even taunt them, never mind that McCullum, a day before the final, exuded confidence and hoped that there would be a sizeable dosage of support for his Black Caps.]]></line><line><![CDATA[However, Vettori said his potential retirement should not be a distraction for New Zealand in their quest of winning their first World Cup. "It's not what I'm thinking about. It's just about having some fun and enjoying the game and enjoying the buildup to a World Cup final. No-one else in New Zealand cricket history has been able to experience that before so it's pretty exciting to experience a grand final week. The chance to play a World Cup final regardless of where you are in your career is something everyone dreams about," he stated.]]></line><line><![CDATA["He's been an outstanding contributor for us. He's played for New Zealand for half his life. (A win) would be a great way to potentially send him off. I guess it was potentially his last game on home soil and for him to be out there at the end and be as instrumental and as calm as he was under pressure, it was superb. He was struggling a bit with his back, too. He's played a lot of his career with bumps and bruises and niggles and strains. He's a tough customer and he's been an amazing servant," McCullum stated.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Vettori has said that Sunday's final will be his last for New Zealand. The curtains will draw for one last time. McCullum said the team would be working hard to ensure Vettori ends his career with a win.]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's not only Australia who have a player playing his last ODI, New Zealand have too. The bespectacled genius. The left-arm spinner. With boyish looks. <b>Of Italian descent</b>. Harry Potter-esque he resembles they say. Debuted at 18. Battled injuries. Retired. Came back. Trained like hell to be fit for this. To play this World Cup. Was even coach of an Indian T20 League side. Couldn't run on the field. Didn't play for a while. Trained. Trained and trained. For one final appearance in a home World Cup. The name is <b>Daniel Luca Vettori</b>. And he is playing his final game on Sunday.]]></line><line><![CDATA[So Australia have one more reason to be motivated come the day of the final. They would be wanting to do it for Pup. To give him the perfect send-off. With a World Cup win.]]></line><line><![CDATA["I'm extremely thankful and grateful - I've just found out that tomorrow will be my 245th one-day game - it's been an honour and a privilege to represent my country for that amount of games. I'm grateful to every player I have been lucky enough to play with and this team is no exception to that. I think it is the right time for me and the Australian team. I was very fortunate four years ago to get the opportunity to captain this one-day team. That was really good preparation for me leading up to this World Cup, I think the next Australian captain deserves the same opportunity. I don't think it is realistic that I'll be fit and healthy and available to play the next World Cup so I believe it is the right time."]]></line><line><![CDATA["Tomorrow will be my last ODI game for Australia. I've just spoken to my team-mates, spoken to James Sutherland and Rod Marsh and Darren Lehmann and informed them that <b>tomorrow will be my last ODI game for Australia."</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Clarke said that he made the decision after leaving the SCG on Thursday, where Australia beat India in the second semi-final by 95 runs, and told his wife Kyly upon reaching home. He hoped that retiring from ODI cricket would prolong his Test career.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Lots of buildup ahead of the game. Let's focus on that now. 244 games. Debut in 2003. 7907 runs. Average 44.42. Eight hundreds. 57 fifties. One World Cup title. Still in with a chance to make it two. Countless injuries. Taken painkillers to get ready for this tournament. So many fitness issues. He battled them all for this. Just to be ready for the World Cup. The whole country fretted on his fitness. It was front-page news everywhere. Michael Clarke's stats before the big game. But he is giving up the ODI game for good. Why you may ask?]]></line><line><![CDATA[Elliott was the unlikely hero as the devastated South Africans went home. Tears flowed and grown men cried. It was sport at its finest and certainly brought Eden Park to life. The 1992 heartbreak was forgotten and forgiven and the ghosts of that day laid to rest.]]></line><line><![CDATA[McCullum came out a man possessed and proceeded to tear Dale Steyn apart. Steyn went for 25 in one over and New Zealand were flying. Morkel got McCullum out and that brought sanity to the proceedings. There were more twists and turns in the game until Grant Elliott - a South African by birth - nailed the final blow, hitting a six off the penultimate ball to spark unseen scenes at Eden Park.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Semi-final:</b> In the game of the tournament, New Zealand won a cliffhanger against South Africa to move into the final. South Africa were placed for the final assault after 38 overs with AB in a devastating mood. But once again rain came in to spoil their party and the game was reduced to a 43-overs per side match. South Africa made 281 and the D/L adjusted target was 298 for New Zealand.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Quarter-final:</b> Martin Guptill made the highest ever score by a batsman in a World Cup knockout game as his unbeaten 237 powered New Zealand to 393. West Indies went hell for leather and lost by 143 runs. Guptill who was dropped on 4 made the West Indies pay heavily for their mistake as the Wellington crowd were treated to his wide range of strokeplay. With the ball, Boult snared the first four wickets and set his side on their way.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>New Zealand:</b> New Zealand were the only side apart from India to have a clean slate in the group stages. Played 6. Won 6. Beat Sri Lanka comfortably. Edged past Scotland. Annihilated England. Won a thriller against Australia in the game of the tournament. Eased past Afghanistan and then held their nerve to beat Bangladesh.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Semi-final:</b> Australia faced India and won a crucial toss to bat first. Warner went early but Smith and Finch rebuilt the innings. The former brought up a hundred and continued his tormenting of India. India fought back well after Smith was dismissed but a late cameo from Johnson took Australia to 329. With the runs on the board, the Aussies withstood an initial onslaught from Dhawan before taking wickets at regular intervals. Eventually they reached their seventh World Cup final with a comfortable 95-run win.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Quarter-final:</b> Pakistan were expected to be tricky opposition in the quarters but except for the tremendous spell from Wahab Riaz which had them on the ropes for a while, Australia were always in command. Once they survived Riaz's spell, Australia cantered home to victory to set up a semi-final date with India at the Sydney Cricket Ground.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Road to the final, Australia</b>: Australia began with a bang thumping England. Then there was a washout against Bangladesh before losing a thriller against New Zealand. The no-result and the loss to New Zealand meant they couldn't finish top of the group. Australia smashed Afghanistan then won a high-scoring game against Sri Lanka before having it easy against Scotland.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The MCG has also played host to the 1956 Summer Olympics, the 2006 Commonwealth Games and a few of the FIFA World Cup qualifier games as well. For more about this magnificent venue, why not head over here and read this brilliant venue description: http://www.cricbuzz.com/cricket-series/2223/icc-cricket-world-cup-2015/venues/87/melbourne-cricket-ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[The venue for today's final is the iconic MCG. It would only be apt and fitting that the final is being played at this great venue. It can fit 100,000 and is one of the great cricketing venues in the world. The MCG is referred to as the 'Spiritual Home of Australian Sport'.]]></line><line><![CDATA[As a result of this incident, the International Cricket Council (then International Cricket Conference), amended the Laws of Cricket and deemed underarm deliveries illegal. Even though this entire fiasco took place 34 years back, it galvanised a Trans-Tasman cricket rivalry, which will be at its apex today.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Doing commentary for Channel 9 at that time, <b>Richie Benaud</b>, the legendary Australian captain, described it as disgraceful and one of the worst things that he has seen on the cricket field. To add to that, Ian Chappell, former Australian captain himself and the older brother of Greg and Trevor, was not too pleased with his brother's action either. He was heard saying, <b>"No, Greg, no, you can't do that"</b> in the commentary box.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Greg Chappell's step created a lot of furore and was condemned all over. Bowling underarm was legal at that point of time, but was considered against the spirit of the game. The incident drew widespread criticism from all quarters, including the then Australian Prime Minister Malcolm Fraser and New Zealand's Prime Minister Robert Muldoon, who described the incident as "the most disgusting incident I can recall in the history of cricket".]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Trans-Tasman rivalry took on a whole new meaning after the 1981 Benson and Hedges World Series Cup, third final at the MCG. New Zealand needed 6 off the final ball to tie the game. Trevor Chappell was the bowler. What happened next became one of the biggest controversies in cricket's history. Greg Chappell, the Australian captain and Trevor's older brother, instructs his bowler/brother, to roll the final delivery under-arm.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The term Trans-Tasman is used for the inter-relations between both Australia and New Zealand, since the two countries are geographically separated by the Tasman Sea.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Since Australia and New Zealand are playing, it will only be apt to focus on the Trans-Tasman rivalry a bit. It may not be competing with the likes of India-Pakistan or Australia-England, but the Trans-Tasman rivalry has a history and a past attached to it as well. So, why is it known as the Trans-Tasman rivalry?]]></line><line><![CDATA[Drumroll please! A great day to everyone tuning in here. We welcome you all for one final time in this World Cup. One final effort. One final coverage. One prize and the grandest of them all is up for grabs. So sit back and enjoy the fun ride. We are just getting started and there is still a long way to go. Make yourself comfortable as we dig in deep to bring you Australia vs New Zealand - battling for the World Cup at the 'G'.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Six semi-final heartbreaks before this edition. A country of just 4.5 million. The widely held view and it's a joke - there are more sheep than people in the country. Heck, New Zealand's population is well less than that of Bangalore - a city in India. Still they punch above their weight in every cricketing contest. There was heartbreak in 1992 in front of their own crowd at Eden Park. The time has come to rewrite history. Now is the time. It will be the "greatest time of their lives" if McCullum and Co. can pull it off.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The big brother vs small brother. The little brother from across the ditch. Australia vs New Zealand. One has won four World Cups. The other none. One an all-time great World Cup outfit. The other trying to carve their own name on the trophy. Australia the favorites always against their kid brothers. So many perceptions. So many subplots. So many stories. So many sidelights. You can add your own stuff here....]]></line><line><![CDATA[West Indies and Clive Lloyd. West Indies and Clive Lloyd. India and Kapil Dev. Australia and Allan Border. Pakistan and Imran Khan. Sri Lanka and Arjuna Ranatunga. Australia and Steve Waugh. Australia and Ricky Ponting. Australia and Ricky Ponting. India and MS Dhoni. Will it be Australia and Michael Clarke or New Zealand and Brendon McCullum who will be added to that list on Sunday?]]></line><line><![CDATA[This is the <b>"greatest time of our lives" as Brendon McCullum</b> put it. The greatest time of their lives for the 22 players who will step out onto the 'G' on Sunday. The greatest time for the rest of their contingent as well. The greatest occasion. The greatest prize on offer. The chance to become great for ever. Greatness beckons. Greatness to be taken in and packed home for posterity. Greatness is available and for sale when 22 players walk out to play the final.]]></line><line><![CDATA[A chance for 22 players from both countries to give it their very best and emerge victorious. Only 11 will be happy. The other 11 will be distraught. 11 will rejoice. 11 will be heart-broken. 11 will hope that tomorrow never comes. 11 will want tomorrow to come like no other day. 11 will be in dreamland. 11 will be in despair. 11 will be heroes for life. 11 will be left villains at least for a day.]]></line><line><![CDATA[It doesn't get bigger or better or grander or greater than this. This is the greatest moment for some. And for some more as well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>This is it! This is the World Cup final!</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Australia's power vs New Zealand's intelligence. Home advantage vs Red-hot streak. 5-match winning streak vs 10-match unbeaten run. Clash of styles. Clash of different strategies. The audacity of Maxwell vs the guile of Vettori. The daredevilry of McCullum vs the calmness of Smith. The serenity of Kane vs the class of Clarke. Left-armer vs Left-armer. The swing of Southee vs the talent of Hazlewood. Australia's fielding vs New Zealand's fielding. No quarter asked for. None given. The winner takes it all. The last man standing. It's on. Game on!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Brendon McCullum vs Michael Clarke.</b> Both inspirational leaders. Both pro-active skippers. Both lead from the front. Both set an example to others. Both put their team above themselves. Both are two of the finest captains in the World at the moment. Both extrovert characters. Both looking to crown themselves in glory.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Centuries - check. Double-centuries - check. Four-fors - check. Five-fors - check. Hat-tricks - check. Dropped catches - check. Sitters - check. Astounding catches - check. Stunning grabs - check. Passion - check. Nerves - check. Great clashes - check. One-sided thrashings - check. Greatness - check. Mediocrity - check. Nerveless endings - check. Retirements - check. Legends taking a bow - check. We've seen it all. There is just one more final hurrah left. One last game. The final frontier. The last chance saloon. I say, lets bring it on!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>12:00 Local Time, 01:00 GMT, 06:30 IST:</b> This is it! 14 teams. 44 days. 210 players. Coaching staff. Physical trainers. Data analysts. Computer analysts. Nutrition consultants. Mentors. Motivational speakers. So forth and so on. Everything comes to a stop here. This is what one plays for. This is the ultimate. This is the grandest prize. This is what everyone yearns for. This is the dream. This is the crowning glory. A sportsperson's greatest moment.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview by G Rajaraman</b><br/><br/>Just another game? Australia and New Zealand may get to the park on Sunday with preparation to suggest that they would be approaching their newest battle as just another game. But they need no reminding that this time, unlike in any of their 126 ODI earlier meetings, there is a little reward that awaits the winners  the ICC Cricket World Cup, no less.<br/><br/>On Saturday, the co-hosts prepared for the big day like they would for any other game, not wanting the occasion or the venue to leave them awe-struck. New Zealand paid attention to detail with bowling coach Shane Bond spending time surveying the expansive outfield from a bowler's perspective. Australia turned up in full force on a day of optional practice.<br/><br/>The absence of needle, with the teams not being at loggerheads, and the presence of enormous respect for one another's combative skills should not be misconstrued as a lack of intent on either side. They are both capable of launching spectacular assaults, with their captains unwilling to take their feet off the pedal.<br/><br/>The teams are equally hungry. They are blessed with explosive batsmen and others who can ensure that the power hitters come in at the appropriate times; they have quality fast bowlers and are terrific fielding sides; New Zealand have cricket's shrewdest left-arm spinner, Daniel Vettori to support pace bowlers while Australia rely on Glenn Maxwell to fill up as fifth bowler.<br/><br/>Given that, it will be tempting to sit on the wall and say that the team which plays the better cricket on Sunday will emerge the winner of the World Cup. But while one should not write off McCullum's New Zealand  especially because of his sharp captaincy  they will find it tough to slip past the home team.<br/><br/>Of course, New Zealand are the only unbeaten squad in the World Cup so far, playing an attacking brand of cricket. What's more, they are the only side that has inflicted a defeat on the world's top ODI team in the World Cup, a thrilling one-wicket victory in a Group A league game in Auckland. But that match was all about great bowling, swing, seam and fast.<br/><br/>The MCG deck is the sort which demands great discipline from the batsmen and greater discipline from the bowlers. Australia, who have constantly summoned World Cup winning legends like Steve Waugh and Adam Gilchrist to chat with the team, can be expected to use their knowledge of MCG to keep their nose ahead of the Black Caps.<br/><br/>New Zealand have not an ODI played in Australia in five years but they will remember that the last time a Black Caps team beat the home side, the game had been played at MCG. As many as seven players in the current squad were part of that team that made light of the fact they were playing on a larger ground than any in their own nation.<br/><br/>Yet, if Australia have been installed as favourites and New Zealand been labelled the underdogs, it is only because the Black Caps have played all their eight World Cup games so far at home. It is the first time they have flown into Australia. How well they adapt to that challenge will determine if they can continue punching like they have done so far.<br/><br/>For all that, if the teams dish out a high quality contest in keeping with the stature of the World Cup final, fans around the globe will add more memories to add to the rich collection from limited-over cricket's biggest event. Australia and New Zealand have the potential to ensure that fans do not remember the game as just another ODI game.<br/><br/><b>Umpires:</b> Kumar Dharmasena (Sri Lanka) and Richard Kettleborough (England). TV umpire: Marais Erasmus (South Africa). Match referee: Ranjan Madugalle (Sri Lanka).]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Australia</b> (From): Aaron Finch, David Warner, Steven Smith, Michael Clarke(c), Shane Watson, Glenn Maxwell, Brad Haddin(w), James Faulkner, Mitchell Johnson, Mitchell Starc, Josh Hazlewood, Pat Cummins, George Bailey, Xavier Doherty, Mitchell Marsh]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>New Zealand</b> (From): Brendon McCullum(c), Martin Guptill, Kane Williamson, Ross Taylor, Grant Elliott, Corey Anderson, Luke Ronchi(w), Daniel Vettori, Tim Southee, Matt Henry, Trent Boult, Tom Latham, Mitchell McClenaghan, Nathan McCullum, Kyle Mills]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>183</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>10</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>45</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="New Zealand">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1457</playerid>
					<name>Martin Guptill</name>
					<batsman-name>M Guptill</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Guptill</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>15</runs>
					<balls>34</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Maxwell</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7662</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Brendon McCullum</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>M Starc</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7710</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6326</playerid>
					<name>Kane Williamson</name>
					<batsman-name>Williamson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Williamson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>12</runs>
					<balls>33</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Johnson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>496</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Johnson</fielder>
						<fielderId>496</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>521</playerid>
					<name>Ross Taylor</name>
					<batsman-name>Ross Taylor</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ross Taylor</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>40</runs>
					<balls>72</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Faulkner</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7789</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Brad Haddin</fielder>
						<fielderId>159</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1064</playerid>
					<name>Grant Elliott</name>
					<batsman-name>Elliott</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Elliott</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>83</runs>
					<balls>82</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Faulkner</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7789</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Brad Haddin</fielder>
						<fielderId>159</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8982</playerid>
					<name>Corey Anderson</name>
					<batsman-name>CJ Anderson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Corey Anderson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Faulkner</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7789</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1396</playerid>
					<name>Luke Ronchi</name>
					<batsman-name>Ronchi</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ronchi</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Starc</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7710</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Michael Clarke</fielder>
						<fielderId>138</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>205</playerid>
					<name>Daniel Vettori</name>
					<batsman-name>Vettori</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Vettori</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>21</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Johnson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>496</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1057</playerid>
					<name>Tim Southee</name>
					<batsman-name>Southee</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Southee</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>11</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Glenn Maxwell</fielder>
						<fielderId>7662</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9067</playerid>
					<name>Matt Henry</name>
					<batsman-name>M Henry</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Matt Henry</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Johnson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>496</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mitchell Starc</fielder>
						<fielderId>7710</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8117</playerid>
					<name>Trent Boult</name>
					<batsman-name>T Boult</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Boult</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>201</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>1</runs>
				<overs>0.5</overs>
				<batsman>Brendon McCullum</batsman>
				<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1457</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>33</runs>
				<overs>11.2</overs>
				<batsman>Martin Guptill</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Guptill</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6326</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>39</runs>
				<overs>12.2</overs>
				<batsman>Kane Williamson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Williamson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>521</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>150</runs>
				<overs>35.1</overs>
				<batsman>Ross Taylor</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Ross Taylor</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8982</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>150</runs>
				<overs>35.3</overs>
				<batsman>Corey Anderson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>CJ Anderson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1396</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>151</runs>
				<overs>36.2</overs>
				<batsman>Luke Ronchi</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Ronchi</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>205</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>167</runs>
				<overs>40.6</overs>
				<batsman>Daniel Vettori</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Vettori</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1064</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>171</runs>
				<overs>41.5</overs>
				<batsman>Grant Elliott</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Elliott</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9067</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>182</runs>
				<overs>44.5</overs>
				<batsman>Matt Henry</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Henry</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1057</playerid>
				<nbr>10</nbr>
				<runs>183</runs>
				<overs>45</overs>
				<batsman>Tim Southee</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Southee</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>6</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>7</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>13</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Australia">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7710</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
					<bowler-name>M Starc</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Starc</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>20</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6258</playerid>
					<name>Josh Hazlewood</name>
					<bowler-name>J Hazlewood</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Hazlewood</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>2</maidens>
					<runsoff>30</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>496</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Johnson</name>
					<bowler-name>Johnson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Johnson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>30</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7662</playerid>
					<name>Glenn Maxwell</name>
					<bowler-name>Maxwell</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Maxwell</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>37</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7789</playerid>
					<name>James Faulkner</name>
					<bowler-name>Faulkner</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Faulkner</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>158</playerid>
					<name>Shane Watson</name>
					<bowler-name>Watson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Watson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>23</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1643</playerid>
					<name>Aaron Finch</name>
					<bowler-name>Finch</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Finch</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1739</playerid>
					<name>David Warner</name>
					<bowler-name>Warner</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Warner</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2250</playerid>
					<name>Steven Smith</name>
					<bowler-name>S Smith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Smith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>138</playerid>
					<name>Michael Clarke</name>
					<bowler-name>Clarke</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Clarke</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>159</playerid>
					<name>Brad Haddin</name>
					<bowler-name>Haddin</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Haddin</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>186</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>3</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>33.1</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Australia">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1739</playerid>
					<name>David Warner</name>
					<batsman-name>Warner</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Warner</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>45</runs>
					<balls>46</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Henry</bowler>
					<bowlerId>9067</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Grant Elliott</fielder>
						<fielderId>1064</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1643</playerid>
					<name>Aaron Finch</name>
					<batsman-name>Finch</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Finch</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>T Boult</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8117</bowlerId>
						<fielder>T Boult</fielder>
						<fielderId>8117</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2250</playerid>
					<name>Steven Smith</name>
					<batsman-name>S Smith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Smith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>56</runs>
					<balls>71</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>138</playerid>
					<name>Michael Clarke</name>
					<batsman-name>Clarke</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Clarke</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>74</runs>
					<balls>72</balls>
					<fours>10</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>M Henry</bowler>
					<bowlerId>9067</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>158</playerid>
					<name>Shane Watson</name>
					<batsman-name>Watson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Watson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7662</playerid>
					<name>Glenn Maxwell</name>
					<batsman-name>Maxwell</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Maxwell</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>159</playerid>
					<name>Brad Haddin</name>
					<batsman-name>Haddin</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Haddin</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7789</playerid>
					<name>James Faulkner</name>
					<batsman-name>Faulkner</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Faulkner</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>496</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Johnson</name>
					<batsman-name>Johnson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Johnson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7710</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
					<batsman-name>M Starc</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Starc</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6258</playerid>
					<name>Josh Hazlewood</name>
					<batsman-name>J Hazlewood</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Hazlewood</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1643</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>2</runs>
				<overs>1.4</overs>
				<batsman>Aaron Finch</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Finch</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1739</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>63</runs>
				<overs>12.2</overs>
				<batsman>David Warner</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Warner</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>138</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>175</runs>
				<overs>31.1</overs>
				<batsman>Michael Clarke</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Clarke</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>6</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>3</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>9</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="New Zealand">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1057</playerid>
					<name>Tim Southee</name>
					<bowler-name>Southee</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Southee</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>65</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8117</playerid>
					<name>Trent Boult</name>
					<bowler-name>T Boult</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Boult</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>40</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>205</playerid>
					<name>Daniel Vettori</name>
					<bowler-name>Vettori</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Vettori</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9067</playerid>
					<name>Matt Henry</name>
					<bowler-name>M Henry</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Matt Henry</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9.1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>46</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8982</playerid>
					<name>Corey Anderson</name>
					<bowler-name>CJ Anderson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Corey Anderson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>7</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<bowler-name>B McCullum</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Brendon McCullum</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1457</playerid>
					<name>Martin Guptill</name>
					<bowler-name>M Guptill</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Guptill</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6326</playerid>
					<name>Kane Williamson</name>
					<bowler-name>Williamson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Williamson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>521</playerid>
					<name>Ross Taylor</name>
					<bowler-name>Ross Taylor</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ross Taylor</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1064</playerid>
					<name>Grant Elliott</name>
					<bowler-name>Elliott</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Elliott</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1396</playerid>
					<name>Luke Ronchi</name>
					<bowler-name>Ronchi</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ronchi</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



