<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="12889" >
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>35th Match, Pool A</gameDesc>
		<series>WC 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Sri Lanka</home>
		<away>Scotland</away>
		<teamsabbr>SL vs SCO</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>SL</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>SCO</awayabbr>
		<homeId>5</homeId>
		<awayId>23</awayId>
		<venue>Bellerive Oval, Hobart</venue>
		<startdate>11 03 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>11 03 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Sri Lanka</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Sri Lanka won by 148 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Sri Lanka</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>148</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Richard Illingworth</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Joel S Wilson</Name>
			<Country>WI</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Michael Gough</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Jeff Crowe</Name>
			<Country>NZ</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>03:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150311105749</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>Sco</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>SL</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>215</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>10</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>43.1</batteamovers>
		<status>Sri Lanka won by 148 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>3053</playerid>
			<name>Alasdair Evans</name>
			<batsman-name>A Evans</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Alasdair Evans</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>1</runs>
			<balls-faced>5</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
			<batsman>
				<name />
				<runs />
				<balls-faced />
				<fours />
				<sixes />
			</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>8393</playerid>
			<name>Dushmantha Chameera*</name>
			<bowler-name>Dushmantha Chameera</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Dushmantha Chameera</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>7.1</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>51</runs>
			<wickets>3</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>111</playerid>
			<name>Lasith Malinga</name>
			<bowler-name>Malinga</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Malinga</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>9</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>29</runs>
			<wickets>2</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>364</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>6657</playerid>
<name>Josh Davey</name>
<player-runs>4</player-runs>
<player-balls>7</player-balls>
<runs>215</runs>
<wicket-nbr>10</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>8393</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Dushmantha Chameera</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>6</wides>
			<noballs>1</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>9</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[. . . 2 W 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>W . . . 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. . 2 . 1 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>W ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_WC/SL_SCO_MAR11/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[So, that's all we have from this game. Many thanks for your company folks. Tomorrow, South Africa will lock horns with UAE in Wellington. So make sure, you join us for that game. On behalf of <b>Krishna, Raju, Sriram</b>, my co-commentators, <b>Akshay, Srivathsa</b> and <b>Pradeep</b>, this is <b>Sidhant Maheshwari</b>, signing off. Take care. Ciao!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Let's glance through some of the <b>tweets</b> from this game:]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@sachin_rt:</b> 4 in a row, Congrats @KumarSanga2  Amazing batting and super consistency #CWC15]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@anilkumble1074:</b> Run machine Sanga... Plenty of fuel in the tank...Well done! #respect #CWC2015]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@IamDimuth:</b> It will take four centuries to find another player like @KumarSanga2 Hats off #legend #4inarow #ICCWC #SLvSCO #CWC15]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@legsidelizzy:</b> Someone needs to pass a law that stops Sangakkara from retiring. @UN ?]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@jatinsapru:</b> Sangakkara's ploy to retire is unfair to the game! He's not blocking any talent, is in prime form, so then why? Let's file a petition #cwc15]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@cricketaakash:</b> Hail Sanga #Legend]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mathews:</b> 'I have got a sore achilles tendon, so the management and the physio thought it was wise to stay out of the field. It was a precautionary effort. I don't think so, it was pretty sore and the physio thought not to risk it and stay out of the field. So, we got assess it for the next couple of days. Looking from the dressing room, it is pretty different than being out there in the middle, but I think the boys played really well. Credit should go to Dilshan and Sangakkara. Sangakkara is getting better and better with each and every game. It's wonderful to have these guys in the team. We just got to take it one game at a time, whoever we get to play, take it as another game, play positive cricket, that we have been doing pretty well in the past 4 games and we just have to go out there and play the same game. If we can improve out bowling and also the fielding quite a bit, it will be a great thing going forward. But I think the batters have been performing really well, getting 300 four times in a row is not easy. I have almost gone on my knees and begged him not to retire. But, unfortunately he has called it a day, so we got to respect his decision. He has served the team, the country for such a long time and we are really thankful for their service (on being asked if there's any possibilty that he could convince Sangakkara not to retire).']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mommsen:</b> 'We got a nice partnership together there, gave ourselves a bit of a platform. Slightly disappointed that we couldn't push hard and get the game deeper. Very disappointed, I think that was a brilliant wicket there but not to go on and get a bigger score is slightly disappointing. Huge amount, today was a huge learning experience, playing against some of the best batters in the world and the way they go about their business. The calmness of their innings is brilliant to watch and learn from. For the bowlers, obviously very difficult, very testing on a very good batting wicket. So, huge amounts of learning happened today. No. 1, for the player we have played against definitely (on where he rates Sangakkara in terms of the best players in the world). They'll have to, this is the level, this is the standard we want to compete at. We want to play against the full members more often and it's important now that we compete at that level. So, we are learning as much as possible day in and day out during this World Cup and today was a brilliant day for learning.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sangakkara</b>: 'Very slowly (on being asked how he gets rid of all his gear after the match). It was a pretty good game, it was important that we finished off strong and playing against a team like Scotland, it is sometimes easy to take things or be a bit complacent. But, today I think the boys were right up for a fight and although the Scots fought hard, we were better on the day. That's what I have been doing for quite a long time, once you get used to a certain routine, it becomes hard of course and now that I am 37, I get a bit slower, the joints start creaking and aching. But I am pretty happy that I am still playing. I consider myself very, very lucky to be a part of such a good side. So, when everything is going well, things look bright. (Laughs loudly) It's hard to say, sometimes things just fall into place, everything clicks. No matter how hard you try to find that one thing, it is difficult to pinpoint it. Maybe, it is because I am making a lot of better decisions, the right decision at the right time, taking the risk at the right time, being more calculated, being a bit more positive in my approach. I don't really know what that one thing is, but whatever it is, it is working for me at the moment and I would like to hold onto that for as long as I can. As long as we our positive, as long as we enjoy ourselves, as long as we believe that we can do it, I think we can go far (on being asked if Sri Lanka can go all the way). We have had a strange World Cup, I think our squad has changed quite a lot from the start. We had a lot of injuries, but the real key for us is the way we enjoy our cricket, the flair with which we play, the brand of cricket we play. As long as there is a smile on our faces and as long as we give everything on the field, we always have a chance. That's what we look at and that's what we believe. I would love to see myself, I would love to see all of us there. We have really got to break it down. If it happens, it happens. You can't worry too much, you just got to keep your focus on the present. Couple of days off, regroup, train hard and play a very good quarter-final. If we are good enough on the day, we will get to the semi-final. So, we will concentrate on that game and if we make it through, I will talk to you again and I will have a bigger smile.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kumar Sangakkara</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his outstanding 95-ball 124. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, Dilshan and Sangakkara added 195 for the second wicket to set up a massive total. The former got his second ton of the competition while the latter notched up his 4th consecutive hundred and became the first batsman to achieve that. Mathews bettered Dinesh Chandimal's record of the fastest Sri Lankan to a World Cup fifty by getting it in 20 balls. They would have got plenty more, if they didn't lose wickets in a heap. Scotland will take on the mighty Aussies next and Sri Lanka will have some time off before they play the quarter-final.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sri Lanka's bowling still has some work to do and they have to get it right as the next game they play is the quarter-final. Malinga looks like a shadow of his old self, Kulasekara is not troubling the batsmen with his indippers. They also failed to strike in the middle overs, they are missing a quality spinner. Chameera was quick, but he didn't have control, he came back well though in the second spell to pick up 3 wickets. So, they need to sort it out, if they have to beat any one of the top teams.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Both batsmen got to their fifties. And they were excellent against the spin of Prasanna, using their feet and playing it right under the eyes. It was Scotland's second 100 plus partnership in World Cups and Mommsen was involved in both of them. However, the duo went in quick succession. Berrington came out attacking and hit a few lusty blows, but he kept losing partners and they were finally bowled out for 215.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The centurion from the previous game, Kyle Coetzer went for a second ball duck today. Scotland were in a bit of trouble early on as MacLeod once again failed to capitalise on the opportunity given. Machan battled for a while before being trapped by Dilshan, he also lost the review in the process. After that, Mommsen and Coleman batted sensibly to add a 118-run stand for the 4th wicket. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Davey, <b>out</b> Caught by Thirimanne!! <b>Sri Lanka win by a massive margin of 148 runs</b>. Scotland have been bowled out and Chameera picks up his third wicket. It was a back of a length delivery just outside off, Davey pushes at it, gets an outside edge that is well caught by Thirimanne at slip, who moves across low to his left to complete the catch. The Sri Lankan players walk off the field as they shake hands with their Scottish counterparts. <b>Davey c Thirimanne b Dushmantha Chameera 4(7)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Dushmantha Chameera to Davey, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Alasdair Evans, no run, low full toss just outside off, Evans looks to clear the man at mid-on, but doesn't time it at all, the ball goes on the bounce to Chameera, who was right at the edge of the circle]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Davey, 1 run, angling in on the pads, Davey flicks it uppishly through the vacant mid-wicket region for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Davey, no run, slower full toss that was dipping in on the leg stump, Davey backs away and just about gets his bat down in time to push it back towards the bowler, had he missed, it would have crashed into the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Davey, 2 runs, slower length delivery just outside off, Davey goes for the loft over cover, doesn't get hold of it properly, but it is good enough to go over the infield and the batsmen take two before the fielder from cover chases it down]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Davey, no run, full and outside off, Davey leans forward and knocks it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Davey, no run, loopy full toss down leg, Davey moves slightly across but fails to tickle it fine, the ball dips and just about misses the leg stump there, good ball first up in the new over]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Davey, 1 run, back of a length delivery on the pads, Davey hops up in the crease and tucks it away towards mid-wicket, there was a slight hesitation as the batsmen went for the single, but the batsman makes it in time at the non-striker's end even as the fielder has a shy at the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Alasdair Evans, 1 run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Evans waits inside the crease, opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Alasdair Evans, no run, full delivery on leg, Evans turns it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Alasdair Evans, no run, yorker on the stumps, Evans jams it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Alasdair Evans, no run, short delivery just outside off, Evans drops his wrists and lets it pass]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Alasdair Evans, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Berrington, <b>out</b> Caught by N Kulasekara!! Another one goes down and Kulasekara just about manages to hold onto the catch. It was fuller and outside off, Berrington was trying to clear the man at mid-on there, but can't get the elevation. He ends up hitting it straight to Kula, who just about drops it as the ball popped out of his hands, but he used his body well to hold onto the catch. <b>Berrington c N Kulasekara b Dushmantha Chameera 29(22) [4s-2 6s-2]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Dushmantha Chameera to Berrington, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Scotland have <b>lost their last 4 wickets for just 20 runs</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Berrington, 1 run, just short of a good length and just outside off, Berrington was early into the punch, but manages to get it square of the wicket and that's good enough for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Josh Davey, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Rob Taylor, <b>out</b> Caught by T Perera!! Taylor's short stay at the crease comes to an end. It was a back of a length slower delivery outside off, Taylor clears the front leg and wanted to loft it over mid-on, he was too early into the shot and mistimes it completely off the toe-end of the bat, the ball goes towards mid-on, who moves back a little and takes a simple catch. The Scottish are falling apart here. <b>Rob Taylor c T Perera b Malinga 3(6)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Malinga to Rob Taylor, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Rob Taylor, 2 runs, slower ball and length delivery around off, Taylor was early into the loft, gets it off the toe-end of the bat and the ball just about clears a backtracking mid-on, the batsmen take two]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Rob Taylor, no run, short delivery outside off, Taylor backs away and goes for the flat-batted pull, but the ball goes under his bat and through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Rob Taylor, no run, down the leg-side, Taylor fails to tickle it fine, the ball clips the pad on its way to the keeper, who dives to his right and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Rob Taylor, no run, good slower ball yorker on middle stump, Taylor did well to get his bat down in time as he squeezed it out]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[The batting powerplay yielded <b>19/3</b>. Sri Lanka have come back strongly in those five overs]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Berrington, <b>FOUR</b>, full delivery just outside off, Berrington drills it back to the right of the bowler, who tries to catch it, but the ball goes past his hands and beats the fielder at mid-off as well, who had no chance of cutting that off]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Rob Taylor, 1 run, tucks this delivery on middle stump line towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Berrington, <b>no ball</b>, 1 run, that's loose from Chameera, it was a high full toss around waist height, the square leg umpire signalled it a no-ball for height as Berrington helps it away down to fine leg for a single, Chameera must have been given a warning as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rob Taylor, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Matthew Cross, <b>out</b> Caught by Sangakkara!! Cross perishes now and it's a great catch by Sangakkara. He can't do anything wrong today. It was short and well outside off, Cross went for the pull, but ends up slicing it high in the air. Sangakkara runs back to his right, gets under it and takes a good catch in the end. These kind of swirlers are difficult, but Sangakkara did well there to take it. First ODI wicket for Chameera as well. <b>Matthew Cross c Sangakkara b Dushmantha Chameera 7(10)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dushmantha Chameera to Matthew Cross, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Matthew Cross, no run, yorker on the stumps, Cross looks to squeeze it out, gets an inside edge that rolls behind the stumps towards the keeper, the batsman was looking for the single, but has to rush back in]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Matthew Cross, 2 runs, <b>what happened there?</b> It was short and well wide outside off, it was the cross-seamer, the ball got stuck into the wicket and Cross was early into his flat-batted shot, the ball takes the top-edge and balloons over the keeper, the batsmen take two]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Berrington, 1 run, banged in short and around off, Berrington jams the pull through mid-wicket for another run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dushmantha Chameera [5.0-0-39-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Matthew Cross, 2 runs, low full toss, Cross made room for himself and wanted to hit it into the off-side, gets an inside edge that rolls away behind square on the on-side, the batsmen take two, had he missed that, the ball would have rattled into the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Matthew Cross, 2 runs, another slower ball from Malinga and that resulted in another wicket, it was on a length and on off, Cross was early into the slog and just about clears mid-on, who was running to his right, the batsmen take two before Chameera hunts it down]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Matthew Cross, no run, almost a yorker on middle, Cross jams out the drive to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Matthew Cross, no run, drives this fullish delivery into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Matthew Cross, no run, full and outside off, Cross was looking to squeeze it out into the off-side, fails to make contact]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sangakkara now has the most number of dismissals as a wicket-keeper in World Cups. He goes past Adam Gilchrist, who had 52 dismissals to his name.]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Matthew Cross, no run, slower ball yorker on off, Cross squeezes it out towards backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Matthew Cross, 1 run, yorker on off, Cross jams it out to mid-off, who fumbles the ball and the batsmen charge across for a single, the fielder has a shy at the non-striker's end, but the batsman was well in]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Matthew Cross, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to M A Leask, <b>out</b> Caught by Sangakkara!! It was another bouncer from Kula, Leask fails to connect with the hook, the umpire doesn't call it a wide. Wait a minute! Sri Lanka have reviewed for a caught behind appeal, there was a little sound as the ball went past the bat and maybe, that's what interested him. Snicko shows a little spike as the ball goes past the bat. The decision has been overturned. Leask has to go. What a review by the Lankans. That review caught everyone by surprise. Nevertheless, Scotland are six down now and the Lankans won't mind it one bit. <b>M A Leask c Sangakkara b N Kulasekara 2(7)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[N Kulasekara to M A Leask, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to M A Leask, no run, slower ball bumper from Kulasekara, Leask went for the hook, but can't connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Berrington, 1 run, yorker outside off, Berrington squeezes out the drive to the left of cover-point, who runs across and puts in the dive, saves three runs for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to M A Leask, 1 run, just short of a good length and outside off, Leask hangs back and cuts it towards square third man, who moves across to his right and keeps the batsmen down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to M A Leask, no run, on a good length and angling in on off, Leask pushes at it off the front foot, gets an inside edge onto the pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Berrington, no run, loopy yorker from Malinga on off, Berrington squeezes it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Berrington, no run, slower ball on middle stump line, it was bowled at 110.4kph, Berrington leans forward and defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Berrington, no run, full toss on the stumps, Berrington defends it to the right of the bowler, the ball rolls away to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to M A Leask, 1 run, a slow, low full toss on middle and leg, Leask was inside the crease, he looks to work it into the on-side, gets an inside edge that dribbles away to fine leg, the batsmen cross over]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to M A Leask, no run, very full and on leg, Leask fails to clip it into the on-side and wears it on the pad, it was snaking down leg though]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to M A Leask, no run, slower ball yorker just outside off, Leask was deceived there as he went pushing at it, the ball goes past the blade and the off stump as well, Leask affords a smile after that ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga [5.0-0-18-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Michael Leask, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Coleman, <b>out</b> Caught by T Perera!! Soft dismissal for Coleman. It was the leg-spinner from Kulasekara, Coleman was looking to launch it over the long-on fence, but he can't time it as it came off the toe-end. The fielder at long-on comes under it and almost drops the simplest of catches as it popped out of his hands, but he did well at the end to hang onto it. Another good knock comes to an end. <b>Coleman c T Perera b N Kulasekara 70(74) [4s-7]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[N Kulasekara to Coleman, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Coleman, no run, 105.8kph slower ball well outside off, Coleman went right across his stumps and was looking to scoop it over short fine, can't connect and the ball rolls away to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Coleman, no run, slower delivery from Kulasekara, it was a back of a length delivery just outside off, Coleman was early into the pull, the ball doesn't bounce much and goes on the bounce to the keeper, it was not too far away from the off stump too]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Berrington, 1 run, full and around off, Berrington waits inside the crease and whips it to the right of long-on, the batsmen take a single before the fielder runs across and fields it]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Berrington, no run, just short of a good length and on top of off, Berrington knocks it towards backward point and says 'no' for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Berrington, no run, length delivery outside off, it was the off-speed delivery, Berrington was looking to guide it down to third man but fails to connect with it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Nuwan Kulasekara [5.0-0-16-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's <b>batting powerplay</b> time. The umpire makes the signal and the ball has been handed over to Kulasekara, who will start the proceedings after the drinks break.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time for a drinks break</b>. Scotland have played really well in this period. Mommsen and Coleman were making the Sri Lankan bowlers sweat hard, but Mommsen got out against the run of play to Perera. Since then, Berrington has been aggressive and is giving good company to Coleman. The target is a little too far away, but Scotland will definitely provide us entertainment if they go after it.]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Berrington, 1 run, touch slower this time and around off stump line, Berrington goes down on one knee and sweeps it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Berrington, <b>SIX</b>, <b>mammoth!</b> It was floated up on off, Berrington kneels down and hammers the slog sweep over the long-on fence, that went quite the distance, good shot from Berrington]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Berrington, no run, darted on the pads, Berrington works it straight to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, 1 run, flighted delivery outside off, Coleman eases it down to long-off and gets off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, no run, tossed up around off, Coleman drills the drive towards short cover off the front foot, where Dilshan dives to his left and saves some runs for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Berrington, 1 run, pushed through down leg, Berrington works it towards backward square leg for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Coleman, <b>FOUR</b>, short but not short enough to trouble the batsman, who rocks back and pulls it behind square with ease, it was the slower one and Coleman had all the time in the world to dispatch it to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Coleman, no run, short of length delivery around off, Coleman defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Coleman, no run, Coleman goes right across his stumps and Perera follows him with a leg-cutter, Coleman can't lay bat on it and the ball just spins away from the batsman's blade]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Coleman, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Coleman goes across and tries to work it through the leg-side, he closes the bat face a little too early, gets a soft leading edge that rolls away towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Coleman, no run, slightly fuller and outside off, Coleman drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Berrington, 1 run, back of a length delivery around off, Berrington stays back and pushes it towards sweeper cover with soft hands, the batsmen take a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Berrington, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Berrington presses forward and drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Berrington, no run, flighted delivery just outside off, Berrington defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Berrington, <b>SIX</b>, that's a <b>super shot!</b> It was floated up on off, Berrington kneels down and sweeps it, the ball went up and over the deep square leg fence. That was timed very sweetly]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Berrington, <b>FOUR</b>, that was a very poor effort from Dilshan at short cover, it was tossed up on the stumps, Berrington drills the drive towards Dilshan, who bends down as he tries to field it, but the ball goes under him and through his legs, crashes into the deep extra cover fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Berrington, no run, in the blockhole just outside off, Berrington jams it out into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, 1 run, floated up just outside off, Coleman drives it wide of long-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Richie Berrington, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, <b>out</b> Caught by Thirimanne!! Mommsen goes against the run of play. It was fuller and around off, Mommsen leans forward and drives uppishly, Thirimanne at short cover leans forward to take the catch, but can't hold onto it. Luckily for him, the ball lobs up off his body and he takes it on the second attempt. Still a good effort from the Sri Lankan vice-captain. Perera is delighted and celebrates with his team-mates. Mommsen was very disappointed and was a little late to leave his ground. It was a good knock nevertheless. <b>Mommsen c Thirimanne b T Perera 60(75) [4s-7]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[T Perera to Mommsen, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Coleman, 1 run, length delivery just outside off, Coleman was pushing at it from the crease, gets an outside edge that runs away down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, 1 run, angling in on middle, Mommsen waits for it and clips it towards mid-wicket to get off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, <b>wide</b>, very poor ball from Perera, another slower one and this one is even further away from the tramline, another wide and Sangakkara doesn't look happy with that effort]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, <b>FOUR</b>, great shot from the Scottish captain, it was short and it sat up nicely for Mommsen to swivel and pull it behind square, the ball rockets away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, no run, length delivery around off, Mommsen leans forward, opens the face of the bat and pushes it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, <b>wide</b>, slower delivery from Perera, but it was well outside the tramline, called a wide by the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Coleman, 1 run, shortish and well outside off, Coleman hangs back and cuts, gets an outside edge that dribbles away to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Thisara Perera [5.0-0-27-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Thisara Perera has come back on. He replaces Chameera]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, 1 run, floated up around off and middle, Coleman backs away and drives it to sweeper cover, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, 1 run, quicker and around off, Mommsen knocks it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, 2 runs, comes down the track and lofts this flighted delivery just over a leaping short mid-wicket, the fielder from deep mid-wicket runs to his left, puts in the dive and saves two runs for his team right near the boundary, good effort from Kusal Perera there]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, 1 run, touch shortish and outside off, Coleman looks to guide it down to third man, but can't beat backward point who dives to his left and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, 1 run, gives the charge and converts this tossed up delivery into a full toss, driven to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, no run, tossed up just outside off, Mommsen drives it to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[There is a slight drizzle in the air. Scotland are 66 runs behind after 30 overs (D/L)]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Coleman, no run, length delivery outside off, Coleman comes charging down the track and looks to go big, but can't lay bat on it and the keeper gloves it]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Coleman, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Coleman was looking to run it down to third man, Coleman ends up chopping it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Mommsen, 1 run, good shot for just a single, it was a shortish delivery well outside off, Mommsen cuts it hard square of the wicket, but there was a fielder in the deep and it went straight to him]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Coleman, 1 run, banged in short and at the batsman, who pulls, but can't time it properly. The batsman take a single as the ball falls in the vacant square leg region]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Mommsen, 1 run, Mommsen reaches his <b>5th ODI fifty</b> with a single, it was a back of a length delivery just around off, Mommsen pushes it square of the wicket and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Mommsen, no run, bowls this one in the channel outside off, Mommsen hangs back and looks to run it down to third man, can't connect and the keeper collects]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, 1 run, a single down to long-off brings up the <b>100-run stand</b> between these two, this is Preston Mommsen's second 100-run partnership in two games]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, no run, flighted delivery just outside off, Mommsen comes forward and drives to the left of cover, Dilshan runs to his left, dives and prevents the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, 1 run, gives the charge and drives this tossed up delivery on the stumps to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, no run, pushed through quicker and fuller on middle and leg, Coleman squeezes it out back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, no run, floated up outside off, Coleman goes for the front foot drive, gets an outside edge that rolls away towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, no run, loopy delivery in the blockhole, Coleman drives it to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Seekkuge Prasanna [4.0-0-28-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Spin after 8 overs as Prasanna replaces Malinga, who just bowled the one over in his second spell]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Mommsen, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Mommsen hops in the crease, opens the face of the bat and pushes it to the right of backward point, shouts a loud 'no' for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Mommsen, no run, full and on off, Mommsen drives hard but can't beat the fielder at mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Coleman, 1 run, length delivery just outside off, Coleman leans forward and drives it to sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Coleman, 2 runs, banged in short and at the batsman, who miscues the pull, but clears mid-on, who was running to his right. The batsmen take two]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Mommsen, 1 run, length delivery outside off, Mommsen was on the back foot and was looking to flat-bat it over the infield, he ends up slicing it off the toe-end of the bat and the ball just about clears the fielder at mid-off, the batsmen take a single before the ball is hunted down]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Mommsen, <b>wide</b>, short and wide outside off, Mommsen goes after it but fails to connect, the umpire calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Coleman, 1 run, <b>ohh dear! That's a dolly that has gone down!</b> It was short and wide outside off, Coleman cuts uppishly and Kusal Perera at sweeper cover was under it, don't know what happened, but he couldn't get his hands around the ball, the ball hits his chest and goes down. That should have been taken and the bowler won't be happy at all]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Looks like Dilshan has done something to his back. The physio is out there, rubbing his back. Dilshan gets up and is ready to go back to his fielding position]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Mommsen, no run, touch fuller and on off, Mommsen drives hard to the left of mid-on, who moves across quickly and stops it]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Coleman, 1 run, banged in short and outside off, Coleman jumps in the crease, gets on top of the bounce and plays a controlled pull to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Mommsen, 1 run, on a good length and around off, Mommsen leans forward and drops it in front of cover and sets off, Thirimanne from cover charges towards the ball, picks it up and fires in the throw at the striker's end, Coleman was diving to make his ground and does so in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Mommsen, no run, fuller and angling in on middle and leg, Mommsen pushes it a little uppishly towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Coleman, 1 run, touch fuller but slower at 115kph, Coleman was early into the drive, ends up chipping it uppishly through the vacant cover region, the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Coleman, no run, banged in short and well outside off, Coleman stays back and looks to ramp it over the keeper, but fails to connect]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga [4.0-0-15-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Malinga is back in action. Can he break this partnership? Let's see if his yorkers work out now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Mommsen, <b>FOUR</b>, the debutant has gone for a boundary every over, he concedes another one off the last ball, it was full and outside off, Mommsen leans forward and drives it throught the covers, the fielder from extra cover gives chase, but the ball beats him to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Mommsen, no run, full and angling in on off, Mommsen drives hard, but picks out mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Mommsen, no run, bit short and wide as well, Mommsen hangs back and cuts uppishly, the ball goes on the bounce to Dilshan at backward point, who just about manages to stop it]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Coleman, 1 run, shortish delivery on the body of the batsman, who stays back and tucks it away behind square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Mommsen, leg byes, 1 run, drifting on the pads, Mommsen fails to work it into the on-side, the batsmen sneak in a leg bye as the ball rolls away into the leg-side after clipping the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Coleman, 1 run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Coleman goes across and wristily works it towards mid-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[It has started to rain again]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Coleman, 1 run, <b>fifty for Coleman </b>, on a good length and just outside off, dabbed to the left of cover for a single, raises his first fifty in ODIs, gets a good round of applause from his mates in the dressing room]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Coleman, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, length ball on the pads, Coleman gets across, presents the full face of the bat and drives it through mid-wicket, races away to the fence in a hurry]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Coleman, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Coleman presses across and works it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, Mommsen stays back and punches it square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Coleman, 1 run, the slower ball from Perera, ends up dragging it short and wide outside off, slapped away to deep cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Coleman, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Coleman presses forward and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Mommsen, <b>FOUR</b>, Mommsen is looking in good touch, this was short and on the stumps, Mommsen swivels across and pulls it in front of square on the on-side for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Mommsen, no run, on a good length and just outside off, dabbed in front of cover, the fielder throws down the stumps at the bowler's end, but Coleman was well in]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Mommsen, no run, short and wide from Chameera, Mommsen throws his bat at that and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Coleman, 3 runs, that's excellent running from Mommsen, converts one into three, it was pushed in front of deep cover by Coleman, Mommsen called for a second run. The fielder shies at the bowler's end and misses, Malinga is sloppy while backing up and allows an extra run]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Coleman, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four</b>, short of a length and holding its line outside off, Coleman hung his bat at that, gets a thick edge that drops in front of MJ at first slip, races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Mommsen, 1 run, yorker length delivery and well outside off, Mommsen plays with an open face and guides it down towards third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, 1 run, width on offer from Perera, cracked away square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Mommsen gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, no run, on a good length and around off, punched back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Mommsen was pressing forward, drops his bottom hand and defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Coleman, 1 run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Coleman drives and gets a thick edge towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, 1 run, back of a length and on the stumps, worked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Coleman, <b>FOUR</b>, back-to-back boundaries for Coleman, this was short and wide from Chameera, Coleman quickly got into position and cracked it square on the off-side. Malinga gets across to his right and puts in the dive, but hits the cushions along with the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Coleman, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a lovely shot, overpitched and on the stumps, Coleman leans forward, presents the full face of the bat and drives it back past the bowler, beats the fielder at mid-on and races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Coleman, no run, <b>appeal for LBW</b>, but the ball was tailing down leg, this was full and angling back into the right-hander, he fell over on the flick and missed, the impact was marginally on leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Coleman, <b>FOUR</b>, nicely played by Coleman, short of a length and holding its line outside off, Coleman waits on it, uses the pace on the ball and steers it past the slip cordon, third man is square and the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Coleman, no run, on a length and just outside off, slapped straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dushmantha Chameera to Mommsen, leg byes, 1 run, full and sliding onto Mommsen's pads, he looks to flick and misses, Coleman calls for a leg-bye and gets it with ease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dushmantha Chameera, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Coleman, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Coleman presses forward and defends it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Coleman, no run, another short ball from Perera, Coleman swivels across and pulls it straight to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, chopped to the right of point, the fielder dives and deflects it away towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Coleman, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, Coleman stays back and cracks it square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Coleman, no run, short of a length and just outside off, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Coleman, 2 runs, back of a length and just outside off, Coleman waits on it and runs it past the lone slip, third man gets across and keeps them down to a brace]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Thisara Perera [2.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Coleman, 1 run, we have 20 overs done and <b>that means a result will be obtained from this match</b>, tossed up and just outside off, dabbed to the left of cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Coleman, no run, flatter and just outside off, punched back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[Back over the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Coleman, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, Coleman comes down the track, gives himself some room and goes up and over mid-off, one bounce and over the ropes for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Mommsen, 1 run, this one is given more air, driven towards mid-off for a quick single. The fielder has a shy and misses, Mommsen was well in though]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Mommsen, no run, slower and on the pads, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Mommsen, no run, short and well outside off, dabbed straight to the fielder at short third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, 1 run, slower and just outside off, Mommsen makes room and punches it square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, no run, pushed through and on Mommsen's pads, he looks to nudge it towards the on-side and misses, the ball lobs off the pads. Sangakkara gets across and takes the catch, no dramatics or appealing though]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a lovely shot, good use of the feet from Mommsen, comes down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and whips it over mid-wicket for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, 1 run, Coleman comes down the track, doesn't get to the pitch and gets an inside edge on the whip behind square for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, 1 run, slower and well outside off, eased past cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, 1 run, tossed up and on off, Coleman comes down the track and drives it towards long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Only the Scots took the drinks break, Sri Lanka were worried about the rain and were just waiting in their positions, for the match to resume]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Coleman, 1 run, Coleman comes down the track and eases a single to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Coleman, no run, slower and just outside off, blocked back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Coleman, no run, Coleman attempts the reverse sweep, but the ball went with the angle and beats his outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Mommsen, 1 run, slower and just outside off, Mommsen dabs it wide of cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Mommsen, no run, pushed through by Dilshan, Mommsen goes back and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Mommsen, no run, tossed up and on the pads, Mommsen presses across and blocks]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Even as the Sri Lankan bowlers were hurrying through their overs, the heavens have opened up, it's just a slight drizzle at the moment, but with 20 overs not yet bowled, SL do not want to take a chance. A wash-out here will tie them with Bangladesh on 7 points. They have an inferior net run-rate as well. New Zealand play Bangladesh in their final match, a positive result or even a wash-out will push Sri Lanka to number four in Pool A, and that will mean a meeting with India in the quarter-finals. We need another 18 balls to be bowled for a result in this game..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, 1 run, Mommsen comes down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and whips it towards mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, no run, tossed up and well outside off, Mommsen presses forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, 2 runs, that's nicely played, Mommsen comes down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and drives it past mid-on, gets back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, no run, flighted delivery and well outside off, pushed forward and defensively towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, 1 run, tossed up and well outside off, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, no run, pushed through flatter and on the middle stump line, Coleman backs away and chops it straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Coleman, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, Coleman goes well back and nudges it behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Coleman, no run, Coleman comes down the track to a flighted delivery and pushes it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Coleman, no run, slower and on the stumps, Coleman presses forward and turns it towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Mommsen, 1 run, flighted delivery and just outside off, driven in front of mid-off for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Coleman, 1 run, slower and on the stumps, worked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Coleman, no run, tossed up and just outside off, driven back towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, 1 run, this one is given more air, on the middle stump line, Coleman presses forward and gets an inside edge past mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, 2 runs, pushed through by Prasanna, ends up sliding onto Coleman's pads, nudged away very fine for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, 1 run, tossed up and just outside off, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, 1 run, fraction shorter and well outside off, Coleman makes room and cracks it square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, 2 runs, the lap sweep from Coleman, gets down very low and sweeps it over Sangakkara's shoulder, back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, 1 run, flighted delivery and well outside off, eased past cover for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Coleman, no run, this one's given more air, Coleman gets well forward and drives it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Mommsen, 1 run, slower and wider from Dilshan, eased square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Mommsen, no run, slower and just outside off, driven back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Mommsen, no run, the slider from Dilshan, went through with the angle, draws Mommsen forward and beats his outside edge. Sangakkara was quick to whip the bails off, Mommsen was dragging his foot forward but was well back in before the stumps were broken]]></line><line><![CDATA[Appeal for a <b>stumping</b>. The third umpire has been called. Sri Lanka aren't really excited, Mommsen has dragged his back-leg back, should be NOT OUT]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dilshan has a leg-slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Mommsen, no run, this one is given more air, driven straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Mommsen, no run, tossed up and just outside off, blocked towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, 1 run, this one's given more air, Mommsen lunges forward and gets an inside edge behind square for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Prasanna, dragged his length back and drifts this one well down leg-side, pulled away over backward square leg for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Mommsen, no run, tossed up and on off, Mommsen gets well forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[The leg-slip moves across to first slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, 1 run, slower and just outside off, nudged wide of extra cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, 2 runs, flighted delivery and well outside off, Coleman drives it square on the off-side, the fielder at sweeper gets across and keeps them down to a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[Just a leg-slip is in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Coleman, no run, tossed up and on the stumps, Coleman prods forward and blocks]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Seekkuge Prasanna, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Mommsen, 2 runs, nicely done by Mommsen, this was pushed through and just outside off, Mommsen goes down on his knees, uses the pace on the ball and laps it fine for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Coleman, 1 run, this one is given more air, driven towards deep cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Coleman, no run, slower and wider outside off, Coleman lunges forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Coleman, no run, flighted delivery from round the wicket, Coleman prods forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Freddie Coleman, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Machan, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Machan will feel unlucky, but that wasn't a good shot. This was the slider from Dilshan, pushed through and came back with the angle, Machan was well inside the line as he looked to whip it away towards the on-side, he misses and the ball clipped the pads, the impact was on leg-stump and the ball was going on to just clip the outer half of leg-stump. The original call was OUT and it stayed with the on-field call. <b>Machan lbw b Dilshan 19(31) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dilshan to Machan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Machan has been given out LBW. He wants a <b>review</b>. He took a long time, chatted with his partner and then asked for the review. This was the arm-ball from Dilshan, slid back into the left-hander, he ended up playing all around it, looks like there's no bat on that. Snicko confirms it as well. The ball should be missing the stumps for Machan to survive. Umpire's call, Machan is <b>OUT</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Machan, no run, Dilshan comes from round the wicket, tosses one on off, whipped away towards mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tillakaratne Dilshan, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, no run, on a good length and well outside off, Mommsen is happy to let it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, <b>FOUR</b>, Mommsen is looking in good touch, too short from Perera, sits up to be pulled, Mommsen swivels across and helps it on its way, races away to the deep square leg boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Machan, 1 run, another short ball from Perera, Machan swivels across and pulls it past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Machan, no run, short and going away with the angle, Machan looks to pull and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mathews is still not on the field. He's getting treated for an ankle injury]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Machan, 2 runs, Machan gets lucky! This was short and just outside off, Machan was early onto the pull, gets a bottom edge that rolls close to the off-stump, the fielder at long leg gets across and keeps them down to a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Machan, 2 runs, Machan leans forward to a length ball and drives it through extra cover. Malinga gives chase from mid-off and keeps them down to a couple of runs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Mommsen, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Mommsen stays behind the line and defends it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Mommsen, no run, tad fuller and swinging back into Mommsen, he was pressing forward on the drive and gets an inside edge towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Mommsen, no run, on a good length and nipping back into Mommsen, he was half-forward, gets an inside edge that rolls away towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Mommsen, <b>wide</b>, Kulasekara slips one well down leg-side, Mommsen looks to flick and misses, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Mommsen, no run, that's a high bouncer from Kulasekara, Mommsen looks to pull and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Machan, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Machan does a little shimmy and hammers it towards mid-on, Chameera gets across from mid-on and makes a half-save, keeps the batsmen down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[A man has been placed on the drive now, Thirimanne is at silly mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Machan, no run, on a good length and well outside off, driven towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, no run, short and wide from Perera, Mommsen throws his bat and misses, close to getting the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, no run, on a good length and well outside off, Mommsen leans forward, plays with an open face and guides it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a lovely drive! Overpitched and well outside off, Mommsen leans forward, gets to the pitch of the ball and caresses it past the diving cover fielder, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, no run, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, Mommsen doesn't need to play those, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, no run, on a length and on the stumps, Mommsen presses forward and defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Mommsen, no run, Perera shortens his length first ball and hits the deck hard, left alone, goes to the keeper at a good height]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Thisara Perera, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Machan, no run, short of a length and just outside off, punched with a straight bat and towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Mommsen, 3 runs, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Mommsen leans forward and drives it square past point. Prasanna gives a good chase, puts the dive in and drags the ball back in. Dilshan was backing up and a run is saved for the team]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Mommsen, no run, fuller length delivery and holding its line outside off, Mommsen gets a big stride forward, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preston Mommsen, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and a gully in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to MacLeod, <b>out</b> Bowled!! MacLeod has been castled! This was full and swung back late into the right-hander, MacLeod was looking to flick it towards the on-side, falls over in the process, the ball brushes his pads and deflects onto the middle stump. First wicket for Kulasekara, he must have enjoyed that. Scotland have lost both openers. <b>MacLeod b N Kulasekara 11(21)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[N Kulasekara to MacLeod, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to MacLeod, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, MacLeod presses across and drives it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to MacLeod, no run, on a good length and just outside off, MacLeod brings down the bat with an angle and defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Machan, no run, fuller length delivery and angling back into the left-hander, almost a yorker, he jams his bat down and digs it out towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[Malinga changes to round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to MacLeod, 1 run, width on offer from Malinga, slashed away behind square on the off-side, bisects the two men at gully and backward point, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to MacLeod, <b>wide</b>, another bouncer from Malinga, but it's too short and going down leg-side as well, MacLeod looks to pull and misses, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to MacLeod, no run, tad fuller and shaping away from outside off, slapped to the left of mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to MacLeod, no run, on a good length and on the stumps, MacLeod presents a straight bat as he drives it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to MacLeod, no run, another bouncer from Malinga, MacLeod was way too late on the pull, the ball had zipped past him by the time he swivelled across on the shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to MacLeod, no run, the bouncer from Malinga, MacLeod drops his wrists and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Machan, 2 runs, tad fuller and just outside off, Machan gets behind the line and punches it past mid-off, good enough for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Machan, no run, too full and on Machan's pads, turned towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Machan, no run, on a good length and angling across the left-hander, pushed with an open face and to the left of point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Machan, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Machan prods forward and defends it with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Machan, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a cracking shot from Machan, width on offer from Kulasekara, Machan stands tall and cracks it square on the off-side, no need to run for those, first boundary of the innings]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Machan, no run, fuller length delivery and on off, Machan presents the full face of the bat and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Machan, 1 run, the slower yorker from Malinga, gets it to dip into Machan, he waits on it and pushes it towards mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Machan, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Machan presses across and defends it with soft hands, the ball rolls away towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to MacLeod, 1 run, tad fuller and shaping away from outside off, draws MacLeod into the drive, gets a thick edge that flies through the vacant gully position]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to MacLeod, no run, another slower ball from Malinga, he's bowling a lot of those in this spell, MacLeod prods forward and defends it solidly]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to MacLeod, <b>wide</b>, another bouncer from Malinga, MacLeod drops his wrists and lets it go, a bit too high though, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to MacLeod, no run, the slower ball from Malinga, he rolled his fingers around it, defended towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to MacLeod, no run, the bumper from Malinga, MacLeod ducks under it and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to MacLeod, 1 run, on a good length and holding its line outside off, MacLeod pushes hard and gets a thick edge, no one at second slip and the ball rolls away towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Machan, 1 run, short and wide from Kulasekara, Machan went chasing after that and slaps it down towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Machan, no run, on a good length and shaping away from outside off, Machan comes down the track and swings, misses by a long way]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to MacLeod, 1 run, on a good length and well outside off, MacLeod presses forward and eases it wide of extra cover. Thisara at mid-off is very lazy on the ball and allows a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to MacLeod, no run, full and swinging onto MacLeod's pads, he was shuffling across on the flick and missed, the ball was sliding down leg. Only Sangakkara belted out a loud appeal]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to MacLeod, no run, full and on MacLeod's pads, he shuffles across and whips it straight to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Machan, no run, yorker length delivery and just outside off, Machan brings his bat down and defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and a leg-slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to MacLeod, 1 run, fuller length delivery and a hint of shape away from middle, MacLeod shuffles across and tucks it past mid-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to MacLeod, 2 runs, tad fuller and well outside off, MacLeod gets well forward and drives it square through cover-point, the fielder at cover gives the chase and keeps them down to a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to MacLeod, 2 runs, back of a length and well outside off, MacLeod stands tall and punches it square on the off-side, the fielder at mid-off gives the chase and keeps them down to a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to MacLeod, 2 runs, Malinga attempts the slower yorker, turns out to be a low full-toss and on MacLeod's pads, clipped away behind square on the on-side for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to MacLeod, no run, short of a length and on MacLeod's pads, he gets inside the line and tucks it towards square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Mathews is off the field, not sure what's the reason]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Machan, no run, back of a length and just outside off, punched towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Machan, no run, on a good length and shaping away from outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Machan, 2 runs, nicely played by Machan, but that's poor fielding by Chameera at mid-on, this was pitched up and just outside off, Machan presents the full face of the bat on the drive, Chameera dives over the ball and allows a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Machan, no run, Kulasekara keeps it full and gets it to shape away from the left-hander, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Machan, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, Machan prods across and defends it towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place for Kulasekara]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Machan, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, Machan covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Nuwan Kulasekara, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Machan, 1 run, Malinga slips in the slower ball, but it turns out to be a wide full-toss, dabbed away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Machan, 2 runs, short and on the stumps, Machan swivels across on the pull, he didn't get hold of the shot, the ball drops well in front of the fielder running across from long leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Machan, no run, good short ball from Malinga, the line was just outside off as well, Machan does well to arch back, drops his gloves and sways away from the line]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Machan, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Machan presses forward and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Matt Machan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and a leg-slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Coetzer, <b>out</b> Caught&Bowled!! That's a dolly for Malinga! A duck for Coetzer, this was back of a length and on the stumps, Coetzer was surprised by the lack of pace on that, he was looking to work it towards the on-side, closed the face of the bat and hits it straight back at the bowler, pops back to the bowler for the simplest of chances. The in-form Coetzer departs, Scotland have lost an early wicket. <b>Coetzer c and b Malinga 0(2)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Malinga to Coetzer, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught&Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Coetzer, no run, on a good length and a hint of shape away from off, Coetzer backs away slightly and defends it towards point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Coetzer and MacLeod are at the crease. Coetzer is on strike. Malinga will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The openers are out in the middle.. Coetzer has been the best bet for Scotland and his 156 against Bangladesh oozed with class. On the other hand, Calum MacLeod has been short of runs. Malinga to open the attack for Sri Lanka. Two slips in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. It's a tough chase for Scotland. They have acquitted themselves well in this tournament so far but haven't had a positive result to show for it. With no pressure, this is another chance to show their class and ability..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dilshan:</b> "I want to carry on this form for the next few games. If I get a start, I try to bat as long as possible. I had a chat with Marvan (Atapattu) and coaching staff as well. Great experience with Kumar (Sangakkara), he is a great player, both together we have more than fifteen 100 plus partnerships in the last few years. He is supporting me in the middle. Hopefully, we can forge more partnerships in the middle. If I'm scoring runs like now, I will carry on for a few more years. I'm enjoying my cricket at the moment and we will see after the World Cup where I can end up my career."]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Scottish bowlers were taken to the cleaners, but they will at least be happy with how they came back at the end. Otherwise, things would have been far worse for them. Also, not to forget they had a mixed day in the field, dropping a few chances, while taking a few difficult ones. Rob Taylor and Richie Berrington were the pick of the bowlers. Even though they didn't take the majority of the wickets, they didn't let the Sri Lankan batsmen dictate terms when they were bowling. Apart from them, Davey took 3 wickets, Evans took 2 and Machan chipped in with 1. It is going to be very difficult for Scotland to chase this down, but who knows if there's a surprise in store for us. The pitch is flat and very good for batting. Take a break and join us in a short while for the run-chase.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Captain Mathews and Kusal Perera, who were new at the crease, never let the aggressive intent fade away as both of them kept going after the bowling. Sri Lanka managed 57/3 from the batting powerplay, but both of them didn't stop there. They kept going after the bowling before Kusal Perera fell for a 13-ball 24. Mathews carried on his show and hit Machan for 4 consecutive sixes to notch up the second fastest fifty of this World Cup. However, he also perished off the very next ball, trying to make it 5 sixes in a row. Since then, batters came and went as Sri Lanka kept pushing for more runs towards the fag end of the innings. However, they lost 4 wickets in a space of 10 runs and that helped Scotland pull things back. Kulasekara hit a few lusty blows at the end and Sri Lanka finished with 363, the highest total against Scotland in an ODI.]]></line><line><![CDATA[At one stage both of them were on 99, but Dilshan was the first one to reach the landmark as he registered his 22nd ODI ton, his 4th in World Cups as well. After that came the big moment as Sangakkara became the first cricketer to hit 4 successive ODI hundreds. He also became the first man to score 4 hundreds in a single edition of the World Cup. Both Sanga and Dilshan then decided to take the batting powerplay in the 35th over. Sri Lanka didn't get off to the best of starts in the powerplay as Dilshan holed out to mid-off in the first over itself. Sanga then took the onus of going big and took 24 runs off Evans' 7th over, where he hit him for a six and 4 fours. While trying to make the maximum of the field restrictions, both Mahela Jayawardene and Kumar Sangakkara perished off consecutive deliveries, leaving Sri Lanka at 245/4 at the end of the 37th over. Davey, who took both those wickets, overtook Boult and became the highest wicket-taker of the tournament.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sri Lanka didn't get off to the best of starts as Thirimanne went back early, trying to flash a drive against Evans. Dilshan was then joined by Sangakkara, who was chasing history, trying to become the first man to hit four consecutive tons in ODIs. Both the batsmen were then looking to stabilize the innings as they kept chipping away with singles, managing to put 46 on the board after 10 overs. After both Dilshan and Sanga got their eye in, both of them started dispatching the poor balls to the fence. The duo reached their fifties in quick succession and then decided to take the attack to the opposition, showing great footwork as they kept lofting the bowlers over the infield. The Scottish bowlers were not up to the task as both batsmen looked as if they were having a race between themselves so as to who reaches his hundred first.]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to N Kulasekara, no run, low full toss outside off, Kulasekara tries to drive through cover and misses, Cross standing up, fails to gather the ball and it ricochets off the gloves, then the keeper's pads and hits the stumps, but Kulasekara had gone nowhere. They don't refer it to the third umpire as Kulasekara was well in]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Dushmantha Chameera, 1 run, low full toss, outside off, driven straight to the fielder at long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Dushmantha Chameera, <b>FOUR</b>, makes room and Taylor can't get the yorker right, it's full and on the stumps, Chameera steers it wide of the short third man, inside the ring, well played and well executed too]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Dushmantha Chameera, 2 runs, pitched up outside off, bottom-handed drive to long-off, well-timed and it's two]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to N Kulasekara, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Kulasekara drives it straight to the fielder at cover, single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to N Kulasekara, no run, yorker outside off, Kulasekara fails to dig it out, Cross makes a good stop standing up to the stumps, the ball rolls towards square leg, they thought about a quick single, but decide against it in the end]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rob Taylor [9.0-0-38-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to N Kulasekara, 1 run, low full toss on the stumps, flicked to deep mid-wicket, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to N Kulasekara, <b>SIX</b>, half-volley on the stumps, Kulasekara presented the full face of the bat and played a copybook front foot loft, straight back over the bowler's head. Went all the way. Held the pose too - one for the cameramen to latch and get their lenses into action, click away now!]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to N Kulasekara, <b>FOUR</b>, that's what he was aiming for the last ball, makes room and goes inside-out, on a bent knee, all the fielders are inside the ring and Kulasekara made full use of that]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to N Kulasekara, no run, why did the square leg ump go upstairs? Not needed at all. A waste of time. Kulasekara hadn't moved anywhere, he backed away and missed the inside-out shot over cover, missed and Cross whipped the bails off, Kulasekara's feet were firmly planted inside the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Dushmantha Chameera, 1 run, low full toss outside off, wristed straight to the fielder at backward square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kyle Coetzer [4.0-0-27-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Good news. Berrington is back on his feet. That's heart-warming news from a Scottish point of view. He was in pain when he fell down, what do we have here? He is walking off the field with the physio. Gets a pat on the shoulder from someone, in the team management. The shoe ripped off while he was about to deliver the ball and made him land awkwardly on the left-ankle. After a bit of treatment, he is able to get up and walk off without showing any pain. Even manages a smile as he goes off]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to N Kulasekara, 1 run, <b>what has Berrington done here</b>? He is in pain and has landed awkwardly on his left-ankle. The shoe came off as he was about to deliver and he couldn't land properly. The ankle took a pounding and we have a slight break in play. The physio is out there, tending to the bowler. Kulasekara drove that to long-off, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[47.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dushmantha Chameera, no run, pitched up outside off, wristed straight to the fielder at mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dushmantha Chameera, 2 runs, now plays a good-looking shot, over mid-on, very full and he lofted it over the fielder, the fielder runs back and keeps it to two]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dushmantha Chameera, 2 runs, pitched up outside off, Chameera mishits the slice, but gets enough bat on that, to clear the off-side ring, the ball falls in no-man's land and that will be the first runs for Chameera in World Cups]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dushmantha Chameera, no run, back of a length outside off, Chameera goes on the back foot and wrists it to mid-on, wants a quick single, but the ball has gone straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[Have to give it to Mommsen. He has a slip now. Slip! For Chameera. In the 48th over. The score is 338 and he has backed his bowler.]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dushmantha Chameera, no run, short and wide outside off, Chameera tries to slash and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to N Kulasekara, 1 run, yorker length on middle and leg, clipped to fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to N Kulasekara, 1 run, full outside off, Kulasekara plays a square drive, will keep strike too]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dushmantha Chameera, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Malinga, <b>out</b> Caught by M A Leask!! Now he can smile. Slower one outside off, Malinga wanted to go over cover, but the weight was on the back foot. Sliced it completely, point ran back and then hung on. It was in the air for a good while, which made the catch easier, despite the fielder having to run back and circle around the ball. <b>Malinga c M A Leask b Berrington 1(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Berrington to Malinga, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to N Kulasekara, 1 run, that is a <b>tough chance, but will go down as a drop.</b> Low full toss, Kulasekara sliced the drive, but hit it hard, and to Berrington's left, the bowler was in his followthrough, reacted, got both hands, but couldn't cling on. Disappointment for Berrington]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Malinga, 1 run, tries to slap through the off-side, but drags it to mid-off, quick single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Malinga, no run, the off-cutter from Berrington, stops on Malinga, who was early into the cut, the inside edge runs to short mid-wicket, no chance of a single even as the batsmen contemplated that thought]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to N Kulasekara, 1 run, yorker length outside off, Kulasekara opens the face of the bat and squeezes it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[45.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to N Kulasekara, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Kulasekara drives it to extra cover, retains the strike with that run]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to N Kulasekara, no run, looked like the cutter, it nips back in and beats Kulasekara's attempted punch through the off-side, beats the inside edge and taken on the bounce by the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to N Kulasekara, <b>wide</b>, down leg, called wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to S Prasanna, <b>out</b> Caught by Coleman!! Despite a couple of drops in the field, Scotland have caught well. Coleman coming from deep mid-wicket and hanging onto a low chance. His third catch of the innings. Prasanna was hurried on the pull and top-edged it as he rocked back to essay the shot, it seemed to be falling short, but Coleman had the plot of the ball tracked and came forward and took it. Evans gets his second wicket. <b>S Prasanna c Coleman b Alasdair Evans 3(5)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Alasdair Evans to S Prasanna, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to N Kulasekara, leg byes, 1 run, down leg, on a short of length, Kulasekara went for the pull, but didn't connect, off the thigh pad and it's a leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to N Kulasekara, no run, short of length outside off, punched back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to S Prasanna, 1 run, back of a length outside off, Prasanna gets inside the line and nudges it to backward square leg, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Alasdair Evans [8.0-0-64-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to N Kulasekara, no run, yorker length outside off, Kulasekara digs it out and the inside edge rolls back onto the pads, the ball stays to the right of Kulasekara, the keeper takes it]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to S Prasanna, 1 run, full and outside off, pushed to cover-point, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Nuwan Kulasekara, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to T Perera, <b>out</b> Caught by Coleman!! Scotland are taking wickets, despite leaking runs. Typical Perera slog, to leg, after clearing his front leg, these are big boundaries and Perera finds the man placed at deep square leg, who takes another well-judged catch to his left. The bowler followed the path of the ball and then clapped the fielder for taking it. It was taken with fingers pointed upwards. <b>T Perera c Coleman b Berrington 7(11)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Berrington to T Perera, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to S Prasanna, 1 run, pitched up outside off, pushed to extra cover, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to S Prasanna, no run, full outside off, Prasanna plays and misses, the keeper takes it standing up]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to T Perera, 1 run, yorker length on the stumps, Perera digs it out past the diving right-hand of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Richie Berrington [4.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Seekkuge Prasanna, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Mathews, <b>out</b> Caught by Coleman!! That is a good catch at the edge of the rope by the fielder. Held his composure and took it above his head. Mathews went for more glory, took on the full toss and hit it well, but hit it a bit too flat for one's liking, he didn't get the required elevation on the hit and it was caught by the fielder at deep mid-wicket. The bowler must have thought it was another six when the ball went off the bat, but relief in the end. The ball was going over the head of the fielder, who arched backwards and took it even as he was losing balance. Checked his footing after taking the catch and he was inside the field of play. That is a big wicket, too for Mathews could've hurt Scotland no end. <b>Mathews c Coleman b Machan 51(21) [4s-1 6s-6]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Machan to Mathews, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Mathews, <b>SIX</b>, this is buffet bowling from Machan and Mathews brings up his <b>fifty</b>. It was floated up on middle and leg, Mathews slogs it high and over cow corner, the fielder watches it sail over his head. He is doing heavy damage here, Mathews]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Mathews, <b>SIX</b>, Machan goes over the wicket, but the result remains the same. Low full toss on off, Mathews gets his front foot out of the way, he slugs it over deep mid-wicket, for the third six in a row. Good catch in the crowd]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Mathews, <b>SIX</b>, this is poor bowling from Machan, full toss on middle and leg, Mathews hoicks it over deep mid-wicket, that is too easy for the Sri Lankan skipper]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Mathews, <b>SIX</b>, monster hit! Machan stays round the wicket for Mathews, fires it full and on leg-stump, Mathews clears his front leg and heaves it over deep mid-wicket, the ball had plenty of air time, but cleared the rope easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to T Perera, 1 run, tossed up around off, Perera leans forward and nudges it wide of mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to T Perera, 1 run, in the air and just in front of long-off, running in and to his right, Perera looking to heave that in the air, and mistimed that completely. Luckily he got away]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Mathews, 1 run, full and on the stumps, flicked to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to T Perera, 1 run, yorker length on the stumps, good bowling that, dug out to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Mathews, 1 run, Mathews wrists it wide of long-on for another single]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to T Perera, 1 run, full on the stumps, slogged straight to the fielder at deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Mathews, 1 run, on the stumps, flicked to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to T Perera, no run, yorker length on off, dug out in front of point, Perera wants a quick single, but is sent back by Mathews]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to T Perera, no run, shortish on middle, backs away and cuts straight to the fielder at cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Mathews, 1 run, another <b>dropped catch.</b> Mathews is early into the flick, leading edge was found, Machan is late to react and the ball bursts through his hands, it was coming straight at his face and it went away, so Scotland let themselves down in the field as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Mathews, 2 runs, that's <b>dropped by Coleman at deep mid-wicket.</b> Slogged high in the air, deep mid-wicket runs forward and tries to take it, but he fails to take it. That should've been taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to T Perera, 1 run, down leg, flicked to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to T Perera, no run, angling in on middle, defended to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Matt Machan [2.0-0-17-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to T Perera, 1 run, full outside off, driven to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Mathews, 1 run, yorker length on the stumps, dug out to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Thisara Perera, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to K Perera, <b>out</b> Caught by MacLeod!! Terrific running catch to his right at long-on. Perera's bat turned as he went for the big hit over long-on, that skewed all timing on the shot, the ball seemed to be falling in no-man's land, but MacLeod running across, took it and then tumbled to the turf. He gets up and has a smile on his face before being congratulated by his mates. <b>K Perera c MacLeod b Rob Taylor 24(13) [4s-2 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rob Taylor to K Perera, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to K Perera, no run, yorker length outside off, Perera digs it out and it's fielded by Taylor diving to his right, he appeals in hope, but clearly it bounced before being fielded by him]]></line><line><![CDATA[The umpires are checking for a possible C&B. But they are fine with it, as they reckon that it's a bump ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to K Perera, <b>SIX</b>, the bottom-hand comes into play as he flicks this over square leg, the fielder was running to his left and trying to catch, but the ball eluded his outstretched left-hand, Perera flicking ala Sanath with those strong wrists of his and gets six]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Mathews, 1 run, driven wide of cover, where the fielder dives to his right and keeps it to a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rob Taylor [7.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to K Perera, no run, wants another piece of Evans, but cannot get it away, inside-edges the big hit to leg, onto his thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to K Perera, <b>wide</b>, the slower ball, goes wrong, down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to K Perera, <b>FOUR</b>, just over the leaping cover. Full toss on off, Perera sliced the chip and got away, the fast outfield doing the rest. Evans is a very disappointed man]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to K Perera, <b>SIX</b>, Perera is a fine striker of the cricket ball and he puts this back of a length delivery away over square leg, rocked back and muscled it flat. A spectator tries to catch it to his left, but fails to do so]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Mathews, 1 run, full and on the stumps, clipped uppishly to deep mid-wicket, fielded on the bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to K Perera, 1 run, back of a length on middle, clipped to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Mathews, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Mathews defends to point and takes a comfortable single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Alasdair Evans [7.0-0-50-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The batting powerplay has produced <b>57 runs for three wickets</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to K Perera, no run, Perera eyes another pull, but doesn't get any bat on the shot, dug in short and Davey ends the over with a dot]]></line><line><![CDATA[Amidst all the hoopla and glitz surrounding Sanga's achievement, <b>Davey is now the leading wicket-taker</b> in this tournament. He has 14 wickets currently and has just eclipsed Boult to go top]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Mathews, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Mathews drives to cover, and takes on the arm of Machan and beats the throw, makes it home]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Mathews, no run, pitched up on the stumps, eased to that fielder at mid-on again]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Mathews, no run, low full toss, Mathews charges out and drives, no timing on that and the ball goes straight to the fielder at mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to K Perera, 1 run, short and down leg, Perera gets inside the line to pull to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to K Perera, <b>FOUR</b>, Perera latches on to a short and wide delivery outside off, cracks it over cover, the width was there and Perera didn't miss out]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Mathews, <b>SIX</b>, make that 16 off the last three balls. Leask is tossing it up and Mathews won't let go. Gets forward and muscles it flat over deep mid-wicket, just too much power packed into that bottom-hand of Mathews]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Mathews, <b>FOUR</b>, Mathews is in the mood to hit today. Shows off his skill by reverse sweeping over point. Saw the leg stump line and lifted it over the fielder. All too easy now]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Mathews, <b>SIX</b>, well-caught in the crowd at deep backward square leg, by a senior citizen. Mathews just knelt down and nonchalantly swept a middle stump delivery over backward square leg, where it was held with both hands by a man in the stands]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Mathews, no run, tucked off the back foot to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place now for Leask as he comes round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to K Perera, 1 run, shortish outside off, cut down to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to K Perera, no run, tossed up on the stumps, from round the wicket, Perera pushes it back to Leask]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Michael Leask [6.0-0-46-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to K Perera, 1 run, the hat-trick ball is nudged down to fine leg as Perera gets off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kushal Janith Perera, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Sangakkara, <b>out</b> Caught by Matthew Cross!! <b>Davey is on a hat-trick now</b>. He has got the big wicket of Sangakkara. Well bowled actually by Davey, saw Sangakkara charging and bowled it full and wide outside off, Sangakkara had to reach out to drive and edged the shot behind, easy take for Cross. Sangakkara walks off, without even waiting for the umpire's decision. A few claps here and there from the sparse crowd. <b>Sangakkara c Matthew Cross b Davey 124(95) [4s-13 6s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Davey to Sangakkara, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Angelo Mathews, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to M Jayawardene, <b>out</b> Caught by MacLeod!! Davey strikes again in the powerplay. Some respite for the Scots. It was a slower delivery from Davey, Jayawardene came down the track and was looking to go over mid-off, but completely mistimed it, the skier is easily held at mid-off. <b>M Jayawardene c MacLeod b Davey 2(6)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Davey to M Jayawardene, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to M Jayawardene, no run, back of a length outside off, dabbed straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Sangakkara, leg byes, 1 run, shuffles across and gets outside the line of off, fired in full and he misses the flick, off the pad and they take a leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Sangakkara, no run, Sangakkara completely mistimes the big cover drive, off the inside half back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Sangakkara, <b>wide</b>, way outside off, wide called]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Sangakkara, 1 run, no he can't! Evans has a wry smile on his face after escaping the ignominy of suffering all boundaries in the over. Including the wide as well. Evans goes over the wicket and bowls a low full toss, Sangakkara was early into the paddle, and since it was well outside off, he couldn't get it past the short fine fielder, the fielder was moving backwards anticipating the shot, but it went to his right and he got there to field eventually. So Sangakkara misses out]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, Sangakkara is waiting to play that stroke and gets one more boundary. Evans bowls that down leg and slower, Sangakkara just played the paddle, but lifted it over short fine inside the ring, the ball beats the chasing fielder. Already <b>23</b> off the over. One more ball to come, can Sangakkara do it?]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Sangakkara, <b>wide</b>, the pressure tells on Evans, who bowls this well down leg, even then Sangakkara wants to paddle that, but can't reach it]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, again over the off-side field. Backs away and creates the room, waits for it and then smashes this over point, who was inside the ring, the ball runs away and it's all boundaries this over. Can Sangakkara emulate Dilshan? who did it the other day]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, what does Sangakkara do now? Manipulates the field by shuffling across to off and takes the full toss, paddles it over short fine, inside the ring, another boundary. What will Evans do now?]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now a deep point is placed]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, all the fielders are in on the off-side and Sangakkara will go over there once more. Makes room and then goes down on a bent knee, to go uppishly over cover. A field change is required I feel]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Sangakkara, <b>SIX</b>, now Sangakkara will help himself. The slower cutting short delivery, Sangakkara skips out, makes room and then carves the bowler over point, the ball thuds into the advertising boards on the full. Evans just shrugs his shoulders and puffs his cheeks out, before walking back to his mark]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Alasdair Evans [6.0-0-26-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to M Jayawardene, no run, back of a length on off, defended. End of a successful and good over from Davey]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to M Jayawardene, no run, Jayawardene pre-meditates the stroke and misses out. Skips out to the bowler and the bowler slips in the slower cutting short delivery, Jayawardene tries to adjust and then ramp it past the keeper, but the ball bounces over his bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to M Jayawardene, no run, back of a length outside off, defended to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to M Jayawardene, 2 runs, Jayawardene is early into the drive and lobs it over cover, and wide of the fielder, is off the mark with that couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mahela Jayawardene, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, <b>out</b> Caught by MacLeod!! Dilshan is gone, trying to clear mid-off. Davey did well to follow Dilshan as he charged down, slipped it in towards Dilshan who mishit the loft, MacLeod at mid-off, leapt and took it on the second attempt. <b>Dilshan c MacLeod b Davey 104(99) [4s-10 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Davey to Dilshan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, sliced away. Full and outside off, Dilshan threw the bat at that and got it in the gap, went hard and got it between short third and backward point, races away]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>The batting powerplay</b> is on now, as if the Scots didn't have anything else to worry about]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, <b>wide</b>, Davey slips one down leg, Dilshan was looking for the Dilscoop but it was well wide of him]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Josh Davey [5.0-0-48-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Sangakkara, 2 runs, <b>Sangaaaaaaaaaa! What.A.Playa! The first man ever in ODI history to make four tons in a row.</b> Many have done it thrice. But no-one till today has got to that peak. What's more. He has done it in a World Cup. At the age of 37. In his last World Cup. Is there a better all-round player than this man in the world currently? Only AB de Villiers can lay claim to that title. Gets there with a steer to third man and takes a couple. Look at that celebration from him. No aggro, no brashness, no over-the-top shouting, no show of emotion. Just a calm face, removes the helmet and then raises the bat. Has a word with Dilshan. That's how to do it - if he wants to, he could bat on for the next three, four years - such is the form he is in at the moment. It was inevitable, the moment he came out to bat today against Scotland, that the record would be broken, without any disrespect shown to the Scots. Sanga is too good a player to miss out on such a golden chance to break a record that has stood there for a long time]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Dilshan, 1 run, <b>fourth WC hundred for Dilshan!</b> 22nd overall for Dilshan. Gets there with a nudge to fine leg. A look at the heavens and then a raise of the bat. Sanath applauds]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Sangakkara, 1 run, Mommsen from cover hits direct and gives away an extra run, off the ricochet. Sangakkara drove it on the bounce to him at cover and he saw Dilshan out of his crease, shied and hit, but Dilshan had got back. The ball runs away and they take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Dilshan, 1 run, back of a length outside off, cut square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Sangakkara, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Sangakkara gets forward and drives well, straight to the fielder at sweeper cover though]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, that is poor, poor bowling. Short and down leg, nothing ball with no-one behind square, on the fence, Sangakkara just had to get it in the gap and he helped that offering on its way, beating backward square inside the ring]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Dilshan, no run, Rob Taylor is doing well, on a length and on the stumps, defended to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Sangakkara, 1 run, low full toss, driven straight to the fielder at long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Sangakkara, no run, back of a length on off, Sangakkara pushes towards point and wants a run, not there reckons Dilshan]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Sangakkara, no run, Sangakkara was eyeing the big hit over mid-wicket, Rob Taylor cramped him for room, by bowling it very full and on the stumps, dragged to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Dilshan, 1 run, back of a length outside off, punched to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Dilshan, no run, short of length outside off, cut straight to the fielder at point. May have been a change of pace as well]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rob Taylor [6.0-0-21-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, Sangakkara is peppering the off-side field today. He has taken a particular liking to the cover region. Goes over there once more, the width was there and he freed his arms to play an airy cover drive, sweeper had no chance. Moves into the nineties]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Sangakkara, no run, pushes it straight to the fielder at point and looks for a single, Dilshan sends Sangakkara back]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Sangakkara, no run, driven sweetly, but cover dives to his left and stops a certain boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Dilshan, 1 run, back of a length outside off, punched to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Dilshan, no run, Dilshan went too hard at the cover drive, another inside edge, rolls to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Dilshan, 2 runs, so nearly dragged on. Dilshan is late on the attempted dab to the off-side, the ball comes on slowly and takes the inside edge, wide of the leg stump and they take a couple]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kyle Coetzer [2.0-0-10-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, did that carry to MacLeod at mid-wicket? Sangakkara's eyes lit up as he saw the high full toss outside off, swung across the line and didn't hit it as well as he would've liked. The bat turned as he hit it, MacLeod at mid-wicket dived full length to his left and just about got a hand on it, couldn't grasp it and shows off his disappointment, the ball runs away to the fence, beating deep mid-wicket. That has to go down as <b>a drop chance.</b> How much will Scotland pay for that miss?]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Sangakkara, <b>wide</b>, Machan slips down leg, wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Sangakkara, no run, pushed off the front foot to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Sangakkara, <b>SIX</b>, so easy for Sangakkara. He sees the tossed up delivery outside off, kneels down and then slog-sweeps way over deep mid-wicket. There are no mishits or mistimes from Sangakkara when he is playing like this. He serenely moves onto 84 now]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Dilshan, 1 run, Dilshan gently works another single through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Sangakkara, 1 run, Sangakkara's weight is back as he lofts over cover's leap, single to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Dilshan, 1 run, on off and middle, Dilshan gets forward and flicks to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, 1 run, short and wide outside off, cut to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Sangakkara, 1 run, full and on the pads, flicked to deep square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, Sangakkara hits the gap once more. Has had enough of blocking and prodding. Waltzes down and then goes inside out, wanted to go towards deep cover, but manages to beat long-off to his right, the fielder didn't dive and the ball beat him to the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Sangakkara, no run, Leask is holding it back a little, Sangakkara flicks and checks his shot, the ball once again doesn't carry to short mid-wicket. Went uppishly but safe]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Sangakkara, no run, stops on Sangakkara who looks to defend, the ball goes uppishly, but doesn't carry to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, 1 run, shortish and turning in, Dilshan rocks back and punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Sangakkara, no run, well bowled by Machan, saw Sangakkara advancing and fired it down on the pads, Sangakkara fails to flick and the ball hits the pads, rolls away to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Dilshan, 1 run, on a length and on the stumps, wristed off the back foot to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Dilshan, no run, short and wide outside off, Dilshan rocks back and cuts, but cover-point dives to his left and saves a certain boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Sangakkara, 1 run, shortish and punched off the back foot wide of short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Sangakkara, no run, Sangakkara turns it to Machan's left, both batsmen thought about a single and took a step forward each, but then Sangakkara sends Dilshan back as he sees the bowler move swiftly towards the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Machan to Dilshan, 1 run, Dilshan comes down the track and drives to mid-off's right, good stop that kept it to a single. Machan bowled that from round the wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Matt Machan, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Sangakkara, no run, driven back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Sangakkara, <b>SIX</b>, Sangakkara plays another of those brilliant strokes of his. So eye-catching and pleasing to the eye. Down the track, makes room and then goes over cover, inside out, hit superbly and deliberately in the air, it carries all the way, just, but that will do]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, 1 run, on the middle and leg line, swept away to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[Leask is coming from round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Sangakkara, 1 run, Sangakkara gets forward and drives to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, 3 runs, Evans does well now to save a run, it was paddled past the diving short fine fielder, Evans came across and slid to pull it back, thereby saving a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, no run, tossed up outside off, pushed to cover off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Sangakkara, 2 runs, excellent running from Dilshan and Sangakkara applauds that effort from his partner. Driven to long-on's right, it was Dilshan who spotted that the fielder was a bit lax, took him on and came back]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Sangakkara, 2 runs, shortish and Sangakkara cracks the cut square of the wicket, placed wide of the sweeper and it's a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Sangakkara, no run, punched straight back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now the keeper is up to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Sangakkara, <b>SIX</b>, Sangakkara wants to join in the fun too. From round the wicket by Berrington, Sangakkara comes down the track and then goes through with the lofted shot, connected beautifully and it went a long way over long-on. Remember these aren't short boundaries at this ground, but Sangakkara cleared long-on comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Dilshan, 1 run, now gets forward and drives the full ball to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, cracking cut shot! Short and wide and Dilshan didn't miss out. Rocked back and smashed the shot past the diving point fielder, quickly Dilshan has raced to 83 after a flurry of boundaries]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Richie Berrington [3.0-0-8-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Sangakkara, no run, floated up on off, Sangakkara turns it gently to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, fantastic shot! Great use of the feet. Sangakkara was just eyeing that gap. He shimmies down the track, makes a bit of room and lofts it inside out over extra cover, the ball whistles to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, 1 run, crouches low and nudges it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Sangakkara, 1 run, Sangakkara just keeps piling it on, he notches up his <b>94th ODI fifty</b>. Another hundred on the cards? Flighted delivery outside off, Sangakkara drives it to deep extra cover and gets to the landmark]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, 1 run, short and down leg, Dilshan pulls it to short fine leg, the fielder dives to his right and saves a certain boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Sangakkara, 1 run, flighted on off, Sangakkara drives it to the left of the bowler, Leask dives and parries it wide of the mid-wicket fielder]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Michael Leask [3.0-0-20-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, no run, low full toss around off, the bat turns in Dilshan's hands and he mistimes it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, <b>SIX</b>, this time Dilshan manages to clear the fence. Davey is taking a pasting here. He is too predictable, keeps it on a length, Dilshan once more goes on his knee and hoicks it over deep backward square, the ball carried over the ropes this time.]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, this is excellent batting, good length ball just outside off, Dilshan shuffles across, bends his front knee and sweeps it behind square, the ball was timed superbly as it races across to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, fabulous shot! It was the off-cutter from Davey, Dilshan spotted it early, he kneels down and heaves it behind square, the ball bounces once before reaching the fence. Another <b>100-run stand</b> between these two]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Sangakkara, 1 run, short and well wide of off, Sangakkara cuts it to deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Sangakkara, no run, back of a length around off, Sangakkara punches it to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, <b>2 wides</b>, slower delivery which is slipped down leg, Cross does well to get a glove and limit it to a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Cross is standing up to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Sangakkara, no run, fuller and angling in, Sangakkara drives off the inner part, no chance for the run as mid-on swoops in quickly]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Sangakkara, no run, short of length on off, defended down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[Switches to round the wicket..]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dilshan, 1 run, fraction short, Dilshan waits in the crease and late cuts it to square third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dilshan, no run, back of a length and tucks the batsman, Dilshan turns it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Sangakkara, 1 run, on a length outside off, Sangakkara square drives it past the diving backward point fielder, sweeper mops up in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Sangakkara, no run, pitched up just outside off, Sangakkara middles the drive and picks out mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, 2 runs, too straight, on middle and leg, Dilshan flicks it to deep backward square leg, Leask runs to his right from deep square and tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Sangakkara, 1 run, fuller and just outside off, Sangakkara eases the drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, 1 run, back of a length on off and middle, Dilshan tucks in front of square on the leg-side, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, no run, the stumps at the non-striker's end saves a couple of runs for Scotland. Full and on off, Dilshan drives it gun barrel straight, ball hits timber and deflects to mid-wicket, Mommsen makes a slight fumble but the duo don't risk a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Sangakkara, 1 run, on a length just outside off, Sangakkara comes well forward and drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, Sangakkara might just be shifting gears. He charges Davey and lofts it straight over the bowler's head, didn't middle it but had got enough wood for the ball to roll away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Josh Davey [3.0-0-22-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sangakkara is the <b>first Sri Lankan</b> player to score 400+ runs in two World Cups. He made <b>465 runs in the 2011 edition</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dilshan, no run, touch short, Dilshan stays on leg-stump and looks to flash the cut, it is too close to the body and the ball beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dilshan, no run, fuller and just outside off, driven straight to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Sangakkara, 1 run, short of length on off, Sangakkara tucks it behind square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Sangakkara, no run, fullish and around off, Sangakkara punches off the front foot and finds mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dilshan, 1 run, back of a length just outside off, Dilshan steers it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dilshan, no run, cramps the batsman for room with the short of length delivery, Dilshan stays leg-side of the ball and knocks it in front of cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Alasdair Evans [4.0-0-22-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Sangakkara, no run, good length ball around off, Sangakkara bunts it in front of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Dilshan, 1 run, again, short and width on offer, Dilshan doesn't time the cut as he picks out the sweeper cover fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Sangakkara, 1 run, shortens the length around off, Sangakkara punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Sangakkara, no run, guides the back of a length towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, poor delivery and Sangakkara capitalises on it. Down leg, he bends his right knee and helps it on the way to the fence, the fine leg fielder was very square and had no chance of stopping that]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Dilshan, 1 run, short and outside off, Dilshan cracks the cut square of the wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, 1 run, wrists it between the bowler and short mid-wicket, sharp single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, 2 runs, Dilshan leans forward and plays this with soft hands in front of square, the fielder had a long way to come in and that allowed the duo to come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, 2 runs, Cross almost pulled off a stunner, flighted around off, Dilshan shuffles across, kneels down and paddles it fine, Cross moves to his left and the ball just about evades his outstretched left hand]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Sangakkara, 1 run, drops it short outside off, Sangakkara cuts it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, 1 run, Leask goes round the wicket, slides it onto the pads, nurdled to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Sangakkara, 1 run, nice floaty off-break outside off, Sangakkara drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Dilshan, no run, fuller and around off, Dilshan pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Dilshan, no run, touch short and outside off, Dilshan misses out on the cut shot. He was undone by the extra bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Sangakkara, 1 run, tucked away in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Sangakkara, no run, <b>almost dragged on!</b> Good length ball on off, Sangakkara defends off the inside part and the ball drops near his feet, he didn't know where the ball was and he was taking off for the single, but just about saw the ball and made it in as Cross moved forward and whipped the bails off]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Dilshan, 1 run, Dilshan brings up another World Cup <b>fifty</b>. It is his third fifty plus score in this World Cup. Short and outside off, Dilshan cuts it to sweeper cover. Jayasuriya and Arnold were seen applauding from the stands]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coetzer to Sangakkara, 1 run, full and on the stumps, Sangakkara punches it to mid-on and takes off immediately. Got the run easily even as the throw comes to his end]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kyle Coetzer, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks are on the field now</b>. Scotland bowlers started by bowling tight line and lengths. That got the better of Thirimanne as he was tied down and finally nicked off. Since then, the experienced duo have gone about things with ease. They are laying the foundation for themselves to launch in the second half of the innings. Scotland need a couple of quick wickets, if they have to restrict Sri Lanka somehwere close to 300.]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, Leask goes over the wicket, pushes it through just outside off, Dilshan comes forward, opens the bat face at the last second and steers it to third man, the ball had enough pace to reach the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Sangakkara, 1 run, short and outside off, Sangakkara cuts to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Sangakkara, no run, slower through the air, Sangakkara was deceived in the flight, he checks his shot and the ball lobs up and drops well in front of the cover fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, 1 run, stays low, rolls his wrists and works it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Sangakkara, 1 run, goes straight on, Sangakkara plays for the turn and the ball goes off the inside half to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, 1 run, pushed across the batsman from round the wicket, Dilshan cuts it to backward point, Coetzer fumbles and the batsmen steal a run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Dilshan, 1 run, short of length on off, Dilshan wrists it to mid-on for a single. Good over from Berrington, just the 1 run from it.]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Dilshan, no run, fuller and outside off, Dilshan drives and picks Machan at cover, he dives to the left to stop the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Dilshan, no run, back of a length around off, Dilshan cuts it to point, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Dilshan, no run, low full toss outside off, Dilshan drives it past the diving cover fielder, he takes a couple of steps out of the crease, Sangakkara responds and was halfway down the wicket before being sent back, the fielder from mid-off doesn't throw the ball and Sanga makes it in comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Dilshan, no run, back of a length on off, Dilshan knocks it to mid-on, he wanted the run but Berrington got across and made sure they don't go through]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Dilshan, no run, fullish and just outside off, Dilshan drives and finds mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, 1 run, tossed up on the leg-stump, Dilshan nurdles it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, 2 runs, gets inside the line and glances it to the left of the leg slip fielder for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, no run, floated up on off, Dilshan leans forward and works it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, no run, not all that short, Dilshan makes room and fails to connect with the cut]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Dilshan, no run, flighted on middle, Dilshan tucks it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[A leg slip in place for Dilshan]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M A Leask to Sangakkara, 1 run, tossed up around off, Sangakkara pushes it to the left of backward point, sets off the for the single, Dilshan waits for the ball to go past the fielder]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Michael Leask, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place for the offie..]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place for the offie..]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Sangakkara, 1 run, full toss outside off, Sangakkara misses out, he punches it to the right of mid-off, for only a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[The keeper is up to the stumps now..]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Dilshan, 1 run, full on middle and leg, Dilshan nudges it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Dilshan, no run, drifts onto leg-stump, Dilshan can't lay bat on the flick, is rapped on the pads, but the ball was sneaking down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Dilshan, no run, fuller and on off, Dilshan wrists it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Sangakkara, 1 run, <b>fifty </b>partnership between the duo, pitched up outside off, Sangakkara drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Sangakkara, 2 runs, that is superb running from these two veterans, Sangakkara plays it with soft hands and nurdles it behind square on the leg-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Sangakkara, 1 run, easily done, flicked in front of square for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, 1 run, back of a length around off, Dilshan eases it off the back foot to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, no run, change of pace from Davey, Dilshan watches it carefully and knocks it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, no run, good length ball on off, defended to mid-off with a straightish bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Sangakkara, 1 run, angled across off, Sangakkara opens the bat face and drives it to square third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Sangakkara, <b>wide</b>, sprays it down leg, Sangakkara doesn't get bat on that and Illingworth signals wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, 1 run, drifts onto the pads, clipped away to deep backward square leg, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Sangakkara, no run, back of a length close to off, Sangakkara taps it in front of backward point, shouts "no, no, no" for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Sangakkara, no run, full and on off, it looked like an off-cutter, Sangakkara drives it back to the bowler, Berrington fires the throw back and Sanga was diving back into the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Dilshan, 1 run, short and outside off, Dilshan cracks the cut towards backward point, MacLeod dives to his left and parries it to third man. He saved a certain boundary there]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Sangakkara, 1 run, on off and middle, Sangakkara shuffles across slightly and clips it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Sangakkara, no run, wicket-to-wicket, Sangakkara defends to the left of Berrington]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Berrington to Sangakkara, no run, starts from round the wicket, angles it in, Sangakkara wrists it to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Richie Berrington, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, no run, fullish on off and middle, Dilshan pushes it to short mid-wicket, who fires a throw at the bowler's end even though Sangakkara was in the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, <b>wide</b>, splays it down the leg-side, wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Sangakkara, 1 run, on the pads, Sangakkara glances it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, 1 run, drifts onto middle and leg, Dilshan flicks it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, no run, pulls the length back, Dilshan stays back and knocks it to point, shouts a loud "no" for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, Davey is just not getting his line and length right against Dilshan. This was full and outside off, Dilshan drives it on-the-up through extra cover, the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, no run, pitched up on off, Dilshan drives down the wicket, Davey sticks his right hand out and deflects it to mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Dilshan, 1 run, low full toss on off, Dilshan drives it gently to mid-off, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Dilshan, no run, slightly short and on off, Dilshan moves to the leg-side and bunts it in front of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Sangakkara, 1 run, back of a length on off, Sangakkara works it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Sangakkara, 2 runs, too straight from Taylor, Sangakkara leans forward and tucks it behind square on the leg-side for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, poor effort from Coetzer at mid-on. It was full and on off, Sangakkara drills it hard and to the right of mid-on, Coetzer gets across and allows the ball to burst through his hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Sangakkara, no run, good length ball around off, Sangakkara defends off the inner part to the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, no run, much better from Davey, close to the off-stump, no width for the batsman to free his arms, defended to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! It was a half volley alright, but still needed to be put away. Dilshan waits for it to arrive and drives it to the left of mid-off, the fielder gives chase only to come second]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, no run, on a length close to off, Dilshan presses forward and knocks it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, full and slanting into the stumps, Dilshan drives it past Sangakkara, beats mid-on to his left and the ball races away to the fence. It was all timing from the Sri Lankan opener]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, no run, good length ball, Dilshan comes half-forward and pushes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Davey to Dilshan, 2 runs, starts with a straight one, on middle stump, Dilshan leans forward and flicks it through the vacant mid-wicket region]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Josh Davey, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Dilshan, 1 run, on a length just outside off, Dilshan pushes it to mid-off, for a single. Easily done as the fielder was right on the edge of the circle]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Dilshan, no run, back of a length around off, Dilshan mistimes the cut to cover, where the fielder dives to his left and stops the ball. It was too close to the off-stump for Dilshan to be playing the cut]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Sangakkara, 3 runs, full and outside off, Sangakkara goes for the drive, he was not to the pitch, the ball takes the outside half and flies over the infield on the off-side, Berrington gives chase, dives full length and hauls it in. Saved a run there]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Sangakkara, no run, back of a length on off, Sangakkara turns it with a roll of the wrist to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Sangakkara, no run, Sangakkara comes forward and push-drives it to mid-off, the ball hit the higher part of the bat and hence no timing on that]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Sangakkara, no run, good length ball on off, Sangakkara presses it to mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dilshan, no run, shortens the length, Dilshan stays in the crease and guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dilshan, no run, pitched up on the fourth stump line, Dilshan drives it slightly uppishly, but well in front of mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Sangakkara, 1 run, full and on off, Sangakkara closes the bat face early on the flick, the leading edge rolls to the left of mid-off, calls for the run and gets it easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Sangakkara, no run, good length ball close to off, Sangakkara pushes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Sangakkara, no run, back of a length around off, Sangakkara gets back and across, pats it in front of point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, superb shot! Fullish and outside off, Sangakkara comes well forward, bends his left knee and drives it beautifully through extra cover, Machan gives up the chase halfway through]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Sangakkara, 1 run, good early call for the single and both batsmen make it comfortably, wrists it between mid-wicket and mid-on, scampers through for a quick single. Sangakkara shows the thumbs up to Dilshan after completing the run]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Sangakkara, no run, drags the length slightly back, Sangakkara is half-forward, defending back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Sangakkara, no run, good length ball around off, Sangakkara taps it off the front foot to the right of Taylor]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Sangakkara, no run, again, Taylor probes away around the off-stump, Sangakkara presses forward and knocks it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Sangakkara, no run, on a length close to off, Sangakkara presents a straight bat and blocks it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Sangakkara, no run, good length ball on off, defended to mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dilshan, 2 runs, slanting in on middle and leg, Dilshan leans forward and tucks it to deep backward square leg for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dilshan, no run, back of a length outside off, Dilshan throws everything at it, but is nowhere close to making contact]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Sangakkara, 3 runs, gets off the mark in typical Sanga style, full and around off, gets a good stride forward and drives it past the diving mid-off, he didn't time it well enough as the ball slowed down]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kumar Sangakkara, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Thirimanne, <b>out</b> Caught by Mommsen!! Evans ends Thirimanne's stay. He never looked comfortable at the crease. And the pressure of the dot balls was getting to him. Full and outside off, teases the batsman to go for it, Thirimanne drives with no footwork, the outside edge flies to second slip, Mommsen takes a good catch. <b>Thirimanne c Mommsen b Alasdair Evans 4(21)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Alasdair Evans to Thirimanne, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dilshan, 1 run, tries to repeat the previous shot, it was on the off-stump this time, Dilshan mistimes it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, Dilshan is quick to pounce on that, it was not all that short, but Dilshan got into position quickly and pulled it square of the wicket to pick up his second boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Thirimanne, no run, touch short and just outside off, Thirimanne has a late poke at that, the ball beats the outside edge. In fact, he was looking to run it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Thirimanne, no run, again, close to off-stump, Thirimanne presses forward and defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Thirimanne, no run, Taylor is not giving away anything, back of a length on off, Thirimanne stays back and knocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Thirimanne, no run, Thirimanne comes on the front foot and defends the full delivery to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Thirimanne, no run, full and on off, Thirimanne goes for the loft through the line, mistimes it completely as it goes on the bounce to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Dilshan, 1 run, back of a length on off, Dilshan arches back and steers it to square third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Thirimanne, no run, short of length on off, Thirimanne stands up and taps it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dilshan, leg byes, 1 run, angled into the pads, Dilshan can't connect with the flick, picks up a run as the ball rolls off the pads to the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Thirimanne, 1 run, banged in halfway down the wicket, Thirimanne pulls it in the air to fine leg. It doesn't carry to Coetzer in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Thirimanne, no run, shortens the length around off, Thirimanne dabs it towards backward point, Berrington dives to his right and saves the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Thirimanne, no run, pushed across the left-hander, Thirimanne lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dilshan, 1 run, short and on the body, Dilshan swivels and pulls it to fine leg, he didn't time it as well as he would have liked]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Thirimanne, no run, tight line from Taylor, in and around off, Thirimanne moves forward and knocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Thirimanne, 2 runs, touch fuller and outside off, Thirimanne went for the loft over mid-off, the bat turned and he sliced it over extra cover for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Thirimanne, no run, good length ball around off, Thirimanne defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Thirimanne, no run, full and on the stumps, Thirimanne drives it down the wicket, Taylor sticks out his left hand and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Dilshan, 1 run, back of a length on off, Dilshan shuffles across slightly and tucks it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Dilshan, no run, on a length close to off, Dilshan presses it to mid-off after coming forward]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Thirimanne, no run, slanted across the left-hander, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Thirimanne, no run, short of length and straightens a touch, Thirimanne is cramped for room, he can't lay bat on the flick, is struck high on the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Thirimanne, no run, Thirimanne missed out there, on the pads, he fails to nail the clip, wears it on the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dilshan, 1 run, angling in from wide of the crease, Dilshan uses that angle and works it through mid-wicket, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dilshan, no run, not all that short, it was also very close to the off-stump, Dilshan goes for the cut, inside edges it onto the pads. Lucky that it didn't go back onto the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Alasdair Evans to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, crunched! Full and well wide of off, Dilshan had plenty of room to throw his bat at that, he drives it in the air well wide of the cover fielder. The ball travels to the fence in no time]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Alasdair Evans, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Thirimanne, no run, low full toss, Taylor was searching for the yorker, Thirimanne turns it to square leg with a closed bat face]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Thirimanne, no run, good length ball around off, Thirimanne presses forward and defends it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Dilshan, 3 runs, too straight, on the middle stump line, Dilshan leans forward and wrists it to the right of mid-on, Machan runs across and shoots at the bowler's end, the ball hits the sticks and ricochets away. The batsmen sneak in two more]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Dilshan, no run, touch short and bit of width on offer, Dilshan frees his arms straightaway and cuts it to backward point, picks out the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Thirimanne, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Thirimanne is lured into the drive, the bat face closes and the ball goes off the inner half wide of mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rob Taylor to Thirimanne, no run, full and hint of shape into the batsman, Thirimanne is not fully forward as he squeezes it to mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Thirimanne and Dilshan are at the crease. Thirimanne is on strike. Rob Taylor will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Scottish players have taken the field. Thirimanne and Dilshan make their way out to the centre. The former will take first strike. The countdown begins. Rob Taylor to start off. He has a couple of slips in place. Here we go..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pitch Report:</b> "The pitch looks glorious. There is a tinge of green. It looks solid. Win the toss, bat first and you can make hay on a pitch that looks good for batting," reckons <b>Rameez Raja</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Scotland</b> (Playing XI): Kyle Coetzer, Calum MacLeod, Matt Machan, Freddie Coleman, Preston Mommsen(c), Richie Berrington, Matthew Cross(w), Josh Davey, Rob Taylor, Michael Leask, Alasdair Evans]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sri Lanka</b> (Playing XI): Lahiru Thirimanne, Tillakaratne Dilshan, Kumar Sangakkara(w), Mahela Jayawardene, Angelo Mathews(c), Kushal Janith Perera, Thisara Perera, Nuwan Kulasekara, Seekkuge Prasanna, Dushmantha Chameera, Lasith Malinga]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sri Lanka have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mommsen:</b> "We would have batted. Looks a good one-day wicket. At the same time, I think it's quite hard a ground to defend on. So, nothing wrong in batting second. We have got three changes, Michael Leask comes in for Majid Haq, off-spinning option, Freddie Coleman and Rob Taylor come in as well. It has been an awesome experience, the first four games for us. We have played some good cricket and unfortunately we haven't been able to get that win. Nonetheless, though it is relatively new for us playing on this world stage and the boys are savouring every moment of it. I think definitely the atmosphere and pressure is amplified when you are playing at a World Cup, so I think each game we have become more relaxed and we have played better cricket as a result."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mathews:</b> "We will have a bat first. Of course it looks really nice and hard. So, we will put the runs on the board, nice conditions to bat first so we will get runs on the board first. It was a good game. I thought 340 would have been a chasable score, but unfortunately 370 was a bit too much, but hopefully we can go well today. Not really, we have been playing pretty good cricket in the past four games and we will look to continue to do that in today's game as well. Kusal (Perera) takes his (Chandimal) place and also we got two more changes. Sachitra (Senanayake) and Upul Tharanga goes out, we have got Nuwan Kulasekara, Chameera Dushmantha and Kusal Janith in. Of course he (Kulasekara) is one of the players we can bank on. So, we look to play him and hope he goes well. He (Sangakkara) is an unbelievable player, isn't he? I mean he has scored three hundreds in a row and hopefully he can get another one today."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-Head:</b> Scotland have only played once against Sri Lanka and naturally it was the Asian team that came out on top. After setting a target of 285, Malinga blew away the Scottish batting line-up with a 5-wicket haul. Will the team winning the toss bat first or will they put the opposition in? We'll find out soon as the toss is on the way. Stay tuned!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather Check:</b> It is a cool day in Hobart. There is a bit of cloud around. The maximum temperature is 23 degress. Even though it's cloudy, there are no chances of rain. Perfect weather to play a game of cricket.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Scotland</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Scotland have had their moments in this tournament. Almost running New Zealand close while defending a paltry 142, losing a thriller against Afghanistan and their best game was the previous one versus Bangladesh. Kyle Coetzer played a magnificent innings to set up a massive 319. But, the bowlers could not contain the Bangladeshi batsmen as Tamim, Mahmudullah, Rahim and Shakib went onto get fifties and helped Bangladesh pull off the second highest successful run-chase in World Cup.]]></line><line><![CDATA[They have lost their games by not winning the key moments. In fact, the Scots are still searching for their first World Cup victory. They have the players who have been performing on an individual level, but the team hasn failed to stitch it together as a unit. The bowling looks settled with Wardlaw, Davey, Evans and Haq. The likes of Coetzer, Machan and Berrington have all scored fifties. But, still they have not contributed in unison. Can they win a game in this World Cup and leave a mark?]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sri Lanka</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sri Lanka didn't start off on the best of notes. They lost to New Zealand by a big margin and were put under tremendous pressure by Afghanistan. But, since then they have been in terrific form. They beat Bangladesh comprehensively, thanks to hundreds from Dilshan and Sangakkara. Once again riding on the back of a Sanga ton, they thrashed England and chased down 310. However, their previous game against Australia didn't pan out the way they wanted. Chasing 375, they were on course with a third ton from Sanga and some fireworks from Chandimal, before the latter had to retire hurt due to a hamstring injury. That tilted the match in Australia's favour and eventually, Australia won by 64 runs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[That defeat should be forgotten quickly as they give Australia a run for their money. They can take heart from the fact that they became the first team to score 300 versus Australia in a World cup game. Nonetheless, Sri Lanka are a side that is suffering from a lot of injury woes. Dinesh Chandimal is the latest addition to their injury list, which already included, Dhammika Prasad, Jeevan Mendis, Dimuth Karunaratne. Kusal Perera has been drafted in as a replacement for Chandimal. With so many players injured, Sri Lanka are yet to decide upon their final XI. So, this game will given them an opportunity to test their best combination before the quarter-finals.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>13:15 Local Time, 02:15 GMT, 07:45 IST:</b> On Monday, Bangladesh created history at the Adelaide Oval. By beating England, they ensured their qualification for the knockouts for the first time. That win also took Sri Lanka through to the quarterfinals. The Islanders currently have 6 points in 5 games and today they will be up against a spirited Scottish team. Let us just have a recap as to what these two teams have been doing lately.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/><br/>After the final over thriller on Saturday between Ireland and Zimbabwe, the Bellerive Oval in Hobart will play host to Sri Lanka's final group stage game. Having already been assured of a place in the quarter-finals following Bangladesh's historic win, an injury-hit Sri Lanka take on Scotland looking to finalize their combination ahead of the crucial knockout phase. Scotland, despite putting in spirited performances, find themselves without a win in four games, with Sri Lanka and Australia to play. The game also assumes importance to determine Sri Lanka's potential quarter-final opponent. A Sri Lanka win will take them above Bangladesh, who are yet to play New Zealand, and potentially avoid a clash with the table-toppers from Pool B (India).<br/><br/><b>Team News:</b><br/><br/><b>Sri Lanka</b><br/><br/>Sri Lanka's injury woes were exacerbated when Dinesh Chandimal hobbled out of the Australia game and the World Cup with a hamstring injury. A significant blow considering he had just scored a 22-ball half-century. Since the start of the warmup games, Sri Lanka have lost Dhammika Prasad, Jeevan Mendis, Dimuth Karunaratne and now Chandimal. Left-arm spinner Rangana Herath, who suffered an injury to his finger during the England game has not sufficiently recovered and is unlikely to recover before the quarters. Kusal Perera has been drafted into the squad while Kithruwan Vithanage has been flown in as cover. Amidst all the injury trouble, a 37-year old Kumar Sangakkara became the first man to score three consecutive World Cup centuries when he scored the 104 at the SCG. Dilshan, Jayawardene, Thirimanne have all scored hundreds but the bowling, especially in the middle overs, remains an area of concern. The trio of Angelo Mathews, Thissara Perera and Seekkuge Prasanna gave away 223 runs in their 26 overs against Australia. The think-tank would consider bringing back Suranga Lakmal to reinforce the bowling department.<br/><br/><b>Probable XI:</b><br/><br/>Lahiru Thirimanne, Tillakaratne Dilshan, Kumar Sangakkara (wk), Mahela Jayawardene, Angelo Mathews (c), Upul Tharanga, Thissara Perera, Kusal Perera/Nuwan Kulasekara, Seekkuge Prasanna, Sachithra Senanayake, Lasith Malinga<br/><br/><b>Player to watch out for:</b> Angelo Mathews - The captain had been the star of Sri Lanka coming in to the World Cup. However, with the Sangakkara-led top-order firing on all cylinders, Mathews hasn't had enough time with the bat. Even with the ball, he endured a forgettable game against the Aussies. Look forward to an improved showing from the versatile Sri Lankan captain.<br/><br/><b>Scotland</b><br/><br/>Scotland travel to Tasmania without a win in any of the four games in their New Zealand sojourn. They haven't been completely woeful either. They succeeded in sending jitters down the red-hot New Zealand side despite defending a small score. Against Afghanistan, they came up against an inspired Samiullah Shenwari, who took the game away from them. The biggest worry for Scotland has been that they haven't succeeded in putting a solid all-round performance, a fact highlighted in their previous game against Bangladesh. Kyle Coetzer's 158 (record for associate nations in World Cups) received no backing from the bowling and Bangladesh chased down 318 at a canter. Matt Machan, Richie Berrington have been good with the bat, without being great. Preston Mommsen will hope for one of the middle-order batsmen to carry on and make it big. Lead bowler Iain Wardlaw has been disappointing in the tournament and will hope for an improved showing. Wardlaw, Josh Davey and Co. now face the daunting prospect of bowling at a marauding Sri Lankan top-order. At the least, they will be expected to put in another spirited show as their World Cup winds down.<br/><br/><b>Probable XI:</b><br/><br/>Kyle Coetzer, Calum MacLeod, Hamish Gardiner, Matt Machan, Preston Mommsen (c), Richie Berrington, Matthew Cross (wk), Josh Davey, Majid Haq, Alasdair Evans, Iain Wardlaw<br/><br/><b>Player to watch out for:</b> Preston Mommsen - The Scottish captain hasn't found the going easy with the bat. His 39 against Bangladesh took his World Cup tally to a meagre 88 runs. He will look to prove a point in the team's two remaining clashes.<br/><br/><b>Pitch and Conditions:</b><br/><br/>The Bellerive Oval hosted the Ireland-Zimbabwe thriller in which 657 runs were scored. Despite being a tad two-paced, the short square boundaries prove to be a handful to defend. Sri Lankan batsmen should enjoy themselves on the Hobart pitch. The forecast indicate a 20% chance of rain but the showers are unlikely to force a washout.<br/><br/><b>Stats and Trivia:</b><br/><br/>- Kumar Sangakkara is the first man to score three successive World Cup centuries.<br/>- Kyle Coetzer needs 29 runs to become the third Scotland player to score 1000 ODI runs. Gavin Hamilton and Neil McCallum are the others.<br/><br/><b>Quotes:</b><br/><br/>"We've been in a couple of winning positions, and just maybe through lack of experience on playing at this stage, we've not been able to win those games"<br/>- Scotland captain <b>Preston Mommsen</b> cited inexperience for his team's failure to close out games.<br/><br/>"There are big game players and he's (Lasith Malinga) one of those. He stands up and he has a big game and in pressure situations, he comes up trumps"<br/>- Sri Lankan coach <b>Marvan Atapattu</b> was happy with the progress made by his strike bowler post his injury.]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>363</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>9</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>50</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Sri Lanka">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>6243</playerid>
					<name>Lahiru Thirimanne</name>
					<batsman-name>Thirimanne</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Thirimanne</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>21</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>A Evans</bowler>
					<bowlerId>3053</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Preston Mommsen</fielder>
						<fielderId>6744</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>105</playerid>
					<name>Tillakaratne Dilshan</name>
					<batsman-name>Dilshan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dilshan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>104</runs>
					<balls>99</balls>
					<fours>10</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>J Davey</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6657</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Calum MacLeod</fielder>
						<fielderId>1416</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>104</playerid>
					<name>Kumar Sangakkara</name>
					<batsman-name>Sangakkara</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sangakkara</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>124</runs>
					<balls>95</balls>
					<fours>13</fours>
					<sixes>4</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>J Davey</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6657</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Matthew Cross</fielder>
						<fielderId>9365</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>101</playerid>
					<name>Mahela Jayawardene</name>
					<batsman-name>M Jayawardene</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M Jayawardene</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>J Davey</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6657</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Calum MacLeod</fielder>
						<fielderId>1416</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1629</playerid>
					<name>Angelo Mathews</name>
					<batsman-name>Mathews</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mathews</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>51</runs>
					<balls>21</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>6</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Machan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6565</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Freddie Coleman</fielder>
						<fielderId>9318</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8116</playerid>
					<name>Kushal Janith Perera</name>
					<batsman-name>K Perera</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>K Perera</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>24</runs>
					<balls>13</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>R Taylor</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8327</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Calum MacLeod</fielder>
						<fielderId>1416</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2281</playerid>
					<name>Thisara Perera</name>
					<batsman-name>T Perera</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>T Perera</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>7</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>R Berrington</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1398</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Freddie Coleman</fielder>
						<fielderId>9318</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8063</playerid>
					<name>Seekkuge Prasanna</name>
					<batsman-name>S Prasanna</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Prasanna</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>A Evans</bowler>
					<bowlerId>3053</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Freddie Coleman</fielder>
						<fielderId>9318</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>507</playerid>
					<name>Nuwan Kulasekara</name>
					<batsman-name>N Kulasekara</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>N Kulasekara</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>18</runs>
					<balls>17</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>111</playerid>
					<name>Lasith Malinga</name>
					<batsman-name>Malinga</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Malinga</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>R Berrington</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1398</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Michael Leask</fielder>
						<fielderId>9383</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8393</playerid>
					<name>Dushmantha Chameera</name>
					<batsman-name>Dushmantha Chameera</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dushmantha Chameera</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>12</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6243</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>21</runs>
				<overs>5.3</overs>
				<batsman>Lahiru Thirimanne</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Thirimanne</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>105</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>216</runs>
				<overs>34.2</overs>
				<batsman>Tillakaratne Dilshan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dilshan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>101</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>244</runs>
				<overs>36.4</overs>
				<batsman>Mahela Jayawardene</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Jayawardene</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>104</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>244</runs>
				<overs>36.5</overs>
				<batsman>Kumar Sangakkara</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Sangakkara</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8116</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>289</runs>
				<overs>40.4</overs>
				<batsman>Kushal Janith Perera</batsman>
				<batsman-name>K Perera</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1629</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>326</runs>
				<overs>43.6</overs>
				<batsman>Angelo Mathews</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mathews</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>2281</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>328</runs>
				<overs>44.4</overs>
				<batsman>Thisara Perera</batsman>
				<batsman-name>T Perera</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8063</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>331</runs>
				<overs>45.4</overs>
				<batsman>Seekkuge Prasanna</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Prasanna</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>111</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>336</runs>
				<overs>46.5</overs>
				<batsman>Lasith Malinga</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Malinga</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>10</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>3</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>13</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Scotland">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8327</playerid>
					<name>Rob Taylor</name>
					<bowler-name>R Taylor</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rob Taylor</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>46</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3053</playerid>
					<name>Alasdair Evans</name>
					<bowler-name>A Evans</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Alasdair Evans</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>72</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6657</playerid>
					<name>Josh Davey</name>
					<bowler-name>J Davey</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Davey</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>63</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>6</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1398</playerid>
					<name>Richie Berrington</name>
					<bowler-name>R Berrington</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Berrington</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>6.1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>31</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9383</playerid>
					<name>Michael Leask</name>
					<bowler-name>M A Leask</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M A Leask</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>63</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1415</playerid>
					<name>Kyle Coetzer</name>
					<bowler-name>K Coetzer</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Coetzer</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4.5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>39</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6565</playerid>
					<name>Matt Machan</name>
					<bowler-name>M Machan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Machan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>46</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1416</playerid>
					<name>Calum MacLeod</name>
					<bowler-name>C MacLeod</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>MacLeod</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9318</playerid>
					<name>Freddie Coleman</name>
					<bowler-name>F Coleman</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Coleman</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6744</playerid>
					<name>Preston Mommsen</name>
					<bowler-name>P Mommsen</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mommsen</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9365</playerid>
					<name>Matthew Cross</name>
					<bowler-name>M Cross</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Matthew Cross</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>215</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>10</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>43.1</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Scotland">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1415</playerid>
					<name>Kyle Coetzer</name>
					<batsman-name>K Coetzer</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Coetzer</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Malinga</bowler>
					<bowlerId>111</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Malinga</fielder>
						<fielderId>111</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1416</playerid>
					<name>Calum MacLeod</name>
					<batsman-name>C MacLeod</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>MacLeod</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>11</runs>
					<balls>21</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>N Kulasekara</bowler>
					<bowlerId>507</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6565</playerid>
					<name>Matt Machan</name>
					<batsman-name>M Machan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Machan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>19</runs>
					<balls>31</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Dilshan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>105</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6744</playerid>
					<name>Preston Mommsen</name>
					<batsman-name>P Mommsen</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mommsen</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>60</runs>
					<balls>75</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>T Perera</bowler>
					<bowlerId>2281</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Lahiru Thirimanne</fielder>
						<fielderId>6243</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9318</playerid>
					<name>Freddie Coleman</name>
					<batsman-name>F Coleman</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Coleman</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>70</runs>
					<balls>74</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>N Kulasekara</bowler>
					<bowlerId>507</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Thisara Perera</fielder>
						<fielderId>2281</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1398</playerid>
					<name>Richie Berrington</name>
					<batsman-name>R Berrington</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Berrington</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>29</runs>
					<balls>22</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Dushmantha Chameera</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8393</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Nuwan Kulasekara</fielder>
						<fielderId>507</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9383</playerid>
					<name>Michael Leask</name>
					<batsman-name>M A Leask</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M A Leask</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>N Kulasekara</bowler>
					<bowlerId>507</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Kumar Sangakkara</fielder>
						<fielderId>104</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9365</playerid>
					<name>Matthew Cross</name>
					<batsman-name>M Cross</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Matthew Cross</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>7</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Dushmantha Chameera</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8393</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Kumar Sangakkara</fielder>
						<fielderId>104</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8327</playerid>
					<name>Rob Taylor</name>
					<batsman-name>R Taylor</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rob Taylor</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Malinga</bowler>
					<bowlerId>111</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Thisara Perera</fielder>
						<fielderId>2281</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6657</playerid>
					<name>Josh Davey</name>
					<batsman-name>J Davey</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Davey</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Dushmantha Chameera</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8393</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Lahiru Thirimanne</fielder>
						<fielderId>6243</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3053</playerid>
					<name>Alasdair Evans</name>
					<batsman-name>A Evans</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Alasdair Evans</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1415</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>0</runs>
				<overs>0.2</overs>
				<batsman>Kyle Coetzer</batsman>
				<batsman-name>K Coetzer</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1416</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>26</runs>
				<overs>7.3</overs>
				<batsman>Calum MacLeod</batsman>
				<batsman-name>C MacLeod</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6565</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>44</runs>
				<overs>11.2</overs>
				<batsman>Matt Machan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Machan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6744</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>162</runs>
				<overs>31.6</overs>
				<batsman>Preston Mommsen</batsman>
				<batsman-name>P Mommsen</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9318</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>189</runs>
				<overs>35.6</overs>
				<batsman>Freddie Coleman</batsman>
				<batsman-name>F Coleman</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9383</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>192</runs>
				<overs>37.5</overs>
				<batsman>Michael Leask</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M A Leask</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9365</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>200</runs>
				<overs>39.4</overs>
				<batsman>Matthew Cross</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Cross</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8327</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>209</runs>
				<overs>40.5</overs>
				<batsman>Rob Taylor</batsman>
				<batsman-name>R Taylor</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1398</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>210</runs>
				<overs>41.1</overs>
				<batsman>Richie Berrington</batsman>
				<batsman-name>R Berrington</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6657</playerid>
				<nbr>10</nbr>
				<runs>215</runs>
				<overs>43.1</overs>
				<batsman>Josh Davey</batsman>
				<batsman-name>J Davey</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>6</wides>
			<noballs>1</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>9</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Sri Lanka">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>111</playerid>
					<name>Lasith Malinga</name>
					<bowler-name>Malinga</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Malinga</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>29</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>507</playerid>
					<name>Nuwan Kulasekara</name>
					<bowler-name>N Kulasekara</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>N Kulasekara</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>20</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2281</playerid>
					<name>Thisara Perera</name>
					<bowler-name>T Perera</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>T Perera</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>41</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>105</playerid>
					<name>Tillakaratne Dilshan</name>
					<bowler-name>Dilshan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dilshan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>15</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8063</playerid>
					<name>Seekkuge Prasanna</name>
					<bowler-name>S Prasanna</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Prasanna</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>57</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8393</playerid>
					<name>Dushmantha Chameera</name>
					<bowler-name>Dushmantha Chameera</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dushmantha Chameera</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7.1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>51</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6243</playerid>
					<name>Lahiru Thirimanne</name>
					<bowler-name>Thirimanne</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Thirimanne</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>104</playerid>
					<name>Kumar Sangakkara</name>
					<bowler-name>Sangakkara</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sangakkara</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>101</playerid>
					<name>Mahela Jayawardene</name>
					<bowler-name>M Jayawardene</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M Jayawardene</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1629</playerid>
					<name>Angelo Mathews</name>
					<bowler-name>Mathews</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mathews</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8116</playerid>
					<name>Kushal Janith Perera</name>
					<bowler-name>K Perera</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>K Perera</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



