<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="12875" >
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>21st Match, Pool B</gameDesc>
		<series>WC 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>India</home>
		<away>United Arab Emirates</away>
		<teamsabbr>IND vs UAE</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>IND</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>UAE</awayabbr>
		<homeId>2</homeId>
		<awayId>7</awayId>
		<venue>W.A.C.A. Ground, Perth</venue>
		<startdate>28 02 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>28 02 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>United Arab Emirates</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>India won by 9 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>India</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>9</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Billy Bowden</Name>
			<Country>NZ</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Michael Gough</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Nigel Llong</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Ranjan Madugalle</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>06:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150228105309</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>Ind</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>UAE</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>104</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>1</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>18.5</batteamovers>
		<status>India won by 9 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>576</playerid>
			<name>Rohit Sharma*</name>
			<batsman-name>Rohit</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Rohit</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>57</runs>
			<balls-faced>55</balls-faced>
			<fours>10</fours>
			<sixes>1</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>1413</playerid>
			<name>Virat Kohli</name>
			<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Kohli</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>33</runs>
			<balls-faced>41</balls-faced>
			<fours>5</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>87</playerid>
			<name>Mohammad Tauqir*</name>
			<bowler-name>M Tauqir</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>M Tauqir</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>2.5</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>21</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>10041</playerid>
			<name>Krishnachandran Karate</name>
			<bowler-name>Karate</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Karate</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>3</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>17</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>103</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>1446</playerid>
<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
<player-runs>14</player-runs>
<player-balls>17</player-balls>
<runs>29</runs>
<wicket-nbr>1</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>9832</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Naveed</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>0</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>0</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[1 2 1 1 . . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 . . 1 4 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. . 1 1 4 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. . . . 4 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_WC/IND_UAE_FEB28/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[That brings an end to the proceedings on this super Saturday - one that the bowlers thoroughly enjoyed. Will the batsmen have their say tomorrow? There are two big matches lined-up, England take on Sri Lanka at the Cake Tin in Wellington and Pakistan lock horns with Zimbabwe at the Gabba, Brisbane. Do join us for all the action. For now, cheers and bye..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jatin Sapru:</b> 'Ruthless'! They looked like bullies in the Champions Trophy, the men in blue seem to be getting there again.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajneesh Gupta:</b> First time India have won their first three matches of a World Cup. #cwc15 #IndvsUAE]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Aakash Chopra:</b> Clinical by India. Can't blame them for the lack of quality in the opposition.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohandas Menon:</b> 4+ wkts hauls in ODIs at WACA, Perth on 36 occasions. Only 3 spinners have done it (R Shastri & Ashwin. G Maxwell twice) #IndvsUAE #CWC15]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajneesh Gupta:</b> India's 7th consecutive win in World Cup since beating WI at Chennai in 2011. Their best winning streak in World Cup is 8 (in 2003).]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here are a few <b>tweets</b> pertaining to this match.]]></line><line><![CDATA['I think there's no secret to it (on doing well in ICC tournaments), I think the guys have taken that extra responsibility - not to forget, there have been a few instances before the ICC tournament, the team has not had a very good run. As we always say, the dressing room atmosphere is a key aspect because it lets you come back into your form quite quickly and we have been able to maintain that and boys have taken the extra responsibility to make sure where the shortcomings are, whatever time they get, to make sure that they are making it one of their stronger points. I feel it's a reflection of that and also the occasion - with a bit more support and a few people turning up - especially with the Indian cricket team, they love to play in front of a houseful crowd and what we have seen is that we are getting good support. Well, that's not entirely what I would say (about India doing better in ODIs and not Tests). Because whenever we turn up on the field, we are representing India, we have to play with the same kind of intensity, but to make that kind of intensity at times is difficult, but we have to make sure - especially in ICC tournaments, it's not like a bilateral series - where we get too many opportunities, so we have to make sure we are playing your best cricket over that period of time. It may be 15 days for the Champions Trophy or 20 days for a World Cup - may be slightly longer period, we have to make sure that all the boys are fit and they are available for selection. In the tri-series, we really pushed for that, we didn't really push players who were having a bit of a niggle']]></line><line><![CDATA['Well, he (Bhuvi) looked good, frankly. You know, the first 5 overs that he bowled, he was looking a bit sharper than what he was after he came back from injury and played the Test match. It's good to see him get a bit more pace under his belt. With the kind of swing bowling or the swing that he gets, he can be a bit more useful if he touches or just crosses the 130 (kmph) mark. Also, if he plays a few more games or if we have the opportunity to play him or give him a few more games, we will see how he bowls in the death overs. You know, the best option for us is when all the 15 are available for selection. So, I think it's a good one for him and the team."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhoni:</b> 'Well yes, it has been (speaking about the win). They had quite a few plans, I think it's important that in these conditions you have to execute your plans. The margin of error - you have to make sure that you are not giving the opportunities to the batsmen to score freely. So I feel the bowlers have really stepped up and also you know, in a team sport, it starts reflecting on other departments also. I feel the batsmen are also doing a good job and fielding has been good - Yes, we dropped one catch today, overall the fielding has been good. Well, when we were losing quite a few games outside the sub-continent, that was the main area of concern. We were not able to get wickets in the middle overs and because of that, the opposition had too many wickets in their hand especially, last 10 overs. So, we were not really able to capitalize. Now, what we are seeing is - we are getting wickets with the new ball and at the same time, because of that, the middle overs - the spinners - are able to put pressure on the batsmen, few false shots, they are pushing the batsmen to play them. Overall, as a complete unit they are doing well. Of course, it's one thing to do it in one game but they have shown that they can do it in game after game. So I think it's good for us but we have to continue with the good effort.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Tauqir:</b> 'Yeah, it was not a par score on this wicket. I think we were outplayed by the Indian bowling, they bowled really well, and in good areas. We should have scored 200+. As I said, he (Ashwin) bowled brilliantly, we couldn't cope up with his bowling, and I think he was getting good bounce and turn on this wicket, bowled really well. I think that's our batting-order, we know that he (Shaiman Anwar) can score a lot of runs down the order. It's the top-order that needs to be a bit more responsible and score runs for us. We need to stick to the basics, play out the 50 overs and put some runs on the board. But India outplayed us and good luck to them for the rest of the tournament.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashwin:</b> 'Yeah, I mean I bowl at such phases of the game where in it's more of looking to buy wickets or pretty much trying to cut the runs out at the back end of the innings. It can just get a little difficult, but today it was playing on my mind after I got three in the first 4-5 overs, it went well. It's not just today, I am an attacking bowler, I love to have wickets behind my back but when it comes to this format of the game, especially I am pretty much unselfish, it doesn't really matter if I get the numbers or not as long as I am actually putting in the effort that needs to be. I have been working on it as well (arm ball). But having said that, my wrist is in a much better position right now, I am able to vary my pace at will. As a result of that, the seam position on the arm-ball is much better and obviously the breeze across the ground helped a bit today. We had a bit of a downtime after the Test series, it was a bit hard and we were also trying to test a few combinations, to give some game time to the other guys as well, but now today, once the ICC event starts, we know that we are going to be on a roll. It was good to have a couple of tight games initially, like play the big teams, but now I think we are on a roll. Yeah, as I said it has pretty much been on the process, the number of wickets or anything, the moment I am actually able to vary the pace at will, then I am able to produce the variations on the spot, it's more than enough.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashwin</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his excellent figures of 4/25]]></line><line><![CDATA[India will be full of confidence when they take on the West Indies in their next game at the WACA. However, UAE need to lift their game considerably for their next match against the mercurial Pakistani set-up in Napier. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Only Shaiman Anwar, by far UAE's best player in this World Cup, made his presence felt by showing quickness of hands and feet to play Ashwin with a degree of confidence. He also put on a useful stand for the last wicket with Manjula Guruge, but by then, India were in firm control of the proceedings. For UAE, Mohammad Naveed and Guruge bowled reasonably well. Rohan Mustafa, with a spark of brilliance in the field took an impressive catch at backward point to send Dhawan back to the pavilion, but once they were dismissed for 102, it was always going to be a herculean task for UAE to make a match out of it. Unfortunately for UAE, their modest total turned out to be their lowest ever score in ODIs.  <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[It was Umesh, who snaffled the first wicket by dismissing Andri Berenger with a short ball. With UAE struggling to cope up with the pace and bounce at the WACA, even Bhuvneshwar decided to bang it short and was rewarded with the wicket of Amjad Ali. Once Ashwin was introduced into the attack, UAE's batsmen just looked clueless while facing up to him and they fell like a pack of cards.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, it was Ravichandran Ashwin, who ripped through UAE's middle-order with a fine spell of off-spin bowling to take four wickets. With his craftily flighted off-breaks, Ashwin troubled UAE's batsmen all the time. He also used the arm ball to good effect. The south-west breeze too played its part as it helped Ashwin to hold it up in the air. Ravindra Jadeja bowled with good control and picked up two wickets. The pacers, Umesh Yadav, Bhuvneshwar Kumar and Mohit Sharma bowled with good disciplines as well. To make it a near perfect day for the Indian camp, their fielding was once again impressive.   <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[India put up a thoroughly professional performance to crush UAE and win their third consecutive game in this World Cup. Once the bowlers had cleaned up UAE for a paltry score on the board, Rohit Sharma played a wide array of shots to compose a fine fifty. Virat Kohli, who came in at the fall of Shikhar Dhawan's wicket, started cautiously before bisecting the gaps through the off-side and collect runs with utmost ease, as India chased down the target under 19 overs.  <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[India have recorded their third straight win and stay at the top of Pool B with 6 points.]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>India win!</b> This was tossed up invitingly by Tauqir, Rohit dances down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and belts it back past the bowler, no stopping that, it races away to the fence in a jiffy. <b>India win by nine wickets</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Rohit, no run, pushed through by Tauqir, the quicker ball, Rohit goes back and defends it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Rohit, no run, slower and drifting into Rohit, worked to the right of mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Rohit, no run, flatter and on the stumps, punched towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Rohit, no run, slower and just outside off, Rohit lunges forward and defends it to the right of cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Kohli, no run, on a length and on the stumps, Kohli shuffles across and works it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, that's easy pickings for Kohli, short and wide from Karate, Kohli waits on it and cuts it late, gets it into the gap between backward point and short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Rohit, 1 run, length ball and on Rohit's pads, nudged away past square leg on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Kohli, 1 run, a direct hit might have had Rohit, Kohli dabbed one straight to short third man, Rohit called for a quick single, the fielder has a shy at the striker's end, but Rohit was very quick to make his ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Kohli, no run, tad fuller and on the stumps, Kohli presents the full face of the bat as he drives it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Kohli, no run, back of a length and just outside off, punched straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Rohit, no run, flighted and on the stumps, Rohit prods across and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>24th ODI fifty for Rohit</b>, Tauqir drops this one short and well outside off, Rohit rocks back and cuts it square on the off-side, beats point and races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Kohli, 1 run, fraction shorter and on the stumps, worked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Kohli, no run, slower and just outside off, defended with an angled bat towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Kohli, no run, flighted and just outside off, driven back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Rohit, 1 run, Tauqir drops one short and just outside off, punched away towards long-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. India have taken the <b>batting PP</b> immediately]]></line><line><![CDATA[Once Dhawan was dismissed, it was Rohit, who opened up his shoulders by essaying a couple of magnificent pull shots off Naveed's bowling in the ninth over of the innings. He also played a crunching drive through the extra cover in the same over. Virat Kohli too looked in fine touch and showed his class with a back foot punch off Guruge to collect four runs. When the umpires called for the dinner break, India looked well on course to chase down the modest target. Earlier, Ravichandran Ashwin was the star performer for India as he took a four-wicket haul. Ravindra Jadeja picked up two wickets. The seamers too chipped in by taking wickets at regular intervals. To make it even better for India, the fielding was good as well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[While chasing down a meagre target, openers Rohit Sharma and Shikhar Dhawan started on a cautious note before Mohammad Naveed snared the wicket of Dhawan, with Rohan Mustafa taking a splendid catch at backward point. In fact, Naveed and Manjula Guruge bowled reasonably well upfront, but UAE just didn't get enough runs on the board to give India a run for their money. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[That's the <b>dinner break</b>. For the second time in this World Cup, we will have a 45-minute break with the match all but over. Talk about the playing conditions.. We have had two D/N matches today. The one at Auckland ended even before the floodlights were switched on, looks like the same case, here in Perth, unless, it gets dark at the end of the 45-minute break.]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Kohli, no run, tad fuller and angling into Kohli, he looks to work it towards the on-side and is struck high on the thigh-pad, stifled shout for LBW, but the ball was sailing over the top of the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Kohli, no run, fuller length delivery and on Kohli's pads, clipped straight to the fielder at mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Rohit, 1 run, short of a length and well outside off, Rohit runs it down towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Kohli, 1 run, full and on the stumps, worked past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Kohli, 2 runs, back of a length and well outside off, Kohli cracks it square on the off-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Rohit, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, dabbed towards third man for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>20 runs</b> to win, this might be the last over before the <b>dinner break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Rohit, 1 run, fraction shorter and just outside off, punched down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, this is an exact copy of the previous shot, once again Rohit is to the pitch of a well flighted delivery and drills it through extra cover, another boundary for Rohit]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, classy from Rohit, Tauqir tossed this one well outside off, Rohit gets a big stride forward, gets to the pitch of the ball and drills it past extra cover, no chance for the fielder running across from long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Rohit, no run, nicely bowled by Tauqir, gave this one more air and gets it to dip into the batsman, the off-break, Rohit nearly overbalanced as he went for the drive and missed, his back foot was well in though even as Swapnil Patil broke the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[The third umpire has been called for a <b>stumping chance</b>. Rohit  doesn't look too fussed though, no excitement from the keeper as well. He is SAFE]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Kohli, 1 run, Tauqir drops one short and on the stumps, punched down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Rohit, 1 run, flatter and just outside off, punched down towards long-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Tauqir, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Kohli, no run, Karate shortens his length and just outside off, defended towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a loopy half-volley from Karate, Kohli gets a big stride forward and drills it past extra cover, it was in the air for a while, but well wide of the diving fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Rohit, 1 run, short and wide from Karate, slapped square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Kohli, 1 run, tad fuller and just outside off, Kohli plays with an angled bat and runs it down towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Kohli, no run, on a good length and just outside off, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Kohli, no run, short of a length and just outside off, punched towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[India are in no hurry to chase this one quickly. They haven't taken the <b>batting PP</b> as yet. The keeper is up to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Krishnachandran Karate, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Rohit, no run, on a good length and around off, Rohit presses forward and defends it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Rohit, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, flicked away towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Kohli, 1 run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, punched towards mid-off, Rohit set-off for a quick single, Kohli was ball watching, the fielder fumbles and allows the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Kohli, no run, tad fuller and on the stumps, Kohli presents the full face of the bat and defends it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Kohli, no run, on a good length and just outside off, driven towards extra cover, the fielder moves across and to his right to stop the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, delightfully played by Kohli, a half-volley on his pads, he leans forward, rolls his wrists and whips it through mid-wicket for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Kohli, 1 run, full and a hint of angle back into Kohli, worked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Kohli, no run, full and wide from Guruge, Kohli gets a big stride on the drive, can't get the placement, straight to the man at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Kohli, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Kohli gets a good stride forward and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Rohit, 1 run, short of a length and on Rohit's pads, flicked away past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Rohit, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Rohit gets across and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Rohit, no run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Rohit creams it straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[India need 44 runs to win. 19 minutes remaining for the <b>dinner break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Rohit, 1 run, Javed shortens his length and on off, tucked behind square on the on-side for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, that's easy pickings for Rohit, too full and too wide from Javed, Rohit reaches out, plays with an open face and lifts it over mid-off, the timing wasn't spot on, but has enough to clear the fielder in the ring]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Rohit, no run, full and wide from Javed, Rohit reaches out for the drive and finds the fielder at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Kohli, 1 run, too straight from Javed, worked away to the right of mid-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Kohli, no run, on a length and just outside off, Kohli stays behind the line and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Rohit, 1 run, full and just outside off, Rohit opens the face of the bat at the last moment and drives it to the left of cover, Amjad dives and makes a half-stop, the batsmen get across for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Amjad Javed, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Kohli, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Kohli presses across and defends it with an open face, the ball rolls away towards the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Kohli, no run, on a length and going away with the angle, Kohli shuffles across and defends it with an angled bat, the ball rolls away towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Kohli, no run, on a length and on the stumps, Kohli prods across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Kohli, 2 runs, back of a length and well outside off, Kohli gets on top of the bounce and steers it square on the off-side, the fielder at third man gets across and keeps them down to a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Kohli, no run, short of a length and angling onto Kohli's pads, tucked away behind square]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, short and wide from Guruge, Kohli stays back, reaches out for the punch and creams it to the left of cover, no need to run for those, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>shot of the innings</b>, much better from Rohit, this was full and wide from Naveed, Rohit leans forward, gets to the pitch of the ball and caresses it through extra cover for the third boundary of the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, no run, that's much better from Naveed, short and just outside off, he put in a lot of effort behind the ball, climbs onto Rohit from a length off the deck, he watches it all along, drops his wrists and brings it down]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, this is much better from Rohit, way too short from Naveed, digs it halfway down the track, Rohit swivels across and pulls it powerfully over mid-wicket, one bounce and over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, too short from Naveed, Rohit swivels across and pulls it over mid-wicket, once again doesn't get hold of the shot, but the ball has enough power to trickle into the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Rohit prods across and defends it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, no run, fuller length delivery and on Rohit's pads, flicked to the left of mid-wicket where Berenger makes a tumbling stop]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Kohli, no run, Guruge shortens his length outside off, Kohli prods across and defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Kohli, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Kohli gets well forward and defends it with a straight bat towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, that's typical Kohli shot, too straight from Guruge, ends up drifting onto Kohli's pads, he presses across, uses his wrists to good effect and flicks it past mid-on for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Kohli, no run, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, Kohli presses across and defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Kohli, no run, Guruge slips in the slower ball, Kohli prods across and turns it towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and a gully in place for Kohli]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Kohli, no run, fuller length delivery and in that channel outside off, Kohli gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Rohit stays behind the line and punches it back at the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Kohli, 1 run, fuller length delivery and angling onto Kohli's pads, he looks to flick and gets an inside edge onto the pad, the ball rolls away behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Kohli, no run, that's a good leave from Kohli, fuller length delivery and coming back with the angle, Kohli gets a good stride forward, covers for the movement and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Virat Kohli, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Dhawan, <b>out</b> Caught by Rohan Mustafa!! A disbelieving Dhawan walks away! This was short and well outside off, Dhawan rode with the bounce and cut it behind point. Mustafa, at backward point, times his jump to perfection and sticks his right hand at the ball. The ball does stick and it's time for Dhawan to make the long walk back to the hut. <b>Dhawan c Rohan Mustafa b Naveed 14(17) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Naveed to Dhawan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Unbelievable catch at <b>backward point</b>, Dhawan is <b>OUT</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, too full and on Dhawan's pads, whipped away past square leg, the fielder dives over the ball and the ball races away to the fence for another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Dhawan, no run, fuller length delivery outside off and shaping away, easy leave for the batsman]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Rohit, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Rohit plays with an open face and guides it behind point, Dhawan wanted a single and was a long way down the track, sent back by Rohit]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Rohit, no run, on a length and around off, Rohit shuffles across and defends it towards the on-side, good dive from backward square leg fielder, saves some runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Rohit, no run, loud appeal for a <b>caught behind</b>, UAE decide against a review, the noise was Rohit's bat hitting the pad, good line from Guruge, tad fuller and shaping away from outside off, lures Rohit forward and into the drive, beats the outside edge by a margin]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Rohit, <b>SIX</b>, <b>top-edge and six</b>, this was banged in short by Guruge, doesn't rise as much as Rohit expected, he was on the front-foot, swivels across and looks to pull, gets a top-edge and the breeze carries it all the way over the long-leg boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Rohit, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Rohit drops it in front of cover-point, Dhawan wants a quick single and is turned back by Rohit]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Rohit, no run, on a length and just outside off, Rohit shuffles across and defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, too full and too wide from Naveed, ends up as a long half-volley, Dhawan leans forward and punches it past cover, no need to run for those, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Dhawan, no run, good comeback from Naveed, that's the line he must maintain, shortens his length and gets it to shape away from the left-hander, Dhawan has a poke at that and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, that should get Dhawan going, Naveed gets his line wrong once again, ends up swinging one onto Dhawan's pads, whipped away in the gap between mid-on and mid-wicket for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, 1 run, wrong line from Naveed, full and on Rohit's pads, whipped away backward of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, no run, on a good length and in that corridor outside off, Rohit watches it all along and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, Rohit gets a good stride forward and drives it towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Dhawan, no run, tad fuller and shaping back into Dhawan, he looks to flick and is struck high on the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Dhawan, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Dhawan stays back and punches it back towards the bowler. Rohit was backing up and has to dive to make his ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Dhawan, no run, full and angling onto Dhawan's pads, turned away towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Dhawan, no run, Guruge shortens his length around off, Dhawan prods across and turns it towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Dhawan, no run, back of a length and just outside off, no room for Dhawan to free his arms, punched away off the back foot and towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Dhawan, no run, on a length and around off, Dhawan gets behind the line and defends it towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, no run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, Rohit doesn't need to play at those, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, that's much better from Rohit, this was short and wide outside off, Rohit rides with the bounce and flashes it over second slip for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, no run, that's a beauty from Naveed, pitched around off and straightens, gets some extra bounce as well, Rohit was opened up as he looked to defend, the ball grazes the forearm on and dies on the way to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, no run, on a good length and angling back into the right-hander, Rohit shuffles across and defends it with a straight bat, the ball rolls away towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, Rohit throws his bat at that and misses, he's struggling for form here]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Dhawan, 1 run, too straight from Naveed, ends up straying onto Dhawan's pads, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Rohit, no run, on a length and around off, Rohit shuffles across and defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Rohit, no run, that's good bowling from Guruge, on a good length and nipping away from outside off, Rohit feels for it and nearly edges it through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Dhawan, 1 run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, Dhawan prods across and pushes it in front of mid-on, calls for a quick single and gets it with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[Looks like there was some disturbance behind the bowler's arm, a steward was running across the sightscreen, Dhawan backs away at the last moment]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Dhawan, no run, Guruge shortens his length and drifts this one onto Dhawan's pads, he looks to flick and misses, gets struck on his thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Dhawan, no run, tad fuller and a hint of shape away from off, Dhawan gets a good stride forward and blocks it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place for Guruge]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Dhawan, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Dhawan stays behind the line and defends it towards point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Manjula Guruge, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, no run, much better from Naveed, on a good length and just outside off, Rohit covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, no run, fuller length delivery and holding its line outside off, Rohit covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, width on offer from Naveed, Rohit stays back and punches it past cover, no need to run for those, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, Rohit doesn't need to play at that, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, no run, back of a length and angling onto Rohit's hips, he shuffles across and defends it towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Rohit, no run, short of a length and shaping away from outside off, Rohit watches it all along and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit and Dhawan are at the crease. Rohit is on strike. Naveed will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. How long will India take to finish this off? Rohit needs some runs, can't get a better opportunity than this. We have around 65-70 minutes for the dinner break.. that will mean - around 15-16 overs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashwin</b>: "It's been a long time since I've got a fourth wicket, I mean in the sense that I've never got a 4-fer before. It was a running on my mind a bit, but having said that I was focusing on my basics and it's coming out really well. The last time I bowled here at Perth against Sri Lanka I enjoyed a lot. There is a wee bit of spin if you bowl it really slow and apart from that, you are really hitting the top of the face all the time because of the bounce. I quite enjoyed bowling here. The arm-ball was going really well because of the two new balls, you got shine on one of the sides and you can use it pretty much better. If you mix up the pace and if you can really bowl the arm-ball and really set-up the batsman and bowl one really slow, you are going to pretty much get the batsman fending on the front foot, then the leg slip is going to come into play. It's not about the numbers as I've always gone about my business. When I've always turned up for India it's about bowling in the tough situations I really want the ball all the time. If there is a scenario where you need to put the hand up and that's what I am looking at all the time. We pretty much spoke about it even before the tournament began, we've always peaked really well at the ICC tournaments and it was quite a hard time after the Test series, we were playing a tri-series in which we were trying a few combinations and all that. But when the tournament comes, we knew we'll pick it up."]]></line><line><![CDATA[India's fielding too was sharp, though the usually reliable Suresh Raina dropped a simple catch to give Mohammad Naveed a reprieve. In fact, it turned out to be the first drop catch of this World Cup for India. India will look to chase down the target quickly and improve their net run rate. At the other end of the spectrum, UAE's total of 102 is their lowest ever score in ODIs. They need to take a few wickets to at least lift their sagging morale. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Once Krishnachandran Karate was dismissed, rest of the batsmen didn't seem to have a clue while facing up to Ashwin's box of tricks. Only Shaiman Anwar, who has clearly been their best player in this mega event showed the application and the technique to score a flurry of boundaries and compile a well-measured innings of 35. He used the depth of the crease to keep the scoreboard moving. Shaiman also stitched a useful partnership for the last wicket with Manjula Guruge. After playing with a dash of fearlessness in the first two games against Zimbabwe and Ireland, it has been a disastrous performance put up by UAE. On the other hand, the Indian camp will be happy after putting up a thoroughly professional show with the ball in hand.   <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, UAE's openers Andri Berenger and Amjad Ali struggled to cope up with the pace and bounce and were dismissed in the first five overs of the innings. Indian pacers, on their part, used the short ball to good effect. Umesh Yadav snared the wicket of Berenger with a short delivery and Amjad followed him back to the pavilion, as a result of another short delivery from Bhuvneshwar Kumar. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[On the back of Ravichandran Ashwin's excellent spell of spin bowling, India skittled out the opposition ranks for a paltry score.  Ashwin used the breeze from south-west to good effect to hold it up in the air and take a four-wicket haul. He also used the arm ball well. It turned out to be Ashwin's best figures in ODIs. Ravindra Jadeja too picked up a couple of wickets. UAE's batsmen didn't help their cause by showing poor technique against both the pacers and Ashwin. None of their batsmen tried to get themselves in and adjust to the extra pace and bounce on offer at the WACA.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Raina pats Ashwin on the back as the players walk off the field. The Indian fans are absolutely ecstatic in the stands.]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Shaiman Anwar, <b>out</b> Bowled!! You miss, I hit! <b>This is the lowest ODI total for UAE</b>. Fast and full from Yadav, Anwar was beaten for pace as he looked to work it on the on-side, plays completely down the wrong line and misses. The ball shatters middle and off. In fact, he didn't bother to get behind the line and hard moved his feet. <b>Shaiman Anwar b U Yadav 35(49) [4s-6]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[U Yadav to Shaiman Anwar, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Shaiman Anwar, no run, short of length delivery just outside off stump, Anwar punches it off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Shaiman Anwar, <b>FOUR</b>, outside edge but it goes between the keeper and the man at fly slip. Big cheer from the crowd as the <b>100 comes up</b>. Short of a length delivery just outside off stump, Anwar backs away and slashes, gets a thick edge but it goes in the gap]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Manjula Guruge, <b>FOUR</b>, tossed up well outside off stump, Guruge goes for the drive and sends it to the left of mid-off. He gets into double-figures now]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now there is a man at leg slip.]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Manjula Guruge, no run, on the stumps, Guruge covers the line and defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Manjula Guruge, no run, down the leg-side, tossed up, easily blocked]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Manjula Guruge, no run, flatter again from Jadeja, Guruge defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Manjula Guruge, no run, bit of extra bounce on this flighted delivery, Guruge leans forward to defend but it hits the glove]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Manjula Guruge, no run, round the wicket, flatter ball on the off stump, defended back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja [4.0-0-19-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Shaiman Anwar, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, punched off the back foot to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Shaiman Anwar, no run, short delivery from Yadav, Anwar ducks under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Shaiman Anwar, <b>FOUR</b>, poor line and Anwar picks up his fifth boundary. Friendly length ball down the leg-side, Anwar waits for the ball and flicks it along the ground through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Shaiman Anwar, no run, short of length delivery just outside off stump, Anwar hops and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Shaiman Anwar, no run, in the air, but safe! Anwar was lining up to play the pull shot, but this short of length delivery hurried onto him, he ends up flat-batting it in the air, but it doesn't carry to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Shaiman Anwar, no run, on a length and outside off stump, Anwar defends it into the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav [5.0-2-7-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ashwin ends 10-1-25-4. He's bowled exceptionally well today.]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Manjula Guruge, no run, back over the wicket to end his spell. Flighted delivery around the off stump line, Guruge defends it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two backward short legs and a slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, flatter ball on the leg stump, Anwar turns it towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Manjula Guruge, 1 run, Ashwin gives this a lot more air, Guruge looks to loft, gets it on the inside half of the bat and it goes over mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Manjula Guruge, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, defended]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Manjula Guruge, no run, arm-ball outside off stump, dabbed towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Manjula Guruge, no run, uppish but there is no one at short leg. Flighted delivery from round the wicket, Guruge pushes at this uppishly and it rolls towards short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shaiman Anwar, <b>FOUR</b>, this time he connects the sweep very well. Gets across the line and sends it from the middle of the bat through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shaiman Anwar, no run, middle stump line, Anwar cuts it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shaiman Anwar, no run, <b>shout for LBW</b>, but Dhoni doesn't want the review. Flighted delivery on the stumps, looks to sweep but the ball takes the bottom edge and rolls to short fine leg. Good call by the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shaiman Anwar, no run, backs away and cuts the short ball to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shaiman Anwar, no run, full and on the off stump, defended to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shaiman Anwar, no run, flatter delivery on the leg stump, Anwar turns it into the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Manjula Guruge, 2 runs, fullish from Ashwin again, Guruge defends with an angled bat, the ball runs away off the outside edge to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Manjula Guruge, no run, flatter ball outside off stump, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Manjula Guruge, no run, carrom-ball outside off stump, extra bounce, Guruge defends and it hits him on the splice]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Manjula Guruge, no run, <b>shout for LBW</b>, not given. Fast flighted delivery on the stumps, Guruge looks to defend off the front foot, the ball hits on the front foot but it spun too much and would have missed leg stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, short and outside off stump, Anwar punches it off the back foot to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Manjula Guruge, 3 runs, flighted delivery outside off stump, Guruge drives uppishly through cover, but it goes in the gap]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shaiman Anwar, no run, dabs this flighted delivery towards point, Anwar wants the run but Raina quickly runs to his right from slip, puts in the dive and denies the run]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shaiman Anwar, 2 runs, another outside edge as Anwar slashes hard, the ball goes uppishly, Ashwin runs from short third man and puts in the slide to save two]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shaiman Anwar, no run, fullish and spinning away, defended]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shaiman Anwar, no run, flighted delivery outside off stump, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shaiman Anwar, no run, the arm-ball from Jadeja and it almost goes through Anwar's defences. He was waiting for the ball to spin away and was on the back foot to cut, but it came in with the angle and took the inside edge, before escaping past the sticks]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shaiman Anwar, <b>FOUR</b>, outside edge but it goes wide of the man at slip. Flighted delivery outside off stump, Anwar swings hard and gets a thick edge, Ashwin gives chase from short third man but the ball wins the race]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, flatter delivery outside off stump, dabbed to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shaiman Anwar, no run, that's too short, cut very well, but again straight to Dhawan at backward point. A couple of yards either side of the fielder would have been a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shaiman Anwar, no run, carrom-ball outside off stump, Anwar cuts and picks out backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shaiman Anwar, no run, Anwar was late on the attempted flick as Ashwin pushed this through, it spun back sharply and hit him on the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shaiman Anwar, no run, flighted delivery ball, watchfully defended]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shaiman Anwar, no run, short and spinning back into the right-hander, Anwar pushes it to point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Manjula Guruge, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to M Tauqir, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Oh he's bowled him round his legs. Tauqir slips as he goes across the line and tries to sweep, that exposes the leg stump line and the full ball sneaks through to hit middle and leg. The UAE captain doesn't make a statement and it's 71/9. <b>M Tauqir b Ravindra Jadeja 1(5)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ravindra Jadeja to M Tauqir, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, tossed up on the leg stump, Anwar flicks it through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to M Tauqir, 1 run, full outside off stump, Tauqir leans forward and pushes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, on the off stump, tucked to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shaiman Anwar, no run, a touch slower through the air, Anwar easily keeps it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shaiman Anwar, no run, flatter ball, defended]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to M Tauqir, no run, slider outside off stump, Tauqir tries to guide it down to third man but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to M Tauqir, no run, slower through the air, Tauqir looks to defend, gets hit on the pad but the ball was doing down the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to M Tauqir, no run, arm-ball on the leg stump, defended]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Tauqir, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Naveed, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Exposes all three sticks and loses the leg pole. Quicker ball from Ash, Naveed goes leg-side and is late on the cut, the ball rattles into the leg stump. This is the <b>first time Ash has taken 4 wickets</b> in an ODI. UAE are 68/8. Can someone give Anwar some support? <b>Naveed b Ashwin 6(7) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ashwin to Naveed, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Naveed, no run, backs away and swings hard but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, spinning back into the right-hander, Anwar turns it to backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Naveed, no run, <b>first dropped catch for India in the World Cup</b>. Quicker through the air from Jadeja, Naveed pokes at it away from the body, get an outside edge, it goes straight to first slip, Raina juggles, he dives forward to grab it on the second attempt but the ball went down very quickly]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Naveed, no run, backs away and tries to go inside-out but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Naveed, no run, leans forward and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Naveed, no run, shortish and flatter in trajectory, Naveed cuts it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Naveed, <b>SIX</b>, brilliant shot and a brave shot too! Flighted delivery from Jadeja, Naveed takes his front leg out of the way and slogs hard, the ball goes all the way over the wide long-on boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Naveed, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Amjad Javed, <b>out</b> Caught by Raina!! What a bowling change by Dhoni! Jadeja comes on and strikes first ball. Flighted delivery just outside off stump, Javed looks to defend, but gets a thick outside edge, Raina moves to his right and completes an easy catch. In fact, it his third catch of the day. <b>Amjad Javed c Raina b Ravindra Jadeja 2(5)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Ravindra Jadeja to Amjad Javed, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Some consolation for UAE - <b>Tanmoy</b> reports that there was a resounding applause from the crowd when UAE raised their team fifty.]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shaiman Anwar, <b>FOUR</b>, too short and Anwar had two hours to rock back and cut the ball fiercely. The ball goes to the right of backward point, who had no chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shaiman Anwar, no run, arm-ball again, Anwar watchfully dabs this into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Amjad Javed, leg byes, 1 run, flatter ball, Javed misses the flick and the ball goes over leg slip off the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Amjad Javed, <b>wide</b>, Ashwin sprays this down the leg-side, Javed overbalances while trying to flick, Dhoni makes a quick stumping, as he always does, Javed lifted his back foot for a while and brought it down in time before the bails were disturbed]]></line><line><![CDATA[Stumping check sent upstairs, but Dhoni isn't confident. Did Javed get his back foot back in time? Looks like he has! NOT OUT!]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Amjad Javed, no run, arm-ball outside off stump, Javed pushes it away from the body towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Amjad Javed, no run, lunges forward to keep this flighted delivery out]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, spinning into the right-hander, Anwar turns it to fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[These two shared a 107-run stand in the last match. Can they do it again? UAE certainly needs them to come to the party today.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Amjad Javed, 2 runs, full and swinging back in, Javed flicks it along the ground backward square leg, but it didn't look convincing though]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Amjad Javed, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rohan Mustafa, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Mohit Sharma gets his name into the wickets column too. Nothing but a good length delivery, Mustafa was beaten for pace as he was so late in bringing his bat down to defend, the ball thuds into the back pad. The ball pitched in line with middle, struck him in line with middle and Hawk-Eye confirms that it would go on to hit middle and off. The umpire took a long time to make the call, but it was a good decision in the end. It's 52/6 now. <b>Rohan Mustafa lbw b Mohit Sharma 2(12)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mohit Sharma to Rohan Mustafa, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Huge <b>shout for LBW</b> and given. The umpire took a long time to make his decision and Mustafa has decided to review. Looked pretty adjacent but did it pitch in line? No problems with the no-ball. I think that's plumb. No inside edge. Pitching in line and hitting middle and off. OUT! UAE lose their only review.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rohan Mustafa, no run, short of length delivery well wide of off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rohan Mustafa, no run, not close enough to make Mustafa play]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rohan Mustafa, no run, full and outside off stump, Mustafa shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips and a gully for the left-hander.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, short and on the off stump, Anwar pulls it along the ground through mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rohan Mustafa, 2 runs, easy ball on the pads, tucked through square leg and that's the <b>50 up</b> for UAE]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rohan Mustafa, no run, spinning away outside off stump, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rohan Mustafa, no run, flighted delivery angling away from the left-hander, Mustafa pokes away from the body and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rohan Mustafa, no run, fast and full on the stumps, Mustafa just about manages to dig it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rohan Mustafa, no run, this flighted delivery bounces extra, but Mustafa controls it well as he plays that with an angled bat towards second slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rohan Mustafa, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, defended off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place and Ashwin to come over the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shaiman Anwar, no run, full and outside off stump, softly punched to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shaiman Anwar, no run, flicked away to square leg again]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shaiman Anwar, no run, flicked uppishly but doesn't carry to the fielder, Dhawan makes an excellent save diving to his right at square leg. Good length delivery swinging back into the right-hander, Anwar timed it well but couldn't get it in the gap]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shaiman Anwar, no run, good length delivery on the off stump, Anwar wrists it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shaiman Anwar, <b>wide</b>, short ball from Mohit, but it was too high]]></line><line><![CDATA[Well, well! Had India reviewed for that caught behind shout against Rohan Mustafa, they would have got their man. The Snicko shows a spike as the ball takes a faint edge.]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shaiman Anwar, no run, short of length delivery just outside off stump, Anwar hops and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shaiman Anwar, <b>FOUR</b>, first boundary for Anwar. Short ball on the off stump, Anwar rocks back and pulls well through backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rohan Mustafa, no run, shout for caught behind, but the umpire says no. Mustafa dangerously opts to leave this flighted delivery alone, it was so close to the off stump. Maybe Dhoni thought it brushed the glove or bat on the way. They think about the review but decide against it]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rohan Mustafa, no run, drifting back into Mustafa, who manages to defend off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket to the left-hander]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohan Mustafa, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to K Khan, <b>out</b> Caught by Raina!! It's a top edge and Raina is very alert, as he moves swiftly to his right to take an easy catch. Flighted delivery around the leg stump line, Khan gets down on his knees to sweep, the ball takes a soft top edge, Dhoni was going for the catch as well, but Raina moved quickly and called early. In the end, he takes an easy catch to reduce UAE to 44/5. That is the third wicket for Ash! <b>K Khan c Raina b Ashwin 14(28) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ashwin to K Khan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to K Khan, no run, flighted delivery outside off stump, Khan shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to K Khan, no run, spinning away outside off stump, Khan steers it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to K Khan, no run, floated outside off stump, tapped to point off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shaiman Anwar, no run, slower ball on the stumps, Anwar defends it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to K Khan, 1 run, good length delivery just outside off stump, Khan gets an inside edge as he looks to defend and it goes past the sticks]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, short ball on the off stump, Anwar mistimes the pull and it rolls towards deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shaiman Anwar, no run, full and around the middle stump, knocked to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shaiman Anwar, no run, short ball just outside off stump, Anwar lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to K Khan, 1 run, <b>edgeddddd</b> but it goes well wide of the man at second slip. Fullish and angling away from the left-hander, Khan pokes at it without much of a feet movement, the ball takes a thick edge and flies away to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Here is <b>Bharath Ramaraj's</b> analysis of the first 15 overs: UAE made a poor start as they lost the wicket of Andri Berenger in the second over of the innings. Amjad Ali and Krishnachandran Karate too struggled to keep the scorecard ticking. Amjad was eventually, dismissed by Bhuvneshwar Kumar. Umesh Yadav used the bounce and carry to good effect to trouble UAE's batsmen. Bhuvneshwar in his comeback game swung the ball, but it was the short delivery that did the trick for him. To make it worse for UAE, Ravichandran Ashwin snared the wickets of Karate and Swapnil Patil. It is crystal clear that UAE's batsmen lack the experience to play on a deck that is offering assistance for the pacers.<br/><br/>Undoubtedly, WACA is famous for producing lightning fast tracks. However, on occasions, the curators have also come under severe criticism for producing cracked up surfaces. In the 1997 Test match played between Australia and the West Indies, Curtly Ambrose produced an unplayable delivery that hit a crack and stayed low to shatter Greg Blewett's stumps. The next year, Simon Cook ripped through New Zealand's batting line-up on a track that had almost become unplayable by Day 4 of that Test match. In 2000, a List A games between Western Australia and Queensland was abandoned after just five overs were bowled as it proved to be a treacherous track. No wonder, from time to time, curators like Ken Johnston, Scott Hamilton, David Crane, Richard Winder and Cam Sutherland have come under pressure.]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shaiman Anwar, no run, bit of drift back into the right-hander as Ashwin gives this a lot more air, Anwar drives it to cover, who dives to his right and makes a good save]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shaiman Anwar, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Swapnil Patil, <b>out</b> Caught by Dhawan!! Edged and that's a good catch. India's catching at this World Cup has been exceptional. Straighter one from Ash, but it drifts away because of the Fremantle Doctor breeze, Patil looks to defend off the front foot, gets a thick edge, the ball went quickly, but Dhawan dived early to his right at first slip to grab with both hands. <b>Swapnil Patil c Dhawan b Ashwin 7(19) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ashwin to Swapnil Patil, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to K Khan, 1 run, softly pushes this flighted delivery to point and takes an easy run]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, flighted delivery on the leg stump, driven down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to K Khan, leg byes, 1 run, flatter and on the leg stump, Khan misses the glance, the ball rolls to fine leg off the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to K Khan, 2 runs, tossed up outside off stump, Khan drives it along the ground past the man at extra-cover, long-off runs to his right and tidies up]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Swapnil Patil, no run, it's a <b>maiden over</b> from Mohit! Short of a length delivery outside off stump, Patil pushes it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Swapnil Patil, no run, just a bit of shape back into the right-hander on this fuller length delivery, Patil manages to defend it though]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Swapnil Patil, no run, full and well outside off stump, Patil shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Swapnil Patil, no run, slightly fuller in length this time, Patil defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Swapnil Patil, no run, on a length and outside off stump, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Swapnil Patil, no run, half-shout for LBW. Good length delivery just swinging back into the right-hander, Patil tries to work it on the on-side, but misses and gets hit on the pad. The ball was going down the leg-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to K Khan, no run, pushed through this time, Khan punches it off the back foot towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to K Khan, no run, flighted delivery around the off stump, defended off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place for Khan]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, leg stump line, tucked away to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Swapnil Patil, no run, flatter ball from Ashwin, defended easily by Patil]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to K Khan, 1 run, allows the ball to turn away and steers it to the left of the man at slip to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to K Khan, no run, short and spinning away, cut to point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Ashwin to bowl round the wicket to the left-hander]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Swapnil Patil, no run, back of a length just outside off stump, Patil defends off the back foot towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Swapnil Patil, no run, right on the off stump, watchfully defended by Patil]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Swapnil Patil, no run, covers the off stump and defends the length ball off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Swapnil Patil, no run, just a bit of inswing on this good length delivery, Patil gets an inside edge onto pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Swapnil Patil, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, defended towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Swapnil Patil, <b>FOUR</b>, nothing ball and it got the treatment it deserved. Short and wide outside off stump, the line and the length is wrong, enough width for Patil to free his arms and he cuts it away over backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Swapnil Patil, <b>wide</b>, Mohit starts his spell with a bouncer, but it's too high]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to K Khan, no run, the slider to end the over, Khan leans forward and defends well]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, hangs back and flicks the flatter ball to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Swapnil Patil, no run, slightly slower through the air, Patil turns this into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Swapnil Patil, no run, flatter delivery on the off stump, defended]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Swapnil Patil, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Karate, <b>out</b> Caught by Raina!! Dhoni's ploy to have a leg slip has worked for him again as the ball goes straight to the fielder. Nothing but a flighted delivery, Karate looks to work it on the on-side, the ball just brushes the glove, then takes the thigh pad and goes to leg slip, where Raina takes an easy catch. <b>Karate c Raina b Ashwin 4(27)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ashwin to Karate, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Karate, no run, flighted delivery on the off stump, defended]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ashwin has a slip and leg slip in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to K Khan, no run, no feet movement from Khan and he gets beaten. Good length delivery outside off stump, Khan is late on the slash and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to K Khan, no run, hits the pad but it was sliding down the leg-side. Fullish and tailing back in, Khan misses the flick and the ball thuds him on the front pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[Yadav to come round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to K Khan, no run, oh almost went through his defences. Full and just swinging back in, Khan is so late on the flick, he almost fell over, but just managed to clip it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to K Khan, <b>wide</b>, short delivery on the stumps, too high says the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Karate, 1 run, <b>in the airrrr</b>, but it's gone between third slip and gully. Karate pokes at this outswinging short of length delivery, gets a thick edge, the ball goes at a catchable height but it went in the gap]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Karate, <b>wide</b>, gets the radar wrong, goes down the leg-side, easy call for the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to K Khan, 1 run, good length delivery down the leg-side, Khan flicks it along the ground to long leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to K Khan, no run, <b>big shout for LBW</b>. No review from India. Khan hardly moves his feet while trying to work this length ball into the on-side, he gets hit on the pad as the ball swings back in slightly, the ball was pitching just outside leg stump and it was a good call by the umpire]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Karate, no run, short of length, blocked off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Karate, <b>wide</b>, Dhoni did well to collect the ball. Kumar sprays this down the leg-side, Karate misses the glance, the ball swings to the right after passing the batsman, Dhoni was moving to his left, made the adjustment well in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Karate, no run, Karate slightly gets across the sticks, but lets the bumper go through to Dhoni]]></line><line><![CDATA[Back over the wicket to the right-hander]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to K Khan, 1 run, Khan dangerously opts to hang back and flicks this inswinger just in front of off stump towards backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to K Khan, no run, great shape into the left-hander on this length ball, Khan is hit on the pad but it was swinging too much and going down the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bhuvneshwar to come round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to K Khan, no run, short of length delivery angling away from the left-hander, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to K Khan, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a bad ball and Khan punishes it. Short and wide outside off stump, a lot of room for the batsman to work with, Khan waits for the ball to come and cuts over backward point to pick up his first boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Not much breeze, says <b>Tanmoy</b>, the temperature is hovering around 29 degrees - Should be pleasant playing conditions]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Karate, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Karate, no run, full and outside off stump, Karate attempts a lazy drive, he was beaten for pace and it was so close to the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Karate, no run, Karate gets his front foot slightly across the line to cover for the outswing and defends this short of length delivery to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to K Khan, 1 run, watchfully steers the short of length delivery off the back foot to square third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to K Khan, no run, good length delivery just swinging back in, Khan gets right behind and line and blocks it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to K Khan, no run, nice and full outside off stump, asking Khan to drive away from the body but the batsman lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to K Khan, <b>wide</b>, that's way outside off stump for the batsman to be playing at it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Karate, no run, very full, the attempted inswinger doesn't swing much, Karate digs it out to the left of mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Karate, no run, short of length delivery just outside off stump, defended nicely off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Karate, 2 runs, big gap at cover as Bhuvneshwar wants the batsman to drive hard at his swinging deliveries. Karate doesn't go hard at this outswinger, just leans forward and pushes it along the ground through extra-cover for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Karate, no run, softly defends this outswinger off the front foot towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to K Khan, 1 run, a touch fuller in length this time, Khan allows the ball to swing back in and brings his bat down very late, the ball runs away to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to K Khan, no run, short of length delivery just swinging back in, Khan lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Our man, <b>Tanmoy Mookherjee</b>, is at the ground and he has this to say: Far from a full crowd here expectedly with UAE playing, but people still filling in]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Karate, no run, good length delivery outside off stump, Karate defends and gets a thickish edge that rolls towards point. <b>Second maiden over</b> for Yadav]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Karate, no run, this is brilliant bowling from Yadav. He's not trying too much. With good swing on offer, he is concentrating on his outswingers, starts it around the off stump, forces the batsman to play and beats the bat with late outswing]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Karate, no run, short and swinging away outside off stump, Karate drops his wrists and lets it go to Dhoni]]></line><line><![CDATA[Three slips and a gully in place now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Karate, no run, short ball on the stumps, Karate sits under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Karate, no run, back of a length on the off stump, Karate defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Karate, no run, that's a top nut from Yadav. Good length delivery swinging away just outside off stump, Karate plays inside the line and gets beaten]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Khurram Khan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Amjad Ali, <b>out</b> Caught by Dhoni!! Shout from the Indians and the crooked finger goes up. Another short ball does the trick for India. This was around the leg stump line from Bhuvneshwar, Ali gets inside the line and tries to hook, but gets a faint edge and the keeper takes an easy catch. Dhoni was confident in his appeal and the umpire obliged. Actually, the batsman didn't wait for the umpire's signal. <b>Amjad Ali c Dhoni b Bhuvneshwar 4(12)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bhuvneshwar to Amjad Ali, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Karate, 1 run, excellent stuff from Bhuvneshwar. After the shaping the previous ones away, he brings this length ball back into the right-hander, Karate was caught in the crease, the ball takes the inside edge and rolls to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Karate, no run, goes on the back foot and softly defends this short of length delivery to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Karate, no run, back of a length from Bhuvneshwar on this occasion, Karate defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Karate, no run, outswinger on a good length, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Karate, no run, short of length delivery on the off stump, Karate defends off the back foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Amjad Ali, no run, pushed to point off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Amjad Ali, no run, short of a length delivery on the leg stump, Ali pulls and misses, the ball takes the thigh pad and flies towards leg slip, Raina jumps high and puts his right hand out to grab the ball, he palms it and tries to take it on the second attempt, but misses. Anyway, there was no bat involved]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Amjad Ali, no run, inswinger on a good length, Ali misses the flick and gets hit on the pad, the ball was going down the leg-side though]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Amjad Ali, no run, Yadav wants Ali to chase at this widish ball, but the batsman was simply ball-watching on that occasion]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now there is a man at leg slip.]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Amjad Ali, no run, short of length delivery angling away from the left-hander, Ali is late on the cut shot and gets beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Amjad Ali, no run, Ali is in no position to meet this short of length delivery, it hurries onto him and he gets into the thigh pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Amjad Ali, 1 run, on the pads, easily worked away down to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Karate, leg byes, 1 run, down the leg-side, Karate misses the glance and it rolls off the pad into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Amjad Ali, 1 run, in the airrrrr but safe! A full length dive was needed from Dhoni. Short ball from Kumar, Ali gloves the pull, the ball goes to the right of the keeper, he runs to his right but doesn't put in the dive]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Amjad Ali, no run, good length delivery angling away from the left-hander, Ali pokes and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Karate, leg byes, 1 run, huge <b>shout for LBW</b>, not given and India don't want to review. Good length delivery swinging away from Karate, he looks to play across the line, misses and is hit on the back pad, maybe it was just little too high. Hawk-Eye shows that ball would have clipped the top of off stump, but it was umpire's call]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Amjad Ali, 1 run, Ali is lucky to have inside-edged that ball. Bhuvneshwar swings this good length delivery back into the left-hander, Ali looks to work it across, gets an inside edge onto pad and it rolls towards backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Karate, no run, Dale Steyn would be so proud of this over from Yadav. On a good length and starting around the off stump, Karate again plays inside the line of the bat as he looks to defend, the ball swings away very late and zooms past the outside edge. A terrific over from Yadav]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Karate, no run, Karate plays inside the line of this outswinging length ball and gets beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Krishnachandran Karate, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Andri Berenger, <b>out</b> Caught by Dhoni!! He's bowled really well and it's a deserving wicket for Yadav. It's a bouncy and pacy pitch, Yadav bangs this short, Berenger has no clue about the pace on this delivery, he is very late in his pull shot, the ball takes the top edge, Dhoni calls 'mine, mine, mine', moves to his left and easily swallows the ball. This is not the start UAE wanted after opting to bat first. <b>Andri Berenger c Dhoni b U Yadav 4(9) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[U Yadav to Andri Berenger, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Andri Berenger, no run, beauty from Yadav! Excellent shape away from the right-hander, Berenger had to play at it. This length ball was close to the off stump, Berenger tries to defend and the ball swings away very late and beats the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Andri Berenger, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Berenger is hurried by pace, he goes for the pull but toe-ends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Amjad Ali, 1 run, catch it is the cry, but the ball just about manages to evade Rohit Sharma. Yadav starts off with a pacy bumper, Ali was late on the pull shot, the ball took the top edge and flew towards backward square leg, Rohit, from mid-wicket ran and dived full length to his left but couldn't get there in time]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Andri Berenger, <b>FOUR</b>, in the air, but in the gap. Full and shaping away outside off stump, Berenger comes on the front foot and square drives the ball through cover-point and opens his account in style]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Andri Berenger, no run, again Bhuvneshwar is asking questions. Good length and swinging away outside off stump, Berenger covers the off stump and lets it go through to Dhoni]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Andri Berenger, no run, good shape away from the right-hander, teasing line from Bhuvneshwar. On a fullish length and outside off stump, Berenger thought about playing at it, but let it go at the last moment]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Andri Berenger, no run, full and outside off stump, Berenger covers the sticks and shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Andri Berenger, no run, Bhuvneshwar bowls this full and attempts the inswinger, the ball swings nicely into the right-hander, Berenger leans forward and drives well, Rahane makes a good stop to his left at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Andri Berenger, no run, nice inswing on this fuller length delivery, Berenger leans forward and defends it into the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Amjad Ali, <b>2 wides</b>, wayward start for Bhuvneshwar. He bowls this down the leg-side, Dhoni had to stretch full length to his right to half-stop the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Amjad Ali and Andri Berenger are at the crease. Amjad Ali is on strike. Bhuvneshwar will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bhuvneshwar Kumar will take the new ball on his return. He has two slips in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The anthems are done and the UAE openers put on their helmets as India walk onto the field.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The teams are walking out for the national anthems. UAE's "Ishy Bilady" will be followed by India's "Jana Gana Mana."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>India</b> (Playing XI): Shikhar Dhawan, Rohit Sharma, Virat Kohli, Ajinkya Rahane, Suresh Raina, MS Dhoni(w/c), Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Mohit Sharma, Umesh Yadav]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>United Arab Emirates</b> (Playing XI): Amjad Ali, Andri Berenger, Krishnachandran Karate, Khurram Khan, Swapnil Patil(w), Shaiman Anwar, Rohan Mustafa, Amjad Javed, Mohammad Naveed, Mohammad Tauqir(c), Manjula Guruge]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>United Arab Emirates have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Tauqir</b>: "I think we were a bit unlucky in the last game, putting up 280 on the board is a good effort by the batsmen. I think we need to bowl well and field well to defend the total. We are just ready for this game, we will try to put up a decent performance again. We will bat first. I think it's a good wicket to bat on first and we would like to put up a total and then defend it. No (when asked if UAE made any changes). It's the same side as the last game."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhoni</b>: "I think we have been putting in a lot of effort and it's starting to reflect in our performances. It's good, you want to win games, you want to execute your plans well and so far, all the three departments, they have done that. Not disappointed, we were looking to bat first, but at the same time it's good that, we have batted first quite a few times and this gives us an opportunity to chase down the total. For the long term benefit we have rested <b>Shami</b> in this game, <b>Bhuvi</b> comes in his place. It also gives us a chance to have a look at Bhuvi. He has been our main bowler for close to an year or so, but it gives him an opportunity coming back from injury. He has been fit for a long time, so he has been just waiting for this opportunity to come and play."]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's <b>toss time</b> folks!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pitch Report</b>: "This is one of the fastest pitches in the world. It's very hard and the fast bowlers will have a big smile on their faces. The ball comes on to the bat, because of its true bounce, so it is good for batting as well. As a batsman, the key word here is if you get through the first 20 balls, you can score runs. India are just starting to show some form. I would be certainly selecting a pure bowler, I wouldn't go for an all-rounder in Stuart Binny. Bat first and get runs on the board." reckon <b>Sanjay Manjrekar</b> and <b>Tom Moody</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[My colleague, <b>Pradeep</b> has this on Krishna Chandran Karate - "Classmate with Robin Uthappa at school. Classmate with Binny at college and also represented Bangalore University at cricket.']]></line><line><![CDATA["For people who saw me playing in my shorts, with a tennis ball, on the streets of my home village of Kollengode, it's going to be a big thing to watch me on TV, playing against India, in a World Cup match, at a ground like the WACA."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here he tells <b>Sportskeeda's Dipankar Lahiri</b> about his younger days. "It's going to be a big moment for people back home," said the 30-year-old all-rounder, who moved to the Gulf in 2010.]]></line><line><![CDATA[One more Indian connection in the UAE camp. Krishna Chandran Karate hails from a village in Kerala and once was part of a Bangalore club side featuring Stuart Binny. He also is a former team-mate of S Sreesanth as the duo had played together for Kerala.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here is Swapnil talking to the <b>Indian Express' Sandeep Dwivedi</b>. "As juniors we have spent much time together. Because of distances in Mumbai, we couldn't hang out together after games but Ajinkya is like a brother. Once I moved out of India, we lost contact. But that day at the Dubai airport, he was returning from India's A tour to South Africa, it was like old times again," says Patil, eagerly awaiting the moment when he'll gets off the flight at Perth airport. "I haven't got in touch with Ajinkya yet since landing here but will meet him there and if possible take him out for dinner. Actually, not just him, I also have also been in Mumbai sides that had Rohit Sharma and Dhawal Kulkarni."]]></line><line><![CDATA[An Indian connection in the UAE camp! UAE's Swapnil Patil was born in Vasai in Mumbai. Swapnil and Ajinkya Rahane were team-mates and were part of the Mumbai Under-14, 16, 19 and 22 middle order. Bigger things were destined for Swapnil but unfortunately the going got tough. He gave up and headed to the Gulf to join a business group that had a cricket team. Job security was there and Swapnil could concentrate on his cricket. Also playing in the UAE league was a far easier proposition.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Tauqir</b> - "Zimbabwe won the game in the 48th over and the Ireland game went up to the last over. We need to cross the line now and we are getting closer to a victory."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Some quotes for your perusal: <b>Dhawan</b> - "Just staying calm, working hard and keeping my work ethic strong."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather update:</b> It never rains at Perth! Or does so rarely. No problems with the weather for Saturday's clash. A high of 31 degrees is expected on match day.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pre-match team news, <b>UAE</b>: UAE will in all probability play the same team that played against Ireland.]]></line><line><![CDATA[With Shami ruled out, either Bhuvneshwar Kumar or Stuart Binny will get a game at Perth. Going by India's training session before the game, it looks like that Binny will get the nod as he was involved in a rigorous practice session. That should be the only forced change that India may make despite playing against UAE.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pre-match team news, <b>India</b>: Mohammed Shami was ruled out of Saturday's clash against UAE with a minor knee injury. Shami had an ultrasound guided injection on his problematic knee yesterday. "Mohammed Shami got mild left-knee problem and had ultrasound guided injection yesterday," India's media manager, RN Baba told at the pre-match press conference in Perth. "For his long term management perspective he won't be available for tomorrow match against UAE."]]></line><line><![CDATA["If you look at the Zimbabwe game and the following one against Ireland, there was a definite improvement in our overall performance," he said. "Zimbabwe won the game in the 48th over and the Ireland game went up to the last over. We need to cross the line now and we are getting closer to a victory."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Despite being unable to put it past Zimbabwe and Ireland, Tauqir is looking at the positive side of things, saying they are inching closer to their maiden victory.]]></line><line><![CDATA[What is the UAE skipper saying ahead of his clash? <b>Mohammad Tauqir</b> has said his team is not daunted by the prospect of facing defending champions India. "We are getting closer to victory and the mood in the dressing room is very positive," Tauqir told reporters in a media interaction ahead of the game on Friday. "Everybody is looking forward to this game. We are not intimidated by any big name or big teams. All the games are equally important to us and the intensity is going to be the same in the next match as it was in the previous two games, and going forward also."]]></line><line><![CDATA["I want to see the likes of Rohit Sharma, (Suresh) Raina get in and get some runs. You never know what can happen later on in the tournament, so it's a perfect opportunity for India to try out a few new players, get them in form, get their confidence up. It is important that you have an entire squad ready to fire and I think Dhoni and Co should be thinking about that. There should not be any reservation about winning or losing because they are playing against one of the minnows," opined Lara.]]></line><line><![CDATA[West Indian legend <b>Brian Lara</b> feels India are playing the best cricket of the World Cup and wants them to test their bench strength against UAE. "I think you would expect the reserves of the Indian team to dominate the opposition (UAE). The likes of Shikhar Dhawan and (Virat) Kohli might be scoring runs now but what is important is that later on in the tournament in the critical games if India is forced to call upon somebody from the reserves then they have the time out in the middle to do so."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhawan also took the opportunity to focus on Ravi Shastri's role which he feels central to him being back in form. "His [Shastri] presence is very big on our side; he has always given me a lot of confidence, especially when I needed it," he said. "Ravi is central to my team-mates and my support staff. Because of that today I'm scoring runs - it is because my team-mates and my support staff have supported me."]]></line><line><![CDATA[He must have changed something, surely, to transform into the Dhawan of Mohali. "Just staying calm, working hard and keeping my work ethic strong," Dhawan reflected. "Of course, it's always a learning thing. I enjoy the journey rather than the destination. So I was enjoying that phase of my life too, and I learned a lot. I changed a few things, but not any major things. Just little things. Maybe you won't be able to see - it's that little of something. I was just [trying to] enjoy the tour."]]></line><line><![CDATA[One man who has turned around his fortunes remarkably is Indian opener, Shikhar Dhawan. After a miserable series Down Under in both the Test and the tri-series that followed, Dhawan's selection for the World Cup was questioned by some. So poor was his form. He was dropped for the Sydney Test as KL Rahul took his place at the top of the order and promptly scored a ton, which only put more pressure on him. The fortunes though have changed in a matter of two games. Against Pakistan he was set for a hundred when he was run out and against South Africa at the 'G' he was just superb. Against Steyn, Philander and Morkel he showed why when he is in form, he is a match-winner for India, at the top of the order.]]></line><line><![CDATA["He regularly works night shifts at our petroleum storage terminal in Al Quoz so that he can train early evenings with the UAE team."]]></line><line><![CDATA["Shaiman has made us all proud. Immediately on arrival he and his family will be gifted a free holiday as a token of our appreciation. His performance is the result of his dedication and hard work," he said.]]></line><line><![CDATA[After watching the match, Ramamoorthy told Gulf News how he had granted leave for Shaiman to play in the World Cup and his reward when he gets back.]]></line><line><![CDATA[UAE had plenty of opportunities in the field when Wilson and O'Brien were batting, but those mishaps proved to be costly as they let the Irish off the hook. UAE, though had shown that they are a side which won't go down without a fight. Shaiman Anwar who scored the hundred was showered with praise. Anwar plays for Wings SRT Cricket Club and is employed as a store in-charge by Trotter Group, the company that owns the team. Anwar and his family earned a free holiday from his local team owner and employer Neeraj Ramamoorthy.]]></line><line><![CDATA[They faced Ireland in their second game and it was a game they should've won. Shaiman Anwar became the first UAE batsman to hit a century in World Cups as his side made 278. Defending the target, Mohammad Tauqir's off-spin caused all sorts of trouble to the Irish with his teasing line and length. Ireland were four down and in trouble at 97/4. Gary Wilson though, stitched useful partnerships with Andrew Balbirnie and then with Kevin O'Brien as he took his side closer. O'Brien was though dropped en route to his 50 and that eventually proved to be the turning point. It came down to 3 needed off 6 balls in the final over with two wickets in hand and George Dockrell took the Irish home to a nerve-wracking win.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now let's see how UAE have done so far in this World Cup. They started off with a game against Zimbabwe at Nelson. They posted 285 and had Zimbabwe at 167/5 in the 33rd over. Their hopes were high at that stage of an upset win but that was thwarted by the two lefties - Sean Williams and Craig Ervine who put on a stand of 83 to take their side closer. Ervine was dismissed but Williams kept his nerve and along with Chigumbura carried his side home. UAE were beaten but not disgraced at all.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riding on Dhawan's brilliant hundred, India posted 307 and then in the field came out like a side possessed. They bowled and fielded as well as they have done for a long time. The pressure got to AB and he got run out, trying to steal a second against Mohit Sharma's arm. That was the turning point of the game and once AB was back in the hut, India just coasted home. It was a comprehensive win that sent a strong statement from the Indian side. They may have struggled on Aussie soil till the World Cup began, but in just two games, with their performances have shown that they won't give up their World Cup that easily.]]></line><line><![CDATA[If Pakistan's match was about trying to keep their streak intact. Against South Africa it was time to break their jinx against the African nation in World Cups. India had met South Africa thrice in World Cups, going into their clash at the MCG and had lost all three. They were beaten in 1992, 1999 and 2011. South Africa were favorites going into this year's clash. India desperately wanted to end their unbeaten run. It set up for a fascinating clash.]]></line><line><![CDATA[They said the streak wouldn't last forever. 5-0 would become 5-1. Pakistan were brimming with hope ahead of their clash with India. Misbah and Afridi were confident that they were going to change history. Nothing of that sort happened. India outplayed Pakistan and extended their streak to 6-0 in World Cups. Pakistan was made to wait once again.]]></line><line><![CDATA[A warm welcome to one and all wherever you are as we welcome you to India's clash with UAE at Perth. It's a battle between David and Goliath. The mighty superpower vs the minnows. A battle of unequals. Before we go any further, let's have a look at how India have done in this World Cup so far.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Zarwani lasted seven balls but later admitted to Donald he was "stupid" not to wear a helmet.]]></line><line><![CDATA["The next ball was a perfect on-the-money bouncer: he could not really duck, he sort of stood up and just flinched. It really hit flush on his head. The ball almost came back to me, that's how hard it hit him. His hat fell off. Everyone rushed to him to check if he was ok. He said he was fine, picked up his bat and said he was ready to bat. Steve Bucknor, one of the on-field umpires on the day, came up to me and told me whether I knew he could not bat. 'There's no way I'm bowling him another bouncer,' I assured him. Symcox was fuming, he wanted another bouncer. I told him the game was dead, they had lost, and I was not going to bowl another bouncer."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Allan Donald revisited the incident a few years back to a prominent cricket website. "When he walked in to bat he wore just a normal floppy hat. I didn't know who he was. The game was going nowhere. I had just got a wicket. A furious Pat Symcox came to me and said 'Listen, who does this guy think he is?' During the huddle Jonty Rhodes took up the fight, saying the batsman had no idea about cricket. He had come into this game without any cricketing pedigree, and had apparently promised his players that if UAE won one game in the World Cup, he would buy each a Mercedes Benz or something like that. But Jonty didn't want me to bowl Zarawani a bouncer as he thought he couldn't bat and I might hurt him. Someone else blurted out, 'Just knock his head off.' I said I'd bowl a bouncer, but make sure it went way over.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Thankfully, even though Zarawani was left tottering by that vicious blow to the head, he survived. It must also be said that Zarawani was a multi-millionaire and owned more than a dozen expensive cars - probably the only player in that tournament to own that many. When anyone talks or starts a conversation regarding UAE, then the first thing that comes to mind is this incident in 1996. There is a thin line between bravery and stupidity and that day certainly, Zarawani's move was bordering on the latter. We couldn't resist bringing that incident up. It was too juicy!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>12:30 Local Time, 04:30 GMT, 10:00 IST:</b> In their opening World Cup, UAE were up against South Africa in 1996. UAE's captain, Sultan Zarawani, walked out to bat without a helmet, wearing just a sunhat. Everyone were wondering why. Did he forget his helmet? Or was he making a statement against Allan Donald and Co.? Well, whatever he was trying to do, it must be said, it wasn't very brave. Allan Donald, fired up on seeing Zarawani walk out with a helmet, pinged him on the head first ball with a vicious bouncer. The ball thudded into the head and legend has it that, Pat Symcox fired Donald up by saying this - "Al, this guy's asking for it," - when Zarawani walked out to bat.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/>The last time India played an ODI at the WACA ground in Perth, they lost their last nine wickets for 97 runs in the last league match of the Carlton Mid tri-series against England, a problem that was not looking like going away anytime soon. However, since the start of the 2015 ICC Cricket World Cup however that problem has been put to bed with the team going on to post 300-plus totals against the bowling might of Pakistan and South Africa.<br/><br/>Having negotiated the two strongest teams in their group already, the next week for India at Perth poses a different conundrum, especially when they face UAE on Saturday: how to approach the game, and what are the positives they are hoping to take out of facing an Associate team that has lost both its opening fixtures.<br/><br/>A cue to that was visible during the team's training session on Friday. While the top-order batsmen went about their usual routine of facing quick bowlers, spinners and a barrage of balls delivered by the sidearm device, captain MS Dhoni had a longer-than-usual batting session at the WACA nets.<br/><br/>In the first session, assistant coach Sanjay Bangar sent in deliveries with the sidearm device which Dhoni negotiated with a straight bat, and proceeded onto the next practice wicket to face the spinners. He took a break after that longish stint and observed the other batsmen while having a light-hearted conversation with the media assembled towards the side, before heading up to Virat Kohli and team director Ravi Shastri, swinging his arms without bat in hand.<br/><br/>While Kohli obliged his young fans with autographs and by acknowledging their cheers, Dhoni went back in to face the sidearm device, this time hitting the ball with the ferocity people have become accustomed to. The Indian captain has observed the team's only visible flaw during this tournament so far, which is not being able to capitalize in the last five overs of the innings, and settling for 300 when they should have got 320 or 330.<br/><br/>With Mohammed Shami out of the game with a knee injury, India have been forced to rethink their combination for Saturday, with Stuart Binny or Bhuvneshwar Kumar the likely replacements, even though both their involvement in the training session didn't indicate as to which of the two would get the nod. While Bhuvneshwar bowled without any discomfort in his ankle that forced him to miss a majority of the Australian tour, Binny also bowled in tandem with his pace-bowling colleague before going on to have a bat towards the end of the team's practice session. Binnys performance in India's last game at Perth - he took 2 for 36 from his 10 overs - may tip the scales in his favour.<br/><br/>India may not be losing any sleep over their opposition but seem to be addressing some of their concerns judiciously, something that may make them reconsider their decision to bat first after winning the toss. Teams in this competition have generally found it difficult to chase down totals with the exception of Ireland and Zimbabwe, who overcame UAE in a high-scoring chase, and India may want to go down that road to test themselves before facing West Indies in their next match.<br/><br/>UAE, on the other hand, have impressed despite narrowly missing out on victories against Zimbabwe and Ireland under the watchful eyes of the Pakistani duo of Aaqib Javed and Mudassar Nazar, the team's head coach and batting coach, respectively. Shaiman Anwar's quickfire century wasn't enough for the team as captain Mohammad Tauqir lamented in his interaction with the media, saying the batsmen needed to take a cue from his efforts in order to bat longer.<br/><br/>Tauqir, however, was positive ahead of the match and was confident of his team standing up to the defending champions, and would be proud of the improvements his team has shown in all three aspects of the game after a poor World T20 last year.<br/><br/>India's bowlers have turned in strong performances in both their games and UAE would have their hands full against Umesh Yadav and Mohit Sharma on a bouncy WACA pitch. Lack of swing in the hot and windy city will encourage the batsmen to play their strokes, but a bigger threat to their batsmen would be in negotiating the spin duo of R Ashwin and Ravindra Jadeja.<br/><br/><b>Probable XIs:</b><br/><br/>India: 1. Shikhar Dhawan, 2. Rohit Sharma, 3. Virat Kohli, 4. Ajinkya Rahane, 5. Suresh Raina, 6. MS Dhoni (capt and wk), 7. Ravindra Jadeja, 8. Stuart Binny/Bhuvneshwar Kumar, 9. R Ashwin, 10. Mohit Sharma, 11. Umesh Yadav<br/><br/>UAE: 1. Amjad Ali, 2. Andri Berenger, 3. Krishna Chandran, 4. Khurram Khan, 5. Swapnil Patil (wk), 6. Shaiman Anwar, 7. Rohan Mustafa, 8. Mohammad Naveed, 9. Amjad Javed, 10. Mohammad Tauqir (capt), 11. Manjula Guruge]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>United Arab Emirates</b> (From): Amjad Ali, Andri Berenger, Krishnachandran Karate, Khurram Khan, Swapnil Patil(w), Shaiman Anwar, Amjad Javed, Rohan Mustafa, Mohammad Naveed, Mohammad Tauqir(c), Manjula Guruge, Nasir Aziz, Fahad Alhashmi, Kamran Shazad, Saqlain Haider]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>India</b> (From): Shikhar Dhawan, Rohit Sharma, Virat Kohli, Ajinkya Rahane, Suresh Raina, MS Dhoni(c/w), Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Umesh Yadav, Mohit Sharma, Stuart Binny, Ambati Rayudu, Axar Patel]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>102</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>10</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>31.3</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="United Arab Emirates">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1365</playerid>
					<name>Amjad Ali</name>
					<batsman-name>Amjad Ali</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Amjad Ali</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Bhuvneshwar</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1726</bowlerId>
						<fielder>MS Dhoni</fielder>
						<fielderId>265</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10124</playerid>
					<name>Andri Berenger</name>
					<batsman-name>Andri Berenger</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Andri Berenger</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Umesh</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1858</bowlerId>
						<fielder>MS Dhoni</fielder>
						<fielderId>265</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10041</playerid>
					<name>Krishnachandran Karate</name>
					<batsman-name>Karate</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Karate</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>27</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Ashwin</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1593</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Suresh Raina</fielder>
						<fielderId>413</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>81</playerid>
					<name>Khurram Khan</name>
					<batsman-name>K Khan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>K Khan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>14</runs>
					<balls>28</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Ashwin</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1593</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Suresh Raina</fielder>
						<fielderId>413</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9834</playerid>
					<name>Swapnil Patil</name>
					<batsman-name>Swapnil Patil</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Swapnil Patil</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>7</runs>
					<balls>19</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Ashwin</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1593</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Shikhar Dhawan</fielder>
						<fielderId>1446</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9837</playerid>
					<name>Shaiman Anwar</name>
					<batsman-name>Shaiman Anwar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shaiman Anwar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>35</runs>
					<balls>49</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Umesh</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1858</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9835</playerid>
					<name>Rohan Mustafa</name>
					<batsman-name>Rohan Mustafa</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rohan Mustafa</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Mohit Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8181</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1366</playerid>
					<name>Amjad Javed</name>
					<batsman-name>A Javed</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Amjad Javed</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>R Jadeja</bowler>
					<bowlerId>587</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Suresh Raina</fielder>
						<fielderId>413</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9832</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Naveed</name>
					<batsman-name>Naveed</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Naveed</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Ashwin</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1593</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>87</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Tauqir</name>
					<batsman-name>M Tauqir</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M Tauqir</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>R Jadeja</bowler>
					<bowlerId>587</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9830</playerid>
					<name>Manjula Guruge</name>
					<batsman-name>Manjula Guruge</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Manjula Guruge</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>10</runs>
					<balls>16</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>10124</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>7</runs>
				<overs>1.4</overs>
				<batsman>Andri Berenger</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Andri Berenger</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1365</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>13</runs>
				<overs>4.6</overs>
				<batsman>Amjad Ali</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Amjad Ali</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>10041</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>28</runs>
				<overs>10.2</overs>
				<batsman>Krishnachandran Karate</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Karate</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9834</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>41</runs>
				<overs>14.5</overs>
				<batsman>Swapnil Patil</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Swapnil Patil</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>81</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>44</runs>
				<overs>16.4</overs>
				<batsman>Khurram Khan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>K Khan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9835</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>52</runs>
				<overs>19.5</overs>
				<batsman>Rohan Mustafa</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rohan Mustafa</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1366</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>61</runs>
				<overs>21.1</overs>
				<batsman>Amjad Javed</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Javed</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9832</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>68</runs>
				<overs>22.3</overs>
				<batsman>Mohammad Naveed</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Naveed</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>87</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>71</runs>
				<overs>23.6</overs>
				<batsman>Mohammad Tauqir</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Tauqir</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9837</playerid>
				<nbr>10</nbr>
				<runs>102</runs>
				<overs>31.3</overs>
				<batsman>Shaiman Anwar</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Shaiman Anwar</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>9</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>4</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>13</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="India">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1726</playerid>
					<name>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</name>
					<bowler-name>Bhuvneshwar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bhuvneshwar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>19</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1858</playerid>
					<name>Umesh Yadav</name>
					<bowler-name>Umesh</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>U Yadav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>6.3</overs>
					<maidens>2</maidens>
					<runsoff>15</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<bowler-name>Ashwin</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ashwin</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>4</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Mohit Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mohit Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>16</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<bowler-name>R Jadeja</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>23</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1446</playerid>
					<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhawan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhawan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>576</playerid>
					<name>Rohit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Rohit</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rohit</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<bowler-name>Kohli</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Kohli</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1447</playerid>
					<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
					<bowler-name>A Rahane</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rahane</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<bowler-name>Raina</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Raina</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhoni</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhoni</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>104</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>1</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>18.5</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="India">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>576</playerid>
					<name>Rohit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Rohit</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rohit</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>57</runs>
					<balls>55</balls>
					<fours>10</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1446</playerid>
					<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhawan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhawan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>14</runs>
					<balls>17</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Naveed</bowler>
					<bowlerId>9832</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Rohan Mustafa</fielder>
						<fielderId>9835</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Kohli</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>33</runs>
					<balls>41</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1447</playerid>
					<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
					<batsman-name>A Rahane</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rahane</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Raina</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhoni</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<batsman-name>R Jadeja</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<batsman-name>Ashwin</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ashwin</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1726</playerid>
					<name>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</name>
					<batsman-name>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Mohit Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mohit Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1858</playerid>
					<name>Umesh Yadav</name>
					<batsman-name>Umesh</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>U Yadav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1446</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>29</runs>
				<overs>6.3</overs>
				<batsman>Shikhar Dhawan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dhawan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>0</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>0</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="United Arab Emirates">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>9832</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Naveed</name>
					<bowler-name>Naveed</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Naveed</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9830</playerid>
					<name>Manjula Guruge</name>
					<bowler-name>Manjula Guruge</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Manjula Guruge</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>6</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>19</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1366</playerid>
					<name>Amjad Javed</name>
					<bowler-name>A Javed</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Amjad Javed</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>12</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10041</playerid>
					<name>Krishnachandran Karate</name>
					<bowler-name>Karate</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Karate</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>17</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>87</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Tauqir</name>
					<bowler-name>M Tauqir</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M Tauqir</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2.5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>21</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1365</playerid>
					<name>Amjad Ali</name>
					<bowler-name>Amjad Ali</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Amjad Ali</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10124</playerid>
					<name>Andri Berenger</name>
					<bowler-name>Andri Berenger</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Andri Berenger</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>81</playerid>
					<name>Khurram Khan</name>
					<bowler-name>K Khan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>K Khan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9834</playerid>
					<name>Swapnil Patil</name>
					<bowler-name>Swapnil Patil</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Swapnil Patil</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9837</playerid>
					<name>Shaiman Anwar</name>
					<bowler-name>Shaiman Anwar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shaiman Anwar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9835</playerid>
					<name>Rohan Mustafa</name>
					<bowler-name>Rohan Mustafa</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rohan Mustafa</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



