<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="12879" >
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>25th Match, Pool B</gameDesc>
		<series>WC 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Pakistan</home>
		<away>United Arab Emirates</away>
		<teamsabbr>PAK vs UAE</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>PAK</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>UAE</awayabbr>
		<homeId>3</homeId>
		<awayId>7</awayId>
		<venue>McLean Park, Napier</venue>
		<startdate>04 03 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>04 03 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>United Arab Emirates</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Pakistan won by 129 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Pakistan</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>129</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Johanes Cloete</Name>
			<Country>RSA</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>S Ravi</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Richard Illingworth</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Chris Broad</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>01:00</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150304084013</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>UAE</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>Pak</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>210</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>8</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>50</batteamovers>
		<status>Pakistan won by 129 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>9832</playerid>
			<name>Mohammad Naveed*</name>
			<batsman-name>Naveed</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Naveed</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>0</runs>
			<balls-faced>0</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>87</playerid>
			<name>Mohammad Tauqir</name>
			<batsman-name>M Tauqir</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>M Tauqir</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>0</runs>
			<balls-faced>1</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1120</playerid>
			<name>Sohail Khan*</name>
			<bowler-name>S Khan</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Sohail Khan</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>9</overs>
			<maidens>2</maidens>
			<runs>54</runs>
			<wickets>2</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1051</playerid>
			<name>Wahab Riaz</name>
			<bowler-name>Riaz</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Riaz</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>10</overs>
			<maidens>1</maidens>
			<runs>54</runs>
			<wickets>2</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>340</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>9834</playerid>
<name>Swapnil Patil</name>
<player-runs>36</player-runs>
<player-balls>68</player-balls>
<runs>210</runs>
<wicket-nbr>8</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>1051</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Riaz</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>12</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>13</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[1 . . . . 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. 3 2 1 4 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. . . 4 . 4 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 Wd W 2 . W . ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_WC/PAK_UAE_MAR04/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[That's it from this game. However, the entertainment continues, hop over to the Australia-Afghanistan game, where the Aussies are piling on the runs and Warner has a chance of getting a double hundred. Hope you enjoyed our coverage as much as we did bring it you. On behalf of <b>Mani, Sriram</b> and my co-commentator <b>Sidhant Maheshwari</b>, this is <b>Akshay Maanay</b> signing off. Until next time, take care and Adios!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@dkmohanty:</b> After all the ridicules he gets, Umar Akmal is now 2nd in the list of most dismissals by wicket keepers in #CWC15 with 8 victims.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@FaisalJavedKhan:</b> Misbah proved it today if there is a solid start and other batsmen stay on the wicket he can play fast. #PakvsUAE #CWC15]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@Saj_PakPassion:</b> Shahid Afridi goes ahead of Shaun Pollock & up to 5th place in the list of leading wicket takers in ODIs #cwc15 #PakvUAE]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@cricket_U:</b> Pakistan win by 129 runs. They have done their NRAJ a huge favour. Above Ireland now and slightly below West Indies. #PakvUAE]]></line><line><![CDATA[Lets have a look at some of the <b>tweets</b> from this game:]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Misbah:</b> "That's a much needed win for us and obviously we won by a big margin. So, now we can just relax a little bit on the net run-rate also. But, the next game is a very important for us and we need to focus on that."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Tauqir:</b> "Definitely, I think 340 something was a big total for us. But, quite a few positives from the batting side. Batting all 50 overs was a very good effort and we are happy with this effort. He (Shaiman Anwar) is a very good batsman and he is very confident player in the team. His nickname in the dressing room is Sir Viv (smiles). We wanted to put up a decent performance throughout the tournament. We had quite a few good games against Zimbabwe and Ireland. I think even today the effort was decent and going forward also we would like to do well."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shehzad:</b> "Pretty much satisified before the big game. Everybody had a look at us with what happened in the last game against Zimbabwe. Wahab (Riaz) really helped us a lot with his innings. Of course we didn't want to be in the similar kind of situation. So, everybody took the responsibility and I pushed myself up. I worked hard with the batting coach and other coaches as well. Everybody has been very supportive. I am very happy to see the way Haris Sohail batted and in the end the way Misbah and Sohaib Maqsood finished the innings. I am very pleased to see them, you know getting the momentum at the right time before the big game against South Africa. We have got no other choice, we need to stand up as a team and we need to show character there."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ahmed Shehzad</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his 93.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Our man, <b>Jamie</b> at the ground tells us, "So the crowd of 2,400 people didn't get a great game. Pakistan won't mind, beating UAE to stay alive."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier in the day, riding on fifties from Shehzad, Sohail and Misbah, Pakistan managed to post 339/6 on the board, their second highest total in a World Cup game. They scored 124 runs off the final 10 overs and 71 off their last 5, all thanks to some good hitting from their lower order. Their batting was great, but the Pakistanis would feel that they should have done much better with the ball.]]></line><line><![CDATA[On the other hand, the Pakistani bowlers bowled well in patches, especially Sohail Khan, who was the chief destroyer. In his first spell of 7 overs, he picked up 2 wickets and gave away just 25 runs. However, Javed carved Sohail for 20, including 2 sixes and 2 fours in his 8th over. The other bowlers chipped in with a few good overs as well, but they lacked the killer instinct as they failed to pick up all the wickets.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Khurram Khan fell for 43 in the 30th over, but Shaiman Anwar kept battling through the middle stages. He registered yet another fifty, his 3rd fifty plus score in this edition of the World Cup. He also overtook Kumar Sangakkara, to become the <b>top run-scorer in the World Cup</b> till now. After Anwar departed on 62, Patil and Javed then took on the mantle of keeping the Pakistani bowlers out. They did extremely well in the final overs. Patil knocked the ball around and looked for singles while Javed hit a few lusty blows out of the park to provide some entertainment to the crowd. In fact, this is UAE's <b>highest score against any top 8 nation in ODIs.</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[So, the inevitable result is out and Pakistan have won this by a big margin. After UAE lost 3 wickets in quick succession at the start of the innings, there was only one result possible from this game and that was a Pakistani win. Even though Khurram Khan and Shaiman Anwar put on 83 runs together to steady the innings, it was never enough to give UAE a chance to take the game away from Pakistan's grasp. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to M Tauqir, no run, <b>Pakistan have won by 129 runs</b>. The players shake hands with each other. Fullish and on off, Tauqir comes half-forward and knocks it to cover. That was bowled with a cross seam. The UAE players come out to congratulate their opposition]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Tauqir, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Cleaned up! It is a perfect delivery from Riaz. The umpire checks for a no-ball, it is fine. A yorker aimed right at the base of off-stump, Patil makes room and fails to lay bat on that, the ball crashes into the stumps and sends the bails flashing. <b>Swapnil Patil b Riaz 36(68) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riaz to Swapnil Patil, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, no run, bouncer following the batsman, Patil looks to pull it while ducking under it, can't reach it in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, 2 runs, slower short ball just outside off, Patil moves away to the leg-side and slaps it over backward point for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Naveed, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Amjad Javed, <b>out</b> Caught by Sohail Khan!! An entertaining innings comes to an end. Sohail Khan throws the ball in frustration. It was banged in midway down the wicket, Javed goes for the pull, splices it to long-on, Sohail settles under it and reverse cups it safely. <b>Amjad Javed c Sohail Khan b Riaz 40(33) [4s-5 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riaz to Amjad Javed, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Amjad Javed, <b>wide</b>, keeps it outside off, it was on the tram-line and the umpire signals a wide. Riaz says that the batsman was moving away to the leg-side, but it was too far away]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, continues from round the wicket, dishes out a full toss, Patil taps it to extra cover and hands the strike back to Javed]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[48.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Javed, <b>FOUR</b>, fantastic shot! Sohail Khan misses the yorker, bowls an overpitched delivery, Javed makes room and lofts it beautifully inside out over extra cover. The timing was simply sublime on that]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Javed, no run, yorker just outside leg, Javed backed away and went for a mighty slog, the ball slipped under his bat, luckily it was not on the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Javed, <b>FOUR</b>, another streaky boundary for Javed! Full and tailing in, Javed clears his front leg and goes for the heave, the ball squirts off the inside edge to the right of short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Javed, no run, quick short ball, bowled at 140.8kph, Javed pulls and fails to make contact]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Javed, no run, in the blockhole, outside off, Javed can't squeeze it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Javed, no run, Javed misses out on a full toss, he was looking to hoick it across the line, mistimes it to mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sohail Khan [8.0-2-46-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Amjad Javed, 1 run, short and outside off, Javed slaps it to extra cover and takes a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Amjad Javed, <b>FOUR</b>, edged and four! Javed is having some fun now. These runs will hurt Pakistan as it will effect their overall run-rate. Shortens the length around, Javed goes for the hoick towards cow corner, the ball takes the top-edge and flies down to third man fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, slower ball well wide of off, Patil toe-ends the steer wide of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, 2 runs, comical from Jamshed. Back of a length just outside off, Patil slashes it down to third man, it bounced a couple of times before reaching Jamshed, who allows it to slip through his legs, then has to dive and stop the ball from reaching the fence. It was a straightforward save which he messed up]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Amjad Javed, 3 runs, digs it midway down the pitch, Javed pulls, gets it high on the bat and it skies towards deep mid-wicket, where there is no one to take the catch]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Amjad Javed, no run, starts from round the wicket, short and outside off, Javed can't reach it to play the cut, it is just inside the tram-line]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz [8.0-1-39-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Amjad Javed, 1 run, pitched up on off, Javed taps it in front of mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Amjad Javed, no run, too full and outside off, Javed is late on the drive, the ball had already gone through to Akmal]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Amjad Javed, no run, yorker just wide of off, Javed fails to dig it out, the ball almost shaved the off-pole]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Amjad Javed, no run, fuller and just outside off, Javed makes room and toe-ends the drive to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Amjad Javed, no run, angled across off, Javed backs away and fails to make any connection]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Patil leans into the drive to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[45.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Javed, <b>SIX</b>, fabulous shot! This over has just spoiled Sohail Khan's figures. It was another slower ball, Javed picks it early, takes the aerial route and goes over long-on for the second six of the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Javed, no run, bumper on middle and leg, Javed backs away and goes for the pull, misses it completely]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Javed, <b>FOUR</b>, what a shot! Not where he intended, but he will take that. Banged in halfway down the wicket, Javed was shaping to play the pull, the ball ends up going over extra cover for a boundary. That came right off the middle as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Javed, <b>SIX</b>, out of the ground! Back of the hand slower ball, Javed spotted it early, clears his front leg and swipes it across the line, sends it saisling over long-on for a big maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Javed, <b>FOUR</b>, drilled! On a length just outside off, Javed hammers the drive past the bowler, none of the fielders moved and there is no one at long-off to cut that off]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, fuller and on the fourth stump, Patil drives and gets a thick outside edge to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sohail Khan [7.0-2-25-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Amjad Javed, no run, off-speed delivery, Javed stays in the crease and knocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Amjad Javed, <b>wide</b>, bumper which sails over Javed's head, too high and wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Amjad Javed, no run, slower ball around off, Javed bunts it behind point, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, again, it is short of length, Patil steers it with an angled bat to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Swapnil Patil, no run, back of a length around off, Patil taps it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Amjad Javed, 1 run, tucks it in front of mid-wicket for an easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riaz has been warned for the second time for running on the danger area. He can continue though, because it is the third official warning that will not allow him to bowl. I apologize for getting it wrong the first time, when I told it was after the second warning.]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, fuller and outside off, Patil drives it square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Amjad Javed, 2 runs, fraction short and outside off, Javed cuts it square of the wicket, Yasir runs to his left from sweeper, tumbles and stops it with one hand]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, fullish and just outside off, Patil leans into the drive to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[Switches to round the wicket!]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, no run, slanted across off, plenty of room to work with, but Patil flashes a cut and fails to make contact]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! Patil used the pace of the bowler on that occasion. Shortish and just outside off, Patil stands tall and guides it in the air to the left of backward point, Shehzad dives and <b>gets a finger on it</b>, but can't latch onto it]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, no run, back of a length around off, Patil rides the bounce and taps it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, no run, that is quick, 148.6kph short of length delivery, Patil has a feel for it away from the body, the ball fizzes past the outside edge. That is too good for Patil]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Amjad Javed, no run, shortish and angled across off, Javed has a late poke and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Amjad Javed, no run, short of length on off, Javed jumps up and blocks it down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Amjad Javed, no run, back of a length around off, Javed toe-ends the punch to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, again, the length is short and outside off, Patil cuts it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Swapnil Patil, 2 runs, slower ball which is short in length, Patil flashes a cut towards the slip fielder, but the ball falls well in front of the fielder, Maqsood dives but can't reach it, trickles away to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Swapnil Patil, no run, starts with a shortish delivery on off, Patil goes deep in the crease, fends with loose hands, the ball rolls to the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rahat Ali [7.0-0-21-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, shortens the length close to off, Patil arches back and guides it to backward point, where Afridi fumbles and allows the duo to steal a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, 2 runs, takes the pace off the ball, Patil plays it with soft hands to backward square leg, hares back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, no run, that is three in a row, shortish and outside off, Patil flashes a cut and the ball beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, no run, peach! Riaz is generating some extra bounce, keeps it back of a length and gets it to rise steeply, Patil has a feel for it, the ball whizzes through to Akmal. Not far away from the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, no run, short of length angled across the right-hander, Patil has a late waft at that, the ball zips past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, no run, back of a length around off, Patil gets behind the line and defends to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Amjad Javed, <b>2 wides</b>, short delivery on leg-stump, Javed half-ducks and allows it to sail past his left shoulder, Akmal dives and doesn't glove it cleanly]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Swapnil Patil, no run, <b>maiden</b> to finish the spell. Quicker and close to off, Patil prods forward to it and pushes at it, the ball turns enough to beat the outside edge. His final figures read: <b>10-1-35-2</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Swapnil Patil, no run, pushed through close to off, Patil goes hard on the drive, the ball squirts off the inside edge to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Swapnil Patil, no run, nice loopy just outside off, Patil lets it go through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Swapnil Patil, no run, slower and on off, Patil turns it gently to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Swapnil Patil, no run, again, stretches forward and defends it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Swapnil Patil, no run, straighter one, Patil leans forward and blocks, he played that close to the pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Amjad Javed, no run, banged in short once again, Javed arches back and leaves it for the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Amjad Javed, no run, bumper just outside off, Javed sways away from the line and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, on a good length and angling away outside off, Patil stays back, opens the face of the bat and guides it down to third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, no run, short of length delivery just outside off, Patil sways away from the line and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Patil gets behind the line and defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Swapnil Patil, 2 runs, angling down leg, Patil glances it fine, the keeper is late to get down and fails to stop it cleanly, the ball rolls away to the deep and the batsmen take a couple, Riaz wasn't happy with that effort one bit]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz [5.0-1-24-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Amjad Javed, no run, flatter through the air, Javed pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Amjad Javed, no run, slower through the air and turning away from the batsman, Javed defends from the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Amjad Javed, <b>wide</b>, quicker one and down the leg-side again, the keeper can't take it cleanly this time as well, the umpire exercises his arms once again]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Amjad Javed, <b>wide</b>, drifting down the leg-side, Javed fails to tickle it fine, the keeper can't take it cleanly either and the umpire signals a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Amjad Javed, no run, floated up outside off, Javed drives it to cover, who moves to his left and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Amjad Javed, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips and a leg slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Rohan Mustafa, <b>out</b> Caught by Ahmed Shehzad!! Afridi takes 2 in 3 balls. Mustafa walks back to the hut. It was floated up, Mustafa kneels down and looks to sweep, but picks out Shehzad at backward square leg, who won't drop those. Mustafa is very disappointed and Afridi has his arms aloft in joy. <b>Rohan Mustafa c Ahmed Shehzad b Afridi 0(2)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Afridi to Rohan Mustafa, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Rohan Mustafa, no run, looks to guide this one down to third man, but the googly beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohan Mustafa, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, <b>out</b> Caught by Jamshed!! Afridi picks up his first wicket of the tournament. It was floated up around off, Anwar makes room and looks to go the distance, but doesn't get under it properly, he ends up giving a simple catch to Nasir Jamshed at long-off, who almost floors it as well. He was trying to reverse cup it and almost dropped it, but somehow recovers in time to take it on the second attempt. <b>Shaiman Anwar c Jamshed b Afridi 62(88) [4s-4 6s-2]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Swapnil Patil, no run, back of a length delivery on middle and leg, Patil fails to tuck it away into the on-side and wears it on the pad, there was no appeal as the ball pitched outside leg and was too high as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Swapnil Patil, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Patil hangs back, opens the face of the bat and pushes it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Swapnil Patil, no run, length delivery just outside off, Patil was looking to push at it, but decides to leave it at the last instance]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Swapnil Patil, no run, short and wide outside off, Patil flashes at it, the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Swapnil Patil, <b>FOUR</b>, banged in short and outside off, Patil waits for it and ramps it past backward point, Sohail from third man runs to his right, dives and tries to stop the ball, but the ball goes under him, it was a good shot nevertheless from Patil]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Swapnil Patil, no run, fullish delivery angling away outside off, Patil was pushing at it, the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, no run, Anwar lines up for a big shot, but fails to connect with this quicker delivery outside off]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, short and wide outside off, Patil cuts it to deep extra cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Swapnil Patil, no run, floated up on middle, Patil turns it towards mid-wicket, where Riaz dives to his right and stops the ball, Patil was charging to the other end and has to rush back into the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Swapnil Patil, no run, wrong 'un on off and middle, Patil reads it well and defends it with his bat close to the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Swapnil Patil, no run, flatter outside off, Patil hangs back, opens the face of the bat and guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, quicker and on middle and leg, Anwar nudges it behind square for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shaiman Anwar has now become the top-scorer in the World Cup</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now. UAE are not playing for the win here, they are looking to bat out their 50 overs. On the other hand, Pakistan have also failed to kill the game. We know the result, but let's see how much can UAE make.]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Swapnil Patil, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Patil pushes at it away from his body, he gets a bottom edge that bounces right of the off stump and then rolls behind, luckily for the batsmen, he didn't drag it back onto the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Swapnil Patil, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Patil hangs back and pushes it to backward point after opening the face of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, length delivery just outside off, Anwar leans forward and punches it to sweeper cover for another run]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, back of a length delivery on leg, Patil tucks it away to fine leg and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, angled across off, Anwar stays back in the crease, opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Shaiman Anwar, no run, just short of a good length and on off, Anwar defends from the crease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rahat Ali [5.0-0-14-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>batting powerplay</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Swapnil Patil, no run, short and on the stumps, Patil pulls it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Swapnil Patil, no run, quicker one from Afridi, Patil pushes it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Swapnil Patil, no run, slower through the air and turning away, Patil was pushing at it away from his body, the ball turns past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Swapnil Patil, no run, tossed up outside off, Patil leans forward and dead-bats it]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, floated up outside off, Anwar knocks it towards sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, 2 runs, flighted delivery outside off, Anwar opens the face of that and pushes it in front of cover-point, he sets off for the single, the fielder from point runs forward, picks up and fires in the throw at the non-striker's end, there was no one backing up and the batsmen take an extra run on the overthrow]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shahid Afridi [6.0-0-28-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Swapnil Patil, no run, down the leg-side, Patil helps it to the right of backward square leg and the batsmen don't take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Swapnil Patil, no run, floated up outside off, Patil drives it to cover off the front foot, where the fielder dives to his right and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Swapnil Patil, no run, touch flatter and on middle and leg, Patil hangs back and punches it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Swapnil Patil, no run, on the pads, Patil nurdles it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, a low full toss on the stumps, Anwar helps it down to long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Comes round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Shaiman Anwar, no run, flatter and outside off, Anwar punches it hard, but picks out cover. It was a poor ball from Maqsood and should have been put away]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, drifting on middle and leg, Anwar nudges it through aquare leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Shaiman Anwar, <b>FOUR</b>, floated up outside off, Anwar makes room and goes inside-out over covers once again, this time the ball had enough to reach the fence, this is great batting from him]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Shaiman Anwar, no run, pushed through just outside off, Anwar blocks it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Shaiman Anwar, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>3rd ODI fifty and 4th 50+ plus score</b> in ODIs, it was short and on the stumps, Anwar rocks back and pulls it to the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Shaiman Anwar, no run, flighted delivery just outside off, Anwar defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, eased down to long-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Shaiman Anwar, 2 runs, makes room and takes two steps forward, goes for the inside-out loft, doesn't connect properly but it's good enough for a couple as the ball falls in no man's land at deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Shaiman Anwar, no run, makes room and was looking to go inside-out first, pushes at it at the end as he was not upto the pitch of the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, quicker through the air this time, Patil bunts it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, pushed through on middle and leg, Anwar eases it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, drags this one short, Patil rocks back and pulls it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Swapnil Patil, no run, flatter on the stumps, Patil pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, touch flatter outside off, Patil knocks it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Swapnil Patil, no run, driven straight to mid-off after coming forward]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Anwar drives it down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Shaiman Anwar, no run, flighted delivery just outside off, Anwar leans forward and pushes it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, floated up on off, Patil drives it towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Swapnil Patil, no run, flighted delivery on off, Patil presses forward and blocks it to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Swapnil Patil, 1 run, gets to the pitch of the ball and eases it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Swapnil Patil, no run, taps it to the off-side, where the cover fielder fields]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Swapnil Patil, no run, push-drives it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Swapnil Patil, no run, stays round the wicket, Patil hangs back and turns it to backward square]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Swapnil Patil, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to K Khan, <b>out</b> Caught by Riaz!! Maqsood has broken the partnership. Khan is disappointed with himself, he puts it's head down and takes a while to make his way back to the pavilion. Flighted on off, Khan goes down on one knee and sweeps, picks out Riaz at backward square to perfection. That is Maqsood's <b>first ODI wicket</b>. <b>K Khan c Riaz b Maqsood 43(54) [4s-3 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Maqsood to K Khan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to K Khan, no run, skidding on, Khan misses the nudge through the on-side, is rapped on the pads but the ball was sliding down leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Shaiman Anwar, no run, arm-ball around off, Anwar hangs back and misses out on the cut, that was very close to the off-stump. Akmal thought it hit the stumps as he didn't gather the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Shaiman Anwar, no run, floated up on off, Anwar presses forward and defends in front of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Shaiman Anwar, <b>FOUR</b>, top shot! Flighted on off, Anwar kneels down and sweeps it in the air behind square, the fielder was very square and had no chance of stopping that]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Shaiman Anwar, no run, dabs it to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to K Khan, 1 run, comes down the track, takes it on the full and drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to K Khan, no run, worked away with the turn to square leg, can't beat the fielder]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Haris Sohail, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Shaiman Anwar, <b>SIX</b>, classy shot! Maqsood gives this more air than the usual. Anwar takes a couple of steps down the wicket, presents the full face of the bat and lofts it handsomely over long-off for his second six]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Shaiman Anwar, no run, too full and on the stumps, Anwar works it to square leg, finds the fielder there]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Shaiman Anwar, no run, bunts it with soft hands to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Shaiman Anwar, no run, shuffles across and tucks it to backward square, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Shaiman Anwar, no run, quicker and outside off, Anwar misses out on the cut, he was outdone by the extra bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Shaiman Anwar, no run, flatter and on off, defended back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, bit more air on this, Anwar lofts it on the bounce to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, no run, pulls the length back, Anwar works it backward square, picks out the fielder there]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, 1 run, nudged away wide of mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, 2 runs, nice loopy delivery just outside off, Khan goes for the inside out loft, ends up slicing it towards deep cover, Riaz runs across, dives and hauls it in just before the rope. The TV umpire checks and deems it as a good save]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Anwar drives it along the floor to deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, no run, bit of turn for Afridi, Anwar waits and dabs it to short third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to K Khan, no run, slightly short and around off, Khan cuts and finds the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to K Khan, no run, tossed up outside off, Khan looks to swipe it across the line, mistimes it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, free-flowing drive to long-off for an easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Shaiman Anwar, no run, angled across off, Anwar chops it off the under edge to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to Shaiman Anwar, no run, continues to operate from round the sticks, quicker and on middle, Anwar bunts it in front of short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to K Khan, 1 run, sliding on from round the wicket, Khan leans forward and nudges it to backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maqsood to K Khan, <b>wide</b>, darted down the leg-side, wide called]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sohaib Maqsood, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bit of sawdust sprinkled on the square. Shehzad slipped while fieling in the last over. Hence, the groundsmen was asked to bring some sawdust]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, no run, skids on after pitching, Anwar goes hard at that, the ball takes the inside edge and rolls to the right of Afridi]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, 1 run, touch short, Khan pulls it on the bounce to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, driven away along the ground to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, 2 runs, drops it fractionally short and outside off, Anwar cuts it square of the wicket, the batsmen come back for the second before the ball is hunted down by the sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, 1 run, slightly uppish, but the flick it well wide of the mid-wicket fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, no run, faster one just outside off, Khan pokes and is beaten, he was looking for the steer down to third man, was beaten for pace]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shaiman Anwar, no run, slanted across the right-hander, Anwar goes for the steer down to third man, misses as the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shaiman Anwar, no run, 140.2kph lifter just outside off, Anwar can't make contact with the pull, it was just a bit too high for him]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shaiman Anwar, no run, punched right off the meat of the bat towards backward point, Shehzad dives to his left and makes a fine save]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shaiman Anwar, no run, back of a length on off, Anwar gets behind the line and defends towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shaiman Anwar, no run, hurried onto the batsman, Anwar misses the nudge through the on-side, is pinged high on the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shaiman Anwar, no run, bouncer on off, Anwar sinks under it and allows it to sail over him]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, driven off the inner part, the ball dribbles away to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, 1 run, Afridi sees the batsman come down the track, drags the length back, Khan adjusts well and cuts it to square third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, no run, flighted on off, Khan drives it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, slower and bit of turn, Anwar closes the bat face early, gets a leading edge that goes wide of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, no run, push-driven straight to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, no run, gives this bit more air, Anwar leans forward and drops it to the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to K Khan, no run, keeps it short of length on off, Khan knocks it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to K Khan, <b>SIX</b>, superb shot! Banged in halfway down the wicket, it was on a leg-stump line, Khan swivels on the back foot and pulls it over deep backward square, it cleared the rope by some distance]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, back of a length on off, Anwar gets inside the line and nurdles it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shaiman Anwar, 2 runs, on a length just outside off, Anwar opens the bat face and guides it between backward point and gully, Sohail Khan tidies up in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shaiman Anwar, no run, short of length on off, Anwar gets behind the line and knocks it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riaz has got an official warning for running on the pitch. Another one and he is off the attack.]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shaiman Anwar, no run, good length ball around off, Anwar bunts it towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, no run, nice loopy leg-break, Khan leans forward and blocks it to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, no run, flatter and on off, Khan whips it to backward square, finds Shehzad there]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, 2 runs, straighter one outside off, Khan waits in the crease and runs it down to third man, comfortable two on offer]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, no run, once again can't pierce the gap on the leg-side, picks out the fielder at mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, no run, turns it with soft hands in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, no run, floated up on middle, Khan works it gently to square leg, where Shehzad fields the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to K Khan, 1 run, slides onto the hips, Khan gets inside the line and nurdles it to fine leg, retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to K Khan, no run, bumper just outside off, Khan goes for the pull, but is nowhere close to the ball. It was too high and Riaz gets away with one]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, on a length just outside off, Anwar presses it to the vacant cover region and takes an easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shaiman Anwar, 2 runs, back of a length on off, Anwar hops across and nudges it to deep mid-wicket for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shaiman Anwar, no run, short of length around off, Anwar punches off the outer half, the ball rolls down to gully]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shaiman Anwar, no run, good length ball on the fourth stump line, Anwar covers his sticks, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, <b>FOUR</b>, bad delivery and it deserved the treatment. Half tracker outside off, Khan stays leg-side of the ball and cracks the cut in front of square, the fielder was at deep backward point and had no chance of stopping that]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, floated up outside off, Anwar drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, 1 run, slider outside off, Khan hangs on the back foot and steers it towards deep backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, no run, waits for the ball to turn in, works it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, poor from Afridi, driven back to him, he bends down and gets both hands, but fails to stop the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, 1 run, nice loopy delivery, Khan leans forward and nudges it to the left of mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shaiman Anwar, 2 runs, banged in midway down the wicket, Anwar swivels and pulls it to deep backward square leg for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to K Khan, 1 run, goes for a more conventional pull, mistimes it completely as the ball dribbles to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to K Khan, 2 runs, back of a length on off and middle, Khan goes on the back foot and plays the short-arm pull over square leg, Yasir tracks back and keeps it down to two]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, slanted across the right-hander, steered away to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shaiman Anwar, no run, on a length close to off, Anwar brings his bat down and manages to keep it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to K Khan, 1 run, good length ball on off, Khan prefers to sit back and runs it down to third man with an angled bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, 1 run, pushed through just outside off, Khan camps on the back foot and guides it to deep backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, no run, tossed up on off, Khan rolls his wrists and turns it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, slower and close to off, Anwar eases the drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to K Khan, 1 run, drifts it onto the pads, Khan tucks it behind square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, fraction short and outside off, Anwar cuts it square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, no run, flighted on off, Anwar presses forward and blocks it to the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Shaiman Anwar, <b>wide</b>, darted down the leg-side, Anwar can't connect with the glance, wide given]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shahid Afridi, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for a <b>drinks</b> break! Pakistan managed to pick up three wickets in succession after the UAE openers started off cautiously. However, these two remain the two best batsmen for UAE and Pakistan cannot afford to relax. Slight delay as the spidercam had lost it's power. It's back now and play resumes..]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to K Khan, no run, back of a length around off, Khan dabs it to point, calls "no" for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to K Khan, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>almost dragged on!</b> Riaz has his hands on his head. It was in the corridor of uncertainty, Khan was in a dilemma whether to play or leave, has a late waft at it, the ball squirts off the inside edge to the fine leg fence. That was inches away from leg-stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to K Khan, no run, good length around off, Khan opens the bat face at the last instant, guides it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to K Khan, no run, on a length close to off, Khan pushes it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to K Khan, no run, tight from Riaz, on the off-stump line, Khan presses it to cover after coming forward]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to K Khan, no run, fullish and on off, Khan leans forward and flick, finds the man at mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Shaiman Anwar, no run, angling away well outside off, Anwar is not interested in playing at those]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Shaiman Anwar, no run, good length ball just outside off, Anwar pushes it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Shaiman Anwar, no run, on a length and just outside off, Anwar stays back and bunts it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Shaiman Anwar, no run, touch fuller and angled across off, Anwar leans forward and drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Shaiman Anwar, no run, in the channel outside off, Anwar leaves it alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to K Khan, 1 run, just short of a good length and outside off, Khan runs it down to third man for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Shaiman Anwar, <b>SIX</b>, <b>massive!</b> It was short and it was wide, it was asking to be hit, Anwar just jumps and cuts it late, gets it up and over the deep backward point fence for the first maximum of the innings]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sohail was also stretching his hamstring after bowling the fifth ball. Irfan is already off the pitch and now Sohail will also be a worry]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Shaiman Anwar, no run, bumper from Sohail, Anwar ducks under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Shaiman Anwar, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a great shot, it was the short of length delivery angling away outside off, Anwar stays on the back foot and punches it through the covers, the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Shaiman Anwar, no run, banged in short and outside off, Anwar goes for the pull, but gets a bottom edge that falls back on the track, he has a look at his bat after that]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Shaiman Anwar, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Anwar punches and picks out cover to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Shaiman Anwar, no run, just short of a good length and around off, Anwar defends from the crease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Shaiman Anwar, 1 run, finally Anwar gets off the mark as he glances this back of a length delivery on the pads to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Shaiman Anwar, no run, short of length delivery well outside off, Anwar goes for the cut but fails to connect, the keeper gloves it]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Shaiman Anwar, no run, angled across off, Anwar leaves it alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Shaiman Anwar, no run, short of length delivery angling away outside off, Anwar jabs it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Shaiman Anwar, no run, back of a length delivery just around off, Anwar jumps in the crease and blocks it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to K Khan, 1 run, back of a length delivery well wide outside off, Khan opens the face of the bat and steers it down to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Irfan is still off the field and it could be a worrying sign for the Pakistanis]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Shaiman Anwar, no run, length delivery on off, Anwar hangs back and punches it back to the bowler, a <b>maiden</b> from Sohail]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Shaiman Anwar, no run, short of length delivery outside off, Anwar flashes at it, but the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Shaiman Anwar, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Anwar defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Shaiman Anwar, no run, that's a <b>peach</b>! It was on a length and shapes away just outside off, Anwar was feeling for it and the ball beats the outside edge, perfect ball from Sohail]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Shaiman Anwar, no run, back of a length delivery that keeps a touch low outside off, Anwar was looking to force it through the off-side off the back foot, fails to make a connection and the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Shaiman Anwar, no run, length delivery just outside off, Anwar pushes it towards point off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to K Khan, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Khan hops in the crease, opens the face of the bat and pushes it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to K Khan, no run, fuller in length and outside off, Khan leans forward and drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to K Khan, no run, length delivery with a hint of shape away around off, Khan did well to get behind the line and and pushes it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to K Khan, no run, a little too straight once again, Khan clips it into the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to K Khan, no run, back of a length delivery on the pads, Khan tucks it away towards mid-on and was looking for the single there, his partner sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to K Khan, <b>FOUR</b>, short and wide outside off, Khan stays back and cuts it past a diving backward point, the ball rockets away to the fence in no time]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shaiman Anwar, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Karate, <b>out</b> Caught by U Akmal!! Sohail bags another wicket. Karate goes for a duck. It was pitched up outside off, Karate was drawn into the drive away from his body, the ball catches the outside edge and goes to the right of the keeper, who dives and takes a good catch. Sohail is extremely happy with that wicket. UAE are in deep trouble here. <b>Karate c U Akmal b Sohail Khan 0(11)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sohail Khan to Karate, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Karate, <b>wide</b>, bumper that sails over the batsman, who was ducking under it, the umpire calls it a wide for height]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Karate, no run, on a length and just outside off, Karate leans forward and bunts it towards mid-off, he was looking for the single there but the ball went too quickly to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Karate, no run, length delivery just outside off, Karate pushes it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Karate, no run, good short ball outside off, Karate was looking to fend it and took his eyes off it, the ball moves away in the air and goes through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Karate, no run, just short of a good length and on off and middle, Karate shuffles across and turns it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to K Khan, 1 run, back of a length delivery angled across off, Khan opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Karate, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Karate leaves it for the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Karate, no run, touch fuller and angling away outside off, Karate mistimes the drive into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to K Khan, 3 runs, fuller length delivery on middle and leg, Khan shuffles across a touch and clips this wide of mid-on, the batsmen take three before the ball is hunted down]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to K Khan, no run, another short of length around off, Khan hops in the crease and pushes it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to K Khan, no run, short of length delivery well outside off, Khan lets it go through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to K Khan, no run, bowls a bumper this time, Khan arches back and lets that one go through]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Karate, no run, fuller length delivery on middle and leg, Karate pushes it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Karate, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Karate defends off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to K Khan, leg byes, 1 run, ohh dear! What happened there? First, there was a <b>big shout for lbw</b> as Khan shuffled across and was hit on the pad, the umpire gave it not out and the ball rolled away towards gully, the non-striker was charging to the other end and Khan was a little late to get off the blocks, there was so much confusion there as Shehzad picked the ball up near the gully region and tries to break the stumps at the striker's end, had he thrown it at the non-striker's end instead, things would have been much more closer, Misbah was looking to review it as well, but the umpire told him that he had crossed the 15 seconds time limit]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Khurram Khan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Andri Berenger, <b>out</b> Caught by U Akmal!! Sohail has his arms wide open as he gets his man this time. It was full just outside off and straightens just a touch, Berenger plays down the wrong line expecting it to come back in. He gets an outside edge and Umar Akmal takes an easy catch a little low to his right. Sohail charges to the keeper in delight. UAE have now lost both the openers in a space of 6 balls. <b>Andri Berenger c U Akmal b Sohail Khan 2(13)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sohail Khan to Andri Berenger, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Andri Berenger, no run, bowls this one well outside off, Berenger is happy to leave that alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Andri Berenger, no run, full and shaping away outside off, Berenger leaves]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Karate, no run, back of a length delivery swinging in from middle, Karate was looking to work it into the on-side, but fails to connect and wears it high on the pad, Rahat appealed but umpire Ravi says 'Not Out'. It was too high to be given out and it pitched outside leg too as Haw-Eye pointed out]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Karate, no run, fuller in length and with a hint of movement in towards the batsman, who shuffles across and shoulders arms at the last moment]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Krishnachandran Karate, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Amjad Ali, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Rahat picks up a wicket in his first over. It was just short of a good length and shaping away outside off, Ali was in two minds whether to leave it or not, he was too late to pull his bat up and ends up getting an inside edge that crashes into the stumps. Rahat is ecstatic and so are the other Pakistani players. <b>Amjad Ali b Rahat Ali 14(30) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rahat Ali to Amjad Ali, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Amjad Ali, <b>wide</b>, full and swinging away well wide outside off, Amjad Ali leaves and the umpires call it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Amjad Ali, no run, on a good length and swinging away outside off, Amjad Ali shoulders arms this time around]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Amjad Ali, 2 runs, back of a length delivery outside off, Ali goes across and pushes at it, the ball goes behind square on the on-side off the inside half of the bat, the batsmen take two before the fielder from square leg runs across and collects it]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Andri Berenger, 1 run, fuller in length and shaping in on middle and leg, Berenger pushes at it, the ball rolls away to fine leg off the inside edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rahat Ali, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Ali, no run, just short of a good length and shaping in from outside off, Ali pushes it back to the bowler off the inside half of the bat, it was played with soft hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Ali, <b>wide</b>, banged in short and outside off, Ali sways away from the line, but the umpire deems it a wide as it was too high]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Ali, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Ali hops, opens the face of the bat and bunts it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, on the pads of the batsman, Ali shuffles acoross and helps it to the fine leg fence, the fielder at fine leg was square and had no chance of stopping that]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Ali, no run, angled across off this time, Ali opens the face of the bat and pushes it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Ali, no run, on a good length and around off, Ali goes across and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, good shot from Ali, it was touch fuller and on off, Ali leans forward and drills it past the bowler, the ball runs away to the fence even though both mid-off and mid-on ran after it, but they had no chance of cutting that off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Irfan is walking off the field. He was clutching his hamstring after the final ball was bowled]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Andri Berenger, no run, back of a length delivery that comes back in from around off and middle, Berenger was pushing at it, the ball beats the blade and hits him on the mid-riff, Berenger looks in some discomfort there]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Andri Berenger, no run, fuller in length and shaping in from middle and leg, Berenger fails to work it into the on-side and is rapped on the pads, there was a stifled appeal from the Pakistanis, but the ball was snaking down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Amjad Ali, 1 run, straighter in line this time around, Ali was looking it to tuck it away into the on-side, he gets an inside edge onto the thigh pad and the ball rolls away behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Amjad Ali, no run, pitched up outside off, Ali was drawn into the front foot drive, the ball shapes away and beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Amjad Ali, no run, fullish outside off, Ali opens the face of the bat and squeezes it towards gully, who dives to his left and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Amjad Ali, no run, fuller length delivery shaping away outside off, left alone by Ali]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Andri Berenger, no run, bowls a bumper this time, Berenger is happy to duck under it and leaves it for the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Andri Berenger, no run, touch fuller and on middle and leg, Berenger puts his bat in front of pad and knocks it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Ali, 1 run, banged in short and at the batsman, Ali looks to pull but mistimes it as the ball rolls away down to fine leg off the bottom part of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Ali, no run, just short of a good length and angled across off, Ali shuffles across and pushes at it, the ball rolls away to square leg off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Ali, no run, length delivery on the stumps, Ali defends it in front of mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Andri Berenger, 1 run, angling in on middle, Berenger pushes at it, the ball rolls away to fine leg off the inside half of the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Amjad Ali, no run, short of length delivery well wide outside off, Ali was looking to cut it at first, but pulls his bat back at the last moment and allows it to go]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Amjad Ali, no run, back of a length delivery angling in on middle, Ali defends from the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Amjad Ali, no run, bowls this on a good length and well outside off, Ali leaves it alone and Umar Akmal collects it head high]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Amjad Ali, no run, banged in short and just outside off, Ali rocks back and looks to pull it hard, but fails to make a connection]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Amjad Ali, no run, back of a length delivery around off, Ali hops in the crease and drops his wrists on it]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Amjad Ali, no run, touch fuller and outside off, Ali goes chasing it and looks to drive, the ball beats the outside edge and the keeper collects]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Andri Berenger, no run, just short of a good length and around off, Berenger gets behind the line and defends it with soft hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Andri Berenger, no run, on a good length and shaping in on middle and leg, Berenger shuffles across and pushes it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Andri Berenger, no run, fullish delivery on off and middle, Berenger pushes it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Ali, 1 run, on a good length and outside off, Ali leans forward, opens the face of the bat and guides it to the left of second slip, where Haris Sohail is swift to move across and he fires in the throw at the striker's end, hits the stumps and the ball ricochets off the stump and goes towards mid-on region, the batsmen take a single on the deflection]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Ali, no run, another inswinger from Sohail that goes down leg, Ali was shuffling across and fails to clip it, it wasn't too far away from the leg stump and that's why the umpire doesn't give it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Ali, no run, full and holding its line well outside off, Ali puts his front foot forward and shoulders arms]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Amjad Ali, <b>wide</b>, swinging down the leg-side, Ali leaves and the umpire calls it a wide]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sohail Khan, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sohail Khan will share the attack with Irfan]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Andri Berenger, no run, very close to the off stump this time, Berenger judges it well and leaves it alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Amjad Ali, 1 run, short delivery at the batsman, Ali looks to fend it away, the ball goes off the gloves to the right of Jamshed at short leg, who was a little slow to react, the batsmen take a single as the ball goes past him]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Amjad Ali, no run, in the channel outside off, Ali shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[There are two slips and a gully in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Amjad Ali, no run, fuller in length this time around and just outside off, Ali was pushing at it, the ball shapes away and goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Amjad Ali, no run, another shortish delivery outside off, Ali pulls his bat back and leaves it alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Amjad Ali, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Ali shuffles across and drops his wrists, lets it go through to the keeper]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Amjad Ali and Andri Berenger are at the crease. Amjad Ali is on strike. Irfan will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back. The players are making their way out to the middle. Irfan will open the bowling and Amjad Ali will face the first ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[Apart from Naveed and Tauqir to a certain extent, the other UAE bowlers were very disappointing. They failed to put pressure on the Pakistanis, especially during the final 10 overs. Now, it is upto their batsmen to put on a show, but with Irfan and Riaz in the team, Pakistan will be confident of defending this total. Folks, take a break for now and be back in a short while for the run-chase.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Both of them were looking set to reach their respective hundreds, but threw their wickets away in the batting powerplay. Sohail got out trying to pull one out of the park and Shehzad was run-out trying to sneak in a second, that too in his nineties. After those two departed, Maqsood and Misbah then took the attack to the opposition, by hitting a few lusty blows out of the park. Maqsood made a 31-ball 45 before getting out, while Misbah notched up a quickfire fifty and finished with 65 off just 49 balls.]]></line><line><![CDATA[So, Pakistan finish with 339/6 on the board, the 16th time in 25 matches this World Cup that a team has gone past 300. Earlier, Pakistan got off to a poor start, losing Nasir Jamshed early in the innings. After that Sohail and Shehzad steadied the innings and played the balls according to their merit. Both of them completed their maiden World Cup fifties and also put on 160 runs for the second wicket, the first 100+ partnership for Pakistan in this World Cup.]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Afridi, 2 runs, low full toss on off, Afridi mistimes the loft, it lands well in front of the long-on fielder, who doesn't pick the ball up cleanly, allows the extra run to be taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Afridi, <b>FOUR</b>, hammered! That was brute power from Boom Boom. Too full and just outside off, it was almost a yorker, Afridi gets under it and hits it in the air wide of long-off, no chance for the fielder to cut that off]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Afridi, <b>SIX</b>, another lovely shot! Javed is bowling right to Afridi's strength. Full and outside off, Afridi bends his front knee and lofts it beautifully inside out, that cleared deep extra cover with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Afridi, 2 runs, too full and close to off, Afridi squeezes it out to long-off, calls for two and sprints back to keep strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Afridi, no run, right in the blockhole, Afridi jams it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Afridi, <b>SIX</b>, <b>8000 runs in ODIs for Afridi</b>, 4th Pakistani to achieve the feat. He stood there and admired the shot, he knew that came right off the meat. Fullish and just outside off, Afridi slices it over sweeper cover for a mximum]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[48.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Riaz, <b>SIX</b>, massive hit! He has started off from where he had left in the previous game. Slower delivery right in the slot, Riaz swings his hands and sends it sailing over deep mid-wicket. Another catch in the crowd!]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Afridi, 1 run, slower ball around off, Afridi steers it to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hat-trick ball coming up!</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Misbah, <b>out</b> Caught by Rohan Mustafa at long on!! Misbah perishes for the team's cause. Guruge picks up his fourth wicket, he is <b>on a hat-trick</b>. Full and slanted outside off, Misbah shuffles across and lofts it to long-on, Mustafa runs to his left and clings onto a good catch, he took it over his head. <b>Misbah c Rohan Mustafa b Manjula Guruge 65(49) [4s-4 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Manjula Guruge to Misbah, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shahid Afridi, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to U Akmal, <b>out</b> Caught by Amjad Ali!! Akmal can't believe that he has picked out the fielder. He stands his ground, but it was a handy cameo from him. It was full and aimed at the stumps, Akmal moves across his stumps and whips it to deep mid-wicket, he middled it but didn't place it, picks out Amjad Ali to perfection, who holds onto a well judged catch. <b>U Akmal c Amjad Ali b Manjula Guruge 19(13) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Manjula Guruge to U Akmal, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Misbah, 1 run, goes on his knee and drills the drive to long-off, he didn't get the elevation]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Misbah, 2 runs, fullish and just outside off, Misbah chips it wide of long-off, it was good enough for a couple]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Manjula Guruge [7.0-0-46-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Misbah, 1 run, low full toss just outside off, Misbah walks forward and across, eases it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to U Akmal, 1 run, fullish and outside off, Akmal lofts it towards sweeper cover, the fielder runs to his right and keeps it to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Misbah, 1 run, yorker just outside off, Misbah shuffles across, toe-ends the scoop adjacent to the pitch on the leg-side, Akmal calls his captain through for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to U Akmal, 1 run, <b>dropped!</b> Shaiman is the culprit this time. Low full toss on off and middle, Akmal crouches low and whips it to deep mid-wicket, Shaiman runs forward and spills a low catch. He had plenty of time to get his hands around it]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Misbah, 1 run, too full and outside off, Misbah squeezes the drive to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to U Akmal, 1 run, full toss with some away movement, Akmal goes for the drive and gets an inside edge towards long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Amjad Javed [7.0-0-50-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Misbah, 2 runs, fullish and outside off, Misbah shuffles around and slices it over backward point for another couple. Another productive over for Pakistan, <b>19 runs came off it</b>. They have managed to muscle <b>35 runs</b> in the last two overs]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Misbah, 2 runs, too full and on the stumps, Misbah whips it to deep mid-wicket for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Misbah, <b>no ball</b>, <b>FOUR</b>, that missed have slipped out of Naveed's hands, high full toss on leg-stump, Misbah does well to help it on the way past short fine. It was above waist height and hence called a no-ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to U Akmal, 1 run, slower short ball, Akmal pulls it on the bounce to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to U Akmal, <b>SIX</b>, what a catch! In the crowd though, by an Indian. A length delivery right in zone, Akmal gets under it and sends it sailing over deep mid-wicket. The spectator takes it with one hand as the other had a drink clasping it]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to U Akmal, 2 runs, shortish and outside off, Akmal upper cuts it to third man, the batsmen hare back for the second before the ball is hunted down]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Misbah, 1 run, Misbah backs away and looks to hoick, is hurried by the full toss, mistimes it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[45.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rohan Mustafa to Misbah, 1 run, <b>Misbah brings up his second fifty on the trot.</b> But, he missed out on a full toss, he reverse sweeps it towards short third man, the fielders gets his body behind the ball and stops it]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rohan Mustafa to Misbah, no run, reverse paddles the full toss straight to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rohan Mustafa to Misbah, <b>FOUR</b>, now the conventional sweep from the Pakistan skipper, floated up on off and middle, Misbah bends down and sweeps it hard and wide of deep backward square]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rohan Mustafa to Misbah, leg byes, 2 runs, goes for the sweep, can't connect, the ball lobs off the pads over the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rohan Mustafa to Misbah, <b>5 wides</b>, Misbah outsmarts the bowler, he bends his front knee and was shaping to play the reverse sweep, Mustafa darts it well down leg, outside the tram-line, no chance for the keeper to collect]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rohan Mustafa to Misbah, <b>FOUR</b>, poor delivery from Mustafa, he misses the yorker and dishes out a full toss, Misbah kneels down and plays the reverse sweep behind point. He placed it right between point and short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rohan Mustafa to Misbah, no run, fired into the blockhole, Misbah digs it out back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Misbah, 1 run, yorker on middle, Misbah squeezes it out to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to U Akmal, leg byes, 1 run, Naveed went up straightaway, it was a low full toss on the stumps, Akmal misses to lay bat on that, is struck in front of leg-stump. The angle was taking it down leg. Good call by umpire Ravi]]></line><line><![CDATA[UAE have reviewed an LBW appeal. Akmal the man in question. No problems as per the no-ball is concerned. Was it sliding down leg? The Hawk-Eye shows that it is missing leg-stump. The onfield call remains]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to U Akmal, <b>FOUR</b>, super shot! It was tad straight from Naveed, on off and middle, Akmal takes a step towards the off-side and whips it in the air, places it well wide of deep backward square]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to U Akmal, no run, back of a length on middle, Akmal defends it back to the bowler. Well bowled by Naveed, didn't provide the batsman room to work with]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Misbah, 1 run, low full toss on leg-stump, Misbah backs away and bunts it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to U Akmal, 1 run, too full, but on the pads, Akmal leans forward and flicks it behind square leg for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Naveed [8.0-0-24-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rohan Mustafa to Misbah, <b>FOUR</b>, excellent placement from the Pakistan captain, kneels down and sweeps the flighted delivery, makes sure that he beats short fine as well as the fielder at deep backward square]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rohan Mustafa to Misbah, no run, reverse sweeps and picks out the fielder at short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rohan Mustafa to Misbah, <b>wide</b>, moves around in the crease, Mustafa fires it down leg, Misbah can't connect with the paddle, wide signalled]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rohan Mustafa to U Akmal, 1 run, pushed through, Akmal makes a bit of room and steers it to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rohan Mustafa to Misbah, 1 run, follows Misbah who was backing away, bunted down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rohan Mustafa to U Akmal, 1 run, low full toss close to off, Akmal eases the drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rohan Mustafa to Misbah, 1 run, darted from round the wicket, Misbah whips it to long-on for a run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohan Mustafa, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Umar Akmal, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Maqsood, <b>out</b> Caught by Rohan Mustafa!! The entertaining knock comes to an end. He has provided the much needed impetus to the innings. It was full and outside off, Maqsood bends down and slices it towards backward point, Mustafa is the fielder, hits him on the chest, he juggled a couple of times and hangs onto it on the third attempt. <b>Maqsood c Rohan Mustafa b Manjula Guruge 45(31) [4s-4 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Manjula Guruge to Maqsood, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Maqsood, <b>SIX</b>, humongous hit! It is a 97 meters six from Maqsood. The replacement one comes out as that went out of the park. Length delivery around off, it was the slower one, Maqsood gets underneath that and hoicks it way over deep mid-wicket. It was all power from Maqsood]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Misbah, 1 run, yorker on off, Misbah jams it back past the non-striker, he wanted two but Maqsood was slow to start off]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Misbah, <b>SIX</b>, lovely shot! These two are dealing in sixes now. It was full and on the stumps, Misbah moves across his stumps, plays the pick up shot to perfection, clears the short boundary with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Misbah, no run, slower ball around off, Misbah dabs it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Misbah, no run, full and angled across off, Misbah looks to target the cow corner, doesn't make contact]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Maqsood, <b>SIX</b>, hammered! Straight onto the comm box. Wasim Akram was ducking for cover, as per Alan Wilkins. On a length just outside off, it was right in the slot, Maqsood clears his front leg and launches it over long-off for the second six of the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Maqsood, 2 runs, saw the batsman walk across his stumps, keeps it full and on the stumps, Maqsood whips it in the air towards long-on. That lands well in front of Mustafa, who was running forward]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Misbah, 1 run, drags the length back, punched down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Misbah, <b>SIX</b>, monster! Misbah takes on the longest boundary on the ground, clears it with ease. It was an off-speed delivery, Misbah kneels down and slog sweeps it wide long-on for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Misbah, 2 runs, short and outside off, Misbah crus it square of the wicket, the fielder from sweeper, dives and stops the ball from reaching the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Misbah, no run, leg-cutter outside off, Misbah cuts and finds backward point, call is for "wait" on the single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Misbah, 1 run, full and on off, Misbah moves across and whips it square of the wicket on the leg-side, keeps the strike with that run]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Maqsood, 1 run, slower ball around off, Maqsood drags the heave to deep square leg, he mistimed it completely]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Misbah, 1 run, off-speed delivery just outside off, Misbah checks his shot, eases it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Maqsood, 1 run, gentle drift into the batsman, Maqsood drills it straight back past the bowler, the ball went through Guruge's legs and down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Misbah, 1 run, takes the pace off the ball, Misbah shuffles across and nurdles it to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Maqsood, 1 run, back of a length on leg-stump, Maqsood punches it to deep mid-wicket, there was slight hesitation between the batsmen about the second run, in the end they don't go through with it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Manjula Guruge [5.0-0-27-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Maqsood, 1 run, slightly back of a length and outside off, Maqsood punches it to the left of the bowler, who gets down in his followthrough but can't make a clean stop, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Misbah, 1 run, another off-speed short of length delivery outside off, Misbah goes for the pull, but mistimes it through mid-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Maqsood, 1 run, short slower one and well outside off, Maqsood cuts it square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Misbah, 1 run, just short of a good length and outside off, Misbah shuffles across and punches it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Misbah, 2 runs, banged in short and outside off, Misbah goes down on one knee and slogs it high, he didn't get it off the middle of the bat, the ball went high and falls in no man's land near the deep mid-wicket rope, the batsmen take two before the ball is hunted down]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Misbah, no run, angling in on off and middle, Misbah pushes it down to mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Maqsood, <b>FOUR</b>, back-to-back boundaries for Javed, another one on the pads, Maqsood waits for it and just helps it over a leaping short fine leg fielder, the ball runs away to the fence, <b>13 runs</b> came off that over]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Maqsood, <b>FOUR</b>, poor bowling from Javed, it was the slower ball down the leg-side, Maqsood just tickles it fine enough to beat the fielder at short fine, the ball beats the fielder to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Maqsood, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Maqsood stays on the back foot and pushes it towards point with soft hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Maqsood, <b>FOUR</b>, straying on the pads, Maqsood clips it behind square and the ball runs away to the fence, the fielder at fine leg was inside the circle]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Misbah, 1 run, just short of a good length and well outside off, Misbah stays inside the crease, opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Misbah, no run, length delivery on off and middle, Misbah goes across and nudges it to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Maqsood, no run, slower short ball and wide outside off, Maqsood cuts hard, but gets an edge that goes on the bounce to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Misbah, 1 run, angling in on middle, Misbah bunts it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Misbah, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Misbah punches it to cover once again]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Misbah, 2 runs, back of a length delivery outside off, Misbah hangs back and goes for the pull, he just about manages to get it over the fielder at mid-wicket, the batsmen take two as the ball rolls away in the deep, it was not that high though]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Misbah, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Misbah punches it and picks out cover once again]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Misbah, no run, slower ball outside off, Misbah stays back and punches it to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Maqsood, 2 runs, length delivery outside off, Maqsood leans forward and punches it through extra cover, the batsmen take two before the fielder from sweeper cover, who runs to his right and hunts the ball down]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Misbah, 1 run, just short of a good length and targetting the stumps, Misbah hangs back inside the crease and nudges it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Maqsood, 1 run, slower fullish ball outside off, Maqsood drives it to sweeper cover and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Maqsood, <b>FOUR</b>, banged in short and just outside off, Maqsood hangs back and short-arm pulls it wide of mid-on, it was in the air, but well over the fielder there and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Maqsood, no run, angling in on off, Maqsood shuffles across and wrists it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Maqsood, 2 runs, short and wide outside off, Maqsood hangs back and cuts it past backward point, the batsmen take two before the fielder from sweeper runs to his left and fields the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Amjad Javed [5.0-0-27-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Maqsood, 1 run, just short of a good length and outside off, Maqsood knocks it to sweeper cover and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Misbah, 1 run, length delivery on off and middle, Misbah pushes it to the right of the bowler, who dives and gets a hand on it, he can't prevent the single though as the ball rolls away towards the mid-on region]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Maqsood, 1 run, angling in on middle, Maqsood goes across a little and works it through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Maqsood, no run, slower shortish ball outside off, Maqsood cuts but picks out point]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Misbah, 1 run, back of a length delivery on the stumps, Misbah pushes it past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Misbah, 2 runs, back of a length delivery outside off, Misbah punches it towards point and sets off, the fielder fires in the throw at the non-striker's end but there was no one backing up, the batsmen run an extra run for the overthrow]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[The batting powerplay yielded <b>29/2</b> for Pakistan. UAE will definitely be the happier side after those 5 overs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Maqsood, no run, back of a length delivery on middle, Maqsood wrists it down to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Maqsood, no run, on a good length and angling in from outside off, Maqsood shuffles across and looks to force it off the front foot, but the ball rolls away into the leg-side off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Maqsood, no run, length ball outside off, Maqsood goes across and pushes it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Maqsood, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Maqsood jumps in the crease and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Misbah, 1 run, very full and outside off, Misbah jams it out towards mid-off and sets off]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Misbah-ul-Haq, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>out</b> Ahmed Shehzad Run Out!! 1 run completed. Shehzad has thrown it away just before reaching his century. It was short and slightly wide outside off, Shehzad cuts it towards deep backward point and sets off, he decides to take on the fielder from sweeper cover, who runs across to his left, picks it up and fires in the throw at the striker's end. Shehzad was struggling to make his ground, but dives to get in the crease. Unfortunately for him, his bat was in the air as he was sliding inside the crease after the dive. He walks back disappointed. Not to forget, the throw from Shaiman Anwar was very good. <b>Ahmed Shehzad run out (Shaiman Anwar/Swapnil Patil) 93(105) [4s-8 6s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[The third umpire has been pressed into service to check a <b>run-out</b>. Shehzad is the man in question. It is close and his bat is in the air while he dives to get back in. He is <b>OUT</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Maqsood, 2 runs, poor fielding effort at long-off, the fielder should have been on his toes there, it was the slower delivery on a good length and outside off, Maqsood lofts it to the left of long-off, the fielder runs across and gets to it, but he was a little too late to relase the throw and allows the batsmen to come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Maqsood, no run, fuller in length and outside off, Maqsood drives and picks out cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, on a good length and angling in, Shehzad hoicks it uppishly through mid-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Maqsood, 1 run, back of a length delivery outside off, Maqsood looks to force it through the off-side off the back foot, gets an outside edge that rolls away to the left of backward point, the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Maqsood, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Maqsood punches it to the right of the bowler, who dives but can't stop the ball. However, Shehzad at the non-striker's end fails to get out of the way and the ball rolls away off his pad towards mid-wicket, the batsmen can't take the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, length delivery on off and middle, Shehzad bunts it down to mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Maqsood, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Maqsood shuffles across and wrists it towards mid-wicket, where the fielder moves to his left and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sohaib Maqsood, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now. Both Shehzad and Sohail did well in this period to compile Pakistan's first 100-plus partnership in this tournament, bringing up their respective fifties in the meantime as well. However, the job is still half done for the Pakistanis as they look to make the most out of the batting powerplay. Shehzad is nearing his hundred and he will look to cut loose once he reaches the landmark.]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Sohail, <b>out</b> Caught by Shaiman Anwar!! Sohail falls while trying to up the ante. The umpires check for Naveed's front foot, but it is fine. It was on a length and around off, Sohail went for the loft over mid-on but gets it high on the bat, ends up giving a dolly to mid-on. He is disappointed with the shot and looks at his bat with anger. Nevertheless, it was a good knock from him. <b>Sohail c Shaiman Anwar b Naveed 70(83) [4s-5 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Naveed to Sohail, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, another full one outside off, Shehzad drives uppishly through the cover, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Sohail, 1 run, touch fuller and on the stumps, Sohail makes room, drops it in front of cover-point and hares across to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Sohail, no run, takes two steps down the wicket and has a wild swing at a length delivery angling away outside off, Sohail can't connect and the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, drop-and-run single from Shehzad, it was on a good length and just outside off, Shehzad waits for it and just pushes it in front of cover, the batsmen take a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Naveed [6.0-0-19-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Sohail, no run, touch shortish and on the stumps, Sohail backs away and punches hard, but picks out cover-point to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, angling in on middle and leg, Shehzad bunts it down to long-on and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Ahmed Shehzad, 2 runs, length delivery around off, Shehzad lofts it over wide of long-off and the batsmen take an easy two]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Ahmed Shehzad, 2 runs, length delivery on middle, Shehzad wrists it wide of long-on, good running ensures that the batsmen come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Sohail, 1 run, angling in on middle and leg, Sohail works it past mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>150 of the partnership</b> comes up with this boundary, it was fuller and around off, Sohail mistimes the heave through mid-wicket but the ball had enough to reach the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, 1 run, Tauqir drags his length back seeing Sohail give the charge, Sohail punches it to long-on and he will keep the strike, Tauqir finishes with figures of <b>0/52 off his 10 overs</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, advances down the track and bunts it towards extra cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, 1 run, comes down the track, pushes this towards mid-on and sets off for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, flighted delivery on middle, Shehzad works it past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>FOUR</b>, shuffles across, gets down and just paddle sweeps this low full toss past backward square leg, he was inside the circle there and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, 1 run, quicker and around off, Sohail punches it down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Pakistan have decided to take the <b>batting powerplay</b> early. Tauqir will bowl his final over.]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, leg-cutter just outside off, Shehzad stands tall and knocks it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Sohail, 1 run, good length ball just outside off, Sohail punches it square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Ahmed Shehzad, 3 runs, drags the length back, Shehzad steers it to third man, it came off the gloves and hence didn't have the pace to beat short third man's chase]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>FOUR</b>, some improvisation from Shehzad, shuffles across his stumps a long way and helps the length delivery to the right of short fine, he got enough wood to pick up a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, this one holds up on the wicket, Shehzad is early into the push, checks his shot and the ball lobs back to the bowler, luckily it lands well in front of Karate]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, good length ball on middle, Shehzad presses forward and knocks it to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, turning into the pads, Shehzad nurdles it behind square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>wide</b>, darted down the leg-side, wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, makes plenty of room, looks to cut, misses and a good take by the keeper. He should have tried and played it to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, bends his front knee and heaves it towards mid-wicket, the fielder dives to his right and makes a fine stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, back aways and guides it towards backward point, wanted the single but Sohail is not interested]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, knocks it towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>FOUR</b>, sloppy from Saqlain. Flighted on off, Shehzad shimmies down the track and chips it over mid-wicket, the fielder from long-on runs to his right, tries to pick it up with one hand, misses and the ball rolls away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, drifts onto Shehzad's pads, flicked away behind square for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, short of length around off, Shehzad knocks it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, on a length just outside off, Shehzad looks to late cut it, is beaten by the extra bounce. Good take by the keeper, who is standing up to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Sohail, 1 run, angled across off, Sohail bunts it to the left of backward point, scampers through for a brisk single]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Sohail, no run, opens the bat face and guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karate to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, back of a length on middle and leg, Shehzad nudges it wide of mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Krishnachandran Karate, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, again, uses his feet to get to the pitch and pushes it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, 2 runs, takes a couple of steps down the wicket, whips it over mid-wicket, wide of long-on and comes back comfortably for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, 1 run, knocks it to sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, slower and just outside off, Shehzad eases it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, flat and on the stumps, Shehzad punches it towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, quicker and just outside off, Shehzad misses out on the cut shot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K Khan to Sohail, <b>SIX</b>, fabulous shot! Afridi also appreciates that shot as he claps in delight from the dug-out. Flighted on off, Sohail dances down the track, meets the pitch of the ball and lofts it handsomely over long-on for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K Khan to Sohail, no run, punched from the crease to the left of the bowler, Khurram moves across and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K Khan to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, tossed up on off, Shehzad drives it along the ground to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K Khan to Sohail, 1 run, tossed up on off, Sohail eases it down to long-on for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K Khan to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, sensible batting, drops it wide of point and sets off for a quick single, good response from Sohail]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K Khan to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>FOUR</b>, superb shot! Trifle short from Khurram, Shehzad was quick to pick up the length, goes deep in the crease and pulls it over mid-wicket, no one protecting the fence in the deep]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, floated up outside off, Shehzad drives it towards cover, the fielder fumbles and the batsmen pinch a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, 1 run, chips down the track and wrists it to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, 2 runs, tad short and on off, Sohail goes back and pulls it to deep mid-wicket, where the fielder from long-on runs to his left, dives and stops the ball from reaching the fence. That couple also brings up his <b>fifty</b>. And also the <b>100-run</b> partnership, first for Pakistan in this World Cup for any wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, no run, hangs back and punches it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, no run, backs away and looks to punch, ekes out an inside edge to short fine, Shehzad wanted the single but Sohail sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, <b>almost chopped on!</b> Slower and spins back in, Shehzad makes room and looks to cut, gets an under edge and the ball rolls past leg-stump, dribbles away to long leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Our man at the ground, <b>Jamie Alter</b>, tells us, "Pretty empty. A bit of a breeze. Kids playing on the banks. A low-key turnout for a low-key game."]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K Khan to Sohail, 2 runs, turns back in from outside off, Sohail backs away slightly and punches it through extra cover for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K Khan to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, comes down the track and whips it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K Khan to Sohail, 1 run, straight roller just outside off, Sohail goes for the drive and the outside edge runs towards short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K Khan to Sohail, no run, punched off the back foot to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K Khan to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, Shehzad brings up his <b>11th ODI fifty</b>. His first in World Cups. Leans forward and eases it to long-off for a single. Sohail walks up and congratulates his partner]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K Khan to Sohail, 1 run, pushed through on off, Sohail punches it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, leans forward and nudges it to square leg, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, 1 run, steps out and wrists it to long-on for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, works it with the turn to the right of mid-wicket for a comfortable single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, 1 run, flatter and just outside off, Sohail punches it square of the wicket, oast the diving point fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, no run, comes down the track and turns it towards mid-wicket, the fielder keeps them calm]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, no run, quicker and around off, Sohail stands tall and punches it towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K Khan to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, nurdles it behind square, picks out the fielder at short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K Khan to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, flighted on off, Shehzad presses forward and blocks it down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K Khan to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, darts it in on the stumps, Shehzad backs away and bunts it to the bowler, bit of extra bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K Khan to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, stays on the back foot and knocks it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K Khan to Sohail, 1 run, flatter and on off, Sohail punches it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K Khan to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, slider down leg, glanced fine to the right of short fine, Karate does well to keep them down to a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Khurram Khan, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, takes a couple of steps and works it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>FOUR</b>, drops it short outside off, Shehzad moves away slightly to the leg-side and cracks a cut square of the wicket, no chance for the sweeper cover to stop that]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, 1 run, bunts it in front of long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, huge shout for lbw, but umpire Ravi says not-out. Shehzad kneels down the wicket, misses the sweep and is struck right in front of middle stump. Umpire Ravi thought there was an inside edge, but replays confirm there was no wood involved. The Hawk-Eye shows that the ball was just clipping leg stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, flatter and on off, Shehzad punches it to extra cover, he backed away to give himself room]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, 1 run, flighted on off, Sohail comes down the track and eases it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, 1 run, short of length outside off, Sohail glides it with an angled bat to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, no run, takes a step down the wicket, opens the bat face and guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, no run, nurdles it with soft hands towards mid-wicket, either side and he would have picked up a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, no run, angling in from round the wicket, Sohail pushes it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, no run, back of a length outside off, Sohail waits for the ball to arrive, cuts it straight to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, no run, good length ball around off, defended towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, punches it gently to the left of the bowler, good stop by the UAE skipper]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, 2 runs, shuffles across his stumps, kneels down and scoops it to long leg, a better throw from Javed would have made it interesting as Shehzad had to hurry back]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, 1 run, skips out of the crease and eases it to long-on, call was for two, but they settle with one as the fielder got there quickly]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, no run, pushed through on off, Sohail knocks it to the left of the bowler, Tauqir gets across and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, no run, flighted close to off, Sohail defends solidly towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, no run, tossed up on off, Sohail comes down the track and blocks it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Ahmed Shehzad, 2 runs, too full and outside off, Shehzad comes on the front foot and drives it to wide long-off, sees that the fielder was Khurram Khan, calls for two and gets it easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, on a length just outside off, Shehzad drops it towards point, thinks about the single but decides against it]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Ahmed Shehzad, 2 runs, short and width on offer, Shehzad cuts it square of the wicket, the fielder at point gets a hand and takes the pace off the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, shortens the length outside off, Shehzad punches and finds backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, 1 run, fullish and outside off, Sohail leans into the drive to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, no run, back of a length on off, blocked with the straightest of bats, down the wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, 1 run, flatter and on off, Sohail stands tall and punches it past the diving bowler, Shehzad was also diving back into the crease as he had taken a start]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, 2 runs, Tauqir sees the batsman shimmy down the track and drags the length back, Sohail nudges it wide of mid-wicket, comes back for the second before the ball is hunted down]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, flighted on off, Shehzad works it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, 1 run, takes a couple of steps down the wicket and wrists it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, no run, slower and around off, Sohail pushes it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, no run, glanced to backward square leg, picks out the fielder there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>SIX</b>, much more like the Shehzad we all know. Gives the charge, converts it into a length ball and plays a free-flowing loft straight over mid-off. The ball clears the rope quite comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, length ball on the fourth stump line, Shehzad knocks it to the right of backward point, the fielder does well to keep the batsmen at their respective ends]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, nice shape, but the line is well wide of off, Shehzad has nothing to do with it, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, 1 run, angling in, Sohail shuffles across and tucks it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, no run, pitched up just outside off, Sohail drives it in the air, on the bounce to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, no run, continues round the wicket to Sohail, keeps it on a length around off, defended to the right of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, 2 runs, tossed up outside off, Shehzad leans forward and drives it wide of long-off, the batsmen take two before the fielder from long-off runs across to his left and fields the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, pushed through on off, Shehzad knocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, floated up on off, Shehzad pushes it to the left of mid-wicket, who dives and saves some runs for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, 1 run, touch quicker and on middle, Sohail pushes it down to long-on and gets off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, eases this flighted delivery down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, flatter and on off, Shehzad punches it to the right of the bowler, who runs across to his rigth and looks to stop the ball, he fails but the fielder from mid-wicket did well to get behind it and prevents the single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now. Pakistan got off to a disastrous start with Nasir Jamshed failing once again. However, these two have since then put on a 50-plus partnership to steady the innings. UAE have only themselves to blame as they dropped Shehzad twice in this period. Even though the first chance was a little difficult, the second one was a regulation catch. Pakistan have improved their run-rate as well, but there's still a long way to go...]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, back of a length delivery on the pads, Shehzad works it to fine leg and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, fullish delivery with a hint of shape away from the batsman, Shehzad presses forward and drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, length delivery shaping away outside off, Shehzad keeps his bat out of the way and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[Comes over the wicket to Shehzad]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, 1 run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Sohail stays back and drops it in front of square leg and sets off, the batsmen take the single comfortably in the end even though the fielder was charging in towards the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, no run, fuller in length and outside off, Sohail comes on the front foot and drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, no run, back of a length delivery on off from round the wicket, Sohail goes across and turns it to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, 2 runs, short and outside off, Shehzad rocks back and punches it square of the wicket, the batsmen take a couple before the fielder from cover-point cuts it off]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, quicker and just outside off, Shehzad gets behind the line and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, 1 run, comes down the track to this tossed up delivery outside off, Sohail drives it down to long-off, the single also brings up the <b>50-run partnership</b> between these two]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, no run, floated up just outside off, Sohail presses forward and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Sohail, no run, flighted delivery just outside off, Sohail leans forward and pushes it in front of cover, he was looking for the single there but Shehzad says no]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Tauqir to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, flatter and on leg, Shehzad shuffles across and tucks it away to backward square leg with the turn]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Tauqir, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Introduction of spin as the captain comes onto bowl]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Sohail leans forward and pushes it in front of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, no run, back of a length delivery angling in around off, Sohail pushes it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, poor delivery from Javed, down the leg-side with the angle, Sohail just glances it fine, the ball runs away to the fence as the fine leg fielder was a little square in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[Comes round the wicket now]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, <b>wide</b>, down the leg-side and the umpire calls it a wide once again]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, good shot from Sohail, it was almost a yorker outside off, Sohail squeezes out the drive to the left of mid-off, who gives chase but the ball beats him to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, <b>wide</b>, down the leg-side, Sohail fails to nurdle it into the on-side, the umpire calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[Just a slip in place for Javed]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, no run, on a good length and shaping in from outside off, Sohail pushes it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amjad Javed to Sohail, 2 runs, low full toss on the pads, Sohail clips it behind square, good running ensures that the batsmen come back for the second before the fine leg fielder runs to his right and stops the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Amjad Javed, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[First change in bowling as Amjad Javed replaces Guruge]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Sohail, 1 run, back of a length delivery outside off, Sohail works it through square leg and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, full outside off, Shehzad drives it to sweeper cover and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, dances down the track and converts this fullish delivery into a yorker outside off, Shehzad squeezes it out into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, banged in short and outside off, Shehzad goes for the pull and gets it high on the bat, he miscues it completely and luckily for him, the ball falls short of the fielder at mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Sohail, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off, Sohail runs it down to third man and gets off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Sohail, 2 runs, back of a length delivery outside off, Sohail opens the face of the bat and steers it down to third man, the fielder was square and the batsmen take two before he gets around]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, slower ball just outside off, Shehzad was looking to run it down to third man, gets an outside edge that falls well short of the fielder at slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>FOUR</b>, comes down the track and lofts this length ball over mid-off, he didn't time it that well, the ball just slows down before the long-off boundary, the fielder gives chase but fails to keep the ball in play as his hand was touching the rope as he tried to flick it in, the TV umpire checks for the contact and then deems it a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, length delivery homing in on middle, Shehzad punches it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, good length delivery just outside off, Shehzad leans forward and defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>wide</b>, now he bowls one well down the leg-side, another wide signalled]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>wide</b>, angling away well wide outside off, Shehzad leaves and the umpire exercises his arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, another one on leg-stump, Shehzad glances but this time he picks out the fielder at short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>FOUR</b>, poor delivery to start the over, it was on his pads, Shehzad goes across just a touch and tickles it to the fine leg fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four!</b> It was fuller in length and outside off, Sohail leans forward and looks to drive, gets an outside edge that runs away to the third man fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Sohail, no run, angling away in the channel outside off, Sohail leaves it alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, <b>another one goes down!</b> It was a short of length delivery outside off, Shehzad drives it on the up but it was uppish, Berenger at backward point dives to his right, gets his hand on it, but drops it as he falls on the ground. It should have been taken, the bowler is very disappointed]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Sohail, 3 runs, length delivery outside off, Sohail comes forward and pushes it through the covers, the fielder from cover gives chase and saves a run for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Sohail, no run, overpitched outside off, Sohail leans forward, opens the face of the bat and drives, but picks out backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Sohail, no run, full and angled across off, Sohail lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Sohail, 1 run, back of a length delivery angling in on middle and leg, Sohail tucks it past square leg and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Sohail, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Sohail punches it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, fuller and around off, Sohail mistimes the heave uppishly through mid-wicket and the ball runs away to the fence, he didn't time it that well but the ball had enough to reach the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, slower one from Guruge, Shehzad drops it in front of point and sets off, the batsmen take the single comfortable in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, 2 runs, <b>dropped!</b> It was a very difficult chance though. It was on a good length and angled across off, Shehzad comes down the track and wanted to loft it over the infield, he doesnt't get the elevation and ends up chipping it towards mid-off, where Khurram Khan jumps up and gets his left hand on it, he can't hold onto it and the batsmen take a couple as the ball rolls away further to the deep, it was a good effort though]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, length delivery on off, Shehzad leans forward and pushes it to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Sohail, no run, short of length delivery on the pads, Sohail fails to nurdle it into the on-side, the ball rolls away into the on-side off the pad, Sohail was looking for the single but it's not there for the taking]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Sohail, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Sohail stays back, opens the face of the bat and punches it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, shortish and wide outside off, Shehzad cuts it uppishly towards squarish third man, the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Shehzad hops a little and defends it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, bowls this one well outside off, Shehzad flashes a cut at it, the ball had a little extra bounce and beats the batsman's blade]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, in the channel just outside off, Shehzad pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Sohail, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Sohail gets behind it and defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Sohail, 2 runs, poor fielding from Mustafa at square leg, it was on a good length and angling in on off, Sohail clips it through mid-wicket off the inside half of the bat, a misfield from Mustafa who had moved across to his right allows the batsmen to take two, the bowler wasn't too happy with that effort]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Sohail, no run, fuller and angling in around off, Sohail shuffles across and works it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, back of a length delivery on middle and leg, Shehzad clips it a little uppishly through mid-wicket, the batsmen take a single before the fielder from mid-on runs to his right and fields it]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, on a good length and on off, Shehzad stays back and defends, the ball was shapin away from him and he was almost squared up, but did well to get behind it]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, angling away well outside off, Shehzad leaves it alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, length delivery outside off, Shehzad leans forward and punches it to the left of mid-off, who runs across to his left and keeps the batsmen down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, full and on off and middle, Shehzad drives it towards mid-on off the inside half of the bat, the fielder moves to his left and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, touch fuller and well outside off, Shehzad shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, good ball from Naveed, it was on a length and outside off, Shehzad gets drawn into it, but the ball shapes away and beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, full and just outside off, Shehzad leaves it for the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, bowls this in the channel outside off, Shehzad lets that one pass]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Sohail, no run, length delivery shaping in from just outside off, Sohail defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Sohail, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Sohail pushes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Sohail, no run, back of a length delivery on off, Sohail gets behind the line and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Haris Sohail, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Jamshed, <b>out</b> Caught by K Khan!! Jamshed falls early once again. His poor form continues and this was a nothing shot from him. It was short and outside off, Jamshed went for the pull but got it off the toe-end of the bat. The ball goes in the air towards mid-on, who takes the simplest of catches. Pakistan are again off to a poor start. In fact, Jamshed broke his bat, the toe-end chipped off and he had a look at it immediately. <b>Jamshed c K Khan b Manjula Guruge 4(12)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Manjula Guruge to Jamshed, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Jamshed, 2 runs, on a good length and angling in on off and middle, Jamshed clips it wide of mid-on, the batsmen take two before the fielder chases it down]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Jamshed, no run, just short of a good length and around off, Jamshed punches it to mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, overpitched outside off, Shehzad drives it straight to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, length delivery just outside off, Shehzad pushes it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Jamshed, 1 run, back of a length delivery around off, Jamshed stays back and works it towards square leg, who dives to his left and makes half a stop, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away to the fielder's left]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Jamshed, no run, back of a length delivery on top of off, Jamshed defends it towards the bowler, who puts his right hand out and collects the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Jamshed, no run, full outside off, Jamshed leans forward and knocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Jamshed, no run, full toss from Naveed, Jamshed pushes it towards mid-on, who moves to his right and stops the ball, Jamshed was a little unhappy with himself for missing out on it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>FOUR</b>, good shot to end the over, it was banged in short and outside off, Shehzad rocks back and pulls it to the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, back of a length delivery on middle stump line, Shehzad hops and turns it towards square leg, he was looking for the single there but it's not there]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, back of a length delivery angling away, Shehzad punches it in front of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, length delivery angled across off, Shehzad bunts it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place for Guruge]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, there was extra bounce on that one as well, Shehzad pushes it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manjula Guruge to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, full and shaping back in on middle, Shehzad clips it to mid-wicket and was looking for the single, but they don't go through as the ball was not far away from the fielder]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Manjula Guruge, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Guruge will share the attack with Naveed...]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Jamshed, no run, peach to end the over, it was full and just outside off, Jamshed was looking to drive it through the off-side, the ball shapes back and goes past the inside edge, it was not very far away from the off stump either]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Jamshed, no run, angling away outside off, Jamshed lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Jamshed, no run, full and well outside off, Jamshed is not tempted to play at it]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Jamshed, <b>wide</b>, bowls this one slightly wide outside off and shaping away further, Jamshed leaves it and the umpire signals a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, full outside off, Shehzad leans forward and drives it through covers, the cover fielder gives chase and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Jamshed, 1 run, Jamshed gets off the mark, it was on a good length and outside off, Jamshed leans forward, opens the face of the bat and pushes it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Naveed to Jamshed, no run, fullish delivery on the pads, Jamshed clips it towards square leg, who dives to his right and stops the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jamshed and Ahmed Shehzad are at the crease. Jamshed is on strike. Naveed will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The teams are done with the national anthems. The openers stride out to the middle. UAE players are also out there. Nasir Jamshed will take the strike first. Mohammad Naveed will open the bowling with two slips in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>United Arab Emirates</b> (Playing XI): Amjad Ali, Andri Berenger, Krishnachandran Karate, Khurram Khan, Shaiman Anwar, Swapnil Patil(w), Rohan Mustafa, Amjad Javed, Mohammad Naveed, Mohammad Tauqir(c), Manjula Guruge]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan</b> (Playing XI): Nasir Jamshed, Ahmed Shehzad, Haris Sohail, Misbah-ul-Haq(c), Umar Akmal(w), Sohaib Maqsood, Shahid Afridi, Wahab Riaz, Sohail Khan, Rahat Ali, Mohammad Irfan]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>United Arab Emirates have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Tauqir:</b> "We had one bad game. We discussed about it, identified what mistakes we did and are ready for this game. We will be bowling first. It looks like a good wicket and with overcast conditions, we want to put pressure on them. He (Shaiman Anwar) has been batting well. Hopefully, the other batters can also do well."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Misbah:</b> "I think nowadays every team knows each other, their games. Especially, the coaches are woking really well with them, specially Aaqib (Javed). So, lets see, we are ready and we need to play really. We are got the same team. And I think we are happy to bat first. The last two games we played here, it was a really good batting pitch. We also played well and in the last game, New Zealand also played really well against us. It is a good batting pitch and it is a really good chance for our batsmen to get back into form. Every game is important and we have no other chance, because we have to win every game. We have to play every game to the best of our capabilities. We need to be more professional. We need a clinical performance in both batting and bowling, especially fielding. We are ready for that."]]></line><line><![CDATA[With many players of the UAE side having a Pakistani connection, it will be interesting to see how they go about their job against the Men in Green. Will Pakistan continue to employ the strategy of having an extra bowler? Or whether Nasir Jamshed will make way for another batsman? Stay tuned for the toss and the teams.]]></line><line><![CDATA[McLean Park has been a high scoring ground in the recent past. New Zealand made 359 for 5 here against Pakistan last month, a game they won by 119 runs. It will be interesting to see whether the team winning the toss decides to bat first here. This game will become all the more important for Pakistan, who will look to boost their net run-rate.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[After losing two consecutive games to India and the West Indies, Pakistan finally opened their account on the points table with a win over Zimbabwe. Misbah won the toss, but his team got off to a poor start. Both the Pakistani openers, Shehzad and Jamshed were back in the hut with just 4 runs on the board. Misbah then steadied the innings with Haris Sohail, who once again threw it away after getting off to a start. Pakistan lost wickets from time to time and if it was not for Wahab Riaz's unbeaten 46-ball 54, Pakistan would have struggled to post 235 on the board.]]></line><line><![CDATA[In reply, their bowlers did extremely well. Even though the Zimbabwean middle-order was threatening to take them the distance, Wahab Riaz and Mohammad Irfan made sure that they kept a tight leash on the batsmen. Both of them finished with 4 wickets each and helped Pakistan bowl Zimbabwe out for 215. This was a much needed win for Pakistan and even though it was not a convincing one, they wouldn't mind the two points they got.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>UAE</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[UAE's last game was a one-sided affair as India thrashed them by 9 wickets. After winning the toss and deciding to bat first, Mohammad Tauqir's men failed to get going. They kept losing wickets and at one stage, they were staring at a score of less than a 100 on the board. It was only after Shaiman Anwar's knock of 35 and a last wicket partnership of 31 runs that the team managed to cross 100, but only just.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chasing 103 to win, India were never going to be put under pressure. After Rohan Mustafa's brilliant fielding effort sent Dhawan back to the pavilion, Rohit and Kohli made sure that they don't give anything away to UAE. Both of them finished unbeaten and UAE's search for a win still continues.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>11:45 Local Time, 23:45 GMT, 05:15 IST:</b> The first game today is an all Asian contest, with Pakistan and UAE locking horns in the coastal city of Napier. Even though Pakistan is a much more accomplished international team, only two points separate these two sides at the bottom of Pool B. However, a win for Pakistan here will lift them above Zimbabwe for sure. Before we go any further, let's take a look at the form guide of both the teams.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>United Arab Emirates</b> (From): Amjad Ali, Andri Berenger, Krishnachandran Karate, Khurram Khan, Swapnil Patil(k), Shaiman Anwar, Rohan Mustafa, Amjad Javed, Mohammad Naveed, Mohammad Tauqir(c), Manjula Guruge, Nasir Aziz, Fahad Alhashmi, Kamran Shazad, Saqlain Haider]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan</b> (From): Nasir Jamshed, Ahmed Shehzad, Haris Sohail, Misbah-ul-Haq(c), Umar Akmal(k), Shahid Afridi, Sohaib Maqsood, Wahab Riaz, Sohail Khan, Rahat Ali, Mohammad Irfan, Younis Khan, Ehsan Adil, Yasir Shah, Sarfraz Ahmed]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>339</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>6</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>50</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Pakistan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1055</playerid>
					<name>Nasir Jamshed</name>
					<batsman-name>Jamshed</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Jamshed</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Manjula Guruge</bowler>
					<bowlerId>9830</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Khurram Khan</fielder>
						<fielderId>81</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1787</playerid>
					<name>Ahmed Shehzad</name>
					<batsman-name>Ahmed Shehzad</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ahmed Shehzad</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>93</runs>
					<balls>105</balls>
					<fours>8</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Shaiman Anwar</fielder>
						<fielderId>9837</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Swapnil Patil</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>9834</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8299</playerid>
					<name>Haris Sohail</name>
					<batsman-name>H Sohail</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sohail</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>70</runs>
					<balls>83</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Naveed</bowler>
					<bowlerId>9832</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Shaiman Anwar</fielder>
						<fielderId>9837</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9524</playerid>
					<name>Sohaib Maqsood</name>
					<batsman-name>S Maqsood</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Maqsood</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>45</runs>
					<balls>31</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Manjula Guruge</bowler>
					<bowlerId>9830</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Rohan Mustafa</fielder>
						<fielderId>9835</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>274</playerid>
					<name>Misbah-ul-Haq</name>
					<batsman-name>Misbah</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Misbah</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>65</runs>
					<balls>49</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Manjula Guruge</bowler>
					<bowlerId>9830</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Rohan Mustafa</fielder>
						<fielderId>9835</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1992</playerid>
					<name>Umar Akmal</name>
					<batsman-name>U Akmal</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>U Akmal</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>19</runs>
					<balls>13</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Manjula Guruge</bowler>
					<bowlerId>9830</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Amjad Ali</fielder>
						<fielderId>1365</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>142</playerid>
					<name>Shahid Afridi</name>
					<batsman-name>Afridi</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Afridi</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>21</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1051</playerid>
					<name>Wahab Riaz</name>
					<batsman-name>Riaz</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Riaz</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1120</playerid>
					<name>Sohail Khan</name>
					<batsman-name>S Khan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sohail Khan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8301</playerid>
					<name>Rahat Ali</name>
					<batsman-name>Rahat Ali</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rahat Ali</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7621</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Irfan</name>
					<batsman-name>Irfan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Irfan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1055</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>10</runs>
				<overs>3.3</overs>
				<batsman>Nasir Jamshed</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Jamshed</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8299</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>170</runs>
				<overs>32.5</overs>
				<batsman>Haris Sohail</batsman>
				<batsman-name>H Sohail</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1787</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>176</runs>
				<overs>34.1</overs>
				<batsman>Ahmed Shehzad</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Ahmed Shehzad</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9524</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>251</runs>
				<overs>42.6</overs>
				<batsman>Sohaib Maqsood</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Maqsood</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1992</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>312</runs>
				<overs>48.3</overs>
				<batsman>Umar Akmal</batsman>
				<batsman-name>U Akmal</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>274</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>312</runs>
				<overs>48.4</overs>
				<batsman>Misbah-ul-Haq</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Misbah</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>12</wides>
			<noballs>1</noballs>
			<legbyes>3</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>16</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="United Arab Emirates">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>9832</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Naveed</name>
					<bowler-name>Naveed</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Naveed</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>50</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9830</playerid>
					<name>Manjula Guruge</name>
					<bowler-name>Manjula Guruge</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Manjula Guruge</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>56</runsoff>
					<wickets>4</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1366</playerid>
					<name>Amjad Javed</name>
					<bowler-name>A Javed</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Amjad Javed</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>76</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>87</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Tauqir</name>
					<bowler-name>M Tauqir</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M Tauqir</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>52</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>81</playerid>
					<name>Khurram Khan</name>
					<bowler-name>K Khan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>K Khan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>21</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10041</playerid>
					<name>Krishnachandran Karate</name>
					<bowler-name>Karate</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Karate</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>58</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9835</playerid>
					<name>Rohan Mustafa</name>
					<bowler-name>Rohan Mustafa</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rohan Mustafa</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>23</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>6</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1365</playerid>
					<name>Amjad Ali</name>
					<bowler-name>Amjad Ali</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Amjad Ali</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10124</playerid>
					<name>Andri Berenger</name>
					<bowler-name>Andri Berenger</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Andri Berenger</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9837</playerid>
					<name>Shaiman Anwar</name>
					<bowler-name>Shaiman Anwar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shaiman Anwar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9834</playerid>
					<name>Swapnil Patil</name>
					<bowler-name>Swapnil Patil</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Swapnil Patil</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>210</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>8</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>50</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="United Arab Emirates">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1365</playerid>
					<name>Amjad Ali</name>
					<batsman-name>Amjad Ali</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Amjad Ali</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>14</runs>
					<balls>30</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Rahat Ali</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8301</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10124</playerid>
					<name>Andri Berenger</name>
					<batsman-name>Andri Berenger</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Andri Berenger</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>13</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>S Khan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1120</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Umar Akmal</fielder>
						<fielderId>1992</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10041</playerid>
					<name>Krishnachandran Karate</name>
					<batsman-name>Karate</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Karate</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>S Khan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1120</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Umar Akmal</fielder>
						<fielderId>1992</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>81</playerid>
					<name>Khurram Khan</name>
					<batsman-name>K Khan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>K Khan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>43</runs>
					<balls>54</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>S Maqsood</bowler>
					<bowlerId>9524</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Wahab Riaz</fielder>
						<fielderId>1051</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9837</playerid>
					<name>Shaiman Anwar</name>
					<batsman-name>Shaiman Anwar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shaiman Anwar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>62</runs>
					<balls>88</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Afridi</bowler>
					<bowlerId>142</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Nasir Jamshed</fielder>
						<fielderId>1055</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9834</playerid>
					<name>Swapnil Patil</name>
					<batsman-name>Swapnil Patil</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Swapnil Patil</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>36</runs>
					<balls>68</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Riaz</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1051</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9835</playerid>
					<name>Rohan Mustafa</name>
					<batsman-name>Rohan Mustafa</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rohan Mustafa</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Afridi</bowler>
					<bowlerId>142</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ahmed Shehzad</fielder>
						<fielderId>1787</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1366</playerid>
					<name>Amjad Javed</name>
					<batsman-name>A Javed</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Amjad Javed</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>40</runs>
					<balls>33</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Riaz</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1051</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sohail Khan</fielder>
						<fielderId>1120</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9832</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Naveed</name>
					<batsman-name>Naveed</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Naveed</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>87</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Tauqir</name>
					<batsman-name>M Tauqir</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M Tauqir</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9830</playerid>
					<name>Manjula Guruge</name>
					<batsman-name>Manjula Guruge</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Manjula Guruge</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1365</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>19</runs>
				<overs>6.4</overs>
				<batsman>Amjad Ali</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Amjad Ali</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>10124</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>19</runs>
				<overs>7.3</overs>
				<batsman>Andri Berenger</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Andri Berenger</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>10041</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>25</runs>
				<overs>9.6</overs>
				<batsman>Krishnachandran Karate</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Karate</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>81</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>108</runs>
				<overs>29.2</overs>
				<batsman>Khurram Khan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>K Khan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9837</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>140</runs>
				<overs>38.1</overs>
				<batsman>Shaiman Anwar</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Shaiman Anwar</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9835</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>140</runs>
				<overs>38.3</overs>
				<batsman>Rohan Mustafa</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rohan Mustafa</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1366</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>208</runs>
				<overs>49.2</overs>
				<batsman>Amjad Javed</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Javed</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9834</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>210</runs>
				<overs>49.5</overs>
				<batsman>Swapnil Patil</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Swapnil Patil</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>12</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>13</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Pakistan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7621</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Irfan</name>
					<bowler-name>Irfan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Irfan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>2</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1120</playerid>
					<name>Sohail Khan</name>
					<bowler-name>S Khan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sohail Khan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>2</maidens>
					<runsoff>54</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8301</playerid>
					<name>Rahat Ali</name>
					<bowler-name>Rahat Ali</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rahat Ali</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>30</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1051</playerid>
					<name>Wahab Riaz</name>
					<bowler-name>Riaz</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Riaz</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>54</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>142</playerid>
					<name>Shahid Afridi</name>
					<bowler-name>Afridi</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Afridi</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9524</playerid>
					<name>Sohaib Maqsood</name>
					<bowler-name>S Maqsood</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Maqsood</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>16</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8299</playerid>
					<name>Haris Sohail</name>
					<bowler-name>H Sohail</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sohail</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>18</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1055</playerid>
					<name>Nasir Jamshed</name>
					<bowler-name>Jamshed</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Jamshed</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1787</playerid>
					<name>Ahmed Shehzad</name>
					<bowler-name>Ahmed Shehzad</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ahmed Shehzad</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>274</playerid>
					<name>Misbah-ul-Haq</name>
					<bowler-name>Misbah</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Misbah</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1992</playerid>
					<name>Umar Akmal</name>
					<bowler-name>U Akmal</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>U Akmal</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



