<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="12859" >
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>5th Match, Pool B</gameDesc>
		<series>WC 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Ireland</home>
		<away>West Indies</away>
		<teamsabbr>IRE vs WI</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>IRE</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>WI</awayabbr>
		<homeId>27</homeId>
		<awayId>10</awayId>
		<venue>Saxton Oval, Nelson</venue>
		<startdate>16 02 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>16 02 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Ireland</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Ireland won by 4 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Ireland</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>4</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Richard Illingworth</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Bruce Oxenford</Name>
			<Country>Aus</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Chris Gaffaney</Name>
			<Country>NZ</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Chris Broad</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>22:00</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>true</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150216054037</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>IRE</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>WI</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>307</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>6</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>45.5</batteamovers>
		<status>Ireland won by 4 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>622</playerid>
			<name>John Mooney*</name>
			<batsman-name>J Mooney</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>J Mooney</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>6</runs>
			<balls-faced>5</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>691</playerid>
			<name>Niall O'Brien</name>
			<batsman-name>N O'Brien</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>N O'Brien</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>79</runs>
			<balls-faced>60</balls-faced>
			<fours>11</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>379</playerid>
			<name>Jerome Taylor*</name>
			<bowler-name>Jerome Taylor</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Jerome Taylor</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>8.5</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>71</runs>
			<wickets>3</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1359</playerid>
			<name>Kemar Roach</name>
			<bowler-name>Roach</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Roach</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>6</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>52</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>305</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>690</playerid>
<name>Kevin O'Brien</name>
<player-runs>0</player-runs>
<player-balls>1</player-balls>
<runs>291</runs>
<wicket-nbr>6</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>0</bowlerid>
<bowlername></bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>4</byes>
			<wides>9</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>13</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[1 1 . 1 . . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. . 1 . W . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>W1 4 4 1 1 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. 1 1 . 4 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_WC/IRE_WI_FEB16/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[That concludes proceedings from this game. Looking forward to your company tomorrow as New Zealand take on Scotland at Dunedin. This is <b>Ramakrishnan</b>, signing off on behalf of <b>Akshay</b>, <b>Sidhant</b>, <b>Raju</b>, <b>Krishna</b> and <b>Bhanu</b>. Goodbye!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Alviro Petersen</b>: Ireland produced a performance of the highest standard, and beat West Indies in the #WC2015]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Glenn McGrath</b>: A great win by @Irelandcricket over the @westindies A brilliant effort to chase down 304 & did it with 4 overs to go #CWC15]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Trent Johnston</b>: Certainly not a shock or upset from this group of players. Warm up games are just that. Enjoy the celebrations as I know you can and will.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Harsha Bhogle</b>: Ireland win. Not an upset.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohandas Menon</b>: Pakistan at Kingston by 3 wkts in WC2007 England at Bangalore by 3 wkts in WC2011 #WIvIre #CWC15]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here are a few <b>tweets</b>:]]></line><line><![CDATA[What a win for Ireland! When the ICC announced that the 2015 World Cup would be contested only among 10 teams, Ireland were not happy and they appealed to the cricket governing body to allow the associates-affiliates as well. Boy, they have justified their inclusion today and played some fantastic cricket for most of the match.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Porterfield</b>: "It's obviously a fantastic win. The way we went about chasing those runs was great. It sets us up nicely for the next few games, so it's a great position to be in. We thoroughly believed in ourselves that we can chase this down. We've just got to continue that in the tournament. They obviously had a strong finish there. 300 was probably about par, we knew it was a good pitch. We knew it was well within our grasp and we just needed to lay that platform. The batsmen were fantastic. Most definitely (when asked if Ireland can qualify for the quarters). We are going to play in completely different conditions in the next game, it tends to be quicker and bouncier at Brisbane."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Holder</b>: "It was a tough loss. We backed ourselves to defend 300, but we didn't defend today. It was a good partnership between Simmons and Sammy, we were struggling in the middle overs and they came in, added impetus to the innings and got us to 300. We tried to be a lot more specific in terms of our powerplay overs and our death bowling at the end. We didn't get wickets today. I think we just need to be more precise when we set the field and just stick to the fields which we set. We are leaking too many boundaries. So I think we just need to tighten up there and we'd be a lot better off in the games to come."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Stirling</b>: "Great to win that first game in the competition and hopefully we can make it two from two in a few days from now. I was happy with my innings. I owed the guys 90 runs after dropping Sammy on nought, so it was nice to get a few. I think it was a good toss to win. We got early wickets and the pitch got better and better as the day went on, thankfully we chased it."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Paul Stirling</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ireland were superb with the bat. They have shown to the world that the tag of 'minnows' is not for them. They keep producing such good performances. They knocked out Pakistan in the 2007 World Cup and defeated England in 2011 as well. West Indies are their newest prey and this is just the start of the tournament. Their win today opens up the group even more. The fourth quarter-final spot from this group could well be decided between Ireland and Zimbabwe, instead of the West Indies.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier in the day, West Indies lost 3 wickets in a space of 14 balls and were tottering at 87/5 at one stage.  However, Sammy and Simmons then got together and put on a 154-run stand for the 6th wicket. Sammy registered his highest ODI score and missed out on a century by 11 runs. Simmons, however, went onto score his 2nd ODI ton and helped his team to go past 300. He was well supported by Russell, who chipped in with a 13-ball 27. The Irish bowlers, who were magnificent at the start and the middle, lost their line and lengths during the death overs. Ireland conceded 124 runs in the last 10 overs and were taken to the cleaners by the West Indian batsmen. As it turns out, it wasn't enough for Holder and Co. to win.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ireland have done extremely well to chase this mammoth total down. After taking a drubbing in the final few overs while bowling, the Irish batters started off brilliantly. Porterfield and Stirling were very good, putting on 71 for the first wicket. However, even after their captain Porterfield departed, Stirling and Ed Joyce batted aggressively, adding 106 for the second wicket in just 86 balls. Unfortunately, Stirling got out in the nineties and the way he batted, he deserved a century. Niall O'Brien then joined Ed Joyce at the crease and both of them thrashed Holder's bowlers to all parts of the park. They put on 96 runs together in just 11.3 overs, before Ed Joyce departed for 84. Even though the West Indies managed to pick up 3 more wickets in quick succession after that, Niall O'Brien made sure that there were no more hiccups and saw his team through. He himself finished with 79 off 60 balls.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mooney jumps in joy and hugs O'Brien. The Ireland players come onto the field and shake hands with their opponents. There has been a good support for the Ireland team today at Nelson and their fans are joyous.]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to J Mooney, <b>FOUR</b>, That's it! <b>It was Pakistan in 2007, England in 2011 and now it's West Indies in 2015</b>. Ireland become the first team to successfully chase down a total in this World Cup. This is the fifth time in World Cup history that a target in excess of 300 has been achieved and Ireland have three of those to their credit. Coming back to the ball, it was a short ball on the stumps, Mooney tries to pull, he was surprised by the pace on the ball as it came quickly onto him, the ball takes the top edge and flies over the keeper's head]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to J Mooney, no run, low full toss outside off stump, punched to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Ireland dug-out is ready to erupt! Interestingly, there is a man at slip.]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to N O'Brien, 1 run, driven hard, but Simmons runs quickly to his right at long-off and keeps them down to one]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to J Mooney, 1 run, back of a length hurrying onto Mooney, who hops and tucks it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to J Mooney, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Mooney looks to run it down to the third man but misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Ireland are just a hit away now and their fans are ecstatic in the stands.]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to N O'Brien, no run, good length delivery outside off stump, O'Brien defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to J Mooney, 1 run, a lazy effort from Gayle and he fumbles the ball at cover, they get a run. Short of a length delivery just outside off stump, Mooney taps it gently, Gayle tries to fetch it with his right hand but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to N O'Brien, 1 run, taps this into the on-side and sets off for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to N O'Brien, <b>FOUR</b>, that's an authoritative shot. Full and outside off stump, O'Brien drives well over extra-cover and it rockets to the boundary. He's doing it easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to N O'Brien, <b>FOUR</b>, friendly ball and O'Brien helps himself to a boundary. Down the leg side, a fine little tickle takes it to the fine leg boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>John Mooney, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to N O'Brien, <b>out</b> K O'Brien Run Out!! 1 run completed. The younger brother is late to respond for the second run and he's run-out for a duck. Slower ball wide outside off stump, Niall drives it to deep point, Smith runs to his right and fires an accurate throw adjacent to the stumps at the bowler's end. Roach stays calm and whips the bails off before Kevin made his ground. <b>K O'Brien run out (Dwayne Smith/Roach) 0(1)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Roach to N O'Brien, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Run-out check has been sent upstairs. Kevin O'Brien is in trouble and he's OUT! Is there a twist in the tale?]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to K O'Brien, no run, full delivery on the off stump, dug out to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kevin O'Brien, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to G Wilson, <b>out</b> Caught by Gayle!! A soft dismissal and West Indies are hardly celebrating. Full and outside off stump, in the slot to be put away, Wilson doesn't control the drive and hits in the air, Gayle moves his hands to his left at cover and reverse-cups the ball easily in the end. <b>G Wilson c Gayle b Jerome Taylor 1(6)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Jerome Taylor to G Wilson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to G Wilson, no run, shortish delivery on the leg stump, Wilson tries to hop and defend, the ball pops up in the air, the bowler rushes forward but it drops just short of him]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to N O'Brien, 1 run, short of length delivery angling into the left-hander, defended to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[O'Brien wants a change of bat.]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to N O'Brien, no run, yorker on the stumps, O'Brien digs it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to N O'Brien, no run, defends this good length delivery to backward point and sets off, but Wilson says no, the fielder has a shy at the stumps and a direct-hit would have been very interesting]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to G Wilson, no run, looks to pull this short ball from outside off stump, but gets beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to G Wilson, no run, fullish and around the off stump, Wilson defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to N O'Brien, 1 run, width on offer outside off stump, O'Brien cuts it to deep extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to N O'Brien, no run, short of length delivery, O'Brien taps it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to G Wilson, 1 run, shortish and outside off stump, Wilson cuts it to deep backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to N O'Brien, 1 run, short of length delivery on the leg stump, O'Brien tucks to backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kemar Roach [4.0-0-38-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to G Wilson, no run, full and on the leg stump, defended to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to N O'Brien, 1 run, full and outside off stump, lofted drive goes on the bounce to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to N O'Brien, no run, short and wide outside off stump, gently tapped into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Gary Wilson, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Balbirnie, <b>out</b> Caught by Darren Bravo!! Short ball and he holes out. Balbirnie pulls, but doesn't get the connection right, hits it in the air and deep square leg just moves to his right to take an easy catch. That's the second catch for Bravo today. <b>Balbirnie c Darren Bravo b Jerome Taylor 9(9) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Jerome Taylor to Balbirnie, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Balbirnie, no run, shortish delivery outside off stump, cut to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Balbirnie, no run, pushed to mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Is there a Lasith Malinga in West Indies to nip out 4 in 4?]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to N O'Brien, no run, slants one into the left-hander, O'Brien misses the flick and is hit on the pad. The ball was going down the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to N O'Brien, no run, slower delivery on the off stump, O'Brien fends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Balbirnie, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Balbirnie dabs it to point and sets off for a sharp run]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Balbirnie, no run, shortish and outside off stump, punched towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Balbirnie, no run, shortish and outside off stump, tapped to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to N O'Brien, 1 run, slower ball on the leg stump, O'Brien tucks it to fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell [5.0-0-31-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ireland need just 22 runs off 60 balls and it's just a matter of time for them.]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Balbirnie, <b>FOUR</b>, oh no! One more slower ball full and in the slot, coach Curtly Ambrose is going to be severe on the West Indies bowlers I guess, Balbirnie just punches it off the front foot to the left of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Balbirnie, <b>FOUR</b>, the boundaries are flowing out there. How many times do I write that a West Indies bowler bowls a fullish slower ball, the result is evident, this time a cover drive timed to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Balbirnie, <b>wide</b>, attempts the bumper but that goes well over Balbirnie's head]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Balbirnie, no run, yorker length delivery from Taylor, Balbirnie digs it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to N O'Brien, 1 run, cut away to sweeper cover for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Andrew Balbirnie, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Ed Joyce, <b>out</b> Caught by Darren Bravo!! That's hit in the air and straight to the fielder. Full and wide outside off stump, Ed Joyce looks to drive hard, he almost slices it, the ball goes flat, it was timed well but he picked out the fielder at sweeper cover. End of a sensational innings. He gets a great applause as he walks back. He raises his bat to acknowledge the applause. <b>Ed Joyce c Darren Bravo b Jerome Taylor 84(67) [4s-10 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Jerome Taylor to Ed Joyce, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Ed Joyce, <b>FOUR</b>, the boundaries don't seem to stop. Taylor looks for a widish yorker, but Ed Joyce out-thinks him by opening the face of the bat at the last moment and squeezes it fine to the third man boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Ireland have stolen 25 runs off the 12 balls.]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to N O'Brien, 2 runs, short and wide outside off stump, O'Brien backs away and slaps it uppishly to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to N O'Brien, 2 runs, full delivery outside off stump, O'Brien drives it down to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to N O'Brien, <b>FOUR</b>, over the top again and four more! Oh come on! Ask them to stop feeding the batsman. Full and outside off stump, O'Brien lofts it flat over mid-off. Maybe they needed a Mohammad Irfan at mid-off, as a few of the boundaries have just about managed to clear the fielder inside the ring]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Ed Joyce, 1 run, Ed Joyce nudges this to square leg, looks for the second, but the fielder rushed in quickly]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to N O'Brien, 1 run, short of length delivery from Holder, pulled away to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to N O'Brien, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>13th ODI fifty</b>, this has come off just 38 balls and what a hand he's played. Full and in the slot, this is unacceptable from West Indies. After scoring a hundred, Simmons said in the innings break that the slower balls aren't stopping on the batsman, the West Indies bowlers seem to have misread the pitch. They continue to take pace off the ball and bowl full, a set batsman like O'Brien doesn't miss out on those juicy balls and he muscles it over mid-off and it's almost a maximum]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Eleven runs off the over and the equation is down to just 50 runs needed off 72 balls.]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Ed Joyce, no run, slower ball wide outside off stump, Ed Joyce drives and picks out cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Ed Joyce, no run, full and outside off stump, Ed Joyce taps it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to N O'Brien, 1 run, walks across the stumps and tucks the slower ball to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to N O'Brien, <b>FOUR</b>, this is so easy for the batsman. Full and in the slot, O'Brien waits for the ball and muscles the drive, it went really fast as he hit it hard, to the right of mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to N O'Brien, <b>FOUR</b>, and he's hurting them straightaway! Full and outside off stump, not sure if this is the right length at this stage, O'Brien lofts the drive, mid-off jumps high but it just evades him]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to N O'Brien, 2 runs, oh no! The <b>West Indies captain drops a vital catch</b>. Nothing is working for them on the field! Slower delivery from Taylor, O'Brien mistimes the slog high in the air, mid-on runs to his left, gets both hands to it, but the ball hits the fingertips and goes down to ground. Holder is livid with himself as he throws the ball back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to N O'Brien, 1 run, O'Brien shuffles in the crease, Holder bowls a good short ball, the batsman manages to hook it down to long leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to N O'Brien, no run, O'Brien gives himself some room and tries to cut this over the infield but is beaten again]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to N O'Brien, no run, Holder changes the angle again, short of length delivery from round the wicket, O'Brien cuts and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to N O'Brien, <b>FOUR</b>, top shot sir! Length ball just around the off stump, O'Brien goes leg-side and easily lofts it inside out over extra-cover. The ball goes almost all the way]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to N O'Brien, no run, short of length delivery angling away from the left-hander, O'Brien looks to cut but chops it to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[Holder comes back over the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Ed Joyce, 1 run, good length delivery outside off stump, Ed Joyce guides it down to square third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jason Holder [7.0-1-24-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The skipper has employed a slip.]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to N O'Brien, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, O'Brien defends it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to N O'Brien, 2 runs, low full toss outside off stump, O'Brien squeezes it down to deep backward point and returns for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Ed Joyce, 1 run, good length delivery outside off stump, Ed Joyce guides it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to N O'Brien, 1 run, O'Brien tries to drive very hard, he loses shape while meeting the ball, hence it goes off the inside half of the bat to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to N O'Brien, no run, full and around the off stump, driven to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Ed Joyce, 1 run, round the wicket to start the new spell. Fullish ball outside off stump, Ed Joyce drives it along the ground to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jerome Taylor [3.0-0-33-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Batting powerplay</b> has been enforced.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now. Ireland are cruising now. Stirling was brilliant and deserved a century, but got out trying to push one into the off-side. He was given good company by Joyce, who has motored to 76 off just 59 balls. Niall O'Brien has given him great support. Ireland are the favourites to win this now. Can the West Indies pull things back? Let's find out.]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to N O'Brien, 2 runs, <b>dropped!</b> Another tossed up delivery on off, O'Brien goes for the lofted drive inside-out over cover, but doesn't get the proper elevation, Holder at cover jumps in the air and gets a hand on it, but can't hold onto it. The batsmen take a couple as the ball dribbles away to the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, 1 run, opens the face of the bat and pushes it to point for another single]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, <b>FOUR</b>, great shot from Joyce, it was slowish and around off, Joyce just lofts it inside-out over cover with ease, the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to N O'Brien, 1 run, floated up outside off, O'Brien drives it to sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to N O'Brien, no run, flatter and on the stumps, O'Brien punches it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, 1 run, flighted delivery just around off, Joyce bunts it through cover for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Gayle [7.0-0-32-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ireland now need <b>81 off 96 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to N O'Brien, <b>FOUR</b>, the extra ball costs West Indies four, it was slightly shortish and outside off, O'Brien opens the face and cuts it late past backward point, the fielder at third man had no chance of cutting that off before the ball reached the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to N O'Brien, <b>wide</b>, bowls a bouncer that is way too high, the umpire calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Ed Joyce, 1 run, Russell is targetting the pads again, it was shortish on leg, Joyce helps it towards fine leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to N O'Brien, 1 run, gets back inside the crease and punches this short of a good length delivery to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to N O'Brien, <b>FOUR</b>, this time he connects with what he was trying to do with the previous ball and gets four for that, it was short again and at the pads, O'Brien helps it to the fine leg fence, the fielder at fine leg was fine and the ball went square of him]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to N O'Brien, no run, back of a length delivery on leg, O'Brien lifts his front leg and looks to help it into the on-side, but can't make a proper connection, wears it on his pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to N O'Brien, no run, bowls a bumper at the batsman, O'Brien was looking to pull, but pulls out at the last moment. Russell is cramping here and he looked in some discomfort there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell [4.0-0-20-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Simmons to N O'Brien, 1 run, another wayward delivery outside off, O'Brien hits it to deep extra cover for single and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Simmons to Ed Joyce, 1 run, angles this one slightly wide outside off, Joyce cuts it to deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Simmons to Ed Joyce, <b>FOUR</b>, short again and at the batsman, Joyce pulls it along the ground to the deep square leg fence, he rolled his wrists to send it along the ground, runs are flowing here from the Irish bats]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Simmons to N O'Brien, 1 run, another poor delivery, short and wide, O'Brien flat-bats it uppishly to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Simmons to N O'Brien, <b>FOUR</b>, great shot from O'Brien, it was a shortish delivery outside off, O'Brien flat-bats it wide of long-on and the ball beats the dive from Samuels to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Simmons to Ed Joyce, 1 run, widish delivery outside off, Joyce reaches out for it and cuts it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Lendl Simmons, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Simmons will chance his arm now]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to N O'Brien, no run, straight roller around off, O'Brien pushes it gently into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to N O'Brien, no run, tries to guide this shortish delivery down to third man, but can't make a connection. He is livid with himself after missing out on that]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to N O'Brien, 2 runs, <b>200-up</b> for Ireland with this couple, it was a flighted delivery just outside off, O'Brien lofts it inside out over cover, the sweeper can't prevent the batsmen from taking the couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ed Joyce, 1 run, pushed through around off, Joyce pushes it to point and sets off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ed Joyce, 2 runs, tossed up outside off, Joyce drives it to deep extra cover for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ed Joyce, <b>FOUR</b>, drags his length back and Joyce rocks back, muscles the pull to the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, 1 run, flighted delivery just outside off, Joyce drives it in front of square on the off-side, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to N O'Brien, 1 run, floated up around off, O'Brien pushes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, 1 run, bunts this one square of the wicket and was looking for the second run, but the fielder in the deep was quick to get across and prevents the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to N O'Brien, 1 run, tossed up around off, O'Brien drives it to sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to N O'Brien, no run, touch quicker and just outside off, O'Brien chops it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to N O'Brien, 2 runs, floated up outside off, O'Brien drives it towards deep extra cover and the batsmen take two before the sweeper runs to his left to collect the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Gayle [6.0-0-26-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ireland need 119 in 120 balls. The game is just going to get more interesting from here. Can Ireland do it? Let's see]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to N O'Brien, 1 run, tossed up just outside off, O'Brien drops it in front of cover and sets off, the fielder swoops in and fires in the throw at the non-striker's end, but the batsman made his ground in time]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to N O'Brien, no run, gives this one more air around off, O'Brien looks to push at it off the front foot, gets an inside edge onto the pad, luckily for the bastman, he didn't drag it back onto the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to N O'Brien, <b>FOUR</b>, shortish outside off, O'Brien goes for the big slash and gets an outside edge that flies past the slip and runs away to the third man fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to N O'Brien, no run, flighted delivery on off, O'Brien lunges forward in defence]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ed Joyce, 1 run, pushed through on middle and leg, Joyce works it past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ed Joyce, no run, floated up just outside off, Joyce drives it to point after opening the face of the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Ed Joyce, 1 run, another one that's short and angling going down leg, Joyce pulls it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to N O'Brien, 1 run, short delivery from Holder and at the batsman, O'Brien manages to fend it towards square leg and charges to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Ed Joyce, 1 run, in the channel outside off, Joyce opens the face of the bat and dabs it towards the squrarish third man region]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Ed Joyce, no run, just short of a good length and straightens outside off, Joyce was pushing at it and the ball goes past the outside edge, Joyce looks at the pitch after that ball went through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Ed Joyce, no run, angles this around off from round the wicket, Joyce punches it back towards the bowler off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Ed Joyce, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Joyce pushes at it off the front foot, gets an inside edge onto the pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to N O'Brien, no run, slowish and shortish outside off, O'Brien was looking to cut, but can't connect as the ball bounces a touch extra and beats the blade]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Niall O'Brien, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Stirling, <b>out</b> Caught by Ramdin!! A great innings comes to an end. Stirling perishes in the nineties. It was the slider that went on with the angle outside off, Stirling was looking to push at it, but can only manage an outside edge. Ramdin snaffles it and celebrates his happiness. West Indies needed that wicket to stay in the game. That also ends a brilliant 106-run stand. <b>Stirling c Ramdin b Samuels 92(84) [4s-9 6s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Samuels to Stirling, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Stirling, no run, on the pads, Stirling fails to glance it fine and wears it on the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ed Joyce, 1 run, eases this one through the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ed Joyce, <b>FOUR</b>, Joyce gets to his <b>10th ODI fifty</b> in style, it was short and wide outside off, Joyce stays back and cuts it past a diving backward point and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Stirling, 1 run, shortish and outside off, Stirling cuts it square of the wicket and gets off strike]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Ed Joyce, no run, fullish just around off, Joyce drives it to cover off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Ed Joyce, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Joyce pushes it back to the bowler after jumping in the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Ed Joyce, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>dropped!</b> It was a very tough chance though. It was short and at the bastman, Joyce lifts his front leg and helps it towards fine leg, where the fielder was running to his right and gets a hand on it, but couldn't help parrying the ball to the fence. This boundary also brings up the <b>100-run partnership</b> between these two]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Ed Joyce, no run, slower one on off, Joyce defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[Comes from round the wicket now]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Stirling, 1 run, in the channel outside off, Stirling stays back, opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Stirling, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Stirling drops it in front of point and looks for the single, but the batsmen decide against it after seeing the fielder charge towards the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jason Holder [5.0-1-16-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Holder comes onto bowl now. This is the <b>5th bowling change</b> in as many overs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Stirling, 1 run, flighted delivery on middle and leg, Stirling bunts it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Stirling, no run, goes down on one knee and looks to sweep this flighted delivery on off, but fails to connect properly, gets it off the glove and onto the pad, there was an appeal, but that can never be given out]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Stirling, no run, slows this one around off, Stirling pushes it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ed Joyce, 1 run, shortish outside off, Joyce cuts it square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Stirling, 1 run, quicker and flatter on the stumps, Stirling punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Samuels to Ed Joyce, 1 run, drags this one short, Joyce pulls it to long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[He will bowl from round the wicket first up]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Marlon Samuels, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[West Indies can't find the right bowling combination right now. Samuels now comes into the attack.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Stirling is probably having cramps and is currently down on the ground as the physio treats him. Ireland have been on the charge, they have scored <b>56 runs in the last 5 overs</b>, out of which <b>43 came in the last 3</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Stirling, <b>FOUR</b>, back-to-back boundaries for Stirling, Stirling pulls this short delivery to the deep backward square leg fence, he was in some discomfort after playing that shot, <b>18 runs</b> came off that over, great batting from Ireland]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Stirling, <b>FOUR</b>, another boundary for Stirling, Taylor bowls this one very straight, Stirling clips it behind square and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Stirling, <b>SIX</b>, super six from Stirling, it was slower, short and outside off, Stirling drags the pull to the deep mid-wicket fence, someone in the crowd tried to catch that with one hand, but drops it and is hit on the chest. That might hurt a little]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Stirling, <b>FOUR</b>, another great shot from the Irish opener, it was on a good length and around off, Stirling slogs it to the deep mid-wicket fence, one bounce and over the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Stirling, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Stirling opens the face of the bat and pushes it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Stirling, no run, angling in on middle and leg, Stirling stays back and shouts 'no' after bunting it to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jerome Taylor [2.0-0-15-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Taylor finally gets the chance to have a bowl as he replaces Roach after a brief one over spell]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Ed Joyce, <b>FOUR</b>, shortish delivery angling away outside off, Joyce cuts it late and gets it very fine, the ball runs away to the third man fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Ed Joyce, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Joyce drops that in the off-side and was looking for the single, he is sent back by his partner]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Ed Joyce, <b>FOUR</b>, take that Sammy! It was short from Sammy and Joyce is quick to rock back, he pulls it hard to the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Ed Joyce, <b>FOUR</b>, fuller on off, Joyce comes on the front foot and dispatches the drive to the deep extra cover fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Stirling, 1 run, back of a length delivery on the pads, Stirling works it through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Stirling, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Stirling opens the face of the bat and guides it to short third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Darren Sammy [2.0-0-12-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Another bowling change as Taylor replaces Gayle in the attack. Hold on. <b>Sammy takes the ball</b> from Taylor and says that he wants to bowl. Taylor obliges and is happy to give him the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Ed Joyce, no run, angles this one across off, Joyce presses forward and drives it on the up to cover, <b>12 runs</b> came off that over]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Stirling, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Stirling waits for it, opens the face of the bat and steers it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Stirling, no run, angles this one on off and middle, Stirling stays back and defends it into the off-side, shouts a loud 'No' to let his partner know that the single was not on]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Stirling, <b>wide</b>, bowls a bumper that goes over the batsman's head, wided by the umpire but Roach didn't seem too happy with the decision]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Stirling, <b>FOUR</b>, banged in short and it sits up nicely for Stirling to latch onto it, he pulls it to the deep mid-wicket fence with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Stirling, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Stirling pushes it into the off-side from the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Stirling, <b>SIX</b>, <b>stand and deliver!</b> Stirling looks in great form. It was slightly shortish outside off, Stirling just swings down the line and muscles it over the long-on fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kemar Roach [3.0-0-26-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sammy has been replaced by Roach after 2 overs]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, no run, tossed up just outside off, Joyce drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, no run, pushed through outside off, Joyce stays back and dabs it towards short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Stirling, 1 run, drifting on the pads, Stirling works it through square leg, the fielder from mid-wicket gets around, but misfields, but no harm done as the batsmen don't go through with the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, 1 run, flighted delivery outside off, Joyce leans forward and drills the drive square of the wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Stirling, 1 run, quicker one outside off, Stirling stays back, opens the face of the bat and punches it to deep backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, 1 run, tossed up on middle and leg, Joyce eases it down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Stirling, no run, slightly shorter and outside off, Stirling cuts it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Stirling, no run, on a good length and around off, Stirling goes across and wrists it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Ed Joyce, 1 run, stays inside the crease and bunts it towards point, the batsmen take a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Stirling, 1 run, comes back over the wicket to the right hander, it was on a length and outside off, Stirling opens the face of the bat and guides it towards the third man region for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Ed Joyce, 1 run, slightly fuller and around off, Joyce drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Ed Joyce, <b>SIX</b>, Sammy comes round the wicket and bowls a slower delivery on a length and on off, Joyce comes on the front foot and launches it over the long-off fence for a maximum, great shot from Joyce]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, 1 run, floated on off, Joyce drives it to sweeper cover off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Stirling, 1 run, pushed through on middle stump line, Stirling punches it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, 1 run, drifiting on the pads, Joyce works it behind square for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, no run, bunts this flighted delivery into the off-side and looks for the single, but decide against it as the fielder at point was charging towards the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, no run, low full toss around off, Joyce drives it back to the bowler, who dives to his left and parries the ball towards the short mid-wicket fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Stirling, 1 run, slowish on the pads, Stirling clips it past mid-wicket for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Ed Joyce, no run, low full toss just outside off, Joyce drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Stirling, 1 run, fullish on off and middle, Stirling eases it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Ed Joyce, 1 run, on a length and angled across off, Joyce leans forward, opens the face of the bat and guides it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[The keeper is upto the stumps for the left-hander]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Ed Joyce, no run, just short of a good length and on leg, Joyce defends it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Stirling, 1 run, on the pads this time, Stirling works it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Stirling, no run, fullish delivery angling in on off, Stirling looks to drive, drags it into the on-side off the inside half of the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Darren Sammy, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Looks like Sammy is fine to come back and bowl. He will start off the proceedings after drinks]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the players to sip on some <b>drinks</b>. Ireland have started off superbly. Porterfield and Stirling came out with a positive mindset and kept up with the required run-rate, the latter also registered his fifty. It will be trouble for West Indies, if they allow the Irish to keep going in the same way.]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! Backs away to give himself some room, Gayle makes it easier for him by bowling it short, he cuts it to deep backward point, Bravo at sweeper had no chance of stopping that]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, no run, pushed to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Stirling, 1 run, well outside leg, Stirling goes on his knee and sweeps it to fine leg. That would have been a wide had he left it alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Stirling, no run, touch short and just outside off, Stirling cuts it straight to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Stirling, no run, leans forward and knocks it gently to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Stirling, 2 runs, Stirling brings up his <b>7th ODI fifty</b>, kneels down and paddles it to long leg for a couple]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Stirling, 1 run, superb yorker, right at the base of off-stump, Stirling manages to get his bat down and squeeze it off the outside edge to third man. Russell had his hands on his head]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Ed Joyce, 1 run, shortens the length just outside off, Joyce steers it with an angled bat to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Ed Joyce, no run, stays back and mistimes the punch back to the bowler, got it off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Ed Joyce, <b>SIX</b>, top shot! He let the last one go through to the keeper, but not this time. Joyce takes on the short delivery and pulls it over backward square. The West Indies fielders thought he found the fielder, but he had placed it to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Ed Joyce, no run, bumper on the stumps, Joyce gets his head out of the way, the umpire signals one for the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Stirling, 1 run, short on middle and leg, Stirling helps it on the way to fine leg with one leg in the air]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Stirling, 1 run, walks across his stumps and nurdles it to mid-wicket, evades the fielder there]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Stirling, <b>FOUR</b>, quicker and Gayle pays the price, it was short and outside off, Stirling uses the depth of the crease and cuts it through the off-side field, no one in the deep to save the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Stirling, no run, 81.2kph tossed up delivery on off, Stirling closes his bat face early, gets a soft leading edge to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, 1 run, floated up outside off, Joyce drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, no run, straighter one on middle, Joyce turns it gently to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Stirling, 1 run, shuffles across and nudges it wide of mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Stirling, 1 run, tickled away to fine leg, keeps the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Stirling, no run, full and on off, Stirling drives it straight down the ground, good stop by Russell in his followthrough]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Ed Joyce, 1 run, sloppy from Smith, short and outside off, Joyce guides it to backward point, he looks to throw the ball even before he collects it. The batsmen pinch a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Ed Joyce, no run, on a length just outside off, Joyce presses forward and knocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Stirling, 1 run, shortens the length on middle and leg, Stirling glances it down to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Stirling, no run, back of a length on off, Stirling stays back and pats it to point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, 2 runs, too straight, on middle stump line, Joyce leans forward and works it to deep mid-wicket for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, no run, flighted on off, Joyce defends it to cover after coming forward]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Ed Joyce, no run, slower and well wide of off, Joyce goes for the drive and is beaten, he could have left that alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ed Joyce, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Porterfield, <b>out</b> Caught by Ramdin!! The breakthrough comes from an unlikely resource. Gayle gets the crucial wicket of the Ireland skipper. Quicker and just outside off, Porterfield goes for the cut, gets a bottom-edge which is taken superbly by Ramdin, who stayed low to collect it. The umpire took his time before raising his finger. <b>Porterfield c Ramdin b Gayle 23(43) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Gayle to Porterfield, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Porterfield, no run, guides it off the back foot towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Stirling, 1 run, continues round the wicket for the right-hander as well, Stirling goes for the drive and gets a thickish inside edge to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Porterfield, no run, bumper just outside off, Porterfield sways back and lets it pass]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Porterfield, no run, lifter around off, Porterfield arches back and gets away from the line of the delivery]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Porterfield, no run, short delivery that gets big on him, Porterfield fends it awkwardly, the ball lobs up and falls in front of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Stirling, 1 run, nudged away in front of square for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Stirling, 2 runs, good length ball on middle and leg, Stirling tucks it behind square for a brace. Good running from the pair]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Porterfield, 1 run, <b>dropped!</b> It was a tough chance though. Fullish and on off, Porterfield drives it in the air straight down the ground, Russell sticks out his right hand in his followthrough, gets a fingertip and the ball goes to mid-off. He had very less time to react and did really well to take the pace off the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Porterfield, 1 run, slows it up than the previous deliveries, eased down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Porterfield, no run, pushed through on middle, Porterfield is hurried onto the back foot, blocks it to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Porterfield, no run, quicker and on the stumps, Porterfield pushes it to the left of Gayle]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Porterfield, no run, kneels down and toe-ends the sweep towards mid-wicket, he wanted the run and was halfway down the pitch before Stirling sends him back. The throw comes in at the keepers end, but Porterfield had made it back]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire called for a run-out check. Porterfield seemed to have made his ground, but umpire Oxenford wanted to be sure. Not Out is the call!]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Porterfield, no run, slider on off, Porterfield hangs back and defends it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Porterfield, no run, flighted outside off, Porterfield drives crisply towards cover, Russell makes a fine stop]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Gayle, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Stirling, no run, back of a length around off, Stirling knocks it towards backward point, no chance for single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Stirling, no run, acrobatic take from Ramdin, short and on leg-stump, Stirling pulls with his eyes closed, fails to make contact as the ball goes over his left shoulder, Ramdin dives to his left and gathers it with one hand]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Porterfield, 1 run, back of a length around off, Porterfield flays it square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Porterfield, no run, short of length on off, Porterfield pats it off the back foot to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Porterfield, 2 runs, fuller and slanted across off, Porterfield leans forward and drives it to deep extra cover, Simmons stops the ball using his boot. There was a chance for three, but the batsmen don't go for it]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Stirling, 1 run, back of a length just outside off, Stirling punches it to the left of cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Porterfield, no run, bangs it in short, Porterfield has to take evasive action, he does well to sway away from the line of the delivery]]></line><line><![CDATA[Goes round the wicket to Porterfield]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Porterfield, no run, short and outside off, Porterfield flashes a cut and finds backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Stirling, 1 run, short and rises steeply, Stirling fends it in front of point and Porterfield calls for a quick single. He did well to play it with soft hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Stirling, no run, goes back to the short stuff, Stirling sinks under it and lets it pass over him]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Stirling, <b>FOUR</b>, fabulous shot! It did not seem to be four when he hit it, but kept going away from the chasing fielder. On a length just outside off, Stirling pushes it between extra cover and mid-off, Holder runs behind it and comes second]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Stirling, no run, Stirling charges down the wicket after giving himself room, Taylor sees that and drags the length back, Stirling swings wildly and fails to make contact]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Porterfield, no run, back of a length and straightens, Porterfield looks to defend away from the body, is beaten all ends up]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Porterfield, no run, back of a length around off, Porterfield shuffles across, taps it in front of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Porterfield, <b>wide</b>, Holder is not happy with the decision, bouncer on the stumps, Porterfield decides against playing the pull, it was too high and the square leg ump calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Porterfield, no run, keeps it in the channel outside off, Porterfield lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Porterfield, no run, back of a length on off, Porterfield goes back and blocks solidly]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket now!]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Stirling, 1 run, shortish and outside off, Stirling cuts it uppishly to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Stirling, no run, fraction short and just outside off, Stirling goes for the cut, does not make contact]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Stirling, 1 run, short of length on off, Stirling punches it without much timing towards mid-off, hares across for a brisk single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Stirling, no run, Taylor peppers him with another bumper, this time Stirling decides to let it go, he sits down and allows the ball to sail past him]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Stirling, <b>SIX</b>, streaky! The umpire checked whether it carried the distance. The TV umpire confirms it did. Another sharp bouncer, Stirling is in no position to play the pull, he still goes through with it, the top-edge is found and the ball flies over fine leg for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Stirling, 2 runs, Taylor follows the short delivery with a low full toss, Stirling is up for it, he goes back in the crease and flicks it to deep mid-wicket for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[The physio is out just to have a check while the substitute brings another helmet. He is ready to go..]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Stirling, no run, pinged! Well directed short delivery, right at the batsman, Stirling goes for the pull, he misses and is struck on the side of the helmet. Fortunately, it is not serious. The helmet takes a dent and he has called for a replacement]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jerome Taylor to Porterfield, 1 run, starts from round the wicket, he also keeps it short and outside off, Porterfield glides it with an open bat face to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jerome Taylor, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Stirling, no run, short and outside off, Stirling cuts and picks out backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Stirling, no run, another solid back foot defence from Stirling, presents the straight bat while doing so]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Stirling, byes, <b>FOUR</b>, these are bonus runs for Ireland, lifter that jags away down leg, Stirling ducks under it, Ramdin dives to his left and the ball evades him]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Stirling, no run, back of a length on off, Stirling gets right behind the line and defends it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Stirling, no run, shortens the length on off, Stirling jams it onto the pads, the ball trickles towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Stirling, no run, back of a length close to off, Stirling taps it to the off-side, calls a loud "no" for the single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Porterfield, <b>FOUR</b>, superb shot! West Indies bowlers are not learning from their mistakes. They keep bowling short and Porterfield keeps feasting on them. He rocks back and pulls it in the air over square leg for a one bounce four]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Stirling, 1 run, shortens the length on off, Stirling pulls it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Porterfield, 1 run, back of a length on middle, Porterfield pulls it off the inside half to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Porterfield, no run, drops it short and provides the batsman room, Porterfield stands up and cracks it straight to cover, either side and he would have picked up four]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Stirling, 1 run, shortish and outside off, Stirling slashes it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Porterfield, 1 run, strays onto leg-stump, Porterfield glances it fine and Samuels does the tidying up near the rope]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Porterfield, 1 run, tucks the back of a length delivery to mid-wicket and retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Porterfield, no run, this line from round the wicket is causing some problems to Porterfield, he is beaten neck and crop as the short of length delivery holds its line and whizzes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Porterfield, no run, bit of extra bounce, Porterfield does not offer a shot, but the ball nips back in and hits him on the glove before dropping down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Porterfield, no run, shortens the length around off, Porterfield knocks it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Porterfield, no run, loud shout for caught behind, but umpire Oxenford says "not out". It was a good decision. Short and angled down leg, Porterfield moves across and fails to tickle it, the ball brushed the thigh pad on the way to Ramdin]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Porterfield, no run, immediately goes past the outside edge, on a length and straightens enough, Porterfield comes forward and is beaten on the forward defensive]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Holder changes to round the wicket!]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Stirling, no run, back of a length close to off, Stirling dabs it to backward point, shouts "no" for the run]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Stirling, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! Overpitched around off, Stirling is not fully forward but his hands reach the ball as he drives it to the right of mid-off. The ball scooted away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Stirling, no run, fraction short just outside off, Stirling hits it hard on the ground, backward point does well to leap and stop the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Stirling, 2 runs, again, short and the line is outside off this time, Stirling cuts it square of the wicket for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Stirling, <b>FOUR</b>, Roach bowls it short on middle and leg, Stirling helps himself to a boundary, transfers his weight onto the back foot and pulls it behind square. The ball hurried across to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Stirling, no run, short of length on off, Stirling shuffles across and tucks it to short fine, thought about the single but Porterfield sends him back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Porterfield, no run, again, the length is not full, Porterfield has enough time to hang back and knock it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Stirling, 1 run, dug in short and at the body, Stirling swivels and pulls it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Stirling, no run, back of a length on off, Stirling gets right behind the line and blocks it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Stirling, no run, good length ball around off, Stirling presses it to cover after coming forward]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Stirling, <b>FOUR</b>, bad delivery from Holder. Short and plenty of width on offer, Stirling frees his arms and cuts it behind point, no chance for third man to cut that off. That was hit really hard]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Stirling, no run, drifts one on the pads, Stirling fails to connect with the flick, is hit on the pads. Going down leg though]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Porterfield, no run, shortens the length around off, Porterfield bunts it in front of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Porterfield, <b>SIX</b>, nailed! Banged in mid-way down the pitch, Porterfield is quick to rock back and muscle the pull over backward square, it went flat and cleared the boundary easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Porterfield, no run, shortish and outside off, Porterfield toe-ends the cut, the ball goes on the bounce to Gayle at first slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Porterfield, 2 runs, <b>run-out chance goes begging!</b> The throws comes in at the wrong end. Porterfield called for two straightaway, but Stirling was not interested, he goes for it once he sees Porterfield halfway down the wicket. Smith throws it to the keeper instead of having a shy at the bowler's end. Porterfield goes for the drive, ball goes off the outside half between point and cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Porterfield, no run, back of a length around off, Porterfield punches it to cover, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Roach to Porterfield, no run, tucks the batsman for room, Porterfield hangs back and knocks it to the right of Roach]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kemar Roach, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Porterfield, 1 run, drags the length back, Porterfield goes on his toes and punches it through cover-point for a run. Good comeback from Holder after a wayward first delivery]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Stirling, 1 run, fullish and close to off, it held its line, Stirling stays rooted to the crease, pushes at it and the ball squirts off the outside edge to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Stirling, no run, shortish and outside off, Stirling lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Porterfield, 1 run, fuller and just outside off, Porterfield goes hard on the drive, mistimes it completely towards mid-off, scampers through for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Porterfield, no run, slanted across the left-hander, Porterfield has nothing to do with it, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Porterfield, no run, much better from the West Indies skipper, close to the off-stump from back of a length, Porterfield covers his sticks and lets it pass]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Holder to Porterfield, <b>5 wides</b>, poor, poor delivery. Ramdin had no chance of collecting that. Sprays it well wide of off, it ended up in front of first slip, Ramdin dived across in vain]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Porterfield and Stirling are at the crease. Porterfield is on strike. J Holder will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. Ireland had the match in their grasp before they let Simmons and Sammy take it away from them. However, they still have a chance to make a match of it. Porterfield on strike. Holder has two slips in place...]]></line><line><![CDATA[The momentum is with West Indies. It will be interesting to see Ireland's approach with the bat. Take a break and join us back in a while.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Simmons</b>: "It was a good innings, I feel good about myself. We needed that partnership, it didn't happen early on, but me and Sammy batted well and we put on a partnership. It's a good batting wicket, the slower ball hasn't been stopping and is sliding. It's a new role for me, batting lower down the order, normally I am an opening batsman, but I accept the challenge. We have better swing bowlers and hopefully they can utilise the pitch."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sammy was struggling with his back but he hit 89 valuable runs, before being dismissed. Simmons carried on and scored his second ODI hundred. Russell too played a handy cameo to push the West Indies score past 300. The Ireland spinners bowled 26 overs and conceded 109 runs, while the pacers leaked 194 runs. McBrine bowled very well for 10-1-26-0, but Dockrell was the pick of the bowlers with figures of 3/50.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, after opting to bowl, Ireland put immense pressure on the West Indies batsmen with disciplined bowling. Smith threw away a start and Gayle, despite getting his eye in, couldn't get going. He took 54 balls to hit a maximum. Ireland captain Porterfield employed spinners and they stemmed the run flow. West Indies lost their way in the middle, but Simmons and Sammy, after spending some time, played their shots to transfer the pressure back onto the Ireland bowlers. Once both were set, it was hard work for the bowlers as they scored boundaries at will.]]></line><line><![CDATA[From 87/5, West Indies have recovered well to post 304. When Dockrell removed Gayle, Samuels and Ramdin in a space of 8 balls, things weren't looking great for Holder and Co. but Simmons and Sammy combined very well to share a 154-run counter-attacking stand to swing the pendulum back in West Indies' favour.]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to A Russell, 2 runs, low full toss, swung away to long-on and they rush back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jason Holder, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Simmons, <b>out</b> Caught by Dockrell!! He's sliced it in the air and sweeper cover takes a good catch running forward. Full and wide outside off stump, Simmons goes hard at it, but the bat turns in his hand. End of a terrific innings from Simmons, he's helped West Indies post an excellent total. <b>Simmons c Dockrell b Sorensen 102(84) [4s-9 6s-5]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sorensen to Simmons, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>hundred number two in ODIs</b> for Simmons and he's pumped. He jumps in joy as he runs between the wickets. Takes the helmet off and raises his bat to acknowledge the applause from his mates and the crowd. Full toss on the leg stump, Simmons swings hard, gets it on the inside half of the bat, it goes through square leg and there is no one in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to A Russell, 1 run, full and wide outside off stump again, driven straight to extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Simmons, 1 run, full and outside off stump, driven along the ground to deep extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to A Russell, 1 run, Russell swings hard and gets an inside edge to short fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Max Sorensen [7.0-0-55-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to A Russell, 1 run, he's mistimed this, long-on approaches the ball but it drops short of him. Short of a length slower ball, Russell mistimes the pull in the air, long-on comes in to his right but couldn't get there in time]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to A Russell, <b>FOUR</b>, the <b>fifty partnership</b> comes up off just 25 balls. Slower delivery down the leg-side, with fine leg inside the ring, Russell slogs it very fine through backward square leg for four]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Simmons, 1 run, short from Mooney, Simmons pulls it to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to A Russell, 1 run, this short of length delivery hurried onto Russell, but he managed to pull it hard to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Simmons, 1 run, Simmons gets an inside edge onto pad and it rolls to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Simmons, <b>wide</b>, short delivery on the stumps, Simmons pulls and misses. The umpire doesn't like the height on that one]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Simmons, <b>SIX</b>, in the air and he's pulled this all the way. He's into the 90s now. Short slower ball, Simmons had to really hit it hard because of the lack of pace and he did well to get it over the wide long-on boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Kevin O'Brien had figures of 7-0-30-1, but now he has 9-0-71-1.]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to A Russell, <b>SIX</b>, it's gone all the way this time. He conceded 22 runs in his previous over and he's gone for 19 this time. Full and in the slot, Russell takes his front leg out of the way and muscles it way over deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to A Russell, <b>FOUR</b>, this is bad bowling from O'Brien. Short and wide outside off stump, can't bowl there with third man inside the ring, Russell rocks back and cuts very hard through backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, 1 run, Simmons pulls this hard, but straight to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, Simmons makes room, O'Brien bowls one full and outside off stump, Simmons slices hard and gets a thickish edge that goes fine to the third man boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, slower ball goes very short and wide outside off stump, Simmons waits and slices it uppishly to the left of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, no run, Simmons steps out and leaves this widish ball as he thought it would be called a wide. It went just inside the line]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kevin O'Brien [8.0-0-52-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Porterfield has a chat with O'Brien.]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to A Russell, no run, slower ball yorker, Russell digs it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Simmons, 1 run, advances and drives the slower ball to the left of the bowler, who makes a half-stop and deflects it towards extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Simmons, no run, slower delivery from Mooney, Simmons misses the flick and is hit on the pad, luckily for him, Mooney's angle from wide of the crease was taking it down the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ireland have reviewed for an LBW shout against Simmons. No problems with the no-ball, no inside edge as well. Impact is in line with leg stump, but the angle takes it past the leg-stump. Wickets missing says Hawk-Eye and the onfield call stays.]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Simmons, no run, Simmons shuffles in the crease but Mooney keeps him calm with a slower ball, tapped to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Simmons, <b>wide</b>, the bumper goes down the leg-side and Simmons lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to A Russell, 1 run, very full and on the off stump, driven down the ground to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to A Russell, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball! Good length and down the leg-side, Russell doesn't miss out and just helps it away along the ground to the fine leg boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[45.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Simmons, no run, full and outside off stump, driven to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Simmons, 2 runs, slower delivery on the off stump, Simmons flicks it to deep mid-wicket and returns for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Simmons, <b>SIX</b>, full toss and Simmons helps himself to a maximum. Simmons swings hard and he smashes it over backward square leg. Easy pickings for the batsman]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Simmons, no run, nice yorker on the off stump, Simmons jams it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Simmons, 2 runs, almost a yorker, dug out past the bowler for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to A Russell, 1 run, fuller length delivery on the leg stump, glanced to backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Max Sorensen [6.0-0-44-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to A Russell, 1 run, slower ball on the stumps, flicked to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Simmons, 1 run, full toss outside off stump, driven square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[What a time for Russell to come.]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Sammy, <b>out</b> Caught by Dockrell!! This time he's holed out in the deep. Sammy is out for his <b>highest ODI score</b>. Slower delivery from Mooney, Sammy tries to manufacture some pace and slog it hard, he also advanced a bit, but doesn't get the connection right. Deep mid-wicket runs forward and completes a good low catch. That ends a brilliant knock and a 154-run stand as well. <b>Sammy c Dockrell b J Mooney 89(67) [4s-9 6s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[J Mooney to Sammy, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Sammy, <b>SIX</b>, <b>dropped</b> and he's palmed it over the boundary! Mooney is livid with the fielder, he's very angry! Short delivery on the leg stump, Sammy pulls, Sorensen at deep square leg takes a few steps back, tries to reverse-cup the ball, but he fumbles it over for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Sammy, <b>FOUR</b>, there is that trademark Sammy whip! Only he can do it! Such strong wrists and somehow he generates so much power. Short of a length delivery on the leg stump, Sammy bends his knees, he was into an awkward position there as he had to fetch the whip, but he did well to smash it]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Sammy, <b>wide</b>, full and way past the leg stump, Sammy lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Sammy, 2 runs, short slower ball, pulled to deep square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>John Mooney [4.0-1-22-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, brilliant batting! Full and wide outside off stump, Simmons just opens the face of the bat at the last moment and splits backward point and short third man to perfection. That is a handy over for the West Indies, 22 runs came off it]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, 2 runs, oh! That has been driven hard, but the man at long-off does well to swiftly run to his left and make a sliding save]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, he's a class act, Lendl Simmons! Low full toss wide outside off stump, Simmons square-drives the ball and beats backward point. Already 16 runs have come off the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, <b>SIX</b>, slower ball and he's smashed that. He swung so hard at it, there was no pace on offer from the bowler, but he did well to send it all the way over deep mid-wicket with a pull]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, guided towards short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, <b>SIX</b>, gets to his <b>16th ODI fifty</b> in style! Ireland are feeling the pressure. Juicy full ball from O'Brien, Simmons doesn't try to over-hit the ball, just lofts it handsomely back over the bowler's head. He gets a good round of applause from the crowd for scoring a fifty]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Sammy, no run, slower through the air just outside off stump, Sammy defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Sammy, <b>FOUR</b>, full and in the slot this time, Sammy swings very hard, hits it flat back over the bowler's head and beats the two fielders in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Sammy, <b>wide</b>, Sammy shoulders arms as it goes leg-side, but it wasn't far away from the leg stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Simmons, 1 run, driven along the ground to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Simmons, no run, Simmons backs away but Stirling keeps him calm by firing one in]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Sammy, 1 run, very full outside off stump, drilled to long-off and that's the <b>200 up</b> for West Indies]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Simmons, 1 run, flatter ball from Stirling, helped to short fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Paul Stirling [5.0-0-25-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, 1 run, advances and slogs the slower ball to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, no run, low full toss wide outside off stump, Simmons guides and picks out the man at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[Simmons changes his bat.]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Sammy, 1 run, hit hard again, this time to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Sammy, <b>FOUR</b>, oh that's a fierce cut shot! He had to reach out for it as it was way outside off stump, Sammy lost his shape as he was on the move, but managed to hit it very hard and it rocketed past backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Sammy, <b>wide</b>, way outside off stump, easy call for the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, 1 run, slower ball way too short, Simmons waits and pulls it to wide long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, no run, slower delivery outside off stump, Simmons punches it towards extra-cover, where the captain makes a good diving save to his right]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kevin O'Brien [6.0-0-22-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mooney is getting some treatment on the sidelines. Looks like he's done his hamstring on the left leg.]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Sammy, no run, slower ball on the off stump, Sammy defends it to cover and yells out a loud 'no' to his partner]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Simmons, 1 run, slower delivery outside off stump, driven to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Simmons, no run, and again, too short as he is not able to steam in, Simmons pulls and picks out short fine leg to perfection. Simmons is livid with himself for missing out on a boundary ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, that's the <b>hundred partnership</b>! Short and wide outside off stump, the bowler is struggling in his approach to the stumps, hardly any gas on this ball and Simmons punches it nicely off the back foot through cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Sammy, 1 run, slower delivery on the off stump, Sammy gets an inside edge onto pad, the ball rolls towards gully, Sammy has to rush to the other end as Simmons calls for a quick single. Now Mooney is limping. Maybe he's struggling with cramps]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Sammy, <b>FOUR</b>, shot sir! Full and down the leg-side, Sammy helps it away on its way and there is no one at fine leg. Sammy is not comfortable at the crease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>John Mooney [3.0-1-12-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[West Indies have scored <b>43/0</b> in the 5-over batting powerplay. The physio comes out and attends to Sammy. He's having some trouble with his back. He's now ready to go!]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Simmons, no run, Simmons taps it back to the bowler, he was just outside his crease, the bowler fires a throw at the stumps and Simmons dives back into the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, deft touch! Good length delivery close to the off stump, Simmons allows the ball to come, opens the face of the bat at the last moment and sends it fine to the left of short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Simmons, <b>wide</b>, sprays this down the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Sammy, 1 run, this time Sammy pulls the short ball to the left of deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Sammy, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Sammy defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Sammy, <b>SIX</b>, take that! An authoritative shot from Sammy. Too short from Sorensen, Sammy rocks back and easily pulls it over the deep mid-wicket fence, a bloke in the stands tries to grab the ball with one hand but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[Oopsy! Between overs, Sammy was flexing his back.]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Sammy, no run, short of length delivery, defended]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Max Sorensen [5.0-0-32-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Sammy, 1 run, pushed away to short cover and he'll keep strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Sammy, <b>FOUR</b>, in the air but in the gap. Another slower ball from O'Brien, Sammy spotted it early, waited for the ball and cut it hard between backward point and third man. After four dot balls, Sammy is delighted to hit a boundary and he punches the air]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Sammy, no run, this short of length delivery just moves away after pitching and beats Sammy's attempted punch off the back foot. The ball bounced extra as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Sammy, no run, fullish and close to the off stump, another slower ball, Sammy keeps it out off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Sammy, no run, slower ball wide outside off stump, Sammy tries to cut hard but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Sammy, no run, slower delivery just outside off stump, Sammy defends off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now. West Indies were reeling at 87/5, but these two have combined well to share a brisk 76-run stand. The Ireland spinners troubled them early on, but as they spent more time in the middle, they played some free-flowing shots. Ireland would be desperate to break this stand. Otherwise, they could well be chasing over 250.]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, 1 run, gets across the stumps and tucks this to short mid-wicket. That's his <b>9th ODI fifty</b> and he gets a good applause from the crowd and his mates. A timely innings this from the former captain. He has to carry on though!]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, no run, flatter delivery outside off stump, Sammy shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, <b>FOUR</b>, gee! He just flicked that over the infield. He hardly hit that and it's easily run away to the boundary. Flatter delivery outside off stump, Sammy clears mid-wicket and picks up four more]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, <b>FOUR</b>, a low full toss and Sammy flicks that with a strong bottom hand grip, it goes all along the ground but it runs away to the backward square leg boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, 2 runs, Sammy gets across the stumps and Dockrell delivers one down the leg-side, he tries to help it away, but the ball takes the inside edge and rolls to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, no run, very full outside off stump, dug out towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, no run, gently nudges this to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, no run, good length delivery on the off stump, Simmons defends it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, <b>SIX</b>, a stylish upper-cut from Simmons. Short and wide outside off stump, asking to be hit and Simmons doesn't miss out. He had enough time to rock back and cut fiercely with an open face. The ball just cleared the boundary at third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, no run, blocked into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Sammy, 1 run, this length ball hurries onto Sammy, he manages to fend it at the last moment, the ball rolls just beside short leg, Simmons calls for a quick single and Sammy was late to take off, but manages to make his ground with a full length dive. The keeper had a shy at the bowler's end, but it hit Sammy. No harm done though]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Simmons, 1 run, slower delivery on the leg stump, Simmons tucks it to square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kevin O'Brien [4.0-0-9-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third man and fine leg are up in the circle.]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, no run, another sweep, this time from Sammy and it goes straight to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Simmons, 1 run, flighted delivery on the off stump, Simmons sweeps it along the ground, short fine leg dives to his right and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Simmons, no run, spinning away outside off stump, Simmons defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, 1 run, this time Sammy goes hard at the pull shot, but can only send it to the man at deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, <b>wide</b>, sprays it down the leg side]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a classy shot! Flighted delivery on the off stump, Sammy waits for the ball and lofts it inside-out over extra-cover. He poses for the camera after playing the shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, no run, flighted delivery on the off stump, Sammy defends]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>George Dockrell [8.0-0-32-3] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>batting powerplay</b>! Can these two push on from here?]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, too short from Stirling, Simmons' eyes lit up seeing the ball. He went deep in the crease and cuts it past a diving backward point, the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Simmons, no run, tossed up on middle stump line, Simmons wrists it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Simmons, no run, defends this flighted delivery off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Simmons, no run, shortish again, Simmons chops it towards point this time, couldn't get the timing right on this one]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Simmons, 2 runs, shortish and a little wide outside off, Simmons goes on the back foot and cuts it towards deep backward point, the batsmen take two before the sweeper tidies up after running to his left]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Simmons, 2 runs, drifting on the pads, Simmons works it behind square for a brace]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Paul Stirling [4.0-0-17-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Sammy, <b>FOUR</b>, this is not good bowling from Sorensen, he is bowling very short here. It was another short delivery at the batsman, Sammy pulls it to the deep mid-wicket fence with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Sammy, no run, slightly back of a length and outside off, Sammy punches it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Sammy, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Sammy pushes it into the off-side and was looking for the single, but is sent back by his partner]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Sammy, no run, on a good length and outside off, Sammy drives it on the up to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Simmons, 1 run, short delivery from Sorensen, Simmons stays back and pulls it behind square]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Sammy, 1 run, angling into the pads, Sammy works it past square leg and was looking for the second, but the fielder was quickly onto the ball and the batsmen can only take a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[McBrine finishes his spell. His figures: <b>10-1-26-0</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Simmons, no run, floated on off, Simmons defends after looking to back away initally]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Sammy, 1 run, quicker one from McBrine, Sammy punches it to sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Sammy, no run, pushed through on middle stump line, Sammy punches it to silly mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Simmons, 1 run, on the pads, Simmons works it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Simmons, no run, flatter just outside off, Simmons makes room and tries to cut, but ends up chopping it back down the track]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Sammy, 1 run, floated up around off, Sammy pushes it through the covers and gets to the other end]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Sammy, 1 run, slightly back of a length and outside off, Sammy punches it in front of cover and takes off, the fielder fires in a throw at the non-striker's end, but Sammy was well in]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Sammy, <b>SIX</b>, <b>mammoth six!</b> It was a shortish delivery outside off, Sammy stays back and muscles the pull over the long-on fence for another maximum, super shot that from Sammy, he almost flat-batted that]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Sammy, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Sammy defends after jumping in the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Simmons, 1 run, bit too straight this time, Simmons works it off his pads to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Sammy, 1 run, short delivery from Sorensen, Sammy pulls, but can't get the timing right. He gets it wide of mid-on and the batsmen can only take a single there]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Simmons, 1 run, <b>run-out miss!</b> It was just short of a good length delivery and outside off, Simmons pushes it in front of mid-off and sets off for a single, the fielder quickly runs forward, picks the ball and fires in the throw at the non-striker's end, a direct-hit would have meant curtains for Simmons]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Max Sorensen [3.0-0-16-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Simmons, 1 run, bowls this one closer to the off stump, Simmons opens the face of the bat and bunts it towards cover-point for an easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Sammy, 1 run, eases this flighted delivery down to long-off to get off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Sammy, no run, quicker one from McBrine, Sammy drills it towards cover, who dives to his right and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Sammy, 2 runs, pushed through outside off, Sammy goes deep in the crease and punches it past a diving cover, the sweeper tidies up and the batsmen take a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Sammy, no run, flatter on the stumps, Sammy punches it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Sammy, no run, flighted delivery on off, Sammy defends with his bat very close to the pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Simmons, no run, another quick delivery to end the over, Simmons was leaning forward to defend and the ball hurried onto him, the ball rolls away into the off-side off the face of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Simmons, no run, pushed through quicker on middle and leg, Simmons leans forward and defends it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Simmons, no run, flighted delivery just outside off, punched to the right of the bowler, who dives and makes a good stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, 1 run, flatter on top of off, Sammy hangs back and punches it towards long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Simmons, 1 run, shortish this time, Simmons pulls it past the non-striker and the ball dribbles away to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Simmons, no run, gives the charge, but wasn't upto the pitch of the ball, defended back on the track]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Simmons, 1 run, on middle stump line, Simmons eases it down to long-on and retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Simmons, no run, quicker one on the stumps, Simmons backs away and was cramped for room, just about manages to defend it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Simmons, no run, pushed through on the stumps, Simmons punches it to the right of the bowler, where the short mid-wicket fielder stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Simmons, no run, straight roller around off, Simmons leans forward and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Simmons, no run, drifting on the pads, Simmons clips it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[A catching straightish short mid-wicket is in place now]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Sammy, 1 run, flighted delivery around off, Sammy gently pushes it in front of cover and sets off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Simmons, no run, touch straighter now, Simmons works it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Simmons, no run, gives this one more air on middle, Simmons defends with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Simmons, no run, flatter on middle stump line, Simmons backs away and punches it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Simmons, no run, lunges forward in defence and dead-bats this slowish delivery on off]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, 1 run, hangs back to this quicker one and pushes it in front of cover for another run]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, no run, on the pads, Sammy fails to clip it through the on-side and is not happy with himself]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Simmons, no run, very full just outside off, Simmons drives it to cover off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Sammy, 1 run, flatter around off, Sammy hangs back and taps it towards point, gets to the other end with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Simmons, 1 run, tossed up just outside off, Simmons leans forward and was looking to drive, the ball squirts off the outside half of the bat and rolls away square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Simmons, no run, slightly quicker around off, Simmons opens the face of the bat and pushes it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Simmons, no run, floated up on off, Simmons comes on the front foot and defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Simmons, no run, on the pads, Simmons flicks it to backward square leg off his pads]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, no run, flighted delivery around off, Sammy bunts it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, no run, another quick one on the stumps, Sammy is hurried into the defensive push]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, no run, quicker one from Dockrell, Sammy was a little late to get his bat down to block, but manages to do so just in time]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, no run, pushed through outside off, Sammy looks to run it down to third man, but the slip fielder dives to his right and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, <b>SIX</b>, good use of the feet from Sammy as he lofts this one over the wide long-off fence for his first six]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, no run, slows this one just outside off, Sammy was in two minds whether to drive or block, he does the latter in an awkward fashion]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[We are ready to go back again]]></line><line><![CDATA[There is a little delay as Sammy is not happy with something. He has taken his pad off and is sitting on the ground. Not sure if the problem is with his foot or he wants a new pad. As it turns out, he wanted a new pair of boots and that's why he took off the pads.]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Sammy, 1 run, gives this one more air around off, Sammy presses forward and pushes it towards point off the outside half of the bat, the batsmen charge to the other end and Sammy will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Sammy, no run, tossed up on the stumps, Sammy drives it hard back at the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Sammy, no run, floated on middle stump line, Sammy leans forward and knocks it a little uppishly to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Simmons, 1 run, pushed through on middle stump line, Simmons eases it down to long-on and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Sammy, 1 run, works this one past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Sammy, no run, tossed up on off, Sammy bunts it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andy McBrine [5.0-1-12-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dockrell has picked <b>3 wickets in a space of 8 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Simmons, no run, floated on off, Simmons defends off the front foot, the ball rolls away off the inside half of the bat, had he missed, he was plumb in front]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Simmons, no run, quicker one on the stumps, Simmons was pushing at it, gets a thickish inside edge that rolls away into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Sammy, 3 runs, <b>almost another wicket!</b> It was tossed up outside off, Sammy comes forward and pushes at it, gets an outside edge that goes to the left of the fielder at slip, the ball runs away down towards third man and the batsmen take three, the slip fielder was probably a little late to react]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Darren Sammy, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Ramdin, <b>out</b> Lbw!! West Indies are struggling here as Ramdin goes now. There are no reviews left and the onfield decision can't be challenged. It was flighted on off, Ramdin goes down on one knee and looks to sweep, he fails to lay bat onto it and the ball goes straight and hits Ramdin on the back thigh. It was in line with the stumps and the umpire immediately raised his finger. Poor batting from the keeper-batsman. Dockrell picks his third wicket of the innings. <b>Ramdin lbw b Dockrell 1(6)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dockrell to Ramdin, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place now]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Simmons, 1 run, quicker one on middle stump line, Simmons goes across slightly and works it wide of mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Simmons, no run, flighted delivery on off, Simmons defends off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Ramdin, no run, floated up around off, Ramdin leans forward and pushes it gently into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Ramdin, no run, on middle and leg this time, Ramdin wrists it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Ramdin, no run, shortish outside off, Ramdin was looking to cut, but fails to connect and the keeper gloves it]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Simmons, 1 run, pushed through on off, Simmons pushes it in front of cover and sets off for a single, the batsmen take a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Ramdin, 1 run, flatter outside off, Ramdin goes back and cuts it square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Ramdin, no run, flighted delivery around off, Ramdin defends]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, goes down on one knee and slog sweeps it wide of long-on, the ball crashes into the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Simmons, 2 runs, drifting on the pads, Simmons clips it past a diving square leg and the batsmen come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Lendl Simmons, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Samuels, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Dockrell takes two wickets in the over. It was the quicker one on middle and leg, Samuels was looking to work it through the on-side, but fails to make a connection. He is hit on the knee-roll and the umpire gave it out after a prolonged appeal from the Irish. Hawk-Eye shows that it was crashing into leg and it was a good decision. <b>Samuels lbw b Dockrell 21(41) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dockrell to Samuels, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Samuels has been <b>given out lbw</b>. He has decided to review the decision. Dockrell's front foot is fine. It pitches in line and even if it's clipping leg, it will be given out. The height is not a problem. There's no inside edge on that and let's wait for the Hawk-Eye. The umpire is however taking a lot of time to check the edge. Hawk-Eye shows that it is hitting leg and the onfield decision is upheld. Samuels has to go.]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Samuels, no run, floated up outside off, Samuels drives it back to the bowler off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Denesh Ramdin, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Gayle, <b>out</b> Caught by K O'Brien!! The dangerous Gayle is gone. The Irish are delighted with this wicket. It was slightly shortish outside off, Gayle went back and across, looks to pull it out of the ground, got the elevation, but not the distance. Kevin O' Brien takes an easy catch running to his left from long-on. The big man goes. <b>Gayle c K O'Brien b Dockrell 36(65) [4s-3 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dockrell to Gayle, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Gayle, no run, flatter on the stumps, Gayle punches it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Samuels, no run, closes the bat face a little too early and gets a leading edge that rolls away into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Samuels, no run, tries to steer it down to third man, but finds backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Samuels, no run, floated up on off, Samuels drives uppishly past cover, the ball stopped on him and that's why it went uppishly]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Samuels, <b>SIX</b>, <b>Samuel goes downtown!</b> It was tossed up on off, Samuels dances down the track and lofts it straight down the ground for his first maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Gayle, 1 run, lines up for the big heave off a flighted delivery, but ends up mistiming it towards long-on, the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Gayle, no run, quicker one around off, Gayle goes back and punches it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Samuels, no run, shortish again and outside off, Samuels hangs back and cuts it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Gayle, 1 run, bowls this one slightly wide outside off, Gayle mistimes the cut towards the cover-point region]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Samuels, 1 run, slows this one on middle stump line, Samuels goes deep in the crease and punches it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Gayle, 1 run, pushed through on off and middle, Gayle eases it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Samuels, 1 run, flatter around off, Samuels hangs back, opens the face of the bat and taps it square of the wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Samuels, no run, flighted delivery on off, Samuels pushes it to the right of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for a <b>drinks</b> break! West Indies started off in a steady fashion. Smith and Gayle took their time, but the former threw it away after doing the hard work. Bravo was then run-out for a diamond duck. Since then, these two have done well to add 36 for the third wicket, but the Irish have kept on putting pressure on them. A lot depends upon the experienced duo and let's see how they go about their job after the drinks break.]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Samuels, 1 run, leans into the drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Samuels, no run, flighted delivery on off, Samuels drives it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Gayle, 1 run, pulls the length back on off, punched down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Samuels, 1 run, gets right to the pitch of the ball and drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Samuels, 2 runs, drops it short and provides the width, Samuels goes deep in the crease and cuts it square of the wicket, the fielder slides and saves a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Samuels, no run, slower and around off, Samuels pushes it to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Gayle, no run, tossed up just outside off, Gayle drives it towards cover, where the fielder makes a fine stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Gayle, no run, flatter and close to off, Gayle taps it off the back foot to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Gayle, no run, goes on his knee and sweeps it to square leg, picks out the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Gayle, no run, shortish and just outside off, Gayle mistimes the cut to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Gayle, <b>SIX</b>, this was always on the cards, left-arm spinner versus Gayle, it had to happen at some point. Floated up on off, Gayle gets underneath it and sends it sailing over the long-on fence for the first maximum of the game]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Gayle, 2 runs, tossed up on off, Gayle kneels down and sweeps it past square leg for a brace, the fielder in the ring dives but couldn't stop the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Gayle, 1 run, drifted in on middle and leg, clipped away to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Samuels, 1 run, steers it with an open bat face square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Samuels, no run, <b>stumping chance missed!</b> It was a tough one, but he should have done better. Samuels plays for the turn once again, the ball goes straight and beats the outside edge. Wilson does not gather the ball, Samuels was out of the crease, but got back in time]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Samuels, no run, Wilson shouted "catch", but falls well short. Floated up outside off, Samuels drives it in the air, the ball lands just in front of the cover fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Gayle, 1 run, flatter and on off, Gayle punches it right between the bowler and short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stirling to Gayle, no run, tossed up on off, Gayle presses forward and dead-bats it to the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Paul Stirling, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Samuels, no run, quicker and on the stumps, Samuels bunts it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Samuels, no run, arm-ball around off, Samuels looks to drive, gets a thickish inside edge to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Samuels, no run, goes on with the angle from round the wicket, Samuels works it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Gayle, 1 run, touch short and just outside off, Gayle slaps it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Gayle, no run, straight roller outside off, Gayle covers his sticks and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dockrell to Gayle, no run, fires in full and on off, Gayle digs it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>George Dockrell, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Samuels, no run, drags the length back on off, Samuels knocks it off the back foot to McBrine]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, 1 run, floated up around off, Gayle drives it along the floor to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, no run, floated up around off, Gayle drives it to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, no run, flighted on off, Gayle push-drives it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, no run, Gayle defends with the bat and pad together to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, no run, quicker and almost in the blockhole, Gayle squeezes it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Gayle, 1 run, too straight from O'Brien, Gayle gets inside the line and glances it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Gayle, no run, back of a length on off, Gayle shuffles across and tucks it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Gayle, no run, pitched up outside off, Gayle plays a crisp drive towards cover, where Dockrell makes a fine save]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Gayle, no run, fullish and on off, Gayle knocks it down the wicket, O'Brien shows off his football skills as he back flicks it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Gayle, no run, fuller and outside off, Gayle does not bother with it]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Gayle, no run, O'Brien continues from round the wicket to Gayle, angles it in on off, Gayle presses it to cover after coming forward]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Samuels, no run, flighted on off, Samuels push-drives it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, 1 run, good call from Gayle, he drops it in front of cover, looks at Samuels, who reciprocates well]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Samuels, 1 run, flighted on off and middle, Samuels drives it along the ground to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Samuels, no run, pushed through on off, Samuels camps on the back foot and blocks it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Samuels, no run, takes a step out of the crease and drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Samuels, no run, tossed up on off, Samuels wrists it towards mid-wicket, where Porterfield intercepts with a dive]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Samuels, 1 run, fuller and around off, Samuels eases it down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Samuels, no run, good length ball around off, Samuels bunts it off the back foot to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Samuels, <b>FOUR</b>, stand-and-deliver from Samuels, it was the slower one from O'Brien, Samuels wanted to go to the left of mid-off, but the ball goes off the inside part to the right of mid-off. Anyway he got the desired result]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Samuels, no run, on a length just outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Samuels, no run, back of a length close to off, Samuels sits on the back foot and knocks it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Samuels, no run, good length ball on off, Samuels prefers to stay back and taps it to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, no run, tad short and Gayle goes for the cut, it was too close to him and under-edges it to the keeper. The ball hits Wilson on the right jaw, but nothing serious. He was not wearing a helmet as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, no run, flatter and around off, Gayle punches it towards cover, Porterfield dives and parries it to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, no run, tossed up from round the wicket, Gayle pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Samuels, 1 run, slower and spinning in, Samuels hangs back and works it wide of mid-wicket, nice early call for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Samuels, no run, turned away with the turn to backward square]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Samuels, no run, was there an edge? No, it missed the bat. The straight roller around off, Samuels plays for the turn and is beaten comprehensively, the keeper fails to gather the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Gayle, no run, short of length just outside off, this might have held up on the pitch, Gayle checks his back foot defence and the ball rolls to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[O'Brien switches to round the sticks!]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Samuels, 1 run, back of a length around off, Samuels steers it with an open bat face to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Samuels, no run, fuller and holds its line, Samuels goes for the drive with laden feet, the inside edge goes to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Samuels, no run, again, the length is tad short, Samuels shuffles across and knocks it towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Samuels, no run, short of length around off, Samuels goes back and across, defends it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Samuels, no run, good length ball on the off stump, defended]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, no run, flighted around off, Gayle dead-bats it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, <b>FOUR</b>, fraction short and Gayle pounces on it, it was outside off as well, Gayle flashes a cut through cover-point. The power on that takes it to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, no run, flighted on off, Gayle bunts it to the right of the bowler, who dives to his right and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, no run, presses forward and defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, no run, once again goes for the drive, it is slower this time and gets a thickish inside edge to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, <b>FOUR</b>, cracking shot! Floated up outside off, Gayle gets a good stride forward and creams it through the packed off-side field, the timing takes the ball to the deep extra cover fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Marlon Samuels, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Gayle, <b>out</b> Darren Bravo Run Out!! Diamond duck for Bravo! What a way to start your World Cup campaign! Shortens the length around off, Gayle is opened up as he looks to defend, he gets a leading edge to the left of backward point, Gayle wanted the single and sets off immediately, Bravo was not interested and was late in responding, McBrine takes aim and hits the bulls-eye at the striker's end. Bravo was nowhere in the picture. <b>Darren Bravo run out (Andy McBrine) 0(0)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[K O'Brien to Gayle, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Gayle, <b>wide</b>, looks to test Gayle with a bouncer, it is too high and wided by the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Gayle, no run, slanted across and shapes away further, Gayle lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Gayle, no run, tight line around off, Gayle stays back and knocks it in front of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Darren Bravo, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Dwayne Smith, <b>out</b> Caught by J Mooney!! The bowling change has worked. And the ploy to keep mid-on back was a masterstroke from Porterfield. O'Brien is delighted. It was fuller and just outside off, Smith wanted to go over mid-off, the bat turns in his hands, gets it off the inside part and it balloons to long-on, Mooney runs forward and hangs onto a good catch. <b>Dwayne Smith c J Mooney b K O'Brien 18(24) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[K O'Brien to Dwayne Smith, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Dwayne Smith, no run, short of length on off, Smith shuffles across and bunts it to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Dwayne Smith, no run, back of a length around off, Smith goes back and across, defends off the inside part to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;K O'Brien to Dwayne Smith, <b>wide</b>, very poor delivery to start off with, short and way down leg, easy call for the ump]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kevin O'Brien, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, no run, <b>second maiden</b> of the innings. Goes on with the arm, Gayle comes forward and turns it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, no run, floated up close to off, Gayle leans forward and knocks it down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, no run, slower and draws Gayle forward, pushed to the right of the bowler, who dives and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, no run, flighted around off, Gayle presses forward and defends it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, no run, sliding onto the pads, Gayle glances it to the man at leg slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and deepish leg slip in place..]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Andy McBrine to Gayle, no run, McBrine starts from round the wicket, tosses it up on off, Gayle eases it to mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andy McBrine, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Gayle, 1 run, full on middle and leg, Gayle works it wide of mid-on and keeps the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, full and slanting into the pads, clipped away to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, clean strike! This was on a length and just outside off, Smith goes through the line, lofts it off the inner half, clears mid-on comfortably and picks up his third boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Dwayne Smith, no run, no room provided, Smith gets half-forward and blocks it to the right of Sorensen]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Dwayne Smith, 2 runs, too straight, on middle stump line, Smith tucks it behind square leg for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Dwayne Smith, no run, shortens the length around off, Smith gets right behind the line and defends to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, fuller and outside off, Smith reaches for that and plays it away from the body, the cover fielder dives to his left and saves a run for the team]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Dwayne Smith, no run, back of a length outside off, Smith bunts it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Dwayne Smith, no run, slants it on middle and leg, Smith stays in the crease and tries to tuck it to the on-side, misses and is rapped on the pads. The ball was heading down leg though]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, Mooney provides a bit of width and Smith cashes in. He reaches out for it and slaps it through cover, the timing on that takes it to the fence quite easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Dwayne Smith, no run, pitched up on the fourth stump line, Smith presses forward and drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, how good is that bat? It was not a convincing shot, but still Smith gets four. Fuller and angling in, Smith looks to drive, the bat turns in his hands and the ball goes off the inside part wide of mid-on for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Gayle, 2 runs, on a length close to off, Gayle pushes hard at it, the ball takes the outer half and goes between point and cover for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Gayle, <b>FOUR</b>, that four should make him feel better, he was searching for that boundary for a few balls now. Finally, manages to get one. Fuller and just outside off, Gayle lifts it over mid-off, even though he didn't middle it, the ball had enough to reach the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Gayle, no run, gives the charge and ends up yorking himself, squeezed it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Gayle, no run, Sorensen goes a bit wide this time, Gayle is not interested in playing at that, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Gayle, no run, walks down the turf and pushes it to mid-off, that came right off the meat of the bat as the ball travelled quickly to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Gayle, no run, Sorensen attacks the stumps with a full delivery, Gayle gently turns it to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Gayle, 1 run, fuller and on off, Gayle eases it down to long-on and retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Gayle, no run, drags the length back on middle and leg, Gayle hangs back and taps it to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Gayle, no run, takes a couple of steps down the wicket, Mooney fires it onto leg-stump, fails to connect with the flick, the ball dribbles off the pads to short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Gayle, no run, angled across off, Gayle has a tentative poke at it, the ball beats the outside edge. Plenty of oohs and aahs from the Irish fielders]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, pitched up on off, Smith drives it off the inside part of the bat straight down the ground, the fielder from mid-on dives and stops the ball. The bat turned in his hands and hence foiling the timing]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Gayle, 1 run, strays onto Gayle's pads, he tucks it behind square for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Gayle, 1 run, fuller and on off, Gayle looks to defend with minimal footwork, gets an outside edge that runs down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, "catch it" was the shout from Sorensen, but the ball is well wide of the fielder. Full and holds its line around off, Smith goes hard at it, the ball squirts off the outside edge to the left of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Dwayne Smith, no run, this one hurries onto Smith, hint of inward movement, Smith misses the nudge through the on-side, wears it high on the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Dwayne Smith, no run, shortens the length and close to off, Smith trusts the bounce and lets it go, nice carry through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Gayle, leg byes, 1 run, first runs on the board for West Indies, it comes in the form of a leg bye, Sorensen drifts onto the pads, Gayle can't connect with the clip and the ball rolls off the pads square of the wicket on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sorensen to Gayle, no run, back of a length and slanted across the left-hander, Gayle lets it pass]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Max Sorensen, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Dwayne Smith, no run, good length ball outside off, Smith has nothing to do with it, lifts his bat and lets it go. A <b>maiden</b> to start off proceedings]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Dwayne Smith, no run, much better from Smith, on a length just outside off, Smith presses forward and shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Dwayne Smith, no run, pitched up and gets it to shape away, Smith looks to push at it away from the body, the movement beats the outside edge. Gayle has a word with his partner, calming his nerves]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Dwayne Smith, no run, the keeper and slip cordon go up for a caught behind appeal, but Mooney is not interested. It was full and outside off, Smith looks to drive, hits the turf and that was the noise. The Snicko confirms that]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Dwayne Smith, no run, once again delivers it from wide of the crease, hint of away movement as well, Smith covers it and knocks it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mooney to Dwayne Smith, no run, angling in from wide of the crease, Smith gets right behind the line and defends it to the right of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Smith and Gayle are at the crease. Dwayne Smith is on strike. J Mooney will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The teams line-up for the anthems. The Irish gather around in a huddle after the national anthems. The West Indies openers make their way out to the middle. Smith, playing his <b>100th ODI</b> will take strike. Here we go..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pitch Report:</b> "A beautiful part of the world. This is one of the better pitches I have seen for a long time. It's got grass on it, but it's an even covering. Speaking to the groundsmen and his team, they feel this will go through, there will be a little bit of bounce and little bit of pace as well. I don't see it turning. The ball will come onto the bat. A lot of runs to be scored on this wicket," reckons <b>Ian Botham</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>West Indies</b> (Playing XI): Chris Gayle, Dwayne Smith, Darren Bravo, Marlon Samuels, Denesh Ramdin(w), Lendl Simmons, Darren Sammy, Andre Russell, Jason Holder(c), Jerome Taylor, Kemar Roach]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ireland</b> (Playing XI): William Porterfield(c), Paul Stirling, Ed Joyce, Niall O'Brien, Andrew Balbirnie, Gary Wilson(w), Kevin O'Brien, John Mooney, Max Sorensen, George Dockrell, Andy McBrine]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Porterfield</b>: "We have a good blend in the squad. Few lads are playing their first World Cup, while few are playing their third. We will have a <b>bowl</b>. We have been here for a couple of days and it swung around a bit in the nets and we can utilize that upfront. I think you got to target every game, but every game is a two point game."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Holder</b>: "It is a great thrill to lead my country. It is a wonderful cricket stadium. I would have liked to bowl as well. Seems to have a bit of grass and having said that we have to bat and put some runs on the board. Benn is struggling this morning, we left him out. We brought in the extra seamer in Kemar Roach. Yeah not too worried about him (Gayle), backing him to give 100 percent today."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ireland have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Hello and welcome to the 5th game of the World Cup. All the previous 4 games saw teams scoring 300 and above batting first. Will the trend continue? We will find out soon. But before that, toss and teams will come your way in a little while from now. Stay tuned.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ireland</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ireland won the Dubai Triangular tournament prior to the warm-up games, a tournament that had Scotland and Afghanistan as the other two teams. However, in their first warm-up game, Scotland defeated Ireland by a mammoth margin of 179 runs, after the Scots posted 296 batting first. The Irish batting never got going and folded for just 117. In their second warm-up game, they were a different outfit altogether, winning by 4 wickets against Bangladesh. Mooney and Sorensen were superb with the ball on that occasion and were the chief architects of the win. They can surely defeat any team on their day.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Talking about Ireland, the team might not be expected to reach the quarter-finals, but they have the firepower to cause an upset. Led by William Porterfield, the Irish team consists of match-winners like Kevin O'Brien, who can take the game away from the opposition single-handedly. Apart from Kevin, his brother Niall can also pack a punch. Their all-rounders lower down the order can be very handy as well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>West Indies</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[West Indies last played in South Africa and lost the ODI series 4-1. They were beaten comprehensively. Looking back at their warm-ups, they were thumped by England, after they were bowled out for a paltry 122. In their second game against Scotland, they went onto score 313 batting first. However, they were lucky to win the game by 3 runs as Scotland lost 4 wickets in 7 runs to finish at 310/9. Their bowling doesn't look threatening and they might find it difficult against the big teams.]]></line><line><![CDATA[West Indies enter the tournament with two big names missing from their squad - Dwayne Bravo and Kieron Pollard. Both of them were important members of the squad before the World Cup squad was announced, but unfortunately a rift with the West Indies board meant they were ignored for this tournament. Apart from that, Sunil Narine pulled out of the World Cup squad, seeking more time to rectify his bowling action.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Let's take a look at the form and composition of both the teams.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Even though West Indies will enter the game as favorites, they will be wary of the Irish challenge, especially after their heroics against England in the 2011 World Cup. West Indies might have big names like Chris Gayle, Marlon Samuels and Kemar Roach in their squad, but if they don't fire, they will be in deep trouble.]]></line><line><![CDATA[South Africa, India and Pakistan are the three teams everyone expects in the quarter-finals of the World Cup. We could well get an idea of who would take the fourth quarters spot from Pool B today. West Indies usually would be the favorites to go through as the fourth team, but with Ireland and Zimbabwe playing well, it could well prove out to be a 3-way fight.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/><br/>Let's go back in time a bit. February 19, 2014 was the date for the West Indies-Ireland T20 encounter in Jamaica. The Caribbean team, winner at the T20 World Cup in 2012, failed to get going and was restricted to 116 for 8, after which the Irish fashioned a six-wicket win in the last over.<br/><br/>Cut to the 2015 World Cup, and both teams are ready again for Monday's Pool B encounter at Nelson. The chances of an Irish upset are greater than they were in Jamaica, even if it's a different format. What gives Ireland a lot of heart is West Indies' recent form. Jason Holder's men in the run-up to the tournament suffered a 4-1 ODI defeat to South Africa and then in both their warm-ups they gave a poor account of themselves. Against England, all they could manage was 122 and lost the match by nine wickets with 27.1 overs still to spare and against Scotland, they barely won: the victory margin of three runs despite scoring 313 for 9 spoke a great deal about how unconvincing their bowling was.<br/><br/>Ireland weren't much convincing either in their warm-ups. They lost to Scotland by 179 runs after getting bowled out for a lowly 117, but then they upset a Test-playing nation in Bangladesh as they chased down 190. If not their upset victory in 2014, the one against Bangladesh will surely give Ireland a lot of confidence.<br/><br/>Ireland's chances of reaching the quarter-finals are next to impossible but they know that they can upset the apple carts of a few teams. West Indies are one of the vulnerable Test-playing nations and Ireland know that too. However, Holder wasn't too worried."They are not to be under-estimated but having said that, we are very confident," he said on Sunday.<br/><br/>"Obviously you go through tough times in your cricket and you just move on and take whatever you can from it.<br/><br/>"We're starting a new campaign and I think it's important that we all put our minds on it and just go out and play some good cricket for West Indies. We'll start from ball one and go out and play some hard, aggressive cricket."<br/><br/>If you thought that was confidence, hear out Ireland captain William Porterfield. "I don't think it will be a surprise. We've played enough cricket now and everyone knows everyone. There are not many teams that won't know much about the 15 lads who are in our squad," he said.<br/><br/>Clearly, both teams are fancying themselves on the high-scoring pitch at Nelson, but looking at the 4-0 ODI head-to-head in West Indies' favour (including two World Cup wins), there are no prizes for guessing as to who is heading into the match as favourites.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>West Indies</b> (From): Dwayne Smith, Chris Gayle, Darren Bravo, Marlon Samuels, Lendl Simmons, Denesh Ramdin(w), Darren Sammy, Andre Russell, Jason Holder(c), Jerome Taylor, Kemar Roach, Nikita Miller, Sheldon Cottrell, Jonathan Carter, Sulieman Benn]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ireland</b> (From): William Porterfield(c), Paul Stirling, Ed Joyce, Gary Wilson(w), Niall O'Brien, Andrew Balbirnie, Kevin O'Brien, John Mooney, George Dockrell, Max Sorensen, Craig Young, Alex Cusack, Peter Chase, Stuart Thompson, Andy McBrine]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>304</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>7</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>50</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="West Indies">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Smith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>18</runs>
					<balls>24</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>K O'Brien</bowler>
					<bowlerId>690</bowlerId>
						<fielder>John Mooney</fielder>
						<fielderId>622</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>247</playerid>
					<name>Chris Gayle</name>
					<batsman-name>Gayle</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Gayle</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>36</runs>
					<balls>65</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Dockrell</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6329</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Kevin O'Brien</fielder>
						<fielderId>690</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1610</playerid>
					<name>Darren Bravo</name>
					<batsman-name>DM Bravo</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Darren Bravo</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Andy McBrine</fielder>
						<fielderId>9667</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>356</playerid>
					<name>Marlon Samuels</name>
					<batsman-name>Samuels</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Samuels</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>21</runs>
					<balls>41</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Dockrell</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6329</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>399</playerid>
					<name>Denesh Ramdin</name>
					<batsman-name>Ramdin</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ramdin</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Dockrell</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6329</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>599</playerid>
					<name>Lendl Simmons</name>
					<batsman-name>L Simmons</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Simmons</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>102</runs>
					<balls>84</balls>
					<fours>9</fours>
					<sixes>5</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Sorensen</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8250</bowlerId>
						<fielder>George Dockrell</fielder>
						<fielderId>6329</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>253</playerid>
					<name>Darren Sammy</name>
					<batsman-name>Sammy</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sammy</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>89</runs>
					<balls>67</balls>
					<fours>9</fours>
					<sixes>4</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>J Mooney</bowler>
					<bowlerId>622</bowlerId>
						<fielder>George Dockrell</fielder>
						<fielderId>6329</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7736</playerid>
					<name>Andre Russell</name>
					<batsman-name>A Russell</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>A Russell</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>27</runs>
					<balls>13</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8313</playerid>
					<name>Jason Holder</name>
					<batsman-name>J Holder</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>J Holder</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>379</playerid>
					<name>Jerome Taylor</name>
					<batsman-name>Jerome Taylor</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Jerome Taylor</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1359</playerid>
					<name>Kemar Roach</name>
					<batsman-name>Roach</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Roach</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>255</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>30</runs>
				<overs>7.3</overs>
				<batsman>Dwayne Smith</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1610</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>31</runs>
				<overs>8</overs>
				<batsman>Darren Bravo</batsman>
				<batsman-name>DM Bravo</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>247</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>78</runs>
				<overs>21.2</overs>
				<batsman>Chris Gayle</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Gayle</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>356</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>78</runs>
				<overs>21.4</overs>
				<batsman>Marlon Samuels</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Samuels</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>399</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>87</runs>
				<overs>23.3</overs>
				<batsman>Denesh Ramdin</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Ramdin</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>253</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>241</runs>
				<overs>44.4</overs>
				<batsman>Darren Sammy</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Sammy</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>599</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>302</runs>
				<overs>49.5</overs>
				<batsman>Lendl Simmons</batsman>
				<batsman-name>L Simmons</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>9</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>10</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Ireland">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>622</playerid>
					<name>John Mooney</name>
					<bowler-name>J Mooney</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>J Mooney</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>59</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8250</playerid>
					<name>Max Sorensen</name>
					<bowler-name>Sorensen</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sorensen</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>64</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9667</playerid>
					<name>Andy McBrine</name>
					<bowler-name>Andy McBrine</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Andy McBrine</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>26</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>690</playerid>
					<name>Kevin O'Brien</name>
					<bowler-name>K O'Brien</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>K O'Brien</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>71</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6329</playerid>
					<name>George Dockrell</name>
					<bowler-name>Dockrell</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dockrell</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>50</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1114</playerid>
					<name>Paul Stirling</name>
					<bowler-name>Stirling</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Stirling</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>6</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>33</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>625</playerid>
					<name>William Porterfield</name>
					<bowler-name>Porterfield</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Porterfield</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>540</playerid>
					<name>Ed Joyce</name>
					<bowler-name>Ed Joyce</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ed Joyce</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>691</playerid>
					<name>Niall O'Brien</name>
					<bowler-name>N O'Brien</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>N O'Brien</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6710</playerid>
					<name>Andrew Balbirnie</name>
					<bowler-name>Balbirnie</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Balbirnie</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>739</playerid>
					<name>Gary Wilson</name>
					<bowler-name>G Wilson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>G Wilson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>307</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>6</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>45.5</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Ireland">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>625</playerid>
					<name>William Porterfield</name>
					<batsman-name>Porterfield</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Porterfield</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>23</runs>
					<balls>43</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Gayle</bowler>
					<bowlerId>247</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Denesh Ramdin</fielder>
						<fielderId>399</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1114</playerid>
					<name>Paul Stirling</name>
					<batsman-name>Stirling</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Stirling</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>92</runs>
					<balls>84</balls>
					<fours>9</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Samuels</bowler>
					<bowlerId>356</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Denesh Ramdin</fielder>
						<fielderId>399</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>540</playerid>
					<name>Ed Joyce</name>
					<batsman-name>Ed Joyce</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ed Joyce</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>84</runs>
					<balls>67</balls>
					<fours>10</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Jerome Taylor</bowler>
					<bowlerId>379</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Darren Bravo</fielder>
						<fielderId>1610</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>691</playerid>
					<name>Niall O'Brien</name>
					<batsman-name>N O'Brien</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>N O'Brien</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>79</runs>
					<balls>60</balls>
					<fours>11</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6710</playerid>
					<name>Andrew Balbirnie</name>
					<batsman-name>Balbirnie</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Balbirnie</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Jerome Taylor</bowler>
					<bowlerId>379</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Darren Bravo</fielder>
						<fielderId>1610</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>739</playerid>
					<name>Gary Wilson</name>
					<batsman-name>G Wilson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>G Wilson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Jerome Taylor</bowler>
					<bowlerId>379</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Chris Gayle</fielder>
						<fielderId>247</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>690</playerid>
					<name>Kevin O'Brien</name>
					<batsman-name>K O'Brien</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>K O'Brien</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dwayne Smith</fielder>
						<fielderId>255</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Kemar Roach</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>1359</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>622</playerid>
					<name>John Mooney</name>
					<batsman-name>J Mooney</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>J Mooney</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8250</playerid>
					<name>Max Sorensen</name>
					<batsman-name>Sorensen</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sorensen</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6329</playerid>
					<name>George Dockrell</name>
					<batsman-name>Dockrell</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dockrell</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9667</playerid>
					<name>Andy McBrine</name>
					<batsman-name>Andy McBrine</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Andy McBrine</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>625</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>71</runs>
				<overs>13.3</overs>
				<batsman>William Porterfield</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Porterfield</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1114</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>177</runs>
				<overs>27.5</overs>
				<batsman>Paul Stirling</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Stirling</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>540</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>273</runs>
				<overs>39.2</overs>
				<batsman>Ed Joyce</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Ed Joyce</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6710</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>285</runs>
				<overs>41.3</overs>
				<batsman>Andrew Balbirnie</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Balbirnie</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>739</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>290</runs>
				<overs>43.5</overs>
				<batsman>Gary Wilson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>G Wilson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>690</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>291</runs>
				<overs>44.1</overs>
				<batsman>Kevin O'Brien</batsman>
				<batsman-name>K O'Brien</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>4</byes>
			<wides>9</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>13</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="West Indies">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8313</playerid>
					<name>Jason Holder</name>
					<bowler-name>J Holder</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>J Holder</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>44</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>6</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1359</playerid>
					<name>Kemar Roach</name>
					<bowler-name>Roach</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Roach</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>6</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>52</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>379</playerid>
					<name>Jerome Taylor</name>
					<bowler-name>Jerome Taylor</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Jerome Taylor</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8.5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>71</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7736</playerid>
					<name>Andre Russell</name>
					<bowler-name>A Russell</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>A Russell</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>6</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>33</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>247</playerid>
					<name>Chris Gayle</name>
					<bowler-name>Gayle</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Gayle</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>41</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>253</playerid>
					<name>Darren Sammy</name>
					<bowler-name>Sammy</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sammy</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>356</playerid>
					<name>Marlon Samuels</name>
					<bowler-name>Samuels</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Samuels</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>599</playerid>
					<name>Lendl Simmons</name>
					<bowler-name>L Simmons</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Simmons</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>12</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<bowler-name>Dwayne Smith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Smith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1610</playerid>
					<name>Darren Bravo</name>
					<bowler-name>DM Bravo</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Darren Bravo</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>399</playerid>
					<name>Denesh Ramdin</name>
					<bowler-name>Ramdin</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ramdin</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



