<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="12886" >
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>32nd Match, Pool A</gameDesc>
		<series>WC 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Australia</home>
		<away>Sri Lanka</away>
		<teamsabbr>AUS vs SL</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>AUS</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>SL</awayabbr>
		<homeId>4</homeId>
		<awayId>5</awayId>
		<venue>Sydney Cricket Ground, Sydney</venue>
		<startdate>08 03 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>08 03 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Australia</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Australia won by 64 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Australia</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>64</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Aleem Dar</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Ian Gould</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Richard Illingworth</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Jeff Crowe</Name>
			<Country>NZ</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>03:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150308112908</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>SL</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>Aus</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>312</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>10</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>46.2</batteamovers>
		<status>Australia won by 64 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>111</playerid>
			<name>Lasith Malinga</name>
			<batsman-name>Malinga</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Malinga</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>0</runs>
			<balls-faced>2</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
			<batsman>
				<name />
				<runs />
				<balls-faced />
				<fours />
				<sixes />
			</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>7710</playerid>
			<name>Mitchell Starc*</name>
			<bowler-name>M Starc</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Starc</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>8.2</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>29</runs>
			<wickets>2</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>7789</playerid>
			<name>James Faulkner</name>
			<bowler-name>Faulkner</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Faulkner</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>9</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>48</runs>
			<wickets>3</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>377</target>
		<extras>
			<byes>2</byes>
			<wides>4</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>5</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>11</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[2 . . 2 4 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 . W . . 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 W . 1 . . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 W ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_WC/AUS_SL_MAR08/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[That concludes a cracking contest. It's a big day for England tomorrow as they take on Bangladesh in a must-win game in Adelaide. Looking forward to your company then. Until then, take care. Goodbye!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@lukewright204</b>: Well played again @Gmaxi_32, on absolute fire. Brilliant to watch. And Sangakkara is just too good. He just keeps getting better.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@bhogleharsha</b>: Seemingly a devil-may-care person, you could see the emotion in @Gmaxi_32's eyes when he got the century. What a player!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@cricketaakash</b>: There's a Starc difference between Sri Lanka and Australia's bowling line-up]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@fwildecricket</b>: Mitchell Starc is arguably the best death bowler in the world and Australia's most important player.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@ProfDeano</b>: Well done @OfficialSLC ... You showed some courage tonight! Awesome knocks by @KumarSanga2 and @Gmaxi_32. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@mohanstatsman</b>: Finally a team (Sri Lanka) has managed to make 300+ total against Australia in a World Cup match. But in vain. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Twitter was abuzz the whole day as records kept on tumbling. Finally, it was Australia who walked away deserving winners. Here's how the folks reacted: ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Another interesting stat is that Sangakkara has now been involved in three 100+ stands in his last three ODIs. He put on an unbeaten 210-run stand with Tillakaratne Dilshan against Bangladesh. With Lahiru Thirimanne, he stitched a superb unbeaten partnership of 212 against England and a 130-run stand with Dilshan in this game. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sangakkara became the seventh batsman in the history of ODIs to compile three back-to-back ODI hundreds. He is also the first batsman to do that in World Cups. Mark Waugh came very close to performing that feat in the 1996 World Cup. Unfortunately for him, after scoring hundreds against India and Kenya, he remained 76 not out against Zimbabwe in Nagpur.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sangakkara and Tillakaratne Dilshan have now stitched 19 century partnerships. Only Sachin Tendulkar and Sourav Ganguly with 26 century stands have been involved in more hundred partnerships.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dinesh Chandimal's fifty that came in a mere 22 balls was the fastest half-century by a Sri Lankan in World Cups.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Kumar Sangakkara crossed the glittering landmark of 14,000 ODI runs. He is only the second player after Sachin Tendulkar to achieve that feat.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mahela Jayawardene now has made the most appearances by a Sri Lankan in ODIs. He has now played 446 ODIs. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Maxwell also broke the record for the fastest hundred by an Australian in ODIs. The previous record was held by James Faulkner, who had reached his hundred in just 57 balls against India in Bangalore in 2013. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Glenn Maxwell's sparkling maiden ton is now the second fastest hundred in World Cups. He reached his century in just 51 balls.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Australia's score of 376 for 9 turned out to be their highest ODI total against Sri Lanka. Their previous highest was 368 for 5 made at the SCG in 2006.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Several records tumbled during the course of the 688 run-fest between the two teams. Here's a collection of all the records: ]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Clarke</b>: "After the last wicket (asked at what point he thought Australia won the match). Credit to the guys for the way they batted. Firstly, Maxwell scoring his first ODI hundred for Australia. The last two innings have been outstanding and we obviously needed his runs once again today. And I thought the way the boys held their nerve with the ball at the end, they were really good under pressure and I think you need that going forward. Obviously, there are some more pressure games along the way and if we can hold our nerve like that, we give ourselves the best chance. Who knows (asked what is a safe total to defend nowadays)! It's unbelievable and I think watching a lot of players around the world score so freely and so quickly, teams can chase any score and you've got beautiful grounds. I think the curator, Tommy Parker, deserves a lot of credit for the way he produced a magnificent wicket and a wonderful outfield here today at the SCG. His (Starc) execution has been fantastic with both new ball and death bowling. I think the other guys around him supported him very well. So a really good performance. One let down was probably my dropped catch, so I've got some work to do tomorrow. I like winning. So, it doesn't matter if we are chasing or defending. I'll take batting first, making 375 and winning as the way to go throughout the rest of this tournament."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mathews</b>: "It was a bit too much (asked about conceding 376). We've got to be honest with ourselves. We conceded 200 runs in the last 16 overs and it was a bit too much or rather way too much. 340 would have been a really good chase. I thought the batters, it was a really good effort by the batters. Congrats to them, but unfortunately we couldn't hold on. He (Sangakkara) is in the form of his life. I think 3 hundreds in 3 games in absolutely brilliant. He's ageing and he's getting better and better. So hopefully he can continue for the next few games as well. Yeah of course we backed ourselves (asked when if he thought Sri Lanka could pull it off when his partnership with Chandimal was going along nicely) and we just have to go through with it. I thought they've got some really good bowlers and they were reversing it a little bit. We had to go for it and we had to take those chances, but unfortunately the wickets fell down. I've been telling this a few times, we've got to improve our bowling and fielding to be honest. If we can keep a good batting line-up to 300, we can chase it down."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Maxwell</b>: "Yeah exactly right (when Mark Taylor told him what a big stage to get your maiden ODI hundred)! It's a massive game for us. Obviously, if we are coming to New Zealand and I suppose playing in New Zealand, it's a big thing for us to win this game and now we have got Scotland to finish off (talking about the importance of winning this game). No, I knew the Australian one because James Faulkner has been talking about it non-stop (when asked if he knew about the fastest World Cup hundred). I knew that one. I was just happy to hit a couple of them in the middle and finally get that monkey off the back. Just shows the quality of the opposition and the quality of the wicket and you've got to have a lot of luck I suppose chasing a big total and to actually successfully chase it down. Luckily enough luck was with us on the night. We've got a few days off, I think we will go in different times to Hobart. So guys will be mentally refreshed, physically refreshed. So will be ready to go for the next game."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Glenn Maxwell</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his 53-ball 102.]]></line><line><![CDATA[On a flat deck and with a lightning fast outfield, most of the bowlers struggled. However, fans would have thoroughly enjoyed a riveting contest. Australia now look set to finish second in Group A and have qualified for the quarter-finals. They will face Scotland in their next game. On the other hand, Sri Lanka too will face Scotland in Hobart. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[It also turned out to be a game full of records and landmarks. Maxwell's ton was the second fastest hundred in World Cups. It was the fastest hundred scored by an Australian in ODIs and Maxwell's first in the abridged version of the game. Australia's total of 376 for 9 was their highest score against Sri Lanka in ODIs. Sangakkara became the first batsman in the history of World Cups to compile three back-to-back hundreds. Sangakkara reached the glittering landmark of 14,000 ODI runs and became the second player to do so after Sachin Tendulkar. This was also Mahela Jayawardene's 446th ODI  and with it, he is the most capped player for Sri Lanka.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Lest we forget that Michael Clarke and Steven Smith also played fine hands to help Australia recover after they lost the wickets of David Warner and Aaron Finch. Watson then gave Maxwell support and when Maxwell was dismissed, he took over and cracked a superb fifty. For Sri Lanka, Lasith Malinga showed his worth in the end overs. They perhaps missed the services of Rangana Herath. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, Glenn Maxwell took the meaning of swagger to a different level by playing shots in a 360-degree arc. He started his innings by lofting Dilshan for a six. Maxwell then proceeded to play a wide array of shots to leave the Sri Lankan attack clueless. On occasions, Maxwell has been troubled by leg-spinners and Mathews introduced Seekkuge into the attack. But Maxwell clubbed him across the line for a six and followed it up with a switch hit in the same over. When Prasanna came back into the attack, Maxwell smashed him for three more fours. He also thrashed Thisara Perera for 20 runs in one over.  Maxwell then went on to complete his hundred in a mere 51 balls and Australia reached a monstrous score.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Even after James Faulkner dismissed Dilshan for 62, Sangakkara threaded through the gaps at will to deal in boundaries. It was Faulkner, who yet again made an impact by snaring the important wicket of Sangakkara. However, Sri Lanka didn't give up as Dinesh Chandimal and Angelo Mathews continued to mercilessly clout the opposition. Xavier Doherty, the slow left-arm orthodox, was hammered for 19 runs in the 37th over of the innings. As the ball kept on ricocheting off the boundary boards, there were worried faces in the Australian camp. Chandimal even reached his fifty in just 22 balls, but he started to struggle with cramps and had to sadly retire hurt. Shane Watson took the crucial wicket of Mathews with a short delivery and that was the decisive blow which ended Sri Lanka's chances of chasing down the target. Faulkner deserves a lot of credit for the way he mixed it up and Mitchell Starc kept it tight. Watson and Johnson picked up crucial wickets. The pacers also used the short ball to good effect. However, the Australian camp perhaps won't be happy with the fact that they missed a few run outs.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Despite Kumar Sangakkara playing with fizz and sparkle and composing a brilliant ton, Australia held their nerve in a high scoring game to win the match. Sangakkara rose up to the occasion of facing a fine pace attack and smashed a flurry of shots to unnerve the opposition. Tillakaratne Dilshan also came out all guns blazing by landing hefty blows to thump Mitchell Johnson for six boundaries in one over.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Is Chandimal going to come out? The Australian players are having a look at the Sri Lankan dressing room. No! They are shaking hands and Chandimal will not bat again. Australia win by 64 runs. Lehmann is a happy man on the sidelines. The Sri Lankan players walk onto the field and shake hands. So it is most likely that Sri Lanka will play South Africa in their quarter-final.]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Senanayake, <b>out</b> Caught by Doherty!! Chipped in the air and Doherty swallows the ball at mid-off. Full and on the stumps, Senanayake falls over a bit as Starc follows him, ends up chipping it and it's a simple catch to the fielder. <b>Senanayake c Doherty b Starc 7(8) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to Senanayake, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Senanayake, <b>FOUR</b>, full and swinging away outside off stump, Senanayake throws his bat at it and gets a thick edge that flies to the right of first slip and it beats third man as well]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[45.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Malinga, no run, a wild swing from Malinga, he only manages to connect with thin air]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Malinga, no run, no pace on offer from Faulkner, Malinga swings hard and gets an inside edge onto pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Senanayake, 1 run, slower ball outside off stump, Senanayake drives it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Senanayake, no run, slower delivery pitching outside leg and hitting Senanayake on the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Tharanga, <b>out</b> Caught by Warner!! That's in the air and it's an easy catch for Warner. Slower ball banged in short, Tharanga makes room and pulls, hits it well and picks out deep mid-wicket to perfection. Warner just moved a few steps and took it easily. It's just a matter of time now for Australia to wrap this up. <b>Tharanga c Warner b Faulkner 4(5)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Faulkner to Tharanga, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Senanayake, 1 run, slower delivery outside off stump, Senanayake guides it down to short third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner [8.0-0-46-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Senanayake, 1 run, full and angling into the right-hander, Senanayake flicks it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Senanayake, no run, good length delivery just moving away outside off stump, Senanayake swings and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Senanayake, no run, great welcome to Senanayake! Bowls a sharp bumper, Senanayake does well to duck under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sachithra Senanayake, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to S Prasanna, <b>out</b> Bowled!! This was coming. You have to get behind the line when Starc is swinging it away from you from round the wicket. Instead, Prasanna goes leg-side and exposes all the sticks, Starc bowls that perfect yorker once again and hits the base of off stump. <b>S Prasanna b Starc 9(11) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to S Prasanna, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to S Prasanna, no run, yorker length and swinging away, Prasanna backs away and misses the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Tharanga, 1 run, full and swinging back in, Tharanga flicks it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc [7.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Swinging Starc is back.]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to S Prasanna, no run, slower ball on the off stump, Prasanna steps out and mistimes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to S Prasanna, <b>FOUR</b>, outside edge and it flies past the keeper. Good length delivery outside off stump, Prasanna slogs across the line and the thick edge goes fine to the third man boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to S Prasanna, 2 runs, slower ball on the stumps, Prasanna backs away and mistimes the slog to mid-on. <b>300 up for Sri Lanka</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to S Prasanna, no run, another short ball and another pull shot missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to S Prasanna, no run, slower ball bouncer, Prasanna pulls early and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to S Prasanna, 2 runs, short ball on the stumps, Prasanna plays the pull, but gets a top edge, Doherty dives to his right at fine leg and saves two]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to S Prasanna, 1 run, length ball, blocked uppishly to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to S Prasanna, no run, full and shaping away, Prasanna looks to drive and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to S Prasanna, <b>wide</b>, short delivery down the leg-side, Prasanna ducks under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[There is a man at slip now]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to S Prasanna, no run, full and swinging away outside off stump, Prasanna pokes and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Tharanga, 1 run, fullish and on the off stump, Tharanga defends it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Seekkuge Prasanna, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to T Perera, <b>out</b> Caught by Doherty!! "Ohhhhhh," says Perera as soon as he hits that and he knows he is in trouble. Johnson bowls a short slower ball around the leg stump line, Perera tries to pull, but doesn't pick the change of pace, goes through with the shot and mistimes it completely. In fact, he loses his bottom hand grip while playing the shot. Long-on comes forward and to his left and holds onto a good catch. Surely, it's advantage Australia now. <b>T Perera c Doherty b Johnson 8(3) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Johnson to T Perera, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Tharanga, 1 run, late shape back into the left-hander on this good length delivery, Tharanga defends it into the on-side and sets off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to T Perera, <b>FOUR</b>, no, Watto! Full and in the slot, can't bowl there to this man, Perera muscles it straight down the ground and it runs away to the boundary. 12 runs off the over, Sri Lanka are still in the hunt]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to T Perera, <b>FOUR</b>, Perera was cramped for room by this short ball, but he's managed to flat-bat it well enough and it clears mid-off easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[Back over the wicket now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Tharanga, 1 run, full and outside off stump, Tharanga drives it to sweeper-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Upul Tharanga, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Mathews, <b>out</b> Caught by Haddin!! Shane Watson is absolutely pumped. "Yessss, come on," says Watto as he pumps his fist. This is a body blow for Sri Lanka. Good surprise short ball from Watson, Mathews tries to hook but gets a thin edge through to the keeper. That Mathews-Chandimal stand was doing it for Sri Lanka, but suddenly, the injury to Chandimal has changed the complexion of the match. Credit to Clarke for continuing with Watson, despite him being very expensive. <b>Mathews c Haddin b Watson 35(31) [4s-2 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Watson to Mathews, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Mathews, 2 runs, bowls a yorker, Mathews flicks it wide of long-on and races back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mathews asks Chandimal to retire hurt and he's going off. Chandimal has <b>retired hurt</b> because he couldn't run. This is so unfortunate for Sri Lanka. Thisara Perera walks in.]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Chandimal, 1 run, round the wicket, low full toss, Chandimal flicks it to fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[This is unfortunate for Sri Lanka. Chandimal was batting so well and suddenly he's hardly able to move. This could make a difference]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Mathews, 2 runs, short of length delivery just outside off stump, Mathews pulls it wide of mid-on, Starc runs back and just manages to pull it back in time before touching the rope. Because Chandimal is struggling with his hamstring, Sri Lanka could not get three]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Chandimal, 1 run, short and on the stumps, Chandimal pulls it to deep backward square leg, Chandimal is clearly struggling]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Chandimal, 2 runs, short of a length delivery just outside off stump, Chandimal pulls and gets a fat top edge, Clarke, who was at square leg realises very late that it was his catch and the ball clears him quite easily. <b>13th ODI fifty</b> for Chandimal. Oops! he's not able to move freely, he is limping]]></line><line><![CDATA[Looks like Chandimal is suffering from cramps. The physio comes out to attend to him. Slight break in play. He takes a tablet. Something is wrong in his right hamstring. He's ready now!]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Chandimal, 2 runs, short ball on the leg stump, Chandimal pulls well, but the man at deep mid-wicket runs swiftly to his right and saves two]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Mathews, 1 run, full and just tailing back in, Mathews tries to drive, but gets a thick inside edge that goes to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Mathews, no run, slower ball angling away from the right-hander, Mathews swings and misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Sri Lanka have scored 64 runs in the last 5 overs. 105 in 60 balls is doable.]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Chandimal, <b>FOUR</b>, thank you very much Shane Watson! Low full toss outside off stump, no one in the deep on the off-side and Chandimal drives it the left of cover to end the over on a high]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Mathews, 1 run, low full toss and Mathews has managed to pick the fielder out to perfection. He should have done better with it, the ball went straight to Finch at deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Mathews, no run, slower ball just outside off stump, Mathews mistimes the slog into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Chandimal, 1 run, short of length delivery on the off stump, Chandimal works it wide of long-on, looks for two but doesn't get it]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Chandimal, <b>FOUR</b>, slower ball from Watto, Chandimal advances and swings hard, gets a thick edge that flies over the man at short third man. Watson is proving to be very expensive]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Mathews, 1 run, back of a length from Watson, Mathews mistimes it to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Coming back to the Sangakkara wicket. Just like how Malinga got away with a close no-ball call when he dismissed Clarke, Faulkner gets away with a tight call for a no-ball. The directive to the third umpire for this tournament is, if there is no conclusive evidence that a bowler has overstepped, the benefit of the doubt will go to the bowler.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Watson [4.0-0-40-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Chandimal, <b>FOUR</b>, slower ball and width on offer, Chandimal goes off-side a bit, he was cramped for room a touch but he manages to time the cut shot really well and sent it to the right of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Chandimal, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Chandimal plays a wild swing but only connects with thin air]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Chandimal, no run, short ball on the stumps, Chandimal goes off-side and tries to help it away on its way but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Chandimal, <b>wide</b>, that's a tough call from the umpire and Johnson is not happy. How is this a wide? It was well inside the line. Full and outside off stump, Chandimal looks to drive but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Chandimal, 2 runs, in the air and just wide of Starc at mid-on. Slower ball outside off stump, Chandimal doesn't pick the change of pace, goes into the wild swing, goes with one hand and chips it, luckily for him it went well wide of Starc, who was running to his right from mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Mathews, 1 run, full and on the leg stump, Mathews whips it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Mathews, <b>FOUR</b>, short of length delivery outside off stump, Mathews rocks back and cuts it fiercely to the deep backward point boundary. Not the ideal start to a new spell from Johnson]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Johnson [6.0-0-38-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, 1 run, dabbed to point and he'll keep strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Chandimal, 1 run, <b>biggg mix-up</b>, but all is well for Chandimal in the end. Slower delivery outside off stump, Chandimal pushes it to extra-cover, hesitates after taking off initially, the throw comes in from Clarke to the bowler's end, Faulkner thinks it would hit the stumps directly and lets it go, but on seeing the ball miss the stumps, he tries to run him about after grabbing the rebound but by then, Chandimal was well in]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, 1 run, slower delivery on the off stump, Mathews hops on one leg and guides it short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Chandimal, 1 run, slower ball outside off stump, driven to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, 1 run, a <b>direct-hit</b> would have been curtains for Mathews. Fullish and outside off stump, Mathews drives it to extra-cover and sets off, he gives up midway as Clarke picked up the ball very early and luckily for him, Clarke missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, <b>wide</b>, slower ball down the leg-side, Mathews tries to help it away but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, no run, driven straight to the man at cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner [7.0-0-40-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sri Lanka have scored <b>35 runs in the last 2 overs</b>. They need 134 more from 78 balls.]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Chandimal, <b>FOUR</b>, the Sri Lankan fans in the stands have gone berserk. Flighted delivery on the stumps, Chandimal gets down on one knee and slogs it over wide mid-on for a one bounce four]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Chandimal, <b>FOUR</b>, excellent placement again from Chandimal. Doherty follows Chandimal as he steps out and goes leg-side, Chandimal plays a lovely on-drive and mid-on was way too square to come into the picture]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Mathews, 1 run, driven down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Mathews, no run, full toss, flicked straight to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Mathews, <b>FOUR</b>, short and on the leg stump, Mathews rocks back and pulls powerfully over mid-wicket. Great start to the over for Sri Lanka]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Mathews, <b>SIX</b>, it's a top edge but it's gone the way! Flighted delivery just outside off stump, Mathews plays the sweep, the ball takes a thick edge, Warner jumps high near the boundary running to his right from deep square leg, but the ball just manages to evade him]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Chandimal, <b>FOUR</b>, what placement from Chandimal! Slower ball on the off stump, Chandimal gets across the stumps and flicks it behind square, Finch runs to his right from deep mid-wicket but the ball beats him. <b>16 runs came off the over</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Chandimal, no run, fullish and just tailing back in, Chandimal defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Chandimal, 2 runs, full and on the stumps, Chandimal looks to drive but gets a thick inside edge that rolls through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Chandimal, <b>SIX</b>, he's made great contact with that and it's gone all the way. Full and in the slot, Chandimal takes his front leg out of the way and slogs very well, gets it from the middle of the bat and flies over deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Chandimal, no run, good length delivery, defended straight back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Chandimal, <b>FOUR</b>, slower ball outside off stump, Chandimal lofts wide of the man at mid-off and picks up four. That wasn't convincing from Chandimal]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Watson [3.0-0-24-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Chandimal, 1 run, tossed up outside off stump, Chandimal drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Chandimal, <b>FOUR</b>, Chandimal gets down on one knee and slog-sweeps this flighted delivery past mid-wicket for four]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Chandimal, no run, flatter delivery on the off stump, Chandimal punches it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[By the way, Sri Lanka have managed to score <b>33/2</b> in the 5-over batting powerplay.]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Mathews, 1 run, turned away to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Mathews, no run, tossed up, defended towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Mathews, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, flicked to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Xavier Doherty [5.0-0-35-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, 1 run, looks to flick, thick leading edge rolls to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dinesh Chandimal, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Sangakkara, <b>out</b> Caught by Finch!! The slower ball does the trick. It's the batting powerplay again that helps the bowling side take wickets. Oh no! Is it a no-ball? It's a tough call. Looks like it's on the line, but the umpire reckons there was just something behind the line. It's a very tough call and a brave call by the third umpire. Looked like the heel landed on the line, but since there was no clear evidence, the benefit of the doubt went to the bowler. Slower delivery outside off stump, Sangakkara goes for the loft after coming down the track, but slices it, in fact the ball hit the toe-end of the bat, the man at deep cover rushes in and takes a good catch. End of a fantastic knock from Sanga! Australia have the upper hand now. <b>Sangakkara c Finch b Faulkner 104(107) [4s-11]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Faulkner to Sangakkara, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, 1 run, short of length delivery down the leg-side, Mathews glances it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, no run, full and outside off stump, Mathews drives but gets a thick edge that rolls along the ground to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, no run, slower ball on the stumps, Mathews flicks it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, no run, good length delivery just outside off stump, Mathews defends from the crease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, no run, brilliant yorker, can't do much about it as a batsman, Sangakkara only manages to jam it out towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, no run, backs away but Starc follows with a yorker, Sangakkara digs it out to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Mathews, 1 run, bit of tail away from Mathews, but he manages to dig it out to mid-off. <b>200 up for Sri Lanka</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, 1 run, reverse-swinging fuller length delivery on the off stump, driven to extra-cover, who fumbles the ball despite diving to his left and getting both hands to it]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, 2 runs, short and wide outside off stump, Sangakkara easily cuts it over point for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[During the drinks break, the physio was seen massaging Mathews' back.]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Mathews, 1 run, pushes the length ball straight down the ground and sets off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Starc now has a slip. Good captaincy from Clarke.]]></line><line><![CDATA[For Sri Lanka to win the match, Sangakkara needs to bat for about 40 overs and others have to give him support. The problem for Sri Lanka is that due to Glenn Maxwell's thunderous knock, Australia were able to score 123 runs in the last 10 overs. It is going to be tough for Sri Lanka to match that.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here is <b>Bharath Ramaraj's</b> analysis of the last 15 overs:  James Faulkner, with his slew of variations and by mixing up the lengths bowled a few tight overs. He was rewarded with the wicket of Tillakaratne Dilshan. Dilshan challenged that LBW decision, but it was rightly upheld. On what looks more like a subcontinental track, Australian pacers tried to hit Sri Lanka with pace upfront. But Faulkner has certainly adjusted to the conditions well. Kumar Sangakkara though, continued to flatten the Australian attack and smashed another century in this World Cup. He is now the seventh batsman to compose three back-to-back hundreds in ODIs. He is also the first player to do that in the history of World Cups. However, Michael Clarke effected a direct hit to run out Mahela Jayawardene. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[This is the 4th consecutive time in ODIs that Sangakkara has not missed out on a hundred after reaching fifty.]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Sangakkara, no run, backs away and tries to hit this slower ball inside-out, but toe-ends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, 1 run, slower ball yorker, Mathews digs it out to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, 2 runs, full and on the leg stump, Mathews works it along the ground to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Sangakkara, leg byes, 1 run, full and down the leg-side, Sangakkara misses the flick, the ball rolls towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Sangakkara, 2 runs, <b>24th ODI hundred for Sangakkara</b> and he's the <b>first man on the planet to score three consecutive hundreds in World Cups</b>. Full and down the leg-side, Sangakkara flicks it along the ground to deep square leg and gets back for the second. He gets a great round of applause from the crowd. Everyone at the SCG stand and applaud. No great celebrations from the legend though. Just takes the helmet off and raises the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Mathews dabs it to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Angelo Mathews, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[I think this is going to be interesting. Starc is getting the ball to reverse and he will be very difficult to handle. Sri Lanka will have to be careful against him.]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to M Jayawardene, <b>out</b> M Jayawardene Run Out!! Starc built the pressure with some lovely reverse-swinging balls and Jayawardene has fallen into the trap trying to steal a run. Needless from the senior pro! Full and outside off stump, Jayawardene pushes it straight to mid-off and takes off, Clarke quickly grabs the ball and fires a direct-hit and catches Jayawardene short despite a full length dive. <b>M Jayawardene run out (Clarke) 19(22) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to M Jayawardene, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[What have you done Mahela Jayawardene! I think he's run-out. YES! He's OUT! Brilliant piece of fielding from the Australian skipper.]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to M Jayawardene, no run, low full toss swinging away outside off stump, Jayawardene looks to drive, but gets an edge that goes on the bounce to Haddin]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, 1 run, wow! Brilliant inswinging toe-crusher from Starc. Interestingly, Starc <b>appeals for LBW</b>, but there was a big inside edge. Sangakkara was completely surprised by the late inswing, somehow he managed to get an inside edge onto the back leg and it rolled to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, no run, full and outside off stump, driven back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, no run, what a ball! Not easy to beat a bloke batting on 98. Full and just outside off stump, it started to tail back in and then held its line after pitching, Sangakkara hardly moved his feet attempting a drive and it almost took the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to M Jayawardene, 1 run, short of length delivery down the leg-side, glanced to fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc [5.0-0-16-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, a <b>hat-trick</b> of boundaries for Sanga! Poor ball from Faulkner again. Short and well outside off stump, asking for trouble and Sangakkara cuts it over point and it runs away to the boundary. Great start to the batting powerplay for Sri Lanka. They have scored 17 runs off the first 6 balls]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, four more! Faulkner gets the slower ball wrong. Bowls this down the leg-side and Sangakkara tickles it on its way. Moves onto 94 now]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, short of length delivery from Faulkner, Sangakkara rocks back and pulls it past the man at short fine leg for four]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Sangakkara, 2 runs, in the airrrr and Maxwell doesn't get there. Great effort though! Full delivery outside off stump, Sangakkara steps out and looks for the lofted drive, slices it towards sweeper cover, maybe Maxwell was a little late to take off and he couldn't get to the ball despite running forward and putting in a full length dive]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to M Jayawardene, 1 run, slower ball down the leg-side, Jayawardene glances it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to M Jayawardene, 2 runs, slower ball on the stumps, Jayawardene flicks it along the ground to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner [4.0-0-15-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third man is in, fine leg is back.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Wow! Sri Lanka have taken the <b>batting powerplay</b> early.]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Sangakkara, no run, full and outside off stump, driven to the right of the bowler, who half-stops the ball with his right hand in his followthrough]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to M Jayawardene, 1 run, poor ball, should have been hit for four, but Jayawardene has flicked this on the bounce to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sangakkara changes his bat.]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Sangakkara, 1 run, short of length delivery just outside off stump, worked away to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Sangakkara, no run, fullish and just a hint of outswing on this full ball, Sangakkara looks to drive but the ball flies off a thickish outside edge, Warner dives to his left at backward point and saves a few]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to M Jayawardene, 1 run, fullish and outside off stump, Jayawardene drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to M Jayawardene, 2 runs, full and outside off stump, Jayawardene goes for a lofted drive, but he slices it as the bat turns in his hands, the ball rolls to deep backward point and Jayawardene races back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Watson [2.0-0-19-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, 2 runs, <b>top-edgeeeee</b>, but it's gone over the keeper. Flighted delivery just outside off stump, Sangakkara goes for the sweep, luckily for him, the edge lands safely behind the keeper. Short fine-leg was a long way away]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to M Jayawardene, 1 run, slider and just outside off stump, wristed along the ground to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, 1 run, advances and drives it to the right of the bowler, who tries to stop the ball with a dive]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to M Jayawardene, 1 run, gets deep in the crease and tucks the flatter delivery through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to M Jayawardene, no run, half-shout for LBW, not given. Nicely tossed up from Maxwell, Jayawardene goes early into the sweep and misses. Maybe it hit Jayawardene outside the line of off stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to M Jayawardene, no run, spinning back in, Jayawardene flicks it to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Interesting to see Doherty get some turn in that over.]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Sangakkara, no run, flighted delivery outside off stump, Sangakkara drives it to cover, they think about a run but decide against it]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Sangakkara, no run, steps out, Doherty fires this wide outside off stump, Sangakkara drags the slog to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Sangakkara, no run, shortish and on the stumps, Sangakkara cuts and picks out point]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Sangakkara, no run, a lovely cover-drive now from Sanga, but straight to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, short and on the stumps, Sanga rocks back and pulls, puts it in the gap, deep mid-wicket runs to his left, Shane Watson was the fielder there, and puts in the dive but the ball wins the race]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to M Jayawardene, 1 run, flighted delivery on the leg stump, Jayawardene turns it towards square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Xavier Doherty [4.0-0-30-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Doherty to come round the wicket.]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to M Jayawardene, 1 run, on the stumps, worked away behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to M Jayawardene, no run, tossed up just outside off stump, defended off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, 1 run, spinning away outside off stump, Sangakkara drives it to deep cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to M Jayawardene, 1 run, flicked uppishly but wide of Smith at mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, 1 run, on the leg stump, tucked to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, no run, flighted delivery from round the wicket, goes for the pull, gets a bottom edge but doesn't carry to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Glenn Maxwell [4.0-0-26-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, 1 run, length ball and on Sangakkara's pads, whipped away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, no run, short of a length and just outside off, dabbed straight to backward point, Sangakkara wants a single but is wisely sent back by MJ]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, no run, Johnson keeps it full and gets it to angle into Sangakkara, flicked straight to the fielder at mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, no run, the bumper from Johnson, Sangakkara ducks under it and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, no run, tad fuller and on the stumps, Sangakkara prods across and turns it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, no run, on a good length and around middle, Sangakkara turns it towards the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Sangakkara, 1 run, short and on Sangakkara's hips, helped away towards long leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to M Jayawardene, 1 run, back of the hand slower ball from Faulkner, flicked away past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to M Jayawardene, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Jayawardene gets behind the line and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to M Jayawardene, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a cracking shot, tad fuller and on the stumps, MJ gets forward, uses his wrists to good effect and flicks it over mid-wicket for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Sangakkara, 1 run, fuller length delivery and on Sangakkara's pads, whipped away in front of square on the on-side. Warner gets across and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Sangakkara, no run, short of a length and just outside off, dabbed straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Coming back to Dilshan's wicket: As he was walking back, Watson got across him and had a few words to say. Not sure if the batsman responded.]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to M Jayawardene, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Jayawardene presses across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, 1 run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, punched to the left of mid-off. The fielder gets across, puts in the dive and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, no run, Johnson slips in the slower ball, Sangakkara presses across and clips it straight to the fielder at mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, Sangakkara presents the full face of the bat and drives it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, leg byes, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a poor ball from Johnson, full and on Sangakkara's pads, he looks to flick and misses, the ball races away past the keeper and into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, driven towards mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Sangakkara, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, tucked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to M Jayawardene, 1 run, a <b>direct hit might have had MJ</b> packing! He pushed one in front of mid-on and set-off for a quick single. Starc is quick on the ball and lets it fly towards the bowler's end, he misses and MJ survives]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to M Jayawardene, no run, short of a length and angling across Jayawardene, he gets across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mahela Jayawardene, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dilshan, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Faulkner has broken through for Australia! The pressure of the dot balls told on Dilshan, this was another slower ball, pitched on the leg-stump and straightened a tad, Dilshan went for a horrible swipe across the line, misses and is struck on the back leg, the impact was around middle and it was going on to crash into the middle stump. Good call from umpire Gould, Dilshan challenged his decision almost immediately, but to no avail. <b>Dilshan lbw b Faulkner 62(60) [4s-8]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Faulkner to Dilshan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dilshan has been given out LBW. He wants a <b>review</b>. It looked good to the naked eye. Needs to just hit the stumps for the decision to stay. Did it pitch in line though? No inside edge, Snicko confirms it. Three REDS, Dilshan is <b>OUT</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dilshan, no run, the back of the hand slower ball from Faulkner, Dilshan was looking to cut and is too early on the shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dilshan, no run, on a good length and angling across Dilshan, slapped straight to the fielder at point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Dilshan, 1 run, short and on the stumps, Dilshan swivels across and gets a bottom edge onto the pull, a single to long leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[Looks like Johnson got hit on the fingers as he stopped the last ball, he has a look at his fingers, a concerned Clarke runs up to him, but he's fine to go]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Dilshan, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, pushed back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[Johnson changes to round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, 1 run, tad fuller and angling into Sangakkara, tucked past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Sangakkara shuffles across and clips it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, no run, Johnson keeps it full and just outside off, punched back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, no run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Sangakkara gets forward and drives it straight to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Johnson [3.0-0-34-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Johnson back for another spell. Australia need a wicket now]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dilshan, no run, another slower back of the hand delivery from Faulkner, Dilshan dabs it straight to backward point, wants a single but is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dilshan, no run, fuller length delivery and on Dilshan's pads, turned straight to the fielder at square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Sangakkara, 1 run, back-of-the-hand slower ball from Faulkner, almost gets the wicket, Sangakkara was early in closing the face of the bat, gets a leading edge towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Sangakkara, no run, on a good length and well outside off, driven straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dilshan, 1 run, full and on Dilshan's pads, flicked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dilshan, no run, the back of the hand slower ball from Faulkner, Dilshan looks to flick and is struck high on the pads]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Dilshan, 1 run, pushed through and on Dilshan's pads, worked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, that's nicely played by Dilshan, Maxwell came from round the wicket and angled one across Dilshan, he made room, gets the gap behind point and cracks it away for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, 1 run, tossed up and well outside off, slapped away towards deep cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, 2 runs, Sangakkara shimmies down the track and plays a check drive back over the bowler's head, falls well in front of the man at long-on, just a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, defended towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, no run, slower and just outside off, dabbed with an open face towards point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Glenn Maxwell [3.0-0-18-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Sangakkara, 1 run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, driven in front of mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dilshan, 1 run, that one stayed a tad low, Dilshan manages to pull it away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Sangakkara, 1 run, the slower ball from Faulkner, Sangakkara runs it down towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Sangakkara, no run, width on offer from Faulkner, Sangakkara cuts it square behind point where Smith throws himself at the ball and prevents runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dilshan, 1 run, short of a length and on the stumps, Dilshan swivels across on the pull, gets a bottom edge behind square, <b>1000 runs for Dilshan in World Cups</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dilshan, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Dilshan arches back and dabs it straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Tillakaratne Dilshan too looked to use the pace of Australian bowlers as he played a volley of thunderous strokes off Johnson's bowling by smashing him for six boundaries in a single over! In particular, the pull shot he played in that over seemed to have crashed into the boundary boards at the speed of light. Dilshan didn't stop there as he used the scoop to collect a four off Mitchell Starc. It was a thrill-a-minute stuff at the SCG. Sri Lanka have a long way to go, but Dilshan and Sangakkara have given them a  great platform. In fact, the story could have been different as Michael Clarke dropped a tough chance to give Dilshan a reprieve. On the other hand, Australia looked to bowl cross-seam. The outfield is lightning quick and that makes it harder for the fielding side. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here is <b>Bharath Ramaraj's</b> analysis of the first 17 overs: Mitchell Johnson gave Australia the perfect start by bowling a vicious lifter to take the wicket of Lahiru Thirimanne. Initially, he also troubled Kumar Sangakkara with his slingy left-armer's angle. Sangakkara, generally, looked to play straight before he took on Johnson with a pull shot. Sangakkara was late on the pull shot, but fortunately for him, he collected four runs.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA["Things have changed so much! Even the Ladies and Members Stands join in the Mexican Wave doing the rounds of SCG," says <b>G Rajaraman</b> from the ground.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely cricket from Sangakkara, shimmies down the track, mid-off was inside the ring and Sangakkara goes over that man, a couple of bounces and over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Dilshan, 1 run, flighted and just outside off, worked wide of cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Sangakkara, 1 run, pushed through and on Sangakkara's pads, tucked behind square for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, Sangakkara is looking in excellent touch, this was tossed up and wider outside off, Sangakkara gets down on his knees and slog sweeps it in front of mid-wicket, one bounce and over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Sangakkara, 2 runs, tossed up and well outside off, Sangakkara drills it square on the off-side. Warner gets across to his right, puts in the slide and saves the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Dilshan, 1 run, slower and just outside off, Dilshan makes room and pushes it wide of cover for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Dilshan, 1 run, flatter and on Dilshan's pads, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Dilshan, byes, 2 runs, Maxwell sees Dilshan attempting the switch-hit, fires it well outside leg, Dilshan misses, so does the keeper, another couple of runs added to the total, brings up the 100-run stand as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, 1 run, flatter and on Sangakkara's pads, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, no run, slower and just outside off, Sangakkara comes down the track and pushes it uppishly, drops well in front of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Dilshan, 1 run, <b>43rd ODI fifty for Dilshan</b>, nudges a well flighted delivery behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Dilshan, no run, Maxwell comes from round the wicket and drifts one onto Dilshan's pads, he looks to sweep and misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Dilshan, 1 run, this one is given more air, eased down towards long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Dilshan, no run, slower and just outside off, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Sangakkara, 1 run, <b>94th ODI fifty for Sangakkara</b>, fraction shorter and well outside off, steered square on the off-side for a single, another fine knock from the Sri Lankan master batsman]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Sangakkara, 2 runs, slower and on off, worked in front of square on the on-side, puts the pressure on the fielder, he fumbles and allows a second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Sangakkara, no run, flighted delivery and going away with the angle, Sangakkara was looking to drive and missed. Haddin was quick to whip the bails off, but Sangakkara went nowhere]]></line><line><![CDATA[Appeal for a <b>stumping</b>. Sangakkara is the man in question, he dragged his left leg, but was well inside the crease, should be SAFE]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Dilshan, 1 run, flatter and well outside off, Dilshan makes room and cuts it square on the off-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, no run, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, that's as delicate as it gets , Maxwell drops one short and on the off-stump line, Sangakkara backs away, waits until the last moment and cracks it square behind point for another boundary. Maxwell was excited for a moment as he belted a LBW appeal, but there was no pad on that]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, Sangakkara comes down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and lifts it over mid-wicket, a couple of bounces and over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, 2 runs, <b>14,000 runs in ODIs for Sangakkara</b>, second man after Sachin Tendulkar to get there, the Sri lankans in the stands are enjoying this, Dilshan comes across and shakes hands, this was flatter and well down leg, Sangakkara gets a bottom edge on the sweep]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, no run, flatter and just outside off, Sangakkara stays back and pushes it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, no run, slower and just outside off, driven straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Dilshan, no run, tossed up and on off, pushed to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Sangakkara, 1 run, flighted delivery and well outside off, eased wide of cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Dilshan, 1 run, <b>Clake has dropped a chance</b>, perhaps, Johnson, coming in from long-on had a better chance. This was tossed up and just outside off, Dilshan went for the slog sweep, gets a top-edge that goes high into the night sky. Clarke ran back from mid-wicket, he was circling around the ball, doesn't get into any position and allows the ball to burst through his hands, he attempts to grab it on the second attempt, but isn't suucessful]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Dilshan, 2 runs, Doherty drops one short and just outside off, Dilshan makes room and cuts it square on the off-side, he wants the second run and takes on Maxwell, the throw isn't right on top of the stumps, Dilshan dives and makes home]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Dilshan, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Dilshan plays with an open face and finds backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Sangakkara, 1 run, slower and on off, worked away past square leg for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, 1 run, Sangakkara comes down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and drives it down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, no run, pushed through flatter and just outside off, nudged in front of point, Sangakkara wanted a run and is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Dilshan, 1 run, tossed up and just outside off, driven towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, 1 run, Maxwell drifts one onto Sangakkara's pads, nudged behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, no run, Maxwell tosses one on Sangakkara's pads, flicked straight to the fielder at backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Sangakkara, 2 runs, tossed up and well outside off, driven to the right of long-off for a couple of runs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Glenn Maxwell, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>G Rajaraman</b> brings this update from the SCG: "The brass band isn't tiring nor are the drummers.. this could well have been Premadasa Stadium."]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Sangakkara, 1 run, flighted and going with the angle, Sangakkara comes down the track and gets an inside edge behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Sangakkara, 2 runs, Doherty drifts one on Sangakkara's pads, tucked behind square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Sangakkara, 2 runs, tossed up and well outside off, Sangakkara comes down the track and drills it to the left of cover, Clarke dives and gets a hand onto it, Johnson gives a good chase and keeps them down to a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Dilshan, 1 run, this one is given more air, eased down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Dilshan, no run, flighted and on the stumps, driven back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Doherty to Sangakkara, 1 run, tossed up and just outside off, driven down towards long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Xavier Doherty, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dilshan, no run, low full-toss from Starc, driven straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc changes to round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dilshan, no run, that's a fine delivery from Starc, the yorker and just outside off, Dilshan hurriedly gets his bat down and is lucky that it wasn't on the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, 1 run, fuller length delivery and on Sangakkara's pads, flicked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dilshan, 1 run, Starc keeps it full and just outside off, Dilshan looks to drive and gets a thick edge towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dilshan, <b>wide</b>, the slower bouncer from Starc, angled across the right-hander, he was shaping for the pull and then let it go, called as a wide for height. Starc isn't convinced]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dilshan, no run, Starc keeps it full and just outside off, driven hard but straight to the fielder at short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, 1 run, fuller length delivery and on Sangakkara's pads, tucked away in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Sangakkara, 1 run, <b>uppish and safe</b>, Sangakkara was hanging back to his full ball, it was there for the drive, he didn't get the balance behind the shot, scoops it in the air but just wide of Clarke at extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Dilshan, 1 run, tad fuller and on the stumps, Dilshan closed the face of the bat and almost got a leading edge, the ball pops in front of mid-on and the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Sangakkara, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, worked away past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Dilshan, 1 run, tad fuller and angling into Dilshan, flicked away in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Sangakkara, 1 run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, driven to the left of mid-off. Johnson slides across and deflects it away towards mid-on, concedes a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sangakkara got a new grip onto his bat at the end of the last over]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Dilshan, 1 run, fuller length delivery and on Dilshan's pads, whipped away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, no run, Starc keeps it very full and outside off, Sangakkara is down on one knee as he drives, can't get it past extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, no run, excellent ball from Starc, full and tailing in very late into Sangakkara, he was looking to drive, the ball bursts through the inside edge and nips away further. Haddin dives across and prevents byes. Clarke and Maxwell are interested in an appeal, but there was no bat on that]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, no run, short and just outside off, doesn't rise as much as Sangakkara expected, he was in a good position on the pull, misses and is struck high on the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, no run, Starc keeps it full and well outside off, Sangakkara drives and finds the man at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Sangakkara presents the full face of the bat and drives it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, width on offer from Starc, Sangakkara cuts it up and over point, watches the ball race away to the fence in a jiffy]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc [3.0-0-8-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Sangakkara, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, steered away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, classy from Sangakkara, short of a length and well outside off, Sangakkara leans forward and cuts it up and over backward point, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Dilshan, 1 run, the reverse Dilscoop, on a good length and just outside off, Dilshan got into a position for the scoop, the ball goes off the face of the bat, hits the helmet and lobs away behind square on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Dilshan, no run, rush of blood from Dilshan, comes down the track and looks to swat this length ball over the SCG, misses it completely]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>7 boundaries in a row for Dilshan</b>, the Dilscoop makes an appearance, on a good length and just outside off, Dilshan gets down on one knee and helps it over short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Sangakkara, 3 runs, on a good length and well outside off, Sangakkara leans forward and eases it square past cover, almost went all the way, the fielder gives chase and hauls the ball back in, Sangakkara takes three]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Watson, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>that's 6 in a row</b>, Johnson has been smashed into oblivion, this was the best of the lot, change of pace from Johnson, gets it to dip onto the batsman. Dilshan leans forward, meets it on the bounce and caresses it past extra cover. Haddin smiles and a has a word or two to say]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>five in a row</b>, Dilshan is on fire, full and well outside off, Dilshan clears his left leg and creams it past extra cover, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>smashed</b>, Johnson responds with a short ball, Dilshan is quick to swivel across and pulls it past square leg, one bounce and over the ropes. Johnson has been put under pressure]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>hat-trick of boundaries!</b> Fraction shorter and just outside off, Dilshan swivelled across and pulls it over square leg, almost went all the way, just one bounce and over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, this is even better! Tad fuller and just outside off, Dilshan presents the full face of the bat and drives it back past the non-striker, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, that's typical Dilshan shot, it was full and well outside off, Dilshan gets forward, closes the face at the point of impact and drives it past mid-off for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, 2 runs, nicely played by Sangakkara, overpitched and just outside off, Sangakkara gets behind the line and merely pushes it past mid-off, good enough to come back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Sangakkara presents the full face of the bat as he pushes it back at the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dilshan, 1 run, <b>top-edged and safe</b>, Dilshan was in no control as he went for the pull, the ball hurried onto him, gets a top-edge that drops behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dilshan, no run, pitched up and just outside off, Dilshan gets well forward and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dilshan, 2 runs, back of a length and on Dilshan's pads, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dilshan, no run, low full-toss and just outside off, Dilshan goes hard on the drive, the bat turned in his hands and gets an inside edge back towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, no run, appeal for LBW, but it looked like there was an inside edge on that, Sangakkara was caught in his crease to one that came back in a fraction, the edge saved him]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, first boundary for Sri Lanka, looked like it was a late call by Sangakkara to pull, this was a high bouncer, Sangakkara pulled it as an afterthought, not all that convincing, but gets enough bat to clear square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, 2 runs, back of a length and just outside off, Sangakkara nudges it through the vacant extra cover region, gets back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Dilshan, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, pushed to the right of cover-point for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Dilshan, no run, change of pace from Johnson, pushes it fuller and wider outside off, Dilshan reaches out and gets a toe-edge towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Dilshan, no run, Johnson shortens his length and cramps Dilshan for space, pushed off the back foot and towards mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, no run, fuller length delivery and on Sangakkara's pads, turned towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Sangakkara hops across and turns it in front of square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, no run, that's a peach from Starc, tad fuller and just outside off, draws Sangakkara into the forward push, the ball nips away at the last moment, beats the outside edge on its way to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Sangakkara, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Sangakkara drops his wrists and defends it with soft hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dilshan, 1 run, on a good length and going away with the angle, Dilshan drives and gets a thick edge towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dilshan, no run, fuller length delivery and nipping away from outside off, Dilshan is rooted to his crease as he went flaying at that, misses by a long way]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Sangakkara rides with the bounce and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Sangakkara, no run, another short delivery from Johnson, Sangakkara drops his wrists and sways away from the line]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kumar Sangakkara, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Thirimanne, <b>out</b> Caught by Haddin!! Early strike by Johnson! That was a nasty lifter, excellent bouncer from Johnson, very well directed, right at the throat of the batsman. Thirimanne was hopping across, the ball followed him as he looked to arch back, doesn't get the gloves out of the way, the ball loops to the keeper. Haddin dives forward and completes the catch. Sri Lanka have lost an early wicket. <b>Thirimanne c Haddin b Johnson 1(5)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Johnson to Thirimanne, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Thirimanne, no run, length ball and on Thirimanne's pads, he prods across and defends it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Dilshan, 3 runs, much better from Dilshan, tad fuller and just outside off, he gets half-forward and pushes it back past the bowler, the timing isn't spot on but the batsmen run well and get back for the third run]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Johnson to Dilshan, no run, fuller length delivery and swinging into Dilshan's pads, he looks to flick and is hit on the pads]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Johnson, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Thirimanne, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Thirimanne defends it with an open face]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dilshan, 1 run, fraction too short and on Dilshan's pads, worked wide of mid-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dilshan, no run, Starc keeps it very full and well outside off, Dilshan looks to steer it towards third man, the ball beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dilshan, no run, swing and a miss from Dilshan, went chasing after a full ball that nipped away, doesn't connect with the drive]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Thirimanne, 1 run, tad fuller and on the stumps, Thirimanne pushes it to the right of mid-on and sets off for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Thirimanne, no run, on a good length and on the stumps, Thirimanne prods across and defends it towards mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place as Starc steams in..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Thirimanne and Dilshan are at the crease. Thirimanne is on strike. Starc will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back..Sri Lanka's batsmen have fired so far in the tournament. But can they chase down 377 against Johnson, Starc and Co?]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@bhogleharsha</b>: The ground looks like it could be Colombo, the pitch seemed slow at the start but the score, I fear, is beyond Sri Lanka. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@mohanstatsman</b>: No team has ever made a 300+ total against Australia in any World Cups. Can SL be the first and also win? ]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@cricketaakash</b>: Weakness in Maxwell's play highlighted again...gives a chance in the 90s. What. A. Player]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@Sidvee</b>: Not sure what is more mindblowing. Maxwell's astonishing strokeplay. Or Maxwell's 'I swear I didn't mean to do that' expression after. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@RicFinley</b>: Just when you think you have seen all manner of possible players, Glenn Maxwell comes along. He really is something special. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here's how twitter reacted to the crazy innings from Maxwell: ]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Maxwell</b>: "It's nice to finally get the monkey off the back. I've got a few 90s of late, but it's good to get the hundred. It's a big relief to finally get it out of the way. The top-order set it up nicely for us to have some fun in the end. We just have to bowl a good line and length to win. The wicket won't change much generally in Australia."]]></line><line><![CDATA[At the other end of the spectrum, Sri Lankan players would be a disappointed lot. They bowled with good disciplines upfront before losing the plot. It could be said that they missed the services of Rangana Herath. Malinga bowled well in spurts, but he still looks short of his best. Unless they play out of their skins, one gets the feeling that Australia may have already batted Sri Lanka out of the game.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[One has to also remember that despite playing second fiddle to Maxwell for most of the time, Shane Watson essayed a key role in what turned out to be an enthralling partnership. Watson played some power-packed strokes, especially he cracked a thunderous shot over the mid-wicket region for a six off Mathews' bowling and went on to compose a well-deserved fifty. In fact, Watson's strike rate was 163.4.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Maxwell played a glorious lofted shot off Dilshan to clear the ropes and start his innings on a great note. He proceeded to annihilate the opposition ranks. After the second drinks break, he hoicked Prasanna across the line for a six and virtually took the mickey out of the bowler with a switch hit in the same over to collect four more runs. In the 39th over of the innings, Thisara Perera looked to bowl a slower one, but it turned out to be a low full toss and not surprisingly, Maxwell thumped it for a six. Angelo Mathews looked to gamble with Prasanna in the 41st over of the game, but Maxwell flayed him for three boundaries. In the past, leg-spinners have troubled Maxwell with a potent googly, but Prasanna doesn't have one. It continued to rain fours and sixes from his willow and Perera came in for some severe punishment as he was clobbered for 20 runs in a single over. Maxwell eventually, completed his hundred in a mere 51 balls and was dismissed by Perera. But by then, the damage was already done. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, Sri Lanka started on a good note, as Lasith Malinga generated a bit of away swing and deceived David Warner with a slower one to dismiss him. Aaron Finch, in an attempt to up the ante, looked to use his feet but was stumped off Seekkuge Prasanna's bowling. However, Clarke and Smith helped Australia to make a smart recovery. Both of them looked to milk the spinners with nimble wrists and by playing late. It was about smothering the spin on the front foot to shorten the length before looking to take advantage of the short delivery. Smith then completed a fine fifty. Clarke, who has been short of match practice in recent times, followed him by notching up a well-measured fifty too. However, Malinga and Tillakaratne Dilshan landed crucial blows to give Sri Lanka genuine hope of coming back into the game. Unfortunately for them, Maxwell shut the door, with those meaty blows. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[After Steven Smith and Michael Clarke set a solid platform with a well-constructed century stand, Glenn Maxwell used his willow like a magic wand to thwack Sri Lanka's bowlers to all corners of the ground and take them to a mammoth total on the board. Maxwell scored the second fastest century in World Cups. However, his ton turned out to be the fastest century for Australia in ODIs. It was also Maxwell's first hundred in ODIs. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Australia will be very happy to see 376 on the board after opting to bat first. When Sri Lanka removed both openers early, it looked like Australia were going to score somewhere around 250-260, but some brilliant batting from the middle-order has given them a huge score.]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Doherty, byes, 1 run, change of pace to end the innings, Doherty advances and swings hard but doesn't make contact. Johnson steals a bye though]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Johnson, 1 run, slower ball outside off stump, Johnson swings it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Xavier Doherty, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Johnson, <b>out</b> Starc Run Out!! 1 run completed. Australia are losing wickets in a hurry but you can understand that in the situation, they are trying to steal every extra run possible. Slower ball well outside off stump, Johnson drills it to long-on, Starc tries races back for the second, but Perera fires a good throw to the bowler and Mathews knocks over the bails before Starc reached his crease. Aleem Dar didn't even want the TV replay. <b>Starc run out (T Perera/Mathews) 0(0)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mathews to Johnson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Haddin, <b>out</b> Caught by T Perera!! Slower ball on the off stump, Haddin tries to play the lofted shot over mid-off, but he ends up slicing it high in the air, Perera runs back from mid-off and takes a good catch. <b>Haddin c T Perera b Mathews 25(9) [4s-4 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mathews to Haddin, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Haddin, <b>FOUR</b>, Haddin gets across the stumps and swings hard at this full ball, gets it on the inside half of the bat, it goes through backward square leg and there was no one in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Johnson, 1 run, slower ball outside off stump, Johnson pushes it to cover off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Angelo Mathews [6.0-0-52-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Johnson, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Watson, <b>out</b> Caught by Chandimal!! That is a good catch by Chandimal. Slower ball outside off stump, Watson goes for the lofted hit but he's mistimed this completely. It went straight up in the air, mid-off takes a few steps back and completes a good catch to his left. End of a handy innings from Watto! Some respite for Perera as he gets to see 2 in the wickets column against him name. <b>Watson c Chandimal b T Perera 67(41) [4s-7 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[T Perera to Watson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Haddin, 1 run, <b>dropped</b>. It was a tough chance, he caught it, but as his elbows hit the ground, it popped out. Full from Perera again, Haddin slogs and hits it flat, the fielder at deep mid-wicket runs to his right and dives, gets both hands to it but doesn't hold on]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Haddin, <b>FOUR</b>, oh that's cruel for the bowler. He's bowled a fine yorker almost beat the batsman as he tried to dig it out, maybe there was an inside edge but it went off the back leg to the fine leg boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Haddin, <b>FOUR</b>, it's common sense that you shouldn't bowl full at the death! Perera is trying the yorker alright, but he simply is not able to control the ball. It's so easy for Haddin, with mid-off inside the ring, all he had to do was just chip it over the infield, which he did very well]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Haddin, <b>FOUR</b>, shuffles in the crease, Perera goes full again, Haddin drives it to the right of extra-cover, where the Sri Lankan skipper dives over the ball and lets it go right through him. That should have been just one]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Haddin, <b>SIX</b>, no! Bad ball! Wow! That was just a gentle lofted drive but it's gone all the way! How well has he timed it? Full and wide outside off stump, a lot of room on offer for the batsman and he doesn't miss out, sends the ball all the way over extra-cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Slinga ends 10-0-59-2]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Haddin, 1 run, slower ball goes very full, Haddin drives it to the left of mid-off, who makes a sliding save. Just 4 runs off the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Watson, 1 run, full and wide outside off stump, Watson had to reach out as he was initially making room, but he did well to connect the lofted drive very well, on the bounce to deep cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Watson, no run, again makes room, but Slinga bowls a pin-point yorker and keeps Watto calm]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Watson, no run, makes room and drills this full ball very hard, but straight to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Haddin, 1 run, very full outside off stump, Haddin drives it to mid-off and sets off]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Watson, 1 run, follows Watto with a slower ball yorker as he backs away, Watson digs it out to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga [9.0-0-55-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Watson, 1 run, low full toss from Perera, Watson flicks it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, this is an amazing shot! How on earth did he manage to time that so well? It was full and way outside off stump, Watson had to reach out for it, in fact he lost balance while meeting the ball, yet he's managed to send it over extra-cover and more importantly time it sweetly]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Watson, 2 runs, full and outside off stump, Watto walks across and drives it to long-on, Haddin races back to the second and the throw was very poor as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Brad Haddin, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Faulkner, <b>out</b> Faulkner Run Out!! Full delivery outside off stump, Faulkner drives it straight to extra-cover and sets off. Perera had the presence of mind to rush back to stumps and Mathews fired an accurate throw adjacent to the stumps. Perera disturbed the stumps just before Faulkner made his ground. It's a <b>golden duck</b> for Faulkner. <b>Faulkner run out (Mathews/T Perera) 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[T Perera to Faulkner, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Run-out check sent upstairs. Faulkner is short of his crease I guess. Oh yes! OUT]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Watson, 1 run, very full outside off stump, Watson drives it to extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Maxwell, <b>out</b> Caught by Malinga!! Would you believe it! He was hitting those fuller ones, length balls, slowers balls, everything out of the ground, but he's mistimed a friendly full toss and offered a simple catch. Hang on! The umpires are checking for height on this high full toss. It's under the waist and Maxwell has to go. That's so poor from the umpire so send it upstairs. It was well under Maxwell's waist. Anyway, Maxwell walks off to great applause from the SCG crowd. He shows his bat to the crowd as he walks off. What an innings from Maxwell. He tried to swing this for six, but the bat turned it his hands and went straight up in the air, mid-on ran to his left and took a simple catch. <b>Maxwell c Malinga b T Perera 102(53) [4s-10 6s-4]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[T Perera to Maxwell, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Thisara Perera [7.0-0-60-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, very full ball from Prasanna, Watson sweeps it along the ground to deep backward square leg and splits the two coverging fielders in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Maxwell, 1 run, driven down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Maxwell, 2 runs, this is <b>fastest ODI hundred for Australia</b> and the <b>second fastest World Cup hundred</b>. Take a bow Maxwell. It's his <b>maiden ODI hundred</b>. He gets a <b>standing ovation</b> from the SCG crowd. He punches the air in delight, pumps his fist, takes the helmet off and raises his bat. He hugs Watto as well! Flighted delivery outside off stump, Maxwell gently lofts it over wide mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Watson, 1 run, a direct-hit would have been very interesting. Flighted delivery just outside off stump, Watson flicks it wide of mid-wicket and races to the bowler's end. Maxi is back on strike now]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, that's his <b>32nd ODI fifty</b>, also the <b>150 partnership comes up</b>. Flighted delivery full and outside off stump, Watson drills the drive very hard and back past the bowler, both long-off and long-on had no chance. Maxwell shakes hands with Watto and congratulates him]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, Watto goes off-side very early, exposes the sticks and forces the bowler to bowl on the stumps and with short fine leg inside the ring, sweeps well and sends it to the left of the fielder there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Seekkuge Prasanna [9.0-0-61-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Great sportsmanship from Maxwell. When umpire Gould asked him, he could have easily said that he hit the ball and Gould would have had no choice but to signal a run, which would have given him the joint-fastest World Cup hundred.]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Watson, 1 run, yorker length from Malinga, dug out to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Watson, no run, widish full ball, Watson backs away and fails to reach out]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Maxwell, leg byes, 1 run, <b>huge appeal for LBW</b>, not given and rightly so, it was going down the leg-side. Drama! Umpire Gould doesn't signal leg bye for a long time, Maxwell reached the non-striker's end, Gould then asked Maxwell did you hit it, Maxwell said no and then the signal came for the leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Watson, 1 run, low full toss as he tries the yorker, dug out to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Maxwell, 1 run, oh he <b>can't get the fastest World Cup ton</b>. Needed to do it this ball. Slower delivery on the leg stump, softly driven towards long-on. Maybe he didn't know about the record]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Maxwell, 2 runs, full toss, Maxwell steps out and lofts it straight back over the bowler, long-on tidies up running to his left. <b>He's onto 98</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga [8.0-0-50-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Watson, no run, yorker outside off stump, Watson digs it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Maxwell, 1 run, very full outside off stump, drilled to extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Maxwell, 2 runs, in the air, Sanga is running back and ohhh he's <b>dropped</b> it. It was a tough chance, but he did very well to get there. He would be disappointed for putting it down. Can Maxwell score a hundred today? We've seen him get out in the 90s so many times. Slower delivery down the leg-side, Maxwell tries to slog-sweep, gets a top edge, Sanga runs back, gets both hands to it but couldn't hold on]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Maxwell, <b>FOUR</b>, no one at sweeper cover and that's a safe shot! Full and outside off stump, nothing ball indeed with that field. Maxwell goes leg-side and carves it over cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Watson, 1 run, makes room, Mathews offers a length ball wide outside off stump, Watto reaches out and cuts very but picks out deep point]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Watson, <b>wide</b>, backs away again, Mathews tries to outsmart the batsman with a widish length ball but he bowls this way outside off stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Watson, <b>SIX</b>, backs away, it's a full ball in the slot, in fact the slower ball attempted by Mathews, Watson goes bangggg and slogs over mid-wicket. Great start to the over for Australia]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Maxwell, 2 runs, low full-toss and just outside off, Maxwell drives and gets an inside edge wide of mid-wicket, gets to <b>his highest WC score</b> as he comes back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Maxwell, <b>wide</b>, Perera goes full and miles outside off, wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Maxwell, <b>SIX</b>, this is clean hitting from Maxwell, can he get the fastest WC hundred? This was short and just outside off, Maxwell swivels across and sends it sailing into the deep square leg boundary, moves onto 87 now]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Maxwell, no run, slower yorker from Perera, driven straight to the fielder at covers]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Maxwell, <b>FOUR</b>, even mishits are going the distance here, the back of the hand slower ball from Perera, Maxwell was done in by the slowness of the ball, mishits it, gets it high on the bat and just about clears mid-off, long-on can't keep it inside the ropes as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Watson, 1 run, Perera slips in the slower ball, Watson makes room and pushes it towards mid-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Watson, <b>SIX</b>, poor ball from Perera, but that's dealt with some power, backs away and goes high and over mid-wicket, went sailing over the ropes for a maximum]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Thisara Perera [6.0-0-40-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Watson, 1 run, Watson backs away to a short ball and carves it through cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Maxwell, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Maxwell pushes forward and gets an inside edge in front of square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Watson, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, steered away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Maxwell, 3 runs, Maxwell has luck on his side as well, looks to slog a slower ball and gets a steepling top-edge. It went high and over square leg, Perera came rushing across from fine leg, but the ball was always dropping wide of him, another three runs added to the total]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Maxwell, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, scythed straight to the fielder at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Maxwell, <b>FOUR</b>, the reverse pull from Maxwell, he's displaying all his abilities here, gets it over backward point and the ball races away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Angelo Mathews [4.0-0-27-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Watson, 2 runs, Prasanna tosses one well outside leg, Watson looks to flick and gets an inside edge, the ball runs away very fine, Watson comes back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Maxwell, 1 run, wide full-toss from Prasanna, slower as well, sliced away to deep cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Maxwell, <b>FOUR</b>, this is exceptional cricket from Maxwell, gets down on his knees to a well flighted delivery and slugs it in front of square on the on-side, beats the man in the deep and races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Maxwell, 2 runs, Maxwell comes down the track, gets inside the line and goes up and over mid-off, Thisara gets across from the deep and keeps them down to a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Maxwell, <b>FOUR</b>, deft cricket from Maxwell, goes down on his knees, delays his sweep, rolls his wrists and sweeps it behind square on the on-side for another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Maxwell, <b>FOUR</b>, Maxwell is picking his spots cleanly, gets down on his knees and slog sweeps it high and wide of deep mid-wicket, one bounce and over the ropes for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Seekkuge Prasanna [8.0-0-44-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Maxwell, 1 run, another slower ball from Malinga, well down leg-side as well, flicked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Maxwell, no run, another slower ball from Malinga, the loopy variety, follows Maxwell as he backed away, he was early on the shovel and is hit on the body]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Watson, 1 run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, chipped away towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Maxwell, 1 run, another full-toss following Maxwell as he backed away, swung away towards fine leg, Perera nearly lost his footing in the deep, just about gets his body behind the line]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Watson, 1 run, low full-toss and on Watson's pads, clipped away to the left of square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, Watson bisects the two men in the deep, this was full and on Watson's pads, he gets across and flicks it behind square on the on-side, beats the two men in the deep and into the boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Maxwell, no run, Maxwell backed away even before the bowler released the ball, he takes all the pace off the ball, beats Maxwell on the cut, the ball bounces through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Watson, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, Watson wrists it away through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Watson, no run, on a good length and just outside off, dabbed with an angled bat towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Maxwell, 1 run, slower ball from Perera, on Maxwell's pads, he looks to help it on its way, gets an inside edge onto the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Maxwell, <b>SIX</b>, can't bowl full-tosses to this man, Maxwell latches onto it and heaves it over mid-wicket, didn't strike it all that well, but gets it well wide of the fielder in the deep, gets to his <b>12th ODI fifty</b> as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Maxwell, 2 runs, slow full toss from Perera, whipped away towards wide mid-wicket, Maxwell hares back for the second run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Thisara Perera [5.0-0-30-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, back-to-back boundaries for Watson, too short from Malinga, Watson swivels across, rolls his wrists and pulls it behind square on the on-side, <b>16 from this over</b>, Sri Lanka are going for plenty in the batting PP]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, Watson joins in the fun as well, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Watson gets a big stride forward, presents the full face of the bat and punches it to the left of mid-on for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Maxwell, 1 run, Malinga follows Maxwell with a slower ball, driven towards mid-on for a quick single, brings up the 50-run stand as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[More discussions regarding the field placements]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Maxwell, <b>FOUR</b>, superb batting from Maxwell, nothing wrong with the ball, full and on the leg-stump line, Maxwell backs away, opens the face of the bat at the last moment and drills it over extra cover for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Watson, 1 run, short and on the stumps, Watson swivels across and pulls it away towards long leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Watson, 2 runs, leg-stump half-volley from Malinga, flicked away behind square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Maxwell, 2 runs, very full and on Maxwell's pads, he makes room and shovels it wide of mid-wicket, gets back for the second run, <b>17 runs from the over</b>, that spoils Prasanna's figures]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Maxwell, 2 runs, the lofted flick now, flighted delivery and just outside off, Maxwell picks out the gap at wide long-on, Chandimal gets across and keeps them down to a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Maxwell, <b>FOUR</b>, Maxwell brings out the switch hit now, this was flighted and just outside off, Maxwell changes his stance, gets underneath the length and hits it over backward point for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Maxwell, 2 runs, Prasanna slows down the pace and offers a low full toss, Maxwell had to reach out for the sweep, gets a bottom edge and in front of square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Maxwell, <b>SIX</b>, that's brilliance personified from Maxwell, this was tossed up and just outside off, he went half-way down on the knee and swings it high and over deep square leg for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mathews has a chat with the bowler, might be about fielding placements]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Watson, 1 run, tossed up and on the stumps, driven down towards long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Seekkuge Prasanna [7.0-0-27-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[With Senanayake in the line-up, it was also surprising to note that they didn't use the around the wicket tactic to Clarke for a long time. It was only in the 31st over of the innings that Senanayake decided to bowl from around the wicket. Clarke likes to play through the mid-wicket region against off-spinners. But by bowling from around the wicket, with a short mid-wicket in place, it can frustrate Clarke and in the past, he has got out to that sort of line. It was successfully used by Graeme Swann in the fourth Ashes Test at the MCG in 2010-11. He tied down Clarke completely before he was dismissed with a straighter one in the second innings. A stumping chance too was missed in that innings.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here is <b>Bharath Ramaraj's</b> analysis of the last 18 overs: Steven Smith and Michael Clarke looked to bisect the gaps in the field and take quick singles. Both the batsmen played late and with supple wrists to place the ball into gaps. They used the crease to good effect as well. Smith also completed a fine fifty. He has become the fulcrum of Australia's batting line-up this summer. Clarke followed up Smith's effort with a well-constructed half-century and then used his feet to play a sumptuous shot and smash a six off Sachithra Senanayake's bowling. He also essayed a glorious straight drive off Lasith Malinga, before Malinga gave a fitting riposte by shattering Clarke's stumps. To make it better for Sri Lanka, Thisara Perera took a fine catch to send Smith back to the pavilion. However, with Glenn Maxwell looking in fine touch, Australia look set to amass a sizeable total on the board. On the other hand, Sri Lanka's spinners tended to bowl short and their fielding was below par. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Watson, 1 run, that's a gift from Malinga, low full-toss and on Watson's pads, whipped away straight to the fielder at deep backward square leg, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Maxwell, 1 run, yorker length delivery and on the stumps, Maxwell backs away and drives it to the left of extra cover, Chandimal gets across and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Maxwell, no run, another pin-point yorker on the middle stump line, Maxwell digs it out towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Maxwell, no run, this is excellent bowling from Malinga, follows Maxwell as he backed away, it's a toe-crusher, Maxwell plays with an open face and guides it straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Maxwell, no run, Malinga follows Maxwell with a low full-toss, Maxwell clears his left leg and clips it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Watson, 1 run, Malinga bangs one short and on the stumps, Watson swivels across, rolls his wrists and pulls it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga [5.0-0-23-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>batting PP</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Watson, 1 run, pushed through and on the middle stump line, worked behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Maxwell, 1 run, psuhed through and on Maxwell's pads, nudged past mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Maxwell, <b>SIX</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, wrong line from Dilshan, mid-off was inside the ring and he gave this one plentry of air and well outside off, Maxwell prods forward and goes up and over the infield, gets plenty of bat and the ball sails over the ropes for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Maxwell, <b>FOUR</b>, that's much better from Maxwell, gets to the pitch of a well flighted delivery, goes inside out and over cover, a couple of bounces and over the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Maxwell, no run, flighted delivery and on off, pushed back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Maxwell, 2 runs, Maxwell is living dangerously, looks to tonk a well flighted delivery over mid-off, ends up spooning it over extra cover, just got enough bat to get it over the fielder there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Watson, 2 runs, pushed through flatter and quicker as Watson set himself up for the lap sweep, gets a bit of a top-edge that loops over Sangakkara. Watson is off the mark with a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Watson, no run, tossed up and on off, Watson gets well forward and turns it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Maxwell, 1 run, the reverse sweep now, fetched it from well outside leg, hits it very square and straight to the man in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Maxwell, <b>FOUR</b>, good use of the feet from Maxwell, comes down the track, gets inside the line and goes over mid-off, one bounce and over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Maxwell, no run, flighted and just outside off, Maxwell prods forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Maxwell, no run, tossed up and on the pads, turned towards the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sachithra Senanayake [8.0-0-52-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Watson, no run, flighted and just outside off, clipped towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Watson, no run, tossed up and just outside off, Watson presses across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Maxwell, 1 run, flighted delivery and well outside off, eased square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Watson, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to S Smith, <b>out</b> Caught by T Perera!! That's an excellent catch from Perera and Australia have lost both set batsmen. This was tossed up and just outside off, Smith came down the track, he wasn't there to the pitch of the ball but still went through with the lofted drive, gets plenty of height. Thisara runs back from mid-off, the fielder at long-on (Thirimanne) sprinted across as well. Perera watches the ball all along and takes it over his shoulder, makes sure that it didn't pop out when he hit the ground. Sri Lanka are back in the contest. <b>S Smith c T Perera b Dilshan 72(88) [4s-7 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dilshan to S Smith, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Maxwell, 1 run, fraction shorter and just outside off, punched off the back foot and towards sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Maxwell, no run, tossed up and just outside off, punched straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tillakaratne Dilshan [3.0-0-17-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Maxwell, 1 run, Malinga attempts a yorker first-up, turns out to be a low full-toss, almost sneaked through Maxwell's defences, just about got his bat down in time, inside edge behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Glenn Maxwell, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Clarke, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Malinga breaks the partnership! This was full and nipped back in late, Clarke was looking to whip it away towards the on-side, misses and the stumps are clattered. But hang on, is it a no-ball? Looks like Malinga had just a bit inside the popping crease, the wicket stands then but just by a hair's breadth. Clarke falls after a superb knock, a run-a-ball innings, he has set up Australia towards a huge score. <b>Clarke b Malinga 68(68) [4s-6]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Malinga to Clarke, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, Malinga misses his yorker, turns out to be a length ball, driven back past the bowler, mid-off dives in vain and the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Clarke, no run, another slower yorker from Malinga, turns out to be a full-toss, pushed towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Clarke, no run, high full-toss from Malinga, Clarke looked like he lost it for a moment, ends up patting it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Clarke, 2 runs, Malinga drops one short and on the stumps, Clarke swivels across, rolls his wrists and pulls it past square leg. Senanayake gets across from deep square leg, puts in the slide and saves a couple of runs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga [4.0-0-16-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to S Smith, no run, flighted and just outside off, pushed back at the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[Back over the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, this is poor bowling from Senanayake, no one in the deep at point and he drops it way too short, Smith backs away and cuts it square on the off-side for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to S Smith, 2 runs, the flat sweep from Smith, Senanayake drifted this one on Smith's pads, gets it very fine and comes back for the brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Clarke, 1 run, tossed up and on Clarke's pads, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Clarke, 2 runs, Clarke is toying with the bowlers here, Senanayake dropped one short and just outside off, Clarke makes room and goes up and over cover, off the back foot, Perera gets across from long-off, gets his boot across and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to S Smith, 1 run, tossed up and on Smith's pads, worked away in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Senanayake shifts to round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, Clarke is in full flow now, this was pitched up and just outside off, Clarke backs away, frees his arm up and goes up and over mid-off with the lofted drive, runs are coming in a real hurry here]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, Sri Lanka are bleeding runs here! This was a short slower ball from Perera, Clarke had made room outside leg, waits on the ball and pulls it behind square on the on-side, races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to S Smith, 1 run, another slower ball from Perera, punched away square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Clarke, 1 run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Clarke throws his bat at that, gets a thick edge towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Clarke, no run, change of pace from Perera, slips in the slower ball, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Clarke, no run, short of a length and just outside off, punched to the left of mid-off. Mathews gets across, puts in the dive and saves a certain boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Thisara Perera [4.0-0-20-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to S Smith, <b>SIX</b>, this is exceptional hitting from Smith, comes down the track, gives himself some room while doing so, gets to the pitch of the ball and swings it high and into the stands at long-off. Australia are on the move now]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Clarke, 1 run, <b>57th ODI fifty from Clarke </b>, worked in front of square on the on-side for a single, raises his bat to thunderous applause]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to S Smith, 1 run, flatter and on Smith's pads, nudged away very fine for a single, good work from Malinga in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Clarke, 1 run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Clarke backs away and cuts it square on the on-side for a single, brings up the <b>100-run stand</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a lovely shot, fraction short and well outside off, Clarke makes room and goes up and over cover with the back foot punch, he's looking very good now]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to S Smith, 1 run, Smith comes down the track to a well flighted delivery and pushes it towards long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sachithra Senanayake [6.0-0-28-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Smith swivels across and works it to the right of mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Clarke, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, punched away towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Smith plays with an open face and runs it down towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, no run, on a good length and just outside off, dabbed with an open face and towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, <b>wide</b>, the bumper from Mathews, but it's too short and too high, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Clarke, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Clarke presents the full face of the bat and punches it towards long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, a long half-volley from Mathews, full and wide outside off, Clarke gets a big stride forward and cracks it square past extra cover, no need to run for those]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[An unoffical drinks break for the Australians. Clarke winced while running during the last over, but he's fine to continue]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Clarke, 1 run, once again on the shorter side, Dilshan, punched down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to S Smith, 1 run, Dilshan dragged this one short as Smith came down the track, slapped straight to the fielder at sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Clarke, 1 run, Dilshan drops one short and on the stumps, pulled away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Clarke, no run, flighted and just outside off, driven straight to the fielder at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to S Smith, 1 run, Smith comes down the track to a well flighted delivery and drives it down towards long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Clarke, 1 run, flighted and on the stumps, punched down towards long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Clarke, 1 run, Mathews keeps it full and on the off-stump channel, Clarke goes for the big drive, ends up getting a thick inside edge behind square for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, 1 run, fuller length delivery and on off, worked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Clarke, 3 runs, that's a poor effort from Tharanga at mid-off, this was full and well outside off, driven to the left of mid-off, Tharanga gets across and lets the ball go through his legs, the batsmen get back for the third run]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Clarke, no run, back of a length and a hint of nip across the right-hander, extra bounce as well, Clarke was looking to run it down towards third man and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, 1 run, Mathews shortens his length outside off, sliced away behind square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Clarke, 1 run, short of a length and well outside off, Clarke takes a step down the track and pulls it towards deep mid-wicket for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Angelo Mathews [2.0-0-11-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>fifty for Smith</b>, his 5th in ODIs, Dilshan drifts one down leg-side, Smith gets inside the line and paddles it very fine, beats the diving short-fine fielder and races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to S Smith, no run, <b>almost a caught and bowled</b>, this was flighted and on the stumps, Smith was looking to work it towards the on-side, closed the face of the bat a tad too early, the leading edge pops up in the air and goes periliously close to the diving bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to S Smith, no run, tossed up and on off, worked towards silly mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Clarke, 1 run, excellent stop from Malinga at backward square leg, this was short and well down leg-side, Clarke rocked back on the pull, Malinga runs across to his left, puts in the dive and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to S Smith, 1 run, more good use of the feet, this time by Clarke, clipped away towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Clarke, 1 run, pushed through on the leg-stump line, Clarke comes down the track and works it towards deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Clarke, 1 run, this one is given more air, Clarke comes down the track and drives it past the non-striker, Smith veered away from the line and silly mid-on can't get across to stop the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Clarke, no run, this one is given more air and just outside off, Clarke comes down the track and drives it to the right of cover, Dilshan makes a diving stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, 1 run, Smith comes down the track and whips a flighted delivery towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Prasanna, drops one short and gets it to skid outside off, Smith backs away, makes room and cuts it square behind point, races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Clarke, 1 run, this one is given more air and just outside off, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Clarke, no run, Clarke comes down the track to a flighted delivery and works it straight to the fielder at mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Clarke, 1 run, Clarke shimmies down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and eases it down towards long-on, <b>brings up Australia's 100</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Clarke, no run, tossed up and on off, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to S Smith, 1 run, nicely done by Smith, shuffles across his crease, gets halfway down on the knee and laps it behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Clarke, 1 run, flatter and on off, punched down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Clarke, 2 runs, pushed through by Dilshan, Clarke goes back and nudges it behind square on the on-side, they decide to take on Malinga and get back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Clarke, no run, tossed up and on off, Clarke comes down the track and drives it straight to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, no run, Smith comes down the track, takes the ball on the full and drives it straight to MJ at silly mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, no run, Smith comes down the track to a well flighted delivery and drives it straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, no run, slower and just outside off, Smith presses forward in defence]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, 2 runs, Prasanna drops one shorter and wider outside off, Smith makes room and cracks it square past point, Malinga gets across from sweeper and puts his boot across, stops the ball from hitting the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, no run, tossed up and just outside off, punched back towards the bowler, he dives across and stops a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, no run, Smith comes down the track to a well flighted delivery and drives it straight to the fielder at mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Clarke, <b>FOUR</b>, that's nicely played by Clarke, fraction fuller and just outside off, right in the slot for Clarke, he gets well forward and swings it through the line, clears mid-on, one bounce and over the ropes for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to S Smith, 1 run, back of a length and some extra bounce for Perera, Smith adjusts well, opens the face of the bat and runs it down towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Clarke, 1 run, on a good length and well outside off, Clarke was pressing forward, arrests his movement and slaps it square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to S Smith, 1 run, full and wide from Perera, Smith leans into the drive and caresses it towards deep cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to S Smith, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Smith plays with an angled bat and dabs it to the left of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to S Smith, no run, on a length and just outside off, Smith prods forward and pushes it towards short cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, 1 run, fraction short and well outside off, spins away after pitching, Smith makes room and carves it towards sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, no run, this one is given more air, Smith presses forward and drops it at his feet]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, no run, this one is drifted on off, driven to the right of silly mid-on, the fielder dives and saves a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, no run, slower and just outside off, Smith prods forward and blocks it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, no run, flighted and on the stumps, turned towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, no run, Smith uses his feet and comes down the track, whips it to the left of mid-wicket where Mathews makes a tumbling stop]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Clarke, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Clarke presses forward and drives it towards short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to S Smith, 1 run, back of a length and on Smith's hips, tucked to the left of square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Clarke, 1 run, short and on the stumps, Clarke swivels across and pulls it behind square on the on-side, the fielder gets across quickly and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to S Smith, 1 run, on a length and on Smith's pads, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to S Smith, no run, the slower ball from Perera, he rolled his fingers around it, goes wide and well outside off, draws Smith into the drive and beats the inside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to S Smith, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, Smith presents the full face of the bat and drives it towards mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[The track at the SCG is dry and that is surprising as in recent times, the groundsmen have left a bit of grass on the wicket. This wicket is similar to what one used to see at the SCG in the 1990s and early 2000s. Sri Lanka won't be complaining for sure.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Malinga, then gave the chance for Finch to free his arms and he duly collected a boundary. Finch is comfortable when he plays back of a length bowling. Interestingly, it was Sachithra Senanayake, the off-spinner, who took the new ball at the other end. It is likely to do with the fact that David Warner and Finch thrive on pace on the ball and Senanayake can skid it off the surface with the new ball. It was Malinga though, who took advantage of Warner going hard at the ball by deceiving him with a slower one and snared his wicket. Finch in an attempt to take on Seekkuge Prasanna came down the wicket and was stumped. However, Smith and Michael Clarke looked to steady Australia's innings.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here is <b>Bharath Ramaraj's</b> analysis of the first 18 overs: Lasith Malinga generated swing in the first over of the innings and should have taken the wicket of Aaron Finch as he edged a delivery that flew more through the vacant second slip. Surprisingly, Angelo Mathews decided to do away with the second slip after the first delivery and Finch survived. In ODIs, it has become imperative to take wickets upfront.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Clarke, no run, flatter delivery on the off stump, Clarke defends from the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, 1 run, on the stumps, Smith comes down the track and works it deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, no run, allows the ball to spin away and punches it to extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Clarke, 1 run, use of the feet to get to the pitch of the ball and Clarke flicks it through square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Clarke, no run, fullish and on the stumps, Clarke defends well off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[Silly mid-on comes in]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, 1 run, tossed up outside off stump, driven to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Seekkuge Prasanna [3.0-0-14-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to S Smith, 1 run, on the off stump, Smith flicks it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to S Smith, no run, shortish and just outside off stump, Smith defends off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Clarke, 1 run, back of a length outside off stump, Clarke hangs back and guides it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to S Smith, 1 run, gets across the stumps and flicks the good length delivery to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to S Smith, no run, back of a length, blocked]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to S Smith, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Smith looks to run it to third man, but gets it on the inside-half of the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Clarke, 2 runs, rocks back and cuts the flatter ball to deep extra-cover, they run two, the call was 'keeper's keeper's' from Sanga but Malinga threw it to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Clarke, no run, Clarke is opened by the drift away from him on this slider, get a thickish edge that rolls towards short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to S Smith, 1 run, bit of drift into Smith on this flighted delivery, but he does well to drive it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Clarke, 1 run, steps out and flicks the flighted delivery to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Clarke, no run, the carrom ball outside off stump, cut to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Clarke, no run, flatter delivery on the leg stump, punched to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to S Smith, no run, just a bit of shape back into the right-hander on this good length delivery, Smith defends it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, overpitched and put away. He's looking very good, Steve Smith. Full and outside off stump, Smith plays a lovely on-drive, mid-on was too square and he had no chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Clarke, 1 run, on a length and on the off stump, Clarke works it through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to S Smith, 1 run, Smith looks to drive, but the bat turns in his hands and it goes to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Clarke, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Clarke cuts it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Clarke, no run, good length delivery outside off stump, Clarke defends it to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Thisara Perera, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to S Smith, no run, shortish and outside off stump, Smith cuts it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Clarke, 1 run, short and down the leg-side, pulled away through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Clarke, no run, steps out and misses the flick, the ball goes to mid-wicket off the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Clarke, no run, short enough for Clarke to hang back and defend]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to S Smith, 1 run, flatter ball, punched to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to S Smith, no run, advances and defends it to the right of the bowler, who deflects the ball to the right with a dive, the ball goes wide of silly mid-on as well but they don't take the run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Clarke, 2 runs, the inside-out drive past extra-cover and long-off runs to his left to tidy up]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, 1 run, flatter delivery on the leg stump, punched to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Clarke, 1 run, Prasanna bowls this one wide outside off stump as Clarke gives him the charge, but Clarke manages to play a lovely cover-drive to deep cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, 1 run, waits for the ball to spin away and drives it to long-off. Good use of the feet again]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Clarke, 1 run, steps out and takes it on the full, driven to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, 1 run, tossed up, driven to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Silly mid-on is in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Clarke, no run, flighted delivery on the off stump, Clarke nudges it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to S Smith, 1 run, on the leg stump, driven to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Clarke, 1 run, dances down the track and drives it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to S Smith, 1 run, steps out and flicks the flighted delivery along the ground to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to S Smith, no run, slower through the air, defended off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Clarke, 1 run, flighted delivery on the off stump, Clarke flicks it along the ground to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sachithra Senanayake [3.0-0-18-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Clarke, 1 run, goes deep in the crease and punches the flatter ball to deep cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, 1 run, shortish and outside off stump, punched along the ground to deep point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to S Smith, no run, tossed up just outside off stump, Smith defends it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Clarke, 1 run, pushed along the ground to sweeper cover and Clarke is off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Clarke, no run, loud appeal for <b>LBW</b>, but again, very optimistic from Sri Lanka. Clarke steps out and looks to defend, gets hit on the pad and the impact was outside off stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Clarke, no run, tossed up outside off stump, left alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, hit on the rise and hit very well again! Good length delivery outside off stump, Smith drives with an angled bat and sends it through cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, punched by Smith, Dilshan runs to his left and makes a good one-handed save at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, wonderful hit from Smith! Full and in the slot, Smith doesn't try to overhit the ball, just waits for the ball and plays a very good straight-drive to move into double-figures]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, no run, back of a length, punched off the back foot to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, no run, good length delivery outside off stump, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, no run, good length delivery well outside off stump, Smith shoulders arms]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Clarke, no run, spinning away outside off stump, Clarke cuts it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Clarke, no run, flighted delivery just outside off stump, Clarke drives it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Michael Clarke, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Leg slip and short mid-wicket in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Finch, <b>out</b> Stumped!! Clever bowling from Prasanna, saw Finch advancing and bowled this down the leg-side, Finch tried to adjust and nudge it into the on-side, but the ball only managed to brush the thigh pad. Sanga takes it well to his left, he was blinded by the batsman a bit but he had it covered and whipped the bails off as Finch was a long way down the wicket. <b>Prasanna gets a wicket in his first over on World Cup debut</b>. <b>Finch st Sangakkara b S Prasanna 24(24) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[S Prasanna to Finch, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Stumped!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Finch has been <b>stumped</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Finch, no run, flatter and close to the off stump, Finch cuts and picks out backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Finch, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a gift! Short and down the leg-side, Finch gets down on one knee and helps it on its way very fine to the fine leg boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Prasanna to Finch, no run, flighted delivery just outside off stump, driven back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Seekkuge Prasanna, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, no run, shuffles across to off and pushes it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, no run, defended off the front foot towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, no run, good length delivery outside off stump, Smith shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, no run, good length delivery from Mathews, Smith misses the drive, the ball hits him on the back leg, impact was outside off stump and height was an issue as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[Optimistic shout for LBW. The impact seemed to be outside off stump. Oh no! He's reviewed it. Poor call I guess! Anyway, let's see. No problems with the no-ball, no inside edge as well. Looks outside off stump to me. This is where common sense has to prevail. They are taking a long time to check for the inside edge, when the impact was the main issue there. Well, <b>they didn't show the Hawk-Eye</b>, and the on-field decision stays. The third umpire assumed there was an inside edge and didn't go for the Hawk-Eye. There was a very small spike on the Snicko, but seemed like it wasn't the edge.]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, no run, length ball well outside off stump, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Finch, 3 runs, gentle full ball outside off stump, Finch drives it along the ground through mid-on, the fielder gives chase and saves one]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Angelo Mathews, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to S Smith, no run, this is close to the back of a length region, Smith defends well off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to S Smith, no run, defends the good length delivery to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to S Smith, no run, not close enough to make Smith play]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to S Smith, no run, covers the stumps and allows the fuller length delivery go through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to S Smith, no run, good length delivery outside off stump, Smith defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to S Smith, 2 runs, full and outside off stump, Smith drives it towards extra-cover, the fielder at short cover couldn't get there with the dive, Senanayake runs to his left from mid-off and only manages to half-stop the ball, Finch wants the second run and he races back in time]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Finch, no run, slowish and on the off stump, Finch defends off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Finch, no run, flighted delivery on the off stump, Finch defends well off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to S Smith, 1 run, dances down the track and takes flighted delivery on the full before driving it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Finch, 3 runs, too short and outside off stump, Finch rocks back and cuts it to sweeper cover. Not the ideal ball with the field set]]></line><line><![CDATA[The leg slip has been moved to backward square leg.]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Finch, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball! Down the leg-side, Finch gets down on one knee and sweeps it to the right of the man at backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Finch, no run, tossed up outside off stump, defended off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, excellent shot from Smith. Fullish and outside off stump, Smith leans forward, there was a bit of outswing but he had it covered. Played the perfect cover-drive and beat the fielder's dive as well. Nice way to get off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to S Smith, no run, very full and on the stumps, Smith flicks it wide of mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to S Smith, no run, slower ball yorker, Smith keeps it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to S Smith, no run, good length delivery just outside off stump, Smith defends off the front foot. This time he doesn't walk across the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[Leg slip in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to S Smith, <b>wide</b>, Smith goes a long way across the stumps, Malinga tries the to bowl this full ball on the leg stump, but it goes down the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Steven Smith, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shane Watson will bat in the middle-order.]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Warner, <b>out</b> Caught by S Prasanna!! Malinga takes the pace off and he has his man. Warner was totally deceived by the lack of pace. Excellent slower ball on a good length, Warner goes early into the push, goes with hard hands and ends up chipping it straight to the fielder at cover, who takes a simple catch. Not the start Australia wanted after opting to bat first. <b>Warner c S Prasanna b Malinga 9(12) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Malinga to Warner, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Warner, no run, fine yorker on the leg stump, Warner digs it out to square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Finch, no run, bit of extra bounce on this flighted delivery, but Finch manages to handle it well off the back foot as he fends it to the right of short leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Warner, 1 run, gets down on one knee and sweeps this flighted delivery to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Warner, no run, flatter delivery on the off stump, Warner defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Warner, no run, Warner looks to force it through the off-side again, but gets it on the inside half of the bat and it rolls back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, nice shot! Flighted delivery just outside off stump, Warner steps out, also gives himself a bit of room and plays a lovely inside-out drive over extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Finch, 1 run, slight hesitation, but Warner gets to the other end easily in the end. Flighted delivery outside off stump, Finch defends it towards cover-point, Warner was late to respond but the fielder was well wide of the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Finch, 1 run, soft hands while defending this short of length delivery to extra-cover and that gives him an easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[The fielder at short extra-cover has been moved to cover-point now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Finch, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Finch drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Finch, no run, soft outside edge! Fullish and just swinging away outside off stump, Finch plays with an angled bat, the ball rolls to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Finch, <b>FOUR</b>, cracking shot from Finch. That should get him going. Short of a length delivery wide outside off stump, Finch frees his arms and plays a front foot drive through point and it races away]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Finch, no run, keeps this good length delivery very close to the off stump, Finch defends well]]></line><line><![CDATA[There is a man at short extra-cover as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Finch, no run, good length delivery swinging away outside off stump, Finch defends off the front foot to point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Now there are two slips in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Finch, 3 runs, down the leg-side again, Finch glances it fine to fine leg for three]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Finch, no run, Finch goes for the drive and gets an inside edge to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Finch, no run, was that <b>dropped</b>? No! Flighted delivery down the leg-side, Finch misses the sweep, the ball hits the pad and then takes the glove on its way to the keeper, Sanga dives low and forward but the ball died down immediately]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Finch, no run, stays round the wicket to the right-hander as well, flighted delivery on the stumps, defended]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Warner, 1 run, shortish and on the off stump, punched off the back foot to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and a short leg in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Warner, no run, starts off from round the wicket, flatter delivery on the off stump, defended into the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sachithra Senanayake, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Wow! A spinner to take the new ball.]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Warner, 3 runs, 'yes' is the call from Warner after gently pushing this good length delivery through cover-point and he quickly races back to complete three runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Warner, no run, Warner slices the drive as he loses his bottom hand grip. The fullish ball is fielded well by the man at cover, who dives to his right to stop the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Warner, no run, on a length and around the off stump, Warner defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Warner, no run, very full and swinging back in, Warner digs it out to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Finch, 1 run, <b>edgeddd</b> and <b>dropped</b>. That's a tough chance. There were two slips in place for the first ball, but before this ball, Mathews removed the second slip fielder and it would have gone straight to him. Good length delivery swinging away outside off stump, Finch defends way away from the body and gets a thick edge, Jayawardene dives full length to his right but could only get his fingertips]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Finch, no run, Malinga starts off with a gentle loosener on a fuller length and outside off stump, Finch softly drives it to mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Finch and Warner are at the crease. Finch is on strike. Malinga will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[There are two slips in place. The countdown begins. Australia v Sri Lanka, here we go...]]></line><line><![CDATA[Both the lovely anthems are done. The Sri Lankan team gets into a huddle. The Australian openers stride out.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The teams are out for the anthems. Sri Lanka's "<b>Sri Lanka Matha</b>", is followed by Australia's, "<b>Advance Australia Fair</b>."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sri Lanka</b> (Playing XI): Lahiru Thirimanne, Tillakaratne Dilshan, Kumar Sangakkara(w), Mahela Jayawardene, Angelo Mathews(c), Dinesh Chandimal, Upul Tharanga, Thisara Perera, Seekkuge Prasanna, Sachithra Senanayake, Lasith Malinga]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Australia</b> (Playing XI): Aaron Finch, David Warner, Steven Smith, Michael Clarke(c), Shane Watson, Glenn Maxwell, James Faulkner, Brad Haddin(w), Mitchell Johnson, Mitchell Starc, Xavier Doherty]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Australia have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mathews</b>: "The batting unit has been really doing a great job in the past three games, hopefully they will continue and that's what we want as a team. Who gets set should go on to make a big one. And yeah, at SCG we've played pretty well in the past but that doesn't carry anything into this game. We've got to start afresh. Not really (asked if he was disappointed to lose the toss). The wicket will spin as, well right throughout the game. I think the spinners will come into play. But I think, if we bowl first or bat first doesn't matter as long as we keep them to chasable target. We've got three changes. Two injured, <b>Herath</b>, <b>Dimuth</b> and <b>Lakmal</b> go out, <b>Sachithra</b>, <b>Seekkuge</b>, <b>Tharanga</b> come in."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Clarke</b>: "Hopefully not (when asked if he would like to have a hit today). If I don't bat, it means we have played like we did in Perth, which is a great sign. Obviously a really big game for both teams. A sell-out crowd and the ground is in fantastic condition. All the Australian boys are really keen to get out here. We are going to have a bat. Get as many runs as we can. The wicket looks dry, I think change of pace and obviously spin is going to play a big part on this wicket. But, the outfield is very fast. So wickets in hand are going to be the key at the end of the innings for us. Couple of changes, <b> Shane Watson</b> comes in for <b>Mitchell Marsh</b>. <b>Xavier Doherty</b> comes in for <b>Josh Hazlewood</b>. You have to ask the selectors (smiles, when asked why they made two changes.) But that's the XI they feel is the best XI to help us win this game against the opposition. I think they've gone a little bit horses for courses. We've got, obviously experience in Watto in regards to coming back in, only playing two front-line fast-bowlers then you've got the experience of Shane Watson with the ball as well and I think it's going to spin. That's why Doey is coming in."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pitch Report</b>: "Can't wait for this game to start. The run-up is so smooth. The pitch looks an absolute cracker. Very, very flat, not too much of grass on it. Batting on this surface will be very good. The fast bowlers will get some swing early on and the spinners will get some purchase as well. Overall, both teams will score heavily," reckons <b>Damien Fleming</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Stat:</b> Mahela Jayawardene will be playing his 446th ODI. He is set to become the most capped Sri Lankan batsman, going past Sanath Jayasuriya. He is now second in the overall list, behind Sachin Tendulkar - who earned 463 caps.]]></line><line><![CDATA[When it comes to matches at the SCG, Sri Lanka surprisingly hold the edge over the Australians since the turn of the decade. They hold a 4-2 winning record with one match washed out.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-head record:</b> Australia have never lost to Sri Lanka in a World Cup match since the 1996 final in Lahore. Overall, it's a commanding 6-1 record in favour of the men from the Kangaroo nation.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather Report:</b>  It's a cloudy day in Sydney. The temperature is expected to hover around 20 degrees with one or two spells of showers expected. But, it shouldn't play a big role in the proceedings.]]></line><line><![CDATA[On the other hand, Sri Lanka have been hit by injuries. Dimuth Karunaratne was ruled out of the tournament and has been replaced by leg-spinner, Seekkugge Prasanna. Left-arm spinner, Rangana Herath, has been ruled out of today's match. It means one of Sachithra Senanayake or Prasanna might be featuring in the playing XI. There's also some talk about Sri Lanka playing an extra specialist batsman. In that case, Upul Tharanga, who came in as an injury replacement for Jeevan Mendis, is expected to slot into the middle-order.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Team News:</b> After struggling with injury concerns during the early stages of the tournament, Australia will now have a full roster of fifteen to select their playing XI. Shane Watson was surprisingly dropped for the match against Afghanistan and early reports indicate that he might be back for this game. With a dry surface expected, Xavier Doherty, might get his first match of the tournament. If Australia do make the two changes, Mitchell Marsh and Josh Hazlewood are two players expected to make way.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>So what lies ahead?</b> One of the biggest matches of Pool A, the winner of this match will in all probability finish second in the pool. That sets them up for a clash with one of Pakistan or Ireland, depending on the result of the match between those two teams on March 15th. On the other hand, the loser will perhaps end up facing South Africa in the quarter-finals, something that the two teams wouldn't want, so early in the knock-out stages.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>The Pitch:</b> Australia's strength has been the dominant form of their pacers and it's no surprise that they were taken aback at the dry nature of the SCG surface. 'Looking at the pitch, if we had to play today, the toss would be crucial. But a day of sun on the pitch and a bit of rolling tomorrow might make it a little bit different," was Michael Clarke's assessment of the pitch. Surely, Sri Lanka couldn't have asked for a friendlier wicket than the one that they are expected to play on today.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Skipper, <b>Angelo Mathews</b>, is confident about putting up a good show. "Recently when we clashed against the Australians in England, we beat them. In Australia as well, I remember a few years ago. So we have the capacity and we have the skill," he said, during the pre-match conference.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sri Lanka:</b> The sub-continental giants are slowly peaking at the right time. After a poor start where they lost to red-hot New Zealand, Angelo Mathews' men have reeled off three straight wins, a hard-fought one against Afghanistan followed by two cruises against Bangladesh and England respectively. They haven't been tested recently though - and that test will come up when they square up against Johnson, Starc and Co.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Another factor that has bogged down the hosts is the amount of travelling. Despite being co-hosts, they have clocked the second most air-miles amongst all the teams in the tournament. Finch though refused to complain, adding that it was part and parcel of being professional cricketers. "It's been difficult. Anytime you're changing time zones as dramatic as Auckland to Perth, it's quite tough. But we did everything possible to counteract that. There's really no excuse for the boys not to be fresh for the game. It's the World Cup. You embrace everything about it, you don't complain, you just get on with it," Finch said.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The hosts are aware of the challenge that Sri Lanka is likely to pose. This is what opening batsman, <b>Aaron Finch</b>, had to say. "This is a big game, it's important. You don't want to finish in the bottom two in your group. It does make it a little bit harder in your path to the final, if you go that far (as to lose on Sunday)."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Australia</b>: It hasn't been smooth riding for the red-hot favorites. After a convincing win over England in the opener, rain robbed them of a potentially easy win against Bangladesh. Deprived of match-practice, they crashed to a nail-biting one-wicket loss against New Zealand in Auckland. Back on their home turf, they bossed around an inexperienced Afghan unit to get their campaign back on track. Sri Lanka is a different challenge all-together and is perhaps one team that hasn't been cowed down by the Aussies on their home turf.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>13:10 Local Time, 02:10 GMT, 07:40 IST:</b> It's super Sunday and it can't get better with two traditional powerhouses up against each other in a key World Cup match. Hosts Australia take on Sri Lanka in a match that might well decide the second place in Pool A. Both teams are coming into this game on the back of convincing wins. Australia set a World Cup record by scoring 417 and then dismissed Afghanistan for 142, thereby recording a 275-run win, the biggest in World Cups. On the other hand, Sri Lanka made light of a challenging target set by England, chasing down 309 for the loss of just one wicket. Sparks are certain to fly as the two teams meet each other at the Sydney Cricket Ground (SCG). Before we go any further, here's the form map of both teams]]></line><line><![CDATA[Preview by <b>G Rajaraman</b><br/><br/>The Sydney Cricket Ground pitch confounded Australia and Sri Lanka on the eve of their ICC Cricket World Cup Group A clash on Sunday. Yet, the opponents, whose predecessors rarely ignored the chance to bring needle into play, have promised to deliver a high-voltage game, irrespective of how the pitch pans out.<br/><br/>Australia captain Michael Clarke said spin would play a big part since the SCG pitch looked dry; Sri Lanka's Angelo Mathews pointed out that the track had looked different each day over the past three days. Soon, the Sri Lankans were watching the groundstaff give the track a spray of water, sprinkled some blades of grass and rolled them in.<br/><br/>With Clarke praising Kumar Sangakkara and speaking highly of Sri Lanka and with Mathews talking of the co-hosts as being hard to beat, Saturday was not the time to look for the needle that existed the last time when a team from the Emerald Isle beat Australia in a World Cup game back in the 1996 final at Lahore.<br/><br/>Of course, this is only a league game, with the teams fighting for second place in the group behind New Zealand. At stake is the chance to avoid India or South Africa in the quarterfinals but both skippers have pointed out that instead of trying to avoid a side, it would be better to reconcile to the fact that to win the World Cup, a team will have to beat the best opposition.<br/><br/>Clarke, in the limelight because of his high-profile rehabilitation from injury and his run-in with Chairman of Selectors Rod Marsh, and Mathews would rather focus on Sunday's match so that they could sustain the winning momentum as the business end of the World Cup draws close. Clarke admitted that he had enough to worry about without looking at the weather.<br/><br/>For, Australia's campaign has acquired a start-stop-restart look and Clarke is hoping that his team will carry the momentum from the massive victory over Afghanistan in Perth while Sri Lanka overcame the opening game defeat by New Zealand to post three straight wins against Afghanistan, Bangladesh and England.<br/><br/>The teams are bound, however, by issues of selection. Australia have come under some pressure from former captain Ricky Ponting who said the decision to drop Shane Watson from the XI left the middle-order short of experience. Clarke took refuge in the fact that he is not a selector and spoke glowingly about the team's senior-most allrounder.<br/><br/>Sri Lanka, on the contrary, have been hit by injury to left-arm spinner Rangana Herath and will need to consider recasting the composition of the XI a bit. Legspinner Seekkuge Prasanna could find himself a place ahead of 'mystery spinner' Sachithra Senanayake. The injury to Dimuth Karunaratne will possibly give Upul Tharana a chance to be one of the seven batsmen.<br/><br/>With Sri Lanka expecting a great deal of support - Mahela Jayawardena hoped that the Sri Lankans would outnumber the Australians in the stands on Sunday - SCG could be the apt stage for Mathews' team to post their first World Cup win over Australia in five matches. Their spinners, even if not first-choice, can seek to play on the minds of the home batsmen.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sri Lanka</b> (From): Tillakaratne Dilshan, Lahiru Thirimanne, Kumar Sangakkara(w), Mahela Jayawardene, Angelo Mathews(c), Dinesh Chandimal, Thisara Perera, Sachithra Senanayake, Seekkuge Prasanna, Lasith Malinga, Suranga Lakmal, Upul Tharanga, Nuwan Kulasekara, Rangana Herath, Dushmantha Chameera]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Australia</b> (From): Aaron Finch, David Warner, Steven Smith, Michael Clarke(c), Glenn Maxwell, Mitchell Marsh, Brad Haddin(w), James Faulkner, Mitchell Johnson, Mitchell Starc, Josh Hazlewood, Pat Cummins, George Bailey, Shane Watson, Xavier Doherty]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>376</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>9</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>50</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Australia">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1643</playerid>
					<name>Aaron Finch</name>
					<batsman-name>Finch</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Finch</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>24</runs>
					<balls>24</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[stumped]]></status>
					<bowler>S Prasanna</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8063</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Kumar Sangakkara</fielder>
						<fielderId>104</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1739</playerid>
					<name>David Warner</name>
					<batsman-name>Warner</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Warner</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Malinga</bowler>
					<bowlerId>111</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Seekkuge Prasanna</fielder>
						<fielderId>8063</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2250</playerid>
					<name>Steven Smith</name>
					<batsman-name>S Smith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Smith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>72</runs>
					<balls>88</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Dilshan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>105</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Thisara Perera</fielder>
						<fielderId>2281</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>138</playerid>
					<name>Michael Clarke</name>
					<batsman-name>Clarke</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Clarke</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>68</runs>
					<balls>68</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Malinga</bowler>
					<bowlerId>111</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7662</playerid>
					<name>Glenn Maxwell</name>
					<batsman-name>Maxwell</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Maxwell</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>102</runs>
					<balls>53</balls>
					<fours>10</fours>
					<sixes>4</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>T Perera</bowler>
					<bowlerId>2281</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Lasith Malinga</fielder>
						<fielderId>111</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>158</playerid>
					<name>Shane Watson</name>
					<batsman-name>Watson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Watson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>67</runs>
					<balls>41</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>T Perera</bowler>
					<bowlerId>2281</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dinesh Chandimal</fielder>
						<fielderId>6245</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7789</playerid>
					<name>James Faulkner</name>
					<batsman-name>Faulkner</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Faulkner</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Angelo Mathews</fielder>
						<fielderId>1629</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Thisara Perera</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>2281</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>159</playerid>
					<name>Brad Haddin</name>
					<batsman-name>Haddin</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Haddin</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>25</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mathews</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1629</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Thisara Perera</fielder>
						<fielderId>2281</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>496</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Johnson</name>
					<batsman-name>Johnson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Johnson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7710</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
					<batsman-name>M Starc</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Starc</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Thisara Perera</fielder>
						<fielderId>2281</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Angelo Mathews</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>1629</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7729</playerid>
					<name>Xavier Doherty</name>
					<batsman-name>Doherty</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Doherty</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1739</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>19</runs>
				<overs>4.2</overs>
				<batsman>David Warner</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Warner</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1643</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>41</runs>
				<overs>8.4</overs>
				<batsman>Aaron Finch</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Finch</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>138</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>175</runs>
				<overs>31.5</overs>
				<batsman>Michael Clarke</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Clarke</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>2250</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>177</runs>
				<overs>32.3</overs>
				<batsman>Steven Smith</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Smith</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7662</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>337</runs>
				<overs>46.1</overs>
				<batsman>Glenn Maxwell</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Maxwell</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7789</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>338</runs>
				<overs>46.3</overs>
				<batsman>James Faulkner</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Faulkner</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>158</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>368</runs>
				<overs>48.6</overs>
				<batsman>Shane Watson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Watson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>159</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>373</runs>
				<overs>49.3</overs>
				<batsman>Brad Haddin</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Haddin</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7710</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>374</runs>
				<overs>49.4</overs>
				<batsman>Mitchell Starc</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Starc</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>1</byes>
			<wides>4</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>6</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Sri Lanka">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>111</playerid>
					<name>Lasith Malinga</name>
					<bowler-name>Malinga</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Malinga</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>59</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6729</playerid>
					<name>Sachithra Senanayake</name>
					<bowler-name>Senanayake</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Senanayake</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>59</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1629</playerid>
					<name>Angelo Mathews</name>
					<bowler-name>Mathews</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mathews</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>59</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8063</playerid>
					<name>Seekkuge Prasanna</name>
					<bowler-name>S Prasanna</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Prasanna</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>77</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2281</playerid>
					<name>Thisara Perera</name>
					<bowler-name>T Perera</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>T Perera</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>87</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>105</playerid>
					<name>Tillakaratne Dilshan</name>
					<bowler-name>Dilshan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dilshan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>33</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6243</playerid>
					<name>Lahiru Thirimanne</name>
					<bowler-name>Thirimanne</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Thirimanne</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>104</playerid>
					<name>Kumar Sangakkara</name>
					<bowler-name>Sangakkara</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sangakkara</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>101</playerid>
					<name>Mahela Jayawardene</name>
					<bowler-name>M Jayawardene</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M Jayawardene</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6245</playerid>
					<name>Dinesh Chandimal</name>
					<bowler-name>Chandimal</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chandimal</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>414</playerid>
					<name>Upul Tharanga</name>
					<bowler-name>U Tharanga</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Tharanga</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>312</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>10</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>46.2</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Sri Lanka">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>6243</playerid>
					<name>Lahiru Thirimanne</name>
					<batsman-name>Thirimanne</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Thirimanne</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Johnson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>496</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Brad Haddin</fielder>
						<fielderId>159</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>105</playerid>
					<name>Tillakaratne Dilshan</name>
					<batsman-name>Dilshan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dilshan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>62</runs>
					<balls>60</balls>
					<fours>8</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Faulkner</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7789</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>104</playerid>
					<name>Kumar Sangakkara</name>
					<batsman-name>Sangakkara</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sangakkara</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>104</runs>
					<balls>107</balls>
					<fours>11</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Faulkner</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7789</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Aaron Finch</fielder>
						<fielderId>1643</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>101</playerid>
					<name>Mahela Jayawardene</name>
					<batsman-name>M Jayawardene</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M Jayawardene</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>19</runs>
					<balls>22</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Michael Clarke</fielder>
						<fielderId>138</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1629</playerid>
					<name>Angelo Mathews</name>
					<batsman-name>Mathews</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mathews</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>35</runs>
					<balls>31</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Watson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>158</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Brad Haddin</fielder>
						<fielderId>159</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6245</playerid>
					<name>Dinesh Chandimal</name>
					<batsman-name>Chandimal</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chandimal</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>52</runs>
					<balls>24</balls>
					<fours>8</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[retired out]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2281</playerid>
					<name>Thisara Perera</name>
					<batsman-name>T Perera</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>T Perera</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>8</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Johnson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>496</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Xavier Doherty</fielder>
						<fielderId>7729</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>414</playerid>
					<name>Upul Tharanga</name>
					<batsman-name>U Tharanga</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Tharanga</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Faulkner</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7789</bowlerId>
						<fielder>David Warner</fielder>
						<fielderId>1739</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8063</playerid>
					<name>Seekkuge Prasanna</name>
					<batsman-name>S Prasanna</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Prasanna</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>M Starc</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7710</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6729</playerid>
					<name>Sachithra Senanayake</name>
					<batsman-name>Senanayake</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Senanayake</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>7</runs>
					<balls>8</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Starc</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7710</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Xavier Doherty</fielder>
						<fielderId>7729</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>111</playerid>
					<name>Lasith Malinga</name>
					<batsman-name>Malinga</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Malinga</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6243</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>5</runs>
				<overs>1.4</overs>
				<batsman>Lahiru Thirimanne</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Thirimanne</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>105</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>135</runs>
				<overs>21.3</overs>
				<batsman>Tillakaratne Dilshan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dilshan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>101</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>188</runs>
				<overs>31</overs>
				<batsman>Mahela Jayawardene</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Jayawardene</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>104</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>201</runs>
				<overs>33.5</overs>
				<batsman>Kumar Sangakkara</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Sangakkara</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1629</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>283</runs>
				<overs>41.3</overs>
				<batsman>Angelo Mathews</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mathews</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>2281</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>293</runs>
				<overs>42.2</overs>
				<batsman>Thisara Perera</batsman>
				<batsman-name>T Perera</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8063</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>305</runs>
				<overs>44.3</overs>
				<batsman>Seekkuge Prasanna</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Prasanna</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>414</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>307</runs>
				<overs>45.2</overs>
				<batsman>Upul Tharanga</batsman>
				<batsman-name>U Tharanga</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6729</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>312</runs>
				<overs>46.2</overs>
				<batsman>Sachithra Senanayake</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Senanayake</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>2</byes>
			<wides>4</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>5</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>11</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Australia">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7710</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
					<bowler-name>M Starc</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Starc</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8.2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>29</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>496</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Johnson</name>
					<bowler-name>Johnson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Johnson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>62</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>158</playerid>
					<name>Shane Watson</name>
					<bowler-name>Watson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Watson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>71</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7729</playerid>
					<name>Xavier Doherty</name>
					<bowler-name>Doherty</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Doherty</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>60</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7662</playerid>
					<name>Glenn Maxwell</name>
					<bowler-name>Maxwell</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Maxwell</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>6</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7789</playerid>
					<name>James Faulkner</name>
					<bowler-name>Faulkner</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Faulkner</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>48</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1643</playerid>
					<name>Aaron Finch</name>
					<bowler-name>Finch</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Finch</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1739</playerid>
					<name>David Warner</name>
					<bowler-name>Warner</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Warner</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2250</playerid>
					<name>Steven Smith</name>
					<bowler-name>S Smith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Smith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>138</playerid>
					<name>Michael Clarke</name>
					<bowler-name>Clarke</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Clarke</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>159</playerid>
					<name>Brad Haddin</name>
					<bowler-name>Haddin</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Haddin</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



