<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14652" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>Qualifier 2</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Chennai</home>
		<away>Bangalore</away>
		<teamsabbr>CHN vs BLR</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>CHN</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>BLR</awayabbr>
		<homeId>58</homeId>
		<awayId>59</awayId>
		<venue>JSCA International Stadium Complex, Ranchi</venue>
		<startdate>22 05 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>22 05 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Chennai</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Chennai won by 3 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Chennai</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>3</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Anil Chaudhary</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Chris Gaffaney</Name>
			<Country>NZ</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Chettithody Shamsuddin</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Roshan Mahanama</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>14:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150522181014</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>CHN</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>BLR</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>140</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>7</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>19.5</batteamovers>
		<status>Chennai won by 3 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>587</playerid>
			<name>Ravindra Jadeja*</name>
			<batsman-name>R Jadeja</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>0</runs>
			<balls-faced>0</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>1593</playerid>
			<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
			<batsman-name>Ashwin</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Ashwin</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>1</runs>
			<balls-faced>1</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>8175</playerid>
			<name>Harshal Patel*</name>
			<bowler-name>Harshal Patel</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Harshal Patel</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>3.5</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>26</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>7710</playerid>
			<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
			<bowler-name>M Starc</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Starc</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>27</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>140</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>265</playerid>
<name>MS Dhoni</name>
<player-runs>26</player-runs>
<player-balls>29</player-balls>
<runs>139</runs>
<wicket-nbr>7</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>8175</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Harshal Patel</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>3</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[1 1 W 2 B3 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 6 2 Wd 1 1 2 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 1 1 2 W W <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>2 . 2 W 1 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/CHN_BLR_MAY22/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[BLR would rue the fact that their fielding was below par and they missed a few chances.  Earlier on in the day, Ashish Nehra and Ravichandran Ashwin bowled with unrelenting control and were rewarded with wickets. CHN now will take on MUM in the grand final of this season's IPL at the Eden Gardens. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Michael Hussey played with calmness and composure to guide CHN to the final. On a track that assisted the spinners, Hussey's wisdom of experience proved to be the telling difference. He rotated the strike before checking in glorious shots off Yuzvendra Chahal in the 16th over to put CHN in a pole position. It got a bit tense in the end, especially with MS Dhoni losing his wicket in the final over, but CHN held their nerve to usurp their formidable foes.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The fireworks go off at Ranchi. Hugs and smiles in the CHN camp. Plenty of glum faces among the BLR players. Kohli and ABD walk off together. The CHN players come out and shake hands with their opposition.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Ashwin, 1 run, <b>CHN are in the final for the 6th time.</b> Ashwin was cool as ever, he walks across his stumps and flicks it through backward square]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dhoni, <b>out</b> Caught by D Karthik!! Well, well, well. Is there still a twist in this game? Full and around off, Dhoni goes for the drive, the outside edge is gobbled up Karthik. He was looking to finish it in style and paid the price. Kohli hares across towards the bowler, he still believes that the game is alive. <b>Dhoni c D Karthik b Harshal Patel 26(29) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Harshal Patel to Dhoni, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dhoni, 2 runs, full and outside off, Dhoni drives wide of long-off, Kohli runs to his left, dives and makes a fine stop, a fine throw right on top of the stumps, Dhoni had made it in even as DK whipped the bails off]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire pressed into service. Dhoni looks to be in. He is and that should be Not Out.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dhoni, no run, banged in halfway down the wicket, Dhoni toe-ends the pull to short mid-wicket, Jadeja was going for the run but is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dhoni, 2 runs, too full and just outside off, Dhoni squeezes it to long-off, Kohli makes a slight fumble and Jadeja called Dhoni for the second. That was poor from the BLR skipper]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Harshal has his task cut out. CHN need 5 to win and Dhoni is on strike.]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Bravo, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Knocked over! The off-stump takes a walk back. Starc comes round the wicket, bowls it full and gets it to straighten, Bravo was playing for the angle, he misses and the off-stump is broken into half. A bit too late for BLR though as CHN are one hit away from sealing the game. <b>Dwayne Bravo b Starc 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to Dwayne Bravo, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dhoni, <b>out</b> Negi Run Out!! Sarfaraz hits the bulls-eye. Yorker around off, Dhoni squeezes it to cover and calls for a risky single, Sarfaraz collects the ball and fires a direct-hit at the striker's end to catch Negi well short of the crease. <b>Negi run out (Sarfaraz Khan) 12(6) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to Dhoni, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire called for a run-out chance. Negi is already walking back. He is OUT!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dhoni, 2 runs, sloppy from Starc, bowls the perfect yorker, Dhoni jams it back to the bowler, Starc tries to throw the ball before collecting, it deflects it to long-off, Negi comes back quickly for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Negi, 1 run, low full toss on off, Negi digs it out to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dhoni, 1 run, yorker around off, Dhoni squeezes it to cover, Negi was backing up too much, Sarfaraz has a shy at the bowler's end, Chahal can't back up correctly and a single is taken. Negi was a goner had that hit]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dhoni, <b>FOUR</b>, Dhoni has decided to finish the game. He gives the charge first ball, gets under it and tonks it over mid-off, he middled it superbly as the ball raced away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc [3.0-0-19-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[CHN need 13 off 12. They have this in the bag. Starc to bowl the 19th. Can he provide a bit of magic?]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Negi, 2 runs, pitched up outside off, Negi creams the drive past extra cover, Chahal couldn't get there with a dive, Starc runs to his left from sweeper cover, slides and keeps it to a double]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dhoni, 1 run, good length ball and slants in, Dhoni was winding up for the big hit, gets an inside edge onto the pad, the ball rolls to the right of the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Negi, 1 run, full and angling in, Negi kneels down and mistimes the big hit to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Negi, <b>wide</b>, wide yorker, it landed on the tramline, but the umpire still signals a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Negi, 2 runs, fuller and outside off, Negi drives past the diving extra cover fielder, they put pressure on the fielder and got it easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Negi, <b>SIX</b>, wow! What a hit from the young man. The slower delivery just outside off, Negi was expecting that, he heaves it across the line, middles it beautifully and sends it over mid-wicket for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dhoni, 1 run, short of length around off, Dhoni drops it with soft hands in front of point, quick single taken]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel [2.0-0-7-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>27 needed now off 18 balls. </b>With Dhoni at the crease, CHN should fancy their chances. Nothing seperating the two sides at this time, BLR were also 113]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Negi, no run, slower delivery on off, Negi defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Dhoni, byes, 3 runs, that was tough for DK, the ball kept low outside off, Dhoni misses the dab to third man, the ball goes through the legs of the keeper, Negi is quick to come back for the third]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Dhoni, 2 runs, short and width on offer, Dhoni cuts it late behind point, it was in the air but wide of backward point, Harshal tidies up near the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pawan Negi, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[After the wicket, BLR were in a huddle and it was ABD who was doing all the talking. He sure was pumped up.]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to M Hussey, <b>out</b> Caught by Harshal Patel!! Huge wicket for BLR. End of a fine innings from Mr. Cricket. He might have just done enough to put CHN ahead. Short delivery at the batsman, Hussey is hurried on the pull, mistimes it completely, the ball spoons to backward square where Harshal takes a simple catch. <b>M Hussey c Harshal Patel b Wiese 56(46) [4s-3 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Wiese to M Hussey, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Dhoni, 1 run, again, no pace on the ball, Dhoni knocks it to extra cover and hares across for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to M Hussey, 1 run, off-cutter on middle, Hussey waits and steers it to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese [3.0-0-26-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>34 runs needed off 24 balls.</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Hussey, 1 run, slower and around off, Hussey gets on top of the bounce, dabs it to backward point, quick single taken. A very good over for CHN, they have just moved ahead in the game]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Hussey, <b>SIX</b>, Hussey brings up his <b>fifty</b> in style. What a player. Big game and he stands up. Quicker delivery just outside off, Hussey kneels down and sends it soaring over long-on for the second six of the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Hussey, no run, googly outside off, Hussey skips out of the crease, drags it off the inside edge towards mid-wicket, Sarfaraz dives to his left and doesn't allow the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dhoni, 1 run, shortens the length and doesn't offer the room, Dhoni works it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Hussey, 1 run, again, comes down the track, almost yorks himself, squeezes the drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Hussey, <b>SIX</b>, fabulous shot! Punch of the gloves between both batsmen. It was tossed up outside off, Hussey shimmies down the wicket and smashes it over long-off for the first maximum of the innings]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to M Hussey, 1 run, full and tailing in, Hussey squeezes the flick to deep square leg. Sensible batting from both batsmen, they just wanted to play out Starc]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dhoni, 1 run, fifth single, slower delivery around off, Dhoni knocks it to cover and calls for the run]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to M Hussey, 1 run, another full ball from Starc, on off and middle, Hussey flicks it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dhoni, 1 run, pitched up just outside off, Dhoni gets forward and drives to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to M Hussey, 1 run, full and outside off, driven away to sweeper cover, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dhoni, 1 run, fuller and on off, Dhoni push-drives it down the wicket, ABD runs across from long-off and keeps it to one]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc [2.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dhoni, 1 run, Dhoni comes down the track, Chahal fires it in, Dhoni yorks himself and manages to squeeze it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Hussey, 1 run, googly around off, Hussey closes the bat face on the nudge, the leading edge lobs to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dhoni, 1 run, short and outside off, Dhoni slaps it hard and towards long-off, Virat keeps it down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dhoni, no run, shortens the length around off, Dhoni punches gently to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dhoni, no run, too full and on the pads, Dhoni digs it to the on-side, DK quickly gets across and stops the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dhoni, no run, flighted on middle, Dhoni presses forward and defends off the inner part to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuzvendra Chahal [2.0-0-10-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out.</b> BLR have done well to stay in the game. However, with a well set Hussey and a cool Dhoni, they know it is a tough job ahead. CHN, on the other hand, would want these two to take them home.]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Dhoni, 1 run, fraction short and outside off, Dhoni cuts towards third man, thought about two but decided against it]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to M Hussey, 1 run, full and on the pads, Hussey clips it behind square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to M Hussey, <b>FOUR</b>, poor delivery, deserved to be put away, short and down leg, Hussey gets inside the line and helps it on the way, fine leg was square and that was easy pickings]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to M Hussey, 2 runs, drops it short and outside off, Hussey guides it square on the off-side, once again good aggressive running ensures that they get two]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to M Hussey, no run, full toss on off, Hussey drags it towards mid-wicket, Sarfaraz dives to his right and makes a fine stop, saved a single there]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to M Hussey, 2 runs, too straight, on middle and leg, Hussey gets inside the line and flicks it to deep square leg, called for two straightaway and gets it comfortably]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sreenath Aravind [3.0-0-15-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to M Hussey, 1 run, fraction short and just outside off, Hussey cuts square of the wicket and retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Dhoni, 1 run, takes the pace off the ball once more, Dhoni reads it well and eases it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to M Hussey, 1 run, slower delivery outside off, Hussey chops it to the right of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to M Hussey, no run, back of a length on the stumps, Hussey wanted to help it on the way, gets it off the toe-end to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to M Hussey, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! It was overpitched outside off, Hussey gets a good stride forward and caresses it through extra cover, Starc at sweeper had no chance of stopping that. Perfect cover drive from Mr. Cricket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Dhoni, 1 run, short of length outside off, Dhoni glides it to third man, the ball got a bit big and went off the outside half of the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese [2.0-0-18-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to M Hussey, no run, the slower ball bouncer outside off, Hussey is way early into the pull, misses it by a distance. Good follow up over from Harshal]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dhoni, 1 run, back of a length outside off, Dhoni waits for the ball and cuts to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dhoni, no run, low full toss outside off, Dhoni reaches out and toe-ends the drive to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dhoni, no run, shortens the length and gets it to bounce a bit more, Dhoni gets up on his toes and defends back to Harshal]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dhoni, no run, slower delivery outside off, Dhoni presses forward and pushes it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to M Hussey, 1 run, starts round the wicket, fuller and around off, Hussey drives to mid-off and runs as soon as he played that]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel [1.0-0-5-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Hussey, 1 run, tossed up around off, Hussey eases it to deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Hussey, no run, beaten! Chahal is causing some trouble. This one goes straight on, Hussey plays for the turn, the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>MS Dhoni, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Raina, <b>out</b> Caught by Wiese!! This match is alive folks. Chahal has picked up the second of the over. It is the big wicket of Raina, who has been a thorn for BLR this IPL with two fifties. Flighted delivery just outside off, the wrong 'un, Raina comes down the track, doesn't get to the pitch of the ball but still goes through with the loft, didn't time it and picks out Wiese at long-off to perfection. <b>Raina c Wiese b Chahal 0(2)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chahal to Raina, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Raina, no run, too full and on off, Raina works it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to du Plessis, <b>out</b> Bowled!! A wicket straightaway after the break. Again Faf tries to pre-meditate and pays the price. He moves across his stumps, goes down on his knee and tries to play the lap sweep, misses and the leg-stump is pegged back. A timely wicket for BLR as this partnership was taking the game away from them. <b>du Plessis b Chahal 21(22) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chahal to du Plessis, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Hussey, 3 runs, top effort from Starc. Flighted outside off, Hussey lofts it inside out over extra cover, it was heading towards the rope, Starc puts in a full length dive, flicks it back in for the long-off fielder. No problems with his back there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>. CHN are cruising along nicely. This partnership has looked good, they have taken on the fielders and picked up sharp singles. BLR need wickets and plenty of them if they have to win it from here.]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, back-to-back boundaries to end the over, full delivery on the stumps, du Plessis squeezes the drive back past Hussey, he didn't time it well but the ball had enough to beat the long-on fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, cheeky! It was pre-meditated from Faf and he got full value. Shuffles across his stumps, kneels down and plays the scoop, the fielder at fine leg was very square and had no chance of stopping that]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to M Hussey, 1 run, off-cutter around off, Hussey knocks it wide of cover, ABD runs quickly across, under-arms the throw at the bowler's end, Hussey was well short had that hit]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to M Hussey, no run, on a length just outside off, Hussey cuts and fails to make contact, that didn't bounce as much as Hussey expected]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to du Plessis, 1 run, takes the pace off the ball, du Plessis eases it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to M Hussey, 1 run, full and width on offer, Hussey reaches out and lofts it on the bounce to deep cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Hussey, 1 run, Chahal keeps it flat and just outside off, punched down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to du Plessis, 1 run, pushed through and just outside off, chopped straight to the fielder at point, du Plessis calls for a quick single, the throw is at his end but he makes it safely]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to du Plessis, 2 runs, this was tossed up and well outside off, du Plessis drilled it to the left of long-off, Abdulla gets across and fumbles, allows the second run to be taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Hussey, 1 run, Chahal tosses one wider outside off, Hussey reaches out and slaps it past cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Hussey, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Hussey stays behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to du Plessis, 1 run, a better throw and Hussey was in huge trouble, AB threw off-balanced, this was very full and on the stumps, du Plessis was looking to drive and gets a thick inside edge to the right of mid-wicket. Hussey was very late in responding and is saved by the poor throw]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuzvendra Chahal, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to du Plessis, 1 run, length ball and on du Plessis' pads, worked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to du Plessis, <b>wide</b>, BLR are not happy, there was a big deflection there, du Plessis was looking to flick and missed, the umpire didn't spot the big deflection there, that's pretty poor by international standards]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to du Plessis, no run, Wiese keeps it on a good length and well outside off, dabbed straight to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to M Hussey, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, chopped behind point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Karthik goes back to his normal position]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to du Plessis, 1 run, on a good length and angling into du Plessis, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to M Hussey, 1 run, that will go down as a <b>chance</b>, but it was a tough one, that came right off the face of the bat as Hussey looked to dab it very fine. DK isn't happy with himself, if at all it was a chance, it was a very tough one]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to du Plessis, 1 run, on a length and angling into du Plessis, he shuffles across and works it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to du Plessis, <b>wide</b>, Wiese slips one well outside off, called as a wide]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to du Plessis, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, punched to the left of cover-point for a single, another tidy over from Aravind]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to du Plessis, no run, short of a length and just outside off, punched to the left of short extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to M Hussey, 1 run, on a good length and well outside off, driven to the right of mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to du Plessis, 3 runs, fuller length delivery and just outside off, du Plessis gets a big stride forward and lofts it over mid-on. Wiese gives the chase, tumbles and pulls the ball back in, saves a run for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to du Plessis, no run, Aravind is keeping it tight and just outside off, the slower ball as well, du Plessis pushes it in front of mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to M Hussey, 1 run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Hussey drives it to the right of mid-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to du Plessis, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, du Plessis was early into the drive, ends up closing the face and spoons it towards mid-on, goes to the fielder on the bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to du Plessis, no run, the slower ball from Harshal, du Plessis plays it late and looks to dab it past the keeper, gets it too close to Karthik though]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to du Plessis, no run, short of a length and well outside off, du Plessis reaches out and mistimes the cut towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to M Hussey, 1 run, another slower ball from Harshal, driven in front of mid-off for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to M Hussey, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Harshal, dropped it halfway down the track, Hussey is quick to swivel across and pulls it behind square on the on-side for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to M Hussey, no run, Harshal starts with a slower dipping delivery, Hussey was early into his push and is beaten, good start from Harshal]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to du Plessis, no run, short of a length and angling across du Plessis, he throws his bat at that and is beaten on the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to du Plessis, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, du Plessis presses forward in defence, the ball rolls away towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to du Plessis, no run, on a good length and on middle, du Plessis looks to flick and is struck high on the pads, the ball was going over the sticks]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to M Hussey, 1 run, nearly another! Patel was a bit late to run in there, the ball bounced just in front of him, short and on the stumps, Hussey swivelled across and pulled it behind square. Harshal rushed in but the ball got to him on the half-volley]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to du Plessis, 1 run, <b>Gayle has dropped a dolly at 1st slip</b>, Aravind has his hands on his head, short of a length and angling across du Plessis, he pushed at that, gets a thick edge and to the left of first slip, Gayle moves across and shells it]]></line><line><![CDATA[Karthik is up to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Faf du Plessis, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Dwayne Smith, <b>out</b> Caught by Starc!! Aravind has struck early! Smith can't believe but has to walk back to the hut. This was banged in short and on the stumps, Smith swivelled across on the pull, connects it beautifully but doesn't bother to keep it down. Starc was placed perfectly at deep square leg, he bends down and accepts the catch. Smith was looking aggressive but has to walk back to the hut. <b>Dwayne Smith c Starc b Aravind 17(12) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Aravind to Dwayne Smith, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, pushed to the right of mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four</b>, this was short and angling across Smith, he was looking to pull, gets a toe-edge to the right of Karthik and left of Gayle at 1st slip. Both dived, but the ball bisected them perfectly before racing away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to M Hussey, 1 run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, worked to the left of mid-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc is feeling his back, he was struggling in the last match as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to M Hussey, no run, fuller length delivery and on Hussey's pads, tucked straight to the fielder at mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, short of a length and on the stumps, nudged in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, that's nicely played by Smith, width outside off from Starc, Smith throws his bat at that and slices it high and over cover, the ball rolls away to the fence in a hurry]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, tad fuller and just outside off, Smith pushes it in front of mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a strange looking shot, but it earns Smith a boundary, short of a length and just outside off, Smith was looking to flat-bat it past the bowler. He stopped the shot, but gets enough to get it past mid-off and into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Dwayne Smith, no run, on a good length and a hint of angle across Smith, he shuffles across and defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to M Hussey, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, Hussey dabs it in front of cover-point for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to M Hussey, no run, tad fuller and shaping away from outside off, dabbed straight to the fielder at cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, on a good length and slanting across the right-hander, punched to the right of cover for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sreenath Aravind, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, leg byes, 1 run, the toe-crusher from Starc, gets the ball to swing back in late, Smith fell over on the flick and is struck on the pads, the batsmen sneak in a leg-bye though]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to M Hussey, 1 run, Starc shortens his length outside off, Hussey was late in bringing his bat down, gets an inside edge onto the pads, the ball rolls in front of point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to M Hussey, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Hussey dabs it in front of backward point, wants a single but is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to M Hussey, no run, lovely delivery from Starc, on a good length and a hint of shape away from off, draws Hussey forward and zips past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Smith pushes forward, closes the face of the bat and gets an inside edge past mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, no run, beaten! On a good length and a hint of nip back into Smith, he was playing way ahead of his body, the ball rushes past his inside edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Smith and M Hussey are at the crease. Dwayne Smith is on strike. Starc will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back. Kohli has plenty to say to his fielders. Can BLR defend 140? A slip is in place for Starc]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashwin:</b> "I think you have got to take the pace off the ball. You have to bowl really slow to get some purchase. It's really confusing, one side is dry and the other side is wet (talking about the dew). We set the right atmosphere to go out and express ourselves. It's a bit tricky as the wicket is slow, but if we bat well, we should chase it down."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nehra and Ravichandran Ashwin were the pick of the bowlers  for CHN. Their fielding too was on the money. Michael Hussey, in particular, took a blinder off Ashwin to dismiss Mandeep Singh.]]></line><line><![CDATA[On the back of a stellar performance by the bowlers, CHN restricted their opponents to a par score. It was Ashish Nehra who gave CHN the perfect start by snaring the wickets of Virat Kohli and AB de Villiers. Chris Gayle and Dinesh Karthik tried to steady the innings. However, just when Gayle looked to up the ante, Suresh Raina landed the decisive blow by sending him back to the pavilion. Sarfaraz  Khan then landed a few crucial blows to give BLR's bowlers something to bowl at. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Aravind, no run, full and fired across the left-hander, Aravind swings through the line and fails to connect. The batsmen don't try to risk running a bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sreenath Aravind, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Sarfaraz Khan, <b>out</b> Caught by Negi!! A fine knock comes to an end. The off-speed delivery doing the trick for Bravo, it was short and around off, Sarfaraz makes room and looks to pierce the off-side field, but his cut finds Negi at cover-point. <b>Sarfaraz Khan c Negi b Dwayne Bravo 31(21) [4s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dwayne Bravo to Sarfaraz Khan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Starc, 1 run, fullish and just outside off, Starc drives towards extra cover and picks up a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Harshal Patel, <b>wide</b>, <b>out</b> Harshal Patel Run Out!! Dhoni hits direct to send back Harshal. Slower delivery goes wrong for Bravo, well outside off, umpire signals it a wide, Harshal wanted to bring Sarfaraz back on strike, he goes but Sarfaraz was not interested, MS takes his time before hitting timber. <b>Harshal Patel run out (Dhoni) 2(2)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dwayne Bravo to Harshal Patel, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Sarfaraz Khan, 1 run, tries to be cheeky, slower one from Bravo, Sarfaraz goes for the reverse paddle, doesn't middle it and the ball rolls towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Sarfaraz Khan, <b>FOUR</b>, Bravo drops it short and outside off, Sarfaraz stands tall and drills it off the back foot over extra cover, Smith at long-off had no chance of cutting that off]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Harshal Patel, 1 run, Harshal comes down the track, takes it on the full and drags it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Sarfaraz Khan, no run, <b>run-out chance missed!</b> Back of a length on the stumps, Sarfaraz moves away and mistimes the punch to cover, Harshal was going for the run before being sent back, Nehra was in a dilemma whether to throw or run across and whips the bails off, he throws and misses, Harshal gets back in]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Sarfaraz Khan, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! Length delivery on the stumps, Sarfaraz leans forward and uses his wrists, flicks it over mid-wicket, one bounce and over the rope. The timing on that was sublime]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Harshal Patel, 1 run, good length ball on off, Harshal backs away and drives to mid-off, brisk single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Sarfaraz Khan, 1 run, shortish and around off, Sarfaraz flat-bats it to long-on, only a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Wiese, <b>out</b> Caught by Dwayne Bravo!! Bravo takes the catch and throws the ball in anger. He should have got Wiese. Back of a length delivery, Wiese goes for the pull, mistimes it completely as it balloons to long-on, it was too easy a chance for Bravo. It was Bravo's <b>15th catch</b> this season, <b>most by any player</b>. <b>Wiese c Dwayne Bravo b Mohit Sharma 12(7) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mohit Sharma to Wiese, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Sarfaraz Khan, 1 run, short and width on offer, Sarfaraz cuts to backward point, Negi fumbles and the batsmen steal a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma [3.0-0-15-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, 2 runs, <b>dropped!</b> Faf puts down a tough chance. Slower delivery around off, Wiese kneels down and tries to play the scoop, gets a top-edge flies over short fine, Faf runs back and tries to take it over his left shoulder, but just couldn't hang on. That would have been another spectacular catch from the South African had he taken it]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, no run, shortens the length, bowled with a normal pace, Wiese inside edges the pull onto the thigh, ball rolls back to Bravo]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, <b>SIX</b>, massive! Wiese races down the wicket and converts it into a length ball, frees his arms and sends it sailing over wide long-on. BLR need plenty more of this, if they have to post a good score]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Sarfaraz Khan, 1 run, change of pace, the length is short, Sarfaraz was early into the cut, toe-ends the cut to extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, 1 run, good length ball on the stumps, Wiese drives it along the ground to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Sarfaraz Khan, 1 run, slower delivery outside off, Sarfaraz chops it wide of backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo [1.0-0-2-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Wiese, 2 runs, shortens the length outside off, Wiese steers it behind point, Faf had a lot of ground to cover from third man, the batsmen come back easily for the second. Nehra completes his quota and yet another fine outing for him against BLR, his figures: <b>4-0-28-3</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Back over the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Sarfaraz Khan, 1 run, shortish and just outside off, Sarfaraz arches back and ramps it on the bounce to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Wiese, 1 run, back of a length around off, Wiese knocks it towards cover and takes off for a sharp run, Raina fires at the striker's end, Sarfaraz just about makes it]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Wiese, <b>wide</b>, splays it down leg, Wiese doesn't play at that, an extra added to the total]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Sarfaraz Khan, 1 run, good length ball around off, Sarfaraz steers it to third man with an angled bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to D Karthik, <b>out</b> Caught by Mohit Sharma!! Nehra once more causing damage. His third wicket of the innings. He loves bowling against BLR. It was a low full toss, Karthik goes deep in the crease, can't get under it as he lofts it to long-on, Mohit runs to his right and takes a simple catch. Just when they were getting the momentum, BLR have lost Karthik. <b>D Karthik c Mohit Sharma b Nehra 28(26) [4s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nehra to D Karthik, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to D Karthik, <b>FOUR</b>, Nehra starts round the wicket, bowls a length ball on off, Karthik stays leg-side of the ball and hammers it over the bowler's head, mid-off was inside the ring and long-on had no chance of stopping that. In fact, he didn't middle it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashish Nehra [3.0-0-18-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sarfaraz Khan, no run, moves away to the leg-side, Jadeja follows him and keeps him calm, defended down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sarfaraz Khan, 2 runs, once more well played by Sarfaraz, works it with soft hands to mid-wicket, by the time Jadeja hunted the ball down the duo picked up two more]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sarfaraz Khan, 2 runs, flatter and on the pads, Sarfaraz nudges it square on the leg-side, the fielders were on the rope and had to run a long way, hence the two was on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sarfaraz Khan, <b>FOUR</b>, top shot! Flighted delivery on the stumps, Sarfaraz shimmies down the wicket, gets to the pitch and tonks it over the bowler's head, one bounce and crashes into the ad boards]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sarfaraz Khan, <b>FOUR</b>, pushed through around off, Sarfaraz backs away and slices it to deep backward point, Ashwin runs to his left from sweeper cover, dives over the ball and lets it reach the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to D Karthik, 1 run, tossed up on off, Karthik comes down the track and pushes it past the bowler and down to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to D Karthik, 1 run, well floated up, Karthik once more was looking to play the sweep, the length was not there, he eases it to long-on and retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to D Karthik, no run, slower through the air, Karthik was shaping to play the slog sweep, decides against it and knocks it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Sarfaraz Khan, 1 run, shortens the length, Sarfaraz works it to the vacant mid-wicket region]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Sarfaraz Khan, no run, flighted around off, Sarfaraz kneels down and toe-ends the sweep back to Negi]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Sarfaraz Khan, no run, comes down the track, checks his shot and chips it to cover, on the bounce to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Sarfaraz Khan, 2 runs, tossed up on the pads, Sarfaraz nudges it with soft hands to mid-wicket, calls for two and gets it. A better throw would have had Sarfaraz in trouble]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pawan Negi, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Sarfaraz Khan, 1 run, flatter and around off, Sarfaraz punches it down to long-off and gets off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to D Karthik, leg byes, 1 run, loud shout for lbw, but umpire Gaffaney shakes his head. Flighted on the stumps, Karthik misses the sweep and is rapped on the pads, the ball had pitched outside leg. Sarfaraz calls for a quick run]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to D Karthik, <b>FOUR</b>, poor delivery, pushes through on leg-stump from round the wicket, Karthik leans forward and tickles it fine, Nehra didn't even bother to chase it down]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sarfaraz Khan, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Gayle, <b>out</b> Caught&Bowled!! Raina has his man. Big wicket for CHN towards the back end of the innings. Gayle goes after a sedate innings. Shortish delivery just outside off, Gayle goes for the pull, the top-edge skies up and goes back over the bowler, Raina runs back, keeps his eyes on the ball and takes a superb catch. <b>Gayle c and b Raina 41(43) [4s-2 6s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Raina to Gayle, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught&Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Gayle, <b>wide</b>, fires it well wide of off, Gayle lets it go, wide given]]></line><line><![CDATA[Plenty of changes in the field. Four fielders in the deep on the leg-side. Raina goes back over the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Gayle, <b>SIX</b>, stand and deliver stuff from Gayle. It has Dhoni worried as he walks to Raina and has a chat. Full delivery on off, Gayle gets underneath it and lofts it handsomely over long-on. Consecutive sixes means Gayle has almost caught up with the balls he has faced]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Gayle, <b>SIX</b>, well, Gayle has got the message. Quicker delivery on the stumps, Gayle plants his front foot forward and heaves it over deep mid-wicket, it was flat and cleared the fence with ease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>. Kohli tells one of the substitutes to talk to both the batsmen. Guess he was sending a message to start playing their shots. For now, it is all CHN and Dhoni is a master when the pitch is behaving like this]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to D Karthik, no run, change of pace outside off, Karthik cuts towards backward point. The fielder had to dive and make the stop, Gayle still not to risk the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to D Karthik, no run, beauty! The off-cutter that grips and bounces a bit more, Karthik was going for the nudge through the on-side, the extra bounce does him in, good take by MSD]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to D Karthik, no run, another off-speed delivery, Karthik is early into the drive, gets an inside edge onto the pad, the ball rolls back to Bravo]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to D Karthik, <b>wide</b>, the slower delivery goes wrong, well outside off, Karthik lets it go and umpire Chaudhary calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Gayle, 1 run, slower delivery close to off, Gayle eases it wide of extra cover, quick single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Gayle, no run, fuller in length and around off, Gayle push-drives to extra cover, still no single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhoni is up to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Gayle, no run, shortish and outside off, Gayle chops it to backward point, Karthik wanted the run but is sent back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Gayle, 1 run, flighted around off, Gayle comes forward and drives to long-off. Still no signs of aggression from the Jamaican]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to D Karthik, 1 run, Karthik comes down the track and chips it to long-on, he didn't try to hit it too hard, just played it for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to D Karthik, 2 runs, quicker and on middle, Karthik takes a step out and nurdles it to deep square leg, calls for two and gets a good response from Gayle]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to D Karthik, <b>FOUR</b>, consecutive fours for Karthik. Again, good use of the feet, shimmies down the wicket, goes inside out lofts it past the diving extra cover, the ball raced away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to D Karthik, <b>FOUR</b>, superb shot! First boundary after 25 balls. Lovely use of the feet, dances down the wicket, meets the pitch of the ball and whips it towards deep mid-wicket for a one bounce four]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Gayle, 1 run, slower and on the stumps, Gayle milks it square of the wicket on the leg-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Gayle, 1 run, fuller and around off, Gayle eases it to long-off and keeps strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to D Karthik, 1 run, drags the length back, Karthik flat-bats it down to long-on, didn't time it that well]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Gayle, leg byes, 1 run, shortish and on off, Gayle looks to play the one-leg pull, misses and is struck high on the pad, stifled appeal for lbw, but it was always going over]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Gayle, 2 runs, pitched up outside off, Gayle comes forward and drives it past extra cover, Karthik pushed the big man for the second and in the end they make it easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Gayle, no run, fuller and around off, Gayle pushes it gently back to the bowler, he looks at the toe-end after playing that]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to D Karthik, 1 run, on a length close to off, Karthik opens the bat face and runs it down to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to D Karthik, 1 run, that's poor running from Gayle, Karthik skips out of the crease, gets to the pitch and laces it wide of long-on, Bravo had a lot of ground to cover, but Gayle was never interested in the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to D Karthik, no run, comes down the track, gets to the pitch and turns it to mid-wicket, can't get it past Mohit]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Gayle, 1 run, quicker, fuller and on the stumps, Gayle works it wide of long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Gayle, <b>wide</b>, fired down the leg-side, Gayle can't meet with the sweep, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to D Karthik, 1 run, fraction short and outside off, Karthik goes back and cuts to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Gayle, 1 run, angling in on the pads from round the wicket, Gayle leans forward and nudges to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Gayle, no run, flatter and on the stumps, Gayle brings his bat down and taps it to the left of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>. In the last 5 overs, BLR have scored 18 runs and lost 3 wickets. CHN are well ahead in the game and it will stay that way if the Jamaican keeps playing like this. Raina comes on as expected. Jadeja and Negi will be a risk against Gayle]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Gayle, 1 run, pitched up just outside off, Gayle mistimes the drive down the wicket, Mohit gets a hand and deflects it towards mid-off, Gayle makes a late call for the single and gets it as Smith fails to collect the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to D Karthik, 1 run, full and angling into the pads, Karthik leans forward and flicks it towards long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to D Karthik, no run, back of a length around off, Karthik stays in the crease and knocks it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhoni up to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Gayle, 1 run, drags the length close to off, Gayle punches it past the non-striker, Karthik called for two, but Gayle was never going back]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Gayle, no run, on a length and around off, Gayle shuffles across and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Gayle, no run, fuller and outside off, Gayle happy to bide his time, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to D Karthik, no run, tad shorter and wider from Ashwin, Karthik makes room and chops it straight to short third man. End of a fine spell from Ashwin, his figures read: <b>4-0-13-1</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to D Karthik, no run, flighted and spinning back from outside off, Karthik lunges forward and gets an inside edge on the defensive push]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to D Karthik, 2 runs, fraction short and wide outside off, Karthik backs away and cracks it in front of square on the off-side, comes back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to D Karthik, no run, this one is given more air, Karthik presses forward and drives it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to D Karthik, no run, tossed up and well outside off, Karthik gets a big stride forward in defence]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dinesh Karthik, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Mandeep, <b>out</b> Caught by M Hussey!! That's a blinder from Hussey at backward square leg! This was tossed up and well outside leg, Mandeep went for the sweep, gets the top-edge as the ball bounced a tad extra. It was going to drop short of Hussey though, he rushes forward, puts in the dive and holds onto a screamer. Raina is delighted as he hugs Hussey, BLR are in trouble now. <b>Mandeep c M Hussey b Ashwin 4(7)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Ashwin to Mandeep, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Gayle, <b>FOUR</b>, much needed boundary for BLR, Mohit dropped one short and on Gayle's pads, he gets inside the line and flicks it very fine, Ashwin was inside the ring at fine leg and the ball rolls away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Gayle, no run, Mohit shortens his length outside off, Gayle presses across and pushes it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Gayle, 2 runs, Mohit keeps it very full and on the stumps, Gayle shuffles across and works it behind square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Gayle, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Gayle plays with an open face towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Mandeep, 1 run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Mandeep drives and gets a thick edge towards third man, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Mandeep, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Mandeep stays behind the line and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Replays in on AB dismissal:</b> The ball pitched marginally outside leg, AB can consider himself unlucky]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Mandeep, 1 run, tossed up and on the stumps, eased in front of mid-on for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Mandeep, no run, flighted delivery and breaking back into Mandeep, he lunges forward and takes it on his pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Mandeep, 2 runs, tossed up and on Mandeep's pads, he looks to defend and gets an inside edge past leg-slip, Faf gives chase and keeps them down to a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Mandeep, no run, slower and just outside off, Mandeep prods across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Gayle, 1 run, flighted delivery and on Gayle's pads, swept away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Gayle, no run, tossed up and just outside off, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mandeep Singh, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to de Villiers, <b>out</b> Lbw!! That's a massive blow! AB isn't happy here but Nehra exults! This was pitched up and nips back in sharply, AB was caught in his crease on the flick, was there an inside edge there? Was it going down leg-side? Was the height an issue? The umpire took a long time before raising the finger. AB has a rueful smile as he walks away. Double blow for BLR. <b>de Villiers lbw b Nehra 1(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nehra to de Villiers, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to de Villiers, no run, short of a length and angling into AB, he presses across and defends it with a closed face]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Gayle, 1 run, on a length and on Gayle's pads, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Gayle, no run, loud shout for LBW, was the ball slipping over the top? Replays suggest that it might have gone over the top, this was pitched up and nipped back into Gayle, he was caught in his crease as he looked to flick, gets hit just above the knee-roll. The impact was slightly outside off as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to de Villiers, 1 run, back of a length and on AB's pads, worked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>AB de Villiers, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, <b>out</b> Caught by Mohit Sharma!! That's a soft dismissal! Kohli is angry with himself as he walks back to the hut. This was short and on Kohli's pads, he could have hit it anywhere, instead, he flicks it in the air and straight to Mohit at backward square leg. He was looking good tonight, but his innings has been cut short. <b>Kohli c Mohit Sharma b Nehra 12(9) [4s-1 6s-1]]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Nehra to Kohli, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Gayle, no run, this is turning out to be a cat-and-mouse game, Ashwin dropped one on middle, Gayle was shaping for the sweep, the ball viciously turns square, Gayle withdraws his shot and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Gayle, no run, slower and just outside off, Gayle lunges forward and blocks it]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Gayle, no run, flighted delivery and on off, Gayle goes back and defends it with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Gayle, no run, lovely bowling from Ashwin, gave this one more air, dragged Gayle forward before getting it to spin past Gayle's edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Kohli, 1 run, this one is given more air, Kohli wristily flicks it towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Gayle, 1 run, tossed up and just outside off, eased down towards long-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Kohli waits on it and dabs it straight to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhoni is up to the stumps now]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, <b>SIX</b>, this is even better! Just a little shimmy down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and goes back over the bowler's head, sails over the ropes for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, fraction too short from Nehra, Kohli is quick to pick up the length, rocks back and pulls it in front of square on the on-side, one bounce and over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, no run, on a good length and shaping across the right-hander, Kohli prods across and defends it with soft hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, no run, Nehra shortens his length and on Kohli's pads, he presses across and nudges it towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, no run, fuller length delivery and on Kohli's pads, whipped straight to the fielder at mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[A slight delay here, Jadeja is getting some medical attention for his knee]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Gayle, no run, lovely drift and flight from Ashwin, tossed up just outside off and spinning slightly across Gayle, he prods forward and defends it with an open face towards short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Gayle, <b>FOUR</b>, Gayle gets lucky! Nehra was late in getting across, this was fired down leg-side, Gayle went for the sweep and got a top-edge. The ball looped to the right of short fine leg, Nehra had a late start wasn't going to get anywhere near the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Gayle, no run, pushed through on Gayle's pads, turned towards mid-wicket, no run there as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Gayle, no run, Ashwin drops one short and gets it to spin away, Gayle rocks back and cuts it towards extra cover. Jadeja gets a bad bounce and is struck on his knees]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Gayle, no run, tossed up slowly and spinning past the off-stump, Gayle prods half forward and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place for Gayle, this will be an interesting contest..]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Kohli, 1 run, Ashwin comes from round the wicket and drifts one onto Kohli's pads, worked towards long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A leg slip in place for Ashwin]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Gayle, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Gayle prods across and defends it towards cover-point. Good over from Nehra, apart from that six, managed to keep Gayle quiet]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Gayle, no run, Gayle winces in pain after smashing an inside edge onto his toes! This was pitched up and held its line outside off, Gayle was looking to hoick it over mid-wicket, gets an inside edge, the ball hits him flush on the legs]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Gayle, no run, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, Gayle was initially looking to play at that, the ball wasn't there though, he lifts his bat and is happy to leave it alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Gayle, no run, fuller length delivery and in that channel outside off, Gayle shuffles across slightly, covers the line and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Gayle, <b>SIX</b>, aggression from Gayle, comes down the track, covers for the swing and goes over cover, he didn't strike it cleanly, but the ball sailed over the ropes for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Gayle, no run, fuller length delivery and holding its line outside off, Gayle plays inside the line and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Gayle and Kohli are at the crease. Gayle is on strike. Nehra will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place..]]></line><line><![CDATA[The umpires are out in the middle. CHN fielders take their positions and are followed by the two BLR openers, Chris Gayle and Virat Kohli. Looks like Ashwin will not open the bowling, it's Nehra with the new ball.]]></line><line><![CDATA[CHN look relaxed in the dug-out, they have been in such situations many times before. New territory for BLR, a win and they will be through to their 3rd IPL final. They had featured at this stage in 2011. They batted first and outclassed MUM then. Can they do an encore now?]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai</b> (Playing XI): Dwayne Smith, Michael Hussey, Faf du Plessis, Suresh Raina, MS Dhoni(w/c), Dwayne Bravo, Pawan Negi, Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Mohit Sharma, Ashish Nehra]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore</b> (Playing XI): Virat Kohli(c), Chris Gayle, AB de Villiers, Mandeep Singh, Dinesh Karthik(w), Sarfaraz Khan, David Wiese, Harshal Patel, Mitchell Starc, Sreenath Aravind, Yuzvendra Chahal]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kohli:</b> 'I think I am a bit more relaxed today. If we play well today, we are into the final. Another exciting game coming up. I have enjoyed playing here, I have scored a few runs when playing for India. Looks a bit dry tonight. I would have batted first, to be honest, it's a big game, better to put the runs on the board. I think this track will crumble as the game goes on, if we keep the ball dry, we should do well. Playing the same eleven.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhoni:</b> 'It's a big match, it's a knock-out stage. A lot at stake, but we need to play well. It's looking dry (the pitch), with a bit of dew around, it will help the pacers initially, should be a good batting surface later on. Good to have Hussey as a back-up to McCullum. We will bowl first, bit worried about the dew factor. No changes for us.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Let us have a look at the key contests that might have a say in this match. First up, it will be Gayle v Ashwin. The Indian off-spinner has had the wood over the West Indies opener. Will the burly Jamaican turn things around today? He hasn't faced CHN this season, having sat out of both league matches. Who will tame ABD? Can CHN openers get past Mitchell Starc? Can BLR do better this time around against Ashish Nehra? The winner of these contests will go a long way in deciding the result of this match.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Recent results are also in favour of CHN. They beat BLR by 27 runs when the two teams met in Bangalore. The return match was no different as well, with CHN handing a 24-run drubbing to BLR. On the whole, they enjoy a 11-7 winning advantage.]]></line><line><![CDATA[BLR are the in-form team as well. AB de Villiers is second in the run-charts, having crossed 500 runs for the first time in his IPL career, Kohli and Chris Gayle have 400+ runs. That has meant that there are three BLR batsmen in the top-10. On the other hand, CHN have only one - Brendon McCullum with 436 runs and he isn't available for this match, having left for national duties. BLR dominate in the bowling front as well, although CHN's Dwayne Bravo is the leader of the pack with 23 wickets. On form, BLR should start favourites, but this being a knock-out game, CHN, with their experience in handling pressure situations, will back themselves to succeed.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The IPL has moved across to Ranchi and CHN's skipper, MS Dhoni, will be playing in front of his adoring home crowd. One thing for sure, there will be a lot more yellow flags waving around the JSCA international stadium tonight. While Ranchi is more or less the home venue for CHN - having played an entire season on this ground last year, BLR might not worry too much about being the visiting team. This is one team that has travelled well this year - securing 6 wins from 8 away matches so far. The pressure will be squarely on Mahendra Singh Dhoni and his CHN outfit and this might free up Virat Kohli's men - as they seek to put in their best foot forward.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:30 Local Time, 13:00 GMT</b>: Call it as the second qualifier or a semi-final, it's yet another knock-out game at Ranchi today. Having finished in the top two, Chennai got a second opportunity to enter the final, despite losing to Mumbai in Qualifier 1. Their opponents tonight will be Bangalore, riding high after a string of good results in recent times. The winner will travel to Kolkata to face MUM in the final. The loser will go home. Plenty at stake then for both teams. Hello, and a warm welcome to one and all to the second qualifier between CHN and BLR.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/>Bangalore have a batting line-up that is the envy of Indian Premier League (IPL). There is power, flair, brilliance and exuberance in their batting. It is baffling that this team has failed to achieve anything substantial other than two losses in the finals of IPL. In IPL 2015, this team is looking in great shape and they will be determined to reach the top of the mountain.<br/><br/>Chennai, though, are a team who have the experience and skill to win the crunch games. They know how to raise their game on the big stage. They may have suffered a loss to Mumbai in the first qualifier, but that will make them fiercely determined to put one over their southern rivals in the second qualifier.<br/><br/>Bangalore will be aware that they are currently at the receiving end of a three-match losing streak against Chennai. With confidence high after their clinical show against Rajasthan, Bangalore will go all-out to break their streak.<br/><br/><b>Venue:</b> JSCA International Stadium Complex, Ranchi<br/><b>Date:</b> May 22, 2015<br/><b>Time:</b> 20:00 IST<br/><b>Weather:</b> Clear skies with a low of 27 degrees<br/><br/><b>Team news</b><br/><br/><b>Chennai</b><br/><br/>The death bowling plans went awry in the qualifier against Mumbai. After a disciplined start, the bowlers leaked 101 runs in the last 10 overs and this is an area that MS Dhoni will have to strengthen ahead of the clash. With the batting depth of Bangalore, the team will have to bowl really well if they are to contain them. Chennai have plenty of options in the bowling department but they might want to boost their pace attack and thus bring in Ishwar Pandey for Pawan Negi.<br/><br/>Probable XI<br/><br/>1 Dwayne Smith, 2 Michael Hussey, 3 Faf du Plessis, 4 Suresh Raina, 5 MS Dhoni (c and wk), 6 Dwayne Bravo, 7 Ravindra Jadeja, 8 R Ashwin, 9 Pawan Negi/Ishwar Pandey, 10 Mohit Sharma, 11 Ashish Nehra<br/><br/><b>Bangalore</b><br/><br/>The power of Chris Gayle, the versatility of Virat Kohli and the genius of AB de Villiers, combined with the raw aggression of Mandeep Singh and Sarfaraz Khan, makes the team's batting look complete. However, their tendency to crack under pressure is well documented and they will be aware that on the big stage, they will have to curb their tendency to choke. With the team composition in good shape, they might not make any changes.<br/><br/>Probable XI<br/><br/>1 Chris Gayle, 2 Virat Kohli (c), 3 AB de Villiers, 4 Mandeep Singh, 5 Dinesh Karthik (wk), 6 Sarfaraz Khan, 7 David Wiese, 8 Mitchell Starc, 9 Harshal Patel, 10 Yuzvendra Chahal, 11 Sreenath Aravind<br/><br/><b>Quotes</b><br/><br/>"We have played better cricket than previous seasons. In 2013, we did not qualify and that hurt." - Bangalore skipper Virat Kohli says the team is determined to do well in IPL 2015.<br/><br/>"We have always done well with our back to the wall, so that's what we can go to Ranchi with". - Chennai skipper MS Dhoni highlights the determination of his team.<br/><br/><b>Stats</b><br/><br/>AB de Villiers has a strike-rate of 158.29, the best in the Bangalore team. He also needs nine sixes to reach the 100-sixes mark in IPL.<br/>In their last encounter in Ranchi during IPL 2014, Bangalore won a close match by five wickets against Chennai.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore</b> (From): Virat Kohli(c), Chris Gayle, AB de Villiers, Mandeep Singh, Dinesh Karthik(w), Sarfaraz Khan, David Wiese, Harshal Patel, Mitchell Starc, Sreenath Aravind, Yuzvendra Chahal, Nic Maddinson, Varun Aaron, Ashok Dinda, Vijay Zol, Abu Nechim, Sandeep Warrier, Yogesh Takawale, Rilee Rossouw, Iqbal Abdulla, Manvinder Bisla, S Badrinath, Darren Sammy, Sean Abbott, Jalaj Saxena, Shishir Bhavane]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai</b> (From): Dwayne Smith, Michael Hussey, Faf du Plessis, Suresh Raina, MS Dhoni(c/w), Dwayne Bravo, Pawan Negi, Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Mohit Sharma, Ashish Nehra, Ishwar Pandey, Baba Aparajith, Matt Henry, Mithun Manhas, Samuel Badree, Ronit More, Rahul Sharma, Kyle Abbott, Ankush Bains, Irfan Pathan, Pratyush Singh, Andrew Tye, Eklavya Dwivedi]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>139</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>8</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Bangalore">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>247</playerid>
					<name>Chris Gayle</name>
					<batsman-name>Gayle</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Gayle</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>41</runs>
					<balls>43</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Raina</bowler>
					<bowlerId>413</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Raina</fielder>
						<fielderId>413</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Kohli</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>12</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Nehra</bowler>
					<bowlerId>269</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mohit Sharma</fielder>
						<fielderId>8181</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>370</playerid>
					<name>AB de Villiers</name>
					<batsman-name>de Villiers</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>de Villiers</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Nehra</bowler>
					<bowlerId>269</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6319</playerid>
					<name>Mandeep Singh</name>
					<batsman-name>Mandeep</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mandeep</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Ashwin</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1593</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Michael Hussey</fielder>
						<fielderId>4772</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>145</playerid>
					<name>Dinesh Karthik</name>
					<batsman-name>D Karthik</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>D Karthik</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>28</runs>
					<balls>26</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Nehra</bowler>
					<bowlerId>269</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mohit Sharma</fielder>
						<fielderId>8181</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9429</playerid>
					<name>Sarfaraz Khan</name>
					<batsman-name>Sarfaraz Khan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sarfaraz Khan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>31</runs>
					<balls>21</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>DJ Bravo</bowler>
					<bowlerId>242</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Pawan Negi</fielder>
						<fielderId>8281</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8589</playerid>
					<name>David Wiese</name>
					<batsman-name>D Wiese</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Wiese</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>12</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mohit Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8181</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dwayne Bravo</fielder>
						<fielderId>242</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8175</playerid>
					<name>Harshal Patel</name>
					<batsman-name>Harshal Patel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Harshal Patel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>MS Dhoni</fielder>
						<fielderId>265</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7710</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
					<batsman-name>M Starc</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Starc</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1850</playerid>
					<name>Sreenath Aravind</name>
					<batsman-name>Aravind</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Aravind</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7910</playerid>
					<name>Yuzvendra Chahal</name>
					<batsman-name>Chahal</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chahal</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1413</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>23</runs>
				<overs>4.1</overs>
				<batsman>Virat Kohli</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>370</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>25</runs>
				<overs>4.6</overs>
				<batsman>AB de Villiers</batsman>
				<batsman-name>de Villiers</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6319</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>36</runs>
				<overs>7.1</overs>
				<batsman>Mandeep Singh</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mandeep</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>247</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>80</runs>
				<overs>13.3</overs>
				<batsman>Chris Gayle</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Gayle</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>145</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>107</runs>
				<overs>16.2</overs>
				<batsman>Dinesh Karthik</batsman>
				<batsman-name>D Karthik</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8589</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>125</runs>
				<overs>18.2</overs>
				<batsman>David Wiese</batsman>
				<batsman-name>D Wiese</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8175</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>138</runs>
				<overs>19.3</overs>
				<batsman>Harshal Patel</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Harshal Patel</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9429</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>139</runs>
				<overs>19.5</overs>
				<batsman>Sarfaraz Khan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Sarfaraz Khan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>5</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Chennai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>269</playerid>
					<name>Ashish Nehra</name>
					<bowler-name>Nehra</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nehra</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>28</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<bowler-name>Ashwin</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ashwin</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>13</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Mohit Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mohit Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>22</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<bowler-name>Raina</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Raina</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>242</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
					<bowler-name>DJ Bravo</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>21</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8281</playerid>
					<name>Pawan Negi</name>
					<bowler-name>Negi</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Negi</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>4</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<bowler-name>R Jadeja</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>13</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<bowler-name>Dwayne Smith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Smith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>4772</playerid>
					<name>Michael Hussey</name>
					<bowler-name>M Hussey</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M Hussey</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7825</playerid>
					<name>Faf du Plessis</name>
					<bowler-name>du Plessis</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>du Plessis</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhoni</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhoni</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>140</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>7</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>19.5</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Chennai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Smith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>17</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Aravind</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1850</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mitchell Starc</fielder>
						<fielderId>7710</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>4772</playerid>
					<name>Michael Hussey</name>
					<batsman-name>M Hussey</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M Hussey</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>56</runs>
					<balls>46</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>D Wiese</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8589</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Harshal Patel</fielder>
						<fielderId>8175</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7825</playerid>
					<name>Faf du Plessis</name>
					<batsman-name>du Plessis</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>du Plessis</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>21</runs>
					<balls>22</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Chahal</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7910</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Raina</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Chahal</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7910</bowlerId>
						<fielder>David Wiese</fielder>
						<fielderId>8589</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhoni</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>26</runs>
					<balls>29</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Harshal Patel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8175</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dinesh Karthik</fielder>
						<fielderId>145</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8281</playerid>
					<name>Pawan Negi</name>
					<batsman-name>Negi</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Negi</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>12</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sarfaraz Khan</fielder>
						<fielderId>9429</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>242</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
					<batsman-name>DJ Bravo</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>M Starc</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7710</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<batsman-name>R Jadeja</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<batsman-name>Ashwin</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ashwin</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Mohit Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mohit Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>269</playerid>
					<name>Ashish Nehra</name>
					<batsman-name>Nehra</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nehra</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>255</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>21</runs>
				<overs>3.1</overs>
				<batsman>Dwayne Smith</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7825</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>61</runs>
				<overs>9.2</overs>
				<batsman>Faf du Plessis</batsman>
				<batsman-name>du Plessis</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>413</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>61</runs>
				<overs>9.4</overs>
				<batsman>Suresh Raina</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>4772</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>108</runs>
				<overs>16.3</overs>
				<batsman>Michael Hussey</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Hussey</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8281</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>135</runs>
				<overs>18.5</overs>
				<batsman>Pawan Negi</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Negi</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>242</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>135</runs>
				<overs>18.6</overs>
				<batsman>Dwayne Bravo</batsman>
				<batsman-name>DJ Bravo</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>265</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>139</runs>
				<overs>19.4</overs>
				<batsman>MS Dhoni</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>3</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Bangalore">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7710</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
					<bowler-name>M Starc</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Starc</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>27</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1850</playerid>
					<name>Sreenath Aravind</name>
					<bowler-name>Aravind</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Aravind</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8175</playerid>
					<name>Harshal Patel</name>
					<bowler-name>Harshal Patel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Harshal Patel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3.5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>26</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8589</playerid>
					<name>David Wiese</name>
					<bowler-name>D Wiese</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Wiese</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>30</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7910</playerid>
					<name>Yuzvendra Chahal</name>
					<bowler-name>Chahal</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chahal</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>28</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<bowler-name>Kohli</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Kohli</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>247</playerid>
					<name>Chris Gayle</name>
					<bowler-name>Gayle</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Gayle</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>370</playerid>
					<name>AB de Villiers</name>
					<bowler-name>de Villiers</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>de Villiers</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6319</playerid>
					<name>Mandeep Singh</name>
					<bowler-name>Mandeep</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mandeep</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>145</playerid>
					<name>Dinesh Karthik</name>
					<bowler-name>D Karthik</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>D Karthik</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9429</playerid>
					<name>Sarfaraz Khan</name>
					<bowler-name>Sarfaraz Khan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sarfaraz Khan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



