<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14635" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>41st Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Rajasthan</home>
		<away>Hyderabad</away>
		<teamsabbr>JAI vs HYD</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>JAI</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>HYD</awayabbr>
		<homeId>64</homeId>
		<awayId>255</awayId>
		<venue>Brabourne Stadium, Mumbai</venue>
		<startdate>07 05 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>07 05 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Rajasthan</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Hyderabad won by 7 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Hyderabad</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>7</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Johanes Cloete</Name>
			<Country>RSA</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Chettithody Shamsuddin</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Kumar Dharmasena</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Javagal Srinath</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>10:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150507140025</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>JAI</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>HYD</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>194</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>7</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>20</batteamovers>
		<status>Hyderabad won by 7 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>8333</playerid>
			<name>Chris Morris*</name>
			<batsman-name>C Morris</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>C Morris</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>34</runs>
			<balls-faced>11</balls-faced>
			<fours>2</fours>
			<sixes>3</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>1530</playerid>
			<name>Stuart Binny</name>
			<batsman-name>Binny</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Binny</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>3</runs>
			<balls-faced>3</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>592</playerid>
			<name>Praveen Kumar*</name>
			<bowler-name>P Kumar</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>P Kumar</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>40</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1726</playerid>
			<name>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</name>
			<bowler-name>Bhuvneshwar</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Bhuvneshwar</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>44</runs>
			<wickets>3</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>202</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>8271</playerid>
<name>Sanju Samson</name>
<player-runs>21</player-runs>
<player-balls>10</player-balls>
<runs>157</runs>
<wicket-nbr>7</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>1726</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Bhuvneshwar</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>1</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>6</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[. 6 L2 1 . 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>W 6 6 W 4 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>6 6 6 2 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 1 1 2 4 1 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/JAI_HYD_MAY07/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[That's it from this game. The action now shifts to Eden Gardens, where Kolkata are taking on Delhi. Switch tabs and enjoy the match. For now, take care and Cya!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Morgan:</b> "I felt good. Since I have touched down here, I have worked on a couple of different things. It was a great wicket to bat on. Given the dimensions of the ground, it was better to go straight. Again we came up trumps (talking about the added responsibility he had as there was no Boult and Steyn). Today me, Shikhar (Dhawan) and a bit of Ravi saw it through. We can't rely on the opening pair everytime."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Eoin Morgan</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his <b>28-ball 63.</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Warner:</b> "We knew that a total around 170-180 was a good score, 200 was a bonus. Before I went up to bat, I seized up. It has happened before, but nothing to worry about. I let the team down by getting out to my fellow team-mate (Watson). We haven't been clicking in the middle order and it was good to do well. We wanted the middle order to gain momentum. It is quite hard to get a smile from Moody, but he is quite a serious man and he has a heart of gold. The positive sign is we batted well on a wicket we were sent in."]]></line><line><![CDATA[The dismissal of Smith - castled by Ravi Bopara, for a 40-ball 68, turned out to be the turning point of the match. Faulkner threw his bat around, but the task was beyond him - caught in the deep for 30. The bowling of the Hyderabad was disciplined, they mixed a lot of slower ones while the yorkers were spot-on, at least until the final stages of the match. It needed the canniness of Bhuvneshwar Kumar, who managed to defend 18 runs from the final over, to ensure that his team stay alive in the tournament.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chasing 202, Rajasthan needed a quick start, but they ended up losing the wickets of their in-form openers, Ajinkya Rahane and Shane Watson, pretty cheaply. Karun Nair struggled during his brief stay and so did Deepak Hooda. At the other end, Steven Smith batted with a lot of authority and threatened to take the game away. He was well supported by James Faulkner as the duo added 44 runs for the fifth wicket.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Superb cameos from Sanju Samson and Chris Morris nearly created an upset of gigantic levels but Hyderabad and Bhuvneshwar Kumar kept their composure to ensure a 7-run victory. A much needed victory for the Hyderabad and they are back in the tournament. Warner's team move up to the fifth position with 10 points while Rajasthan stay second with 14 points.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to C Morris, 1 run, <b>HYD win by 7 runs</b>. Bhuvi held his nerve in the final over. Leg-cutter just outside off, Morris mistimes the cut to sweeper cover, the duo get only a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to C Morris, <b>FOUR</b>, cracking shot! Bhuvneshwar misses the yorker length, Morris clears his front leg and smacks it straight back past the bowler, the fielder at long-on dives in vain]]></line><line><![CDATA[Warner and Bhuvneshwar have a discussion. Morris is taking a look at the field. Fine leg and third man are inside the ring. Now, the batsmen are having a chat. Two sixes for a Super Over.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to C Morris, 2 runs, yorker around off, Morris winds up for the mighty heave, the ball squirts off the inside edge towards short fine leg, Ishant dives to his right and makes a half stop. He saved a couple of runs there]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Binny, 1 run, Binny has missed out there, it was a full toss from Bhuvi, Binny takes a step down and mistimes the big hit to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to C Morris, 1 run, short and outside off, Morris cuts to sweeper cover, that would have been a wide, if Morris had let it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Binny, 1 run, full toss on the stumps, Binny hammers it past Morris, Bopara runs to his left from long-on and keeps it to a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>22</b> from Praveen's over means Bhuvi has <b>18 to defend in the last over.</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Binny, 1 run, almost a yorker around off, Binny can't get underneath that, he squeezes the drive to long-off and keeps strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to C Morris, 1 run, very full and just short of yorker length, Morris drills it straight to long-on, Warner keeps it to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to C Morris, 2 runs, much better, yorker on the stumps, Morris squeezes it in front of long-on, Binny pushes Morris for the second and they take it with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to C Morris, <b>SIX</b>, <b>hat-trick of sixes.</b> The change of angle didn't work for Praveen. Drags the slower delivery halfway down the wicket, Morris waits for it and pulls it over deep square leg. The fielder was a mere spectator]]></line><line><![CDATA[Praveen goes round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to C Morris, <b>SIX</b>, another six and RAJ are still in it. Praveen is dishing out length deliveries, Morris is cashing in, he gets his front leg out of the way and plays the pick-up shot wide of long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to C Morris, <b>SIX</b>, great start to the over. Morris is hitting them alright. Full delivery on off and middle, Morris plants his front forward and flicks it in the air towards deep mid-wicket, Morgan runs to his right, dives full length and tries to flick it in, but is not able to do that]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Praveen Kumar [3.0-0-18-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>40 runs off 12 balls</b>. Surely, HYD's game from here on. Or will Binny and Morris pull a rabbit out of the hat?]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to C Morris, 1 run, leg-cutter around off, Morris is early into the shot, adjusts and nurdles it square of the wicket on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to C Morris, <b>FOUR</b>, cheeky! Morris gets going with a pre-meditated shot. The back of the hand slower ball, Morris shuffles across and scoops it over short fine, he just about clear the fielder to pick up four]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Morris, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Samson, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Bhuvi has the last laugh. Samson's little cameo comes to an end and RAJ are coming apart. It was the slower delivery on a length, Samson goes for the swipe towards cow corner, the under-edges goes on and crashes into the stumps. <b>Samson b Bhuvneshwar 21(10) [6s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bhuvneshwar to Samson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Samson, <b>SIX</b>, consecutive sixes for Samson. He is not giving up just yet. Bhuvneshwar dishes out a full toss on middle and leg, Samson clears his front leg and hoicks it over deep mid-wicket for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Samson, <b>SIX</b>, fabulous shot! That is the second six he has hit effortlessly. Bhuvneshwar misses the yorker and bowls a length ball, Samson lofts it straight down the ground, clears the sightscreen comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Stuart Binny, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Faulkner, <b>out</b> Caught by Bopara!! That might be the match for HYD. They have got rid of the big-hitting James Faulkner. It was a low full toss, Faulkner gets underneath it and hammers it flat to long-on, he couldn't get the elevation to clear Bopara, who takes a good catch. <b>Faulkner c Bopara b Bhuvneshwar 30(19) [4s-2 6s-2]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Bhuvneshwar to Faulkner, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bhuvneshwar Kumar [2.0-0-17-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[RAJ still need 57 runs from 18 balls. A lot will depend on Faulkner, who is known for his finishing abilities.]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Faulkner, 1 run, drags the slower delivery halfway down the wicket, Faulkner slaps it to extra cover and retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Faulkner, no run, another back of the hand slower ball, Faulkner looks to force it off the back foot, the ball squirts off the inside edge and hits the back pad. If not for the pad, that was going onto the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Samson, 1 run, off-speed delivery on off, Samson shuffles across and scoops, finds the fielder at short fine leg, didn't get it off the middle]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Samson, leg byes, 2 runs, slower delivery around off, Samson misses the defensive push, the ball hits the thigh and rolls away fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Samson, <b>SIX</b>, fantastic shot! This youngster can bat. It was a very straight full delivery, Samson comes forward and plays the pick-up shot, he timed it so well that it cleared the deep mid-wicket fence with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Samson, no run, back of the hand slower delivery, Samson was on his knee to play the sweep, the ball does not come on and he ends up jamming it onto the pads]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Faulkner, no run, off-cutter outside off, Faulkner cuts and misses, once again deceived by the lack of pace]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Faulkner, no run, bouncer outside off, Faulkner was shaping to play the pull, but decided against it. He looks at the umpire for a wide as it was the second short delivery, but he gets nothing]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Faulkner, no run, change of pace and Faulkner misses out, he is early into the swipe to cow corner, the ball goes under his bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Faulkner, <b>FOUR</b>, Faulkner is liking the pace on the ball. Henriques bowls a bumper outside off, Faulkner fetches the pull from there, top-edges it over the keeper and collects another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Faulkner, <b>FOUR</b>, banged in halfway down the wicket, Faulkner pulls to deep mid-wicket, Vihari runs to his right, slides but lets the ball go through his legs. That should have been stopped]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Samson, 1 run, off-speed delivery on middle, Samson leans forward and flicks to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Moises Henriques [2.0-0-20-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Samson, leg byes, 1 run, half hearted appeal for lbw, Samson walks down and across the pitch, Bopara slips in the slower one, Samson misses the flick and is struck on the pad, the impact was outside off though]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Faulkner, 1 run, shortish and around off, Faulkner flat-bats it past the non-striker and down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Faulkner, 2 runs, takes the pace off the ball, Faulkner works it with soft hands in front of square on the leg-side, calls for two and gets it comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Samson, 1 run, Samson walks down the pitch, almost yorks himself, digs it out to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sanju Samson, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to S Smith, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Knocked over! Smith is livid with himself as he bangs his bat hard on the turf. This was a good length delivery on the stumps, Smith backs away and misses the cut, the ball crashed into middle stump. It is a very crucial wicket for HYD as Smith was looking in ominous touch. <b>S Smith b Bopara 68(40) [4s-9 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bopara to S Smith, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, good start to the over, back of a length around off, Smith waits for the ball to arrive and pulls it in front of square, between deep mid-wicket and long-on. Some placement that]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravi Bopara [1.0-0-6-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to S Smith, 1 run, low full toss on off, Smith knocks it gently to long-on, called for two first, but settles with one as the fielder gets there quickly]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, there comes the boundary of the over. Pitched up delivery around off, Smith drives it to the left of the bowler, just eludes Praveen and beats Warner at long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Faulkner, leg byes, 1 run, full and on leg-stump, Faulkner misses the flick and the ball rolls away off the pads towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to S Smith, 1 run, Smith gives the charge, converts it into a fuller length delivery and drives to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Faulkner, 1 run, change of pace and the length is short, Faulkner pulls straight to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Faulkner, 2 runs, leg-cutter around off, Faulkner nudges it to the vacant mid-wicket region, the batsmen run two before the fielder from the deep comes in to field the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Praveen Kumar [2.0-0-9-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Smith, no run, expects the ball to be shorter, Smith goes back in the crease and cuts to cover-point, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Smith, <b>SIX</b>, RAJ are on the charge now. That is the 4th six in 9 balls. Tossed up delivery just outside off, Smith shimmies down the wicket, goes through with the loft and sends it sailing over long-off. That is some great footwork from Smith]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Faulkner, 1 run, slower and on the stumps, Faulkner turns it gently to short mid-wicket and hands the strike back to Smith]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Faulkner, no run, stifled appeal for lbw, Faulkner hangs back and misses the straighter one. The ball pitched on leg-stump and would have missed the sticks as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Smith, 1 run, quicker and on leg-stump, Smith comes down the track and whips it behind square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Smith, <b>SIX</b>, back-to-back sixes for RAJ. Smith reaches his <b>fifty</b> as well. Flighted delivery on middle, Smith dances down the wicket, gets to the pitch and lofts it handsomely straight back over the bowler's head. Everyone in the RAJ dug-out are up on their feet applauding the innings]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to Faulkner, <b>SIX</b>, Ishant has been smacked for the second six in the over. Another nice juicy full toss, Faulkner gets his front leg out of the way and hoicks into the crowd at deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to S Smith, 1 run, slower delivery that is dragged short, Smith swipes it across the line to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to Faulkner, 1 run, very full and on the stumps, Faulkner squeezes it to the right of the bowler, Smith couldn't get out of the way, the ball ricochets off his pads towards mid-wicket. He could have gone for the second, but he doesn't. That is good sportsmanship from Smith]]></line><line><![CDATA[The fourth umpire brings out the box for the onfield umpires to select one that is close to 11 overs old.]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to Faulkner, <b>SIX</b>, this time Faulkner does not miss out on a full toss. It was on leg-stump, Faulkner says thank you very much and heaves it over backward square for a maximum. The ball is out of the park]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to S Smith, leg byes, 1 run, Ojha has saved some runs for the team, Ishant drifts onto leg-stump, Smith shuffles across and misses the glance, the ball brushes the pad and was on its way to the fine leg fence before a Ojha intercepted with a dive to his left]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to Faulkner, 1 run, starts his second spell with a full toss on the pads, Faulkner backs away and works it to deep square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ishant Sharma [2.0-0-10-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Deepak Hooda, <b>out</b> Caught by Bhuvneshwar!! Just when they started to shift gears, Hooda has thrown it away. This was tossed up well wide of off, Hooda skips out of the crease, doesn't get to the pitch, but still goes through with the loft, skies it towards long-off, Bhuvi misjudged it at first, but did well to hang onto it over his head. <b>Deepak Hooda c Bhuvneshwar b Karn Sharma 7(9)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Karn Sharma to Deepak Hooda, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Deepak Hooda, 2 runs, again, these two sneak in a second. Karn drags the length back as Hooda shimmies down, the batsman pushes it in front of deep extra cover, hares across for the second and had to put in the dive]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Deepak Hooda, no run, floated up outside off, Hooda comes down the track and pads it away, he couldn't get to the pitch of the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Smith, 1 run, uses his feet, gets to the pitch of the ball and drills it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, Smith on the move now. This was not all that short, he uses the depth of the crease and cuts it right between two fielders, split cover-point and backward point to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Smith, 2 runs, flighted outside off, Smith advances down the wicket and whips it to the right of long-on, Warner sprints across and tidies up]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Karn Sharma [1.0-0-5-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to S Smith, 1 run, full and way outside off from Henriques, Smith goes a long way across his stumps and works it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to S Smith, 2 runs, that's excellent running from Smith, pushes a full ball in front of long-on. Ishant was late to get across, Smith runs hard and gets back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, third boundary of the over, slower bouncer from Henriques, Smith rocks back and pulls it behind square on the on-side, third boundary off the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to S Smith, no run, another slower ball from Henriques, Smith looks to cut and misses, the off-cutter from Henriques, the ball goes to the keeper after two bounces]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, this is excellent batting from Smith, another slower ball from Henriques, Smith swivels across, rolls his wrists and pulls it behind square, bisects the two men in the deep for another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, no pace to work with, but Smith manufactures all the power himself, comes down the track, makes room and slaps it past cover for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>. RAJ are going nowhere in this chase. The required rate is now closing towards 14 RPO.]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Deepak Hooda, no run, slower short ball from Bopara, Hooda cuts it straight to the fielder at point, Smith wanted a run and has to hurry back]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to S Smith, 1 run, Smith shimmies down the track and chips the slower ball towards deep mid-wicket, another single added to the total]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, another slower ball from Bopara, comes down the track and dabs it away behind square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Deepak Hooda, 2 runs, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Hooda looks to drive and gets an inside edge, the ball rolls away towards long-on, Smith is back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to S Smith, 1 run, another slower ball from Bopara, driven down towards long-on for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, slower full toss from Bopara, punched down towards long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravi Bopara, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, it was the slower ball as well, Hooda flicked it towards mid-wicket and called for a quick single. Praveen fumbles and the run is completed with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Deepak Hooda, no run, short and wide from Henriques, Hooda feels for that, ends up playing away from his body and nearly nicks it to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to S Smith, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, worked towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Deepak Hooda, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Nair, <b>out</b> Caught by N Ojha!! The pressure of the chase gets to Karun, charges down the track, Henriques slips in the short ball. He was in no position on the pull, gets a fat top-edge to the left of the keeper. Ojha called for the catch, moved across and takes it safely. RAJ have lost their third wicket and are in trouble now. <b>Nair c N Ojha b Henriques 4(10)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Henriques to Nair, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Nair, <b>wide</b>, full and way outside off from Henriques, Karun was looking to go over extra cover and missed, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to S Smith, 1 run, another slower ball from Henriques, Smith shuffles across and nudges it towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Nair, 1 run, Henriques starts with a slower short ball, Karun cuts it square past point for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Moises Henriques, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Smith, no run, the slider from Karn, Smith made room for the cut and gets an inside edge, the ball went dangerously close to the leg-stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Nair, leg byes, 1 run, appeal for LBW, but the impact was well outside off, Karun was looking to play the lap sweep and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Smith, 1 run, tossed up and on the stumps, Smith jumps down the track and drives it against the spin, single to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Nair, 1 run, flighted delivery and on the stumps, Karun goes down on his knees, rolls his wrists and sweeps it behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Nair, 2 runs, tossed up and on off, Karun drives it to the left of long-off, Smith wants the second run and makes it with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Smith, 1 run, Smith shimmies down the track to a well flighted delivery and drives it down towards long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Karn Sharma, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for spin, Karn is into the attack..]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to Nair, no run, width on offer from Ishant, Karun cuts it straight to the fielder at backward point, just one run from the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to Nair, no run, back of a length and just outside off, dabbed in front of backward point, Karun wants a single and is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to Nair, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, driven straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to Nair, no run, on a good length and around the off-stump line, Karun defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to S Smith, 1 run, short of a length and on the stumps, flicked away in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to S Smith, no run, Ishant shortens the length as Smith came down the track, defended towards point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Nair, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Karun gets behind the line and blocks it]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to S Smith, 1 run, <b>dropped by Henriques</b>, Smith is living a charmed life, pitched up and on Smith's pads, he shuffled across and flicked it in the air over square leg. Henriques made a lot of ground from deep mid-wicket, gets to the ball and shells it as he slid. How costly will this life prove to be?]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four</b>, this was the awayswinger from Praveen, gets it to wobble in the air and nips away, lures Smith into the drive, finds the outside edge and the ball goes through the vacant slip cordon]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to S Smith, no run, on a good length and in that channel around off, Smith pushes forward and gets an inside edge towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to S Smith, no run, another shout for LBW, but this was going over the top. Pitched up and holding its line around middle, Smith was shuffling across on the flick and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to S Smith, no run, appeal for LBW, but the ball was slipping down leg, Smith was looking to flick and missed. The impact was outside leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Praveen Kumar [1.0-0-4-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Karun Nair, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to Watson, <b>out</b> Caught by P Kumar!! That's a half-hearted shot from Watson and he finds Praveen at mid-on. Huge blow for RAJ, this was pitched up and held its line around off, Watson was looking to play the flick over mid-wicket, looked like he checked it at the last moment, ends up spooning it to Praveen at mid-on. That's an absolute dolly, RAJ have lost both openers now. <b>Watson c P Kumar b Ishant 12(12) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ishant to Watson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to Watson, no run, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, defended towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to S Smith, 1 run, on a good length and on the stumps, Smith makes room outside leg-stump and guides it to the left of cover-point, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, width on offer from Ishant, Smith leans forward, presents the full face of the bat and caresses it through extra cover for another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to S Smith, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Smith presents the full face of the bat and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, Ishant is on the floor and the ball races away to the fence, full and just outside off, Smith presents the full face of the bat and punches it past mid-on. Ishant lost his balance and fell onto the ground on the followthrough]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ishant Sharma, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Watson, no run, short of a length and well outside off, Watson chops it hard and onto the ground, straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Watson, no run, on a good length and well outside off, driven straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four</b>, full and wide from Bhuvneshwar, Watson went hard on the drive, gets a thick edge that flies past the diving first slip fielder, another boundary for Watson]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, width on offer from Bhuvneshwar, Watson stands tall and punches it square past point, beats the fielder and races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to S Smith, 1 run, Smith gets lucky! The ball landed right in between two fielders. Warner ran across from mid-off, Karn came across from mid-on, both stopped for the other to take the catch, the ball landed right in between them. Going back to the ball, this was a mistimed pull from Smith, got a top-edge on the shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to S Smith, no run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, Smith presses across and punches it back at the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Watson, no run, another big inswinger from Praveen, Watson looks to flick and gets an inside edge onto the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Watson, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Watson stays behind the line and punches it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, that's sublime from Watson, swings this one onto Watson's pads, he gets inside the line and flicks it past square leg, beats the man getting across from the deep, off the mark with a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Watson, no run, fuller length delivery and swinging onto Watson's pads, he looks to flick and misses, the ball rolls away towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Watson, no run, on a good length and well outside off, Watson looks to drive and gets an inside edge. Ojha gets across quickly, puts in the dive and saves some runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Watson, no run, fuller length delivery and a hint of shape back into Watson, he prods across and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Praveen Kumar, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Steven Smith, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place for Praveen]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, <b>out</b> Caught by N Ojha!! Lovely riposte from Bhuvneshwar, pitched this one up and got it to nibble away a fraction, drew Rahane into the forward push, the outside edge is found. Ojha dives in front of first slip and holds onto a good catch. The orange-cap holder is dismissed cheaply, a huge wicket this for HYD. <b>Rahane c N Ojha b Bhuvneshwar 8(6) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, full and wide from Bhuvneshwar, that was there to be smashed, Rahane leans into the drive and hammers it past cover, the ball races away in a jiffy]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, no run, late away movement for Bhuvneshwar, nearly had Rahane in trouble, this was pitched up and shaped away very late, Rahane closed the face of the bat and gets a leading edge, the ball drops in front of the man at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>short, wide and four</b>, width on offer from Bhuvneshwar, Rahane quickly gets on top of the bounce and cracks it square of cover, the ball races away to the fence in a hurry]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, no run, short of a length and well outside off, cracked straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, no run, on a good length and a hint of away shape, Rahane presses forward and defends it towards cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rahane and Watson are at the crease. Rahane is on strike. Bhuvneshwar will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. Warner leads the team huddle. Watson and Rahane stroll into the middle..]]></line><line><![CDATA[Morgan's quickfire 28-ball 63 provided the much needed impetus to the innings. RAJ once again struggled at the death as they leaked 68 runs in the last 5 overs. The pitch is good for batting and HYD don't have either Boult or Steyn, so can defend this score? We shall find out soon as the run-chase is coming up in a short while...]]></line><line><![CDATA[Watson opted to bowl on an absolute belter and his bowlers couldn't respond. Warner and Dhawan got HYD off to a blazing start, but a troublesome back spasm cut short Warner's stay at the wicket. Dhawan, however, continued striking the ball with precision and notched up his 3rd fifty this season. After his dismissal, Morgan took up the mantle and carted the RAJ bowlers all over the park. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Bopara, 1 run, low full toss, flicked straight to the fielder at backward square leg, inside the ring. Just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to N Ojha, 1 run, 200 is up as Ojha mishits one to long-off. Length on the stumps, but Ojha didn't get under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to N Ojha, no run, Morris had a chance to run Bopara out but he calmly collects the ball and walks back. Gets the yorker right as he follows Ojha who was making room, inside-edged back down the track]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Bopara, 1 run, low full toss on the stumps, slogged on the bounce to Smith at long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Bopara, <b>wide</b>, Morris fires it well outside off, knows it is a wide after Bopara failed to reach it]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to N Ojha, 1 run, another low full toss on the stumps, flicked to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Bopara, 1 run, low full toss, hit straight to the fielder at long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Morris [3.0-0-32-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to N Ojha, <b>FOUR</b>, Tambe with a fumble now. Much like Smith he does all the hard work, running to his right at third man but allows the ball to slip under his body on the dive, it was sliced to his right and Tambe put in an awkward effort]]></line><line><![CDATA[Faulkner is fine, he is ready to bowl the final delivery of the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Bopara, 1 run, low full toss and Bopara clobbers it hard and at Faulkner, who stuck his left-hand out, taking evasive action, it hits the wrist and goes down. Only an insane man would even begin to think about calling that a <b>drop</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Bopara, no run, slower delivery outside off, Bopara slogs and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Bopara, <b>FOUR</b>, would you believe that - Smith has fumbled one? He is cross with himself and fists hard into the ground. Driven wide of him at long-off, he did all the hard work as he ran to his left and then slid but allowed it to slip through his hands. Did he get a bad bounce? Maybe but Smith is such a fine fielder that he expected to stop the four]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Bopara, no run, full and outside off, but Bopara had already made too much room outside leg and fails to reach it]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to N Ojha, 1 run, low full toss outside off, driven straight to the fielder at sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to N Ojha, <b>wide</b>, yorker length delivery outside off, called a wide as it was outside the tramline]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner [3.0-0-26-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to N Ojha, 1 run, slower delivery outside off, Ojha arrested his front foot push and found cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Bopara, 3 runs, look at the sprint from Tambe, he nearly outsprints a much younger Faulkner, but the Aussie gets ahead of his mate and pulls it back just inside the ropes before jumping over the LED ad boards. Short and pulled behind square, it needed a sprint which Faulkner provided along with Tambe]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Naman Ojha, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Eoin Morgan, <b>out</b> Caught by S Smith!! If this was the Chinnaswamy it would've been a six but here at Brabourne Eoin Morgan has picked out long-off. Another length delivery outside off, right in the hitting zone, Morgan times the loft pretty well, but flat to Smith who won't drop that. They check for the no-ball but Watson was fine there. <b>Eoin Morgan c S Smith b Watson 63(28) [4s-4 6s-5]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Watson to Eoin Morgan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Eoin Morgan, <b>SIX</b>, VVS and Murali clap and are all smiles in the Hyderabad camp. Full outside off, Eoin Morgan shuffles across deep inside the crease and gets under the lofted hit, hit clean and clears long-on comfortably. Eoin Morgan is hurting Rajasthan big time]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Eoin Morgan, 2 runs, length outside off, Eoin Morgan comes down the track and flat-bats it to the left of Binny at sweeper. Another two]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Eoin Morgan, 2 runs, full and outside off from round the wicket, carved to sweeper cover, where the fielder slides to keep it to two]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Watson [2.0-0-22-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, full outside off, driven square of the wicket, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Eoin Morgan, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>50 for Eoin Morgan</b>. Magnificent from the Irishman. Poor from Morris and he knew it, grunted out in frustration after slipping it down leg, all it needed was a deflection and Eoin Morgan got it done, beating short fine inside the ring]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Eoin Morgan, <b>SIX</b>, belted. Eoin Morgan charged the big Morris and carted it flat and into the sightscreen. It was bowled on a back of a length but Morgan timed it superbly. This must hurt Rajasthan now]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now Morris round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Eoin Morgan, 2 runs, fraction short outside off, cut late to square third man, for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Eoin Morgan, <b>wide</b>, short down leg, Eoin Morgan hooks and misses, called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Eoin Morgan, <b>FOUR</b>, poor from Hooda at point. Length outside off, Eoin Morgan times the square drive but hits it straight to the fielder and he has <b>nutmegged Hooda. Not quite Lionel Messi-esque on James Milner</b>, but it escapes to the boundary. Hooda is disappointed]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Bopara, 1 run, length outside off, punched to long-on, Eoin Morgan is back on strike]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Morris [2.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Eoin Morgan, <b>SIX</b>, another wristy special from Eoin Morgan. Bottom-handed too. He is so dominant with his bottom-hand. Sees the tossed up delivery outside off, gets forward and laces it flat and into the sightscreen. Nothing the bowler can do there, Eoin Morgan supplying the magic late on for the Hyderabad. 18 off that over]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Eoin Morgan, <b>FOUR</b>, what timing from Eoin Morgan. Another googly from Tambe, Eoin Morgan just wristed that drive through cover, in the air but wide of the fielder and long-off was just a mere spectator. The way he uncorks those wrists is the key to all his timing]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Eoin Morgan, 2 runs, the wrong 'un from Tambe, on the stumps, eased wide of long-off, Bopara wants two and they get it easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Eoin Morgan, <b>SIX</b>, this time he doesn't miss out. On middle and leg, Eoin Morgan gets forward and then hoicks across the line, gets enough bat to go all the way at deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Eoin Morgan, no run, short and wide outside off, poor delivery but Eoin Morgan cuts and finds cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Eoin Morgan, no run, Eoin Morgan has missed a high full toss down leg, into the hoick early and it hits the thigh and nearly falls on the stumps. That would've been some way to get out]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pravin Tambe [3.0-0-14-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out.</b> Perhaps Samson would've been best advised to go with two hands. He went instinctively with one and it didn't stick]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Bopara, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>dropped</b> but must say a very difficult chance for Samson. Faulkner induced the flashy drive from Bopara, away from the body, there was a slip in place but he too was wide. It would've carried comfortably to a regulation first slip, Samson had to go and went full length to his right, it hit the edge of the gloves and deflected away to the fence. Faulkner just turns away in disappointment]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Bopara, no run, angled across Bopara who watches it through to Samson. How often do you see that in T20s?]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, slower delivery on a back of a length outside off, punched to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Bopara, 1 run, pushed to mid-off, quick single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Replays in: No bat. Clean bowled</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravi Bopara, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dhawan, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Dhawan has a surprised smile on his face after being bowled. His wife is watching from the stands too. Length and pacy on off, Dhawan pre-meditated the reverse paddle and went for it but the ball was too quick and beats the shot. Not sure whether he edged it onto the stumps. Once the replay is in will confirm. <b>Dhawan b Faulkner 54(35) [4s-6 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Faulkner to Dhawan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, good length on the stumps, Eoin Morgan is on the walk, pushed to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner [2.0-0-19-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, predictably this one is fired in, maybe Dhawan was expecting it, reversed hit it wide of Tambe at short third. That spoils Deepak Hooda's over]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Dhawan, <b>SIX</b>, there was a fielder at deep backward square but the ball sailed over his head. Full on off, a top-edged slog sweep and Dhawan gets to <b>fifty</b> in the process. Warner and his mates are up to applaud that effort]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, flat on the stumps, punched past the left-hand of the diving Deepak Hooda]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Eoin Morgan, <b>wide</b>, fired down leg, Eoin Morgan sweeps and misses. Samson collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Eoin Morgan, 2 runs, punched through mid-wicket and two taken. Deepak Hooda isn't impressed - he shouts 'come on yaar' to the fielder running in]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Dhawan, 1 run, shortish down leg, pulled to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Dhawan, 2 runs, reverse paddled over Tambe at short third, he runs back and puts in the dive to pull it back to Jinks who was following up. Superb commitment from the old man - if I may call him so]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Eoin Morgan, <b>SIX</b>, tremendous blow from Eoin Morgan. He is so quick on his feet, jumps out to the slower delivery and then lofts the bowler way over long-off. Was more of a slice but still went quite a distance]]></line><line><![CDATA[Slip gone out. Mid-wicket in]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Eoin Morgan, <b>FOUR</b>, too full and too wide from Watson, outside off, Eoin Morgan leans forward and lifts it over cover with that unconventional technique of his, two bounces over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Eoin Morgan, no run, called one short ball for the over, dug in short, Eoin Morgan was looking to pull and then decided against it, swaying away]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Dhawan, 1 run, Dhawan makes room and then flat-bats the cutter to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, good length outside off, Eoin Morgan skips out and punches it square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[Watson has a wide slip in place. More of a third slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Dhawan, 1 run, length outside off, Dhawan is on the walk as he belts it to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Watson [1.0-0-9-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Dhawan, 1 run, wayward full toss, way outside off, Dhawan reaches out and hits it straight to the fielder at deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Eoin Morgan, leg byes, 1 run, Deepak Hooda is watching the batsman till the last moment, again follows Eoin Morgan who was down the track, a leg bye as it is off the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Dhawan, 1 run, Deepak Hooda fires it down leg, seeing Dhawan advance, nudged to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Tom Moody</b> on air: 'Warner has had a slight spasm in the back - which flared up again. He is a tough character, he should be back soon']]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, fraction short outside off, flashed to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Eoin Morgan, no run, down leg, swung straight to the fielder at short fine leg. Eoin Morgan missed out there]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Dhawan, 1 run, from round the wicket, on the stumps, reverse paddled to short third man, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Deepak Hooda [1.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Eoin Morgan, no run, pushed further outside off, Eoin Morgan gets forward and opens the face of the bat to drive to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Dhawan, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, driven to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, low full toss, driven to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Eoin Morgan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Henriques, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Double fist-pump from Tambe. That means only one thing. A wicket. Henriques this time made room to go over mid-wicket, this was bowled slower and beat the batsman's shot, who was early into the execution. Ball hits timber. <b>Henriques b Tambe 20(21) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Tambe to Henriques, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Henriques, no run, Henriques is charging Tambe but the bowler keeps his wits about him and fires it into the pads, inside-edged back down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Dhawan, 1 run, 'catch it' shrieked Tambe, but Dhawan gets away as the ball is fielded on the bounce at long-off, Dhawan comes down the track and tonked it on the full]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Henriques, no run, back of the hand slower delivery outside off, very full, dug out to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Henriques, 2 runs, length outside off, Henriques gets forward and drives on the rise, wide of long-off for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Henriques, <b>FOUR</b>, a carbon copy of the first boundary in the over. Faulkner isn't impressed. But this was hit with more power, skipped across the turf and Binny running and diving at deep mid-wicket didn't even get a hand on it. Takes his time getting up too]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dhawan, 1 run, length outside off, slogged to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Henriques, 1 run, short of length on off, punched over the leaping Faulkner, hit hard into the ground so it cleared Faulkner]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Henriques, <b>FOUR</b>, lackadaisical from Binny but I will give him breathing space as it is very hot out there. Short outside off, pulled over mid-wicket, Binny runs lazily and then puts in an even more lazy dive parrying the ball into the cushions]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner [1.0-0-7-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Henriques, 1 run, Tambe nearly yorks Henriques. But the batsman having made room somehow manages to squeeze that to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Dhawan, 1 run, very full outside off, jammed out to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Dhawan, <b>SIX</b>, that is a flat slog sweep over deep mid-wicket for six. Pre-meditated but Dhawan nailed that kneeling down and it skimmed over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Henriques, 1 run, fired in on middle, pushed off the front foot to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Henriques, no run, Henriques skips out once more and looks to go over cover, inside-edged onto the boot and the ball goes to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Henriques, no run, Henriques comes down the track and nearly yorks himself, digs it out to the right of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Dhawan, no run, Dhawan has shuffled well across outside off to that even before Kulkarni delivered the ball, the bowler fired it following Dhawan who mistimed the drive to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, and now four. Dhawan makes room and then marmalises the length delivery through cover. Gave it all and sweeper was just ball-watching that time]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Dhawan, no run, beautiful delivery from Kulkarni and he beats Dhawan all ends up, this one just shaped away slightly off the seam beating Dhawan's walking drive on the rise]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Dhawan, no run, that is loose from Dhawan. Bit of extra bounce outside off for Kulkarni, Dhawan looks to guide it to third man and nearly edges behind]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Dhawan, <b>wide</b>, seeing Dhawan charge he fires it way outside off, called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, this short ball sits up for Dhawan, who rocks back and pulls over mid-wicket, one bounce over the ropes. That was begging to be hit]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Dhawan, no run, slower delivery on off, tapped with soft hands to Jinks at point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhawal Kulkarni [1.0-0-10-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Dhawan, 1 run, punched wide of Smith at long-on, there is a fumble but they settle for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Henriques, 1 run, very full on middle, eased to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Henriques, no run, magnificent from Jinks at cover. Went airborne to his left at cover and grabbed it one-handed. Saved four and that stop draws Tambe and Watson to go up to the fielder to applaud the effort. Sensational stuff]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Henriques, no run, flat outside off, cut straight to the fielder at point. That's three dots in a row]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Henriques, no run, Henriques comes down the track and punches it straight to Jinks at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Henriques, no run, skids on, but Henriques defends to point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pravin Tambe, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dhawan, no run, short of length outside off, Dhawan opens the face of the bat and dabs it to short third - to which Rameez on air somehow invents a new fielding position and calls it 'short fine point']]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dhawan, 2 runs, pitched up outside off, Dhawan gets forward and drives to deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dhawan, no run, full on the stumps, driven sweetly, too sweetly to allow the quick single to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dhawan, no run, length outside off, punched off the front foot but straight to the fielder at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Henriques, 1 run, full on middle and leg, a bit of an inside edge onto the pads on the flick, the ball dribbles to square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Henriques, <b>FOUR</b>, Faulkner starts poorly, length outside off, Henriques took a step forward and sliced it over point. Got it over the infield which meant an easy boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Henriques, 1 run, good length on middle and leg, Henriques shuffles across a tad and nudges it to fine leg, to get off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Henriques, no run, that stopped on Henriques who adjusted and didn't go with hard hands, stabbed at it but softened the impact, so the ball dies down on the way to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Henriques, no run, Watson is down but nothing alarming. Went down after delivering the ball, length on the stumps, pushed to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Moises Henriques, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Warner, <b>out</b> Caught by Samson!! An Aussie gets an Aussie. <b>A New South Welshman gets a New South Welshman.</b> Watson has his hands up in celebration. Length delivery outside off, Warner gave room to thrash that through the off-side but feathered an edge to Samson. <b>Warner c Samson b Watson 24(18) [4s-5]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Watson to Warner, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, now brutalised over point. Short and outside off, Warner goes up and over, carving it in the air to get consecutive boundaries]]></line><line><![CDATA[That shot brings up 400 runs for Warner this season]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, that is touch from Warner. Sees the width from Watson, well outside off, he opens the face of the bat and guides it between short third and backward point. Split the gap perfectly]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Watson, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Warner, 1 run, short of length on off, tapped with soft hands in front of mid-off for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Understandable to see the ball slipping out of the bowler's hands as the heat and humdity can cause a lot of sweating]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Warner, <b>5 wides</b>, that is a bad ball and Morris knows it, he apologises immediately. Slipped out of his hands as he slinged the full toss well down leg, gave the keeper no chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third man back, sweeper in on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Warner, no run, yorker length outside off, dug out to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[Warner is still grimacing. As soon as he hit it to the boundary, one saw his face contort]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, first time Morris has erred in the over and Warner puts him away. It was back of a length outside off, Warner flat-bats it past Morris and beats mid-on too]]></line><line><![CDATA[Morris too has a slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Warner, no run, Morris again cramps Warner for room with a pacy back of a length delivery on the stumps, Warner stays leg-side of the ball and dabs it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Warner, 2 runs, looked like a change of pace, the cutter, Warner hops a little and wrists it between mid-on and mid-wicket for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Warner, no run, very full outside off, dug out to mid-off, no chance of a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[What do we have here between overs - Warner is down on the ground and the physio was pressing his back. One saw a grimace from Warner after he got up. But for now he continues to bat on]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, silky smooth from Dhawan. On a back of a length and outside off, Dhawan leant forward and presented the fullest of blades as he punched it past cover, the timing was serene. Balance, poise, technical execution of that shot was of the highest quality]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Warner, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Warner gets forward and slices the lofted hit through cover-point, but there is a man in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Warner, no run, the off-cutter outside off, Warner flat-bats it straight to the fielder at short cover. Mistimed it]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Dhawan, 1 run, length on middle and leg, tucked to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, too much width from Kulkarni and Dhawan has flashed that away to the third man fence. Came off a thick outside edge but it raced away over slip giving third man no chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[A lone slip in place for Kulkarni]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Dhawan, no run, pitched up outside off, Dhawan leans into the cover drive but finds Faulkner at cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhawal Kulkarni, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Morris got steepling bounce and caused Warner problems in that over]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Warner, no run, that is a fine opening over apart from the first delivery, another delivery that rises on Warner who adjusts and dabs the cut to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Warner, no run, Morris is hitting the bat hard, dug in short and climbs on Warner who looks to pull and splices it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Warner, no run, this one kept a touch low, short of length outside off, Warner rises to tap it to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Warner, no run, again Morris gets disconcerting bounce from a length, pitches outside leg and raps Warner high on the thigh pad, Warner was on the hop there]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Dhawan, 1 run, short of length outside off, bit of extra bounce, cut to square third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Dhawan, leg byes, <b>FOUR</b>, poor first delivery from Morris, down leg, all it needed was a faint tickle which Dhawan provided, beats Tambe at short fine and races away. Hello - hang on; it has been given as leg byes]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Morris, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, 13 off the opening over. Actually Deepak Hooda did well there, cramped Warner on the cut but he managed to get it past the dive of Jinks at cover-point. Not well-timed but once it beat Rahane it was four]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, there goes Warner. One ball is enough for a sighter. Down the track and then smashes it flat over cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Warner, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Warner makes room and tries to go inside out but hits it straight to the fielder at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Dhawan, 1 run, Dhawan comes down the track and then works this through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, elegantly driven wide of cover. Tossed up and outside off, Dhawan got forward and drove it on the rise and in the gap. Nice way to get off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[One ball into the match and Dhawan already has issues with movement behind the bowler's arm. Nuisance this!]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Dhawan, no run, flatter and on the stumps, Dhawan gets forward to block with bat and pad close together]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhawan and Warner are at the crease. Dhawan is on strike. Deepak Hooda will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A surprise first up it will be Deepak Hooda to begin proceedings. The countdown begins and ends quickly. Hooda will come from round the wicket. No close-in catchers in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[All set for the action. It is a scorching hot afternoon in Mumbai. Will definitely test the players in the middle. Let's see how they cope up with such stifling conditions. The Rajasthan jog out as do the openers. For Hyderabad to have any chance it is up to Dhawan and Warner to fire. Whether they can do so remains to be seen]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajasthan</b> (Playing XI): Ajinkya Rahane, Shane Watson(c), Karun Nair, Steven Smith, Sanju Samson(w), Deepak Hooda, James Faulkner, Stuart Binny, Dhawal Kulkarni, Chris Morris, Pravin Tambe]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hyderabad</b> (Playing XI): David Warner(c), Shikhar Dhawan, Naman Ojha(w), Moises Henriques, Eoin Morgan, Ravi Bopara, Hanuma Vihari, Karn Sharma, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Praveen Kumar, Ishant Sharma]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Warner:</b> 'We need to score more runs in the middle. We have come in today with a lot of pride and will to win. <b>Ishant Sharma</b> is in for <b>Bipul Sharma</b>. <b>Ravi Bopara</b> replaces <b>Dale Steyn</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Watson:</b> 'We will bowl. No particular reason, nice grass cover, will not change a lot. We just need to continue to get better, need to play the perfect game. Two changes, <b>Chris Morris</b> is in place of <b>Tim Southee</b> and <b>Pravin Tambe</b> replaces <b>Rajat Bhatia</b>.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajasthan have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather Report:</b>  It's a clear day with temperatures expected to hover around 32 degree Celsius. But with humidity levels at 72%, it's going to be an energy sapping day, especially for the team fielding first.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-Head record:</b> The two teams have faced each other 6 times with the Rajasthan enjoying a 4-2 winning advantage.]]></line><line><![CDATA[On the other hand, Hyderabad have struggled to make the most of their quality overseas professionals. The gaping hole in the middle order hasn't been sorted out and the team depends heavily on its two openers, David Warner and Shikhar Dhawan. Kane Williamson has been surprisingly jettisoned while Eoin Morgan and Ravi Bopara haven't made most of their opportunities. Hyderabad' bowling has been their strong point, but the team management has been forced to break the Steyn-Boult combination, owing to their weak batting line-up. Coach Tom Moody has conceded that the middle order has been a huge cause of concern. With tougher matches lying ahead, the Hyderabad franchise can't afford any more losses.]]></line><line><![CDATA[After being winless for five matches, the Watson-led Rajasthan stormed back to winning ways, thrashing Delhi in their last match. With 14 points in their kitty, they are pretty well placed at second position. There's an incentive for finishing in the top two, with the teams getting two chances at reaching the final. For that to happen though, Rajasthan can't falter going into the final stages of the tournament. Ajinkya Rahane is the owner of the orange cap while Shane Watson and Steven Smith have held their own with the bat. Tim Southee has been a revelation with the new ball but Rajasthan must solve their death overs problems with the ball. It's an issue that has cost them more than just one match this season and it might come back to haunt them - going into the business end of the tournament.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>14:45 Local Time, 09:15 GMT</b>: It's Match 41 of the Indian Premier League and Rajasthan host Hyderabad. A completely different scenario for both teams today. A win will all but seal RAJ's place in the playoffs and put HYD's chances in jeopardy. On the other hand, HYD need to win to keep themselves in the hunt for a place in the playoffs. Mumbai's Brabourne Stadium will play host to what should be a battle between the two Australian skippers, Warner v Watson.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview</b><br/><br/>Two play-off spots are potentially up for grabs and five teams are vying for it in IPL 2015. Hyderabad are currently in the tail-end of the mid-table scramble. One slip-up and their chances could take a big dent.<br/><br/>Rajasthan, on the other hand, are in a comfortable position and they will be buoyed by the fact that they have finally got back to winning ways. The win over Delhi has boosted their campaign after a middle period during which they failed to win. The main aim for Rajasthan will be to sustain their consistency and ensure they finish in the top two.<br/><br/>Venue: Brabourne Stadium, Mumbai<br/><br/>Date: May 7, 2015<br/><br/>Time: 16:00 IST<br/><br/>Weather: High of 35 degrees with clear skies<br/><br/><b>Team news</b><br/><br/><b>Rajasthan</b><br/><br/>The team ticked all the right boxes in the game against Delhi and they may not change the combination.<br/><br/><b>Probable XI</b><br/><br/>1 Ajinkya Rahane, 2 Shane Watson (c), 3 Karun Nair, 4 Steven Smith, 5 Sanju Samson (wk), 6 Stuart Binny, 7 Deepak Hooda, 8 James Faulkner, 9 Rajat Bhatia, 10 Dhawal Kulkarni, 11 Tim Southee<br/><br/><b>Hyderabad</b><br/><br/>The team is still heavily reliant on the contributions of David Warner and Shikhar Dhawan. Against the Kolkata, the bowling lacked purpose, with the likes of Bhuvneshwar Kumar and Dale Steyn conceding more than nine runs per over. The fact that Praveen Kumar bowled only one over was baffling. With Eoin Morgan struggling and the rest of the Indian bench proving to be ineffective, Hyderabad will have to strengthen their batting if they are to make a mark.<br/><br/><b>Probable XI</b><br/><br/>1 David Warner (c), 2 Shikhar Dhawan, 3 Naman Ojha (wk), 4 Moises Henriques, 5 Eoin Morgan/Kane Williamson, 6 Hanuma Vihari, 7 Karn Sharma, 8 Bipul Sharma, 9 Praveen Kumar, 10 Bhuvneshwar Kumar, 11 Dale Steyn/Trent Boult<br/><br/><b>Stats</b><br/><br/>- Shikhar Dhawan needs 59 runs to reach the 1000-run mark for Hyderabad while David Warner needs 90 runs.<br/><br/>- Ajinkya Rahane needs 63 runs to become the second Rajasthan batsman to reach 2,000 runs after Shane Watson.<br/><br/><b>Quotes</b><br/><br/>The next five games are on good wickets and our bowlers have been defending well so we're looking forward to playing there on those good wickets: David Warner is still positive despite losing to Kolkata.<br/><br/>I knew I was batting really well and played a rash shot in the last match. I was very hurt by that and wanted to make this count: Ajinkya Rahane after his unbeaten 91 against Delhi.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hyderabad</b> (From): David Warner(c), Shikhar Dhawan, Naman Ojha(w), Moises Henriques, Eoin Morgan, Hanuma Vihari, Bipul Sharma, Karn Sharma, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Dale Steyn, Praveen Kumar, Ishant Sharma, Lokesh Rahul, Parvez Rasool, Ashish Reddy, Ricky Bhui, Chama Milind, Kane Williamson, Ravi Bopara, Trent Boult, Prasanth Padmanabhan, Siddarth Kaul]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajasthan</b> (From): Shane Watson(c), Ajinkya Rahane, Karun Nair, Steven Smith, Sanju Samson(w), Deepak Hooda, Stuart Binny, James Faulkner, Rajat Bhatia, Tim Southee, Dhawal Kulkarni, Abhishek Nayar, Ben Cutting, Dishant Yagnik, Vikramjeet Malik, Ankit Sharma, Rahul Tewatia, Pravin Tambe, Chris Morris, Dinesh Salunkhe, Rusty Theron, Pardeep Sahu, Brainder Sran, Sagar Trivedi]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>201</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>4</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Hyderabad">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1446</playerid>
					<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhawan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhawan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>54</runs>
					<balls>35</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Faulkner</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7789</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1739</playerid>
					<name>David Warner</name>
					<batsman-name>Warner</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Warner</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>24</runs>
					<balls>18</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Watson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>158</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sanju Samson</fielder>
						<fielderId>8271</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1437</playerid>
					<name>Moises Henriques</name>
					<batsman-name>Henriques</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Henriques</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>20</runs>
					<balls>21</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Tambe</bowler>
					<bowlerId>9237</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>624</playerid>
					<name>Eoin Morgan</name>
					<batsman-name>E Morgan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Eoin Morgan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>63</runs>
					<balls>28</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>5</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Watson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>158</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Steven Smith</fielder>
						<fielderId>2250</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>571</playerid>
					<name>Ravi Bopara</name>
					<batsman-name>R Bopara</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bopara</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>17</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1599</playerid>
					<name>Naman Ojha</name>
					<batsman-name>N Ojha</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>N Ojha</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>8</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8424</playerid>
					<name>Hanuma Vihari</name>
					<batsman-name>Vihari</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Vihari</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1844</playerid>
					<name>Karn Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Karn Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Karn Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1726</playerid>
					<name>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</name>
					<batsman-name>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>592</playerid>
					<name>Praveen Kumar</name>
					<batsman-name>P Kumar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>P Kumar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>702</playerid>
					<name>Ishant Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Ishant</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ishant</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1739</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>48</runs>
				<overs>4.3</overs>
				<batsman>David Warner</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Warner</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1437</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>89</runs>
				<overs>10.3</overs>
				<batsman>Moises Henriques</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Henriques</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1446</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>127</runs>
				<overs>14.2</overs>
				<batsman>Shikhar Dhawan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dhawan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>624</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>180</runs>
				<overs>17.4</overs>
				<batsman>Eoin Morgan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>E Morgan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>10</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>5</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>15</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Rajasthan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>9427</playerid>
					<name>Deepak Hooda</name>
					<bowler-name>Deepak Hooda</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Deepak Hooda</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>34</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8333</playerid>
					<name>Chris Morris</name>
					<bowler-name>C Morris</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>C Morris</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>38</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>7</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1451</playerid>
					<name>Dhawal Kulkarni</name>
					<bowler-name>D Kulkarni</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>D Kulkarni</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>19</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>158</playerid>
					<name>Shane Watson</name>
					<bowler-name>Watson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Watson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7789</playerid>
					<name>James Faulkner</name>
					<bowler-name>Faulkner</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Faulkner</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>37</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9237</playerid>
					<name>Pravin Tambe</name>
					<bowler-name>Tambe</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Tambe</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>32</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1447</playerid>
					<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
					<bowler-name>A Rahane</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rahane</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8257</playerid>
					<name>Karun Nair</name>
					<bowler-name>Nair</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nair</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2250</playerid>
					<name>Steven Smith</name>
					<bowler-name>S Smith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Smith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8271</playerid>
					<name>Sanju Samson</name>
					<bowler-name>Samson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Samson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1530</playerid>
					<name>Stuart Binny</name>
					<bowler-name>Binny</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Binny</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>194</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>7</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Rajasthan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1447</playerid>
					<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
					<batsman-name>A Rahane</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rahane</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>8</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Bhuvneshwar</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1726</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Naman Ojha</fielder>
						<fielderId>1599</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>158</playerid>
					<name>Shane Watson</name>
					<batsman-name>Watson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Watson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>12</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Ishant</bowler>
					<bowlerId>702</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Praveen Kumar</fielder>
						<fielderId>592</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2250</playerid>
					<name>Steven Smith</name>
					<batsman-name>S Smith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Smith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>68</runs>
					<balls>40</balls>
					<fours>9</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>R Bopara</bowler>
					<bowlerId>571</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8257</playerid>
					<name>Karun Nair</name>
					<batsman-name>Nair</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nair</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Henriques</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1437</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Naman Ojha</fielder>
						<fielderId>1599</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9427</playerid>
					<name>Deepak Hooda</name>
					<batsman-name>Deepak Hooda</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Deepak Hooda</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>7</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Karn Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1844</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</fielder>
						<fielderId>1726</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7789</playerid>
					<name>James Faulkner</name>
					<batsman-name>Faulkner</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Faulkner</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>30</runs>
					<balls>19</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Bhuvneshwar</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1726</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ravi Bopara</fielder>
						<fielderId>571</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8271</playerid>
					<name>Sanju Samson</name>
					<batsman-name>Samson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Samson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>21</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Bhuvneshwar</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1726</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1530</playerid>
					<name>Stuart Binny</name>
					<batsman-name>Binny</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Binny</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8333</playerid>
					<name>Chris Morris</name>
					<batsman-name>C Morris</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>C Morris</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>34</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1451</playerid>
					<name>Dhawal Kulkarni</name>
					<batsman-name>D Kulkarni</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>D Kulkarni</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9237</playerid>
					<name>Pravin Tambe</name>
					<batsman-name>Tambe</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Tambe</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1447</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>8</runs>
				<overs>0.6</overs>
				<batsman>Ajinkya Rahane</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Rahane</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>158</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>30</runs>
				<overs>3.6</overs>
				<batsman>Shane Watson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Watson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8257</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>45</runs>
				<overs>7.3</overs>
				<batsman>Karun Nair</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Nair</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9427</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>77</runs>
				<overs>10.6</overs>
				<batsman>Deepak Hooda</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Deepak Hooda</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>2250</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>121</runs>
				<overs>14.2</overs>
				<batsman>Steven Smith</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Smith</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7789</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>145</runs>
				<overs>17.1</overs>
				<batsman>James Faulkner</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Faulkner</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8271</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>157</runs>
				<overs>17.4</overs>
				<batsman>Sanju Samson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Samson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>1</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>6</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Hyderabad">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1726</playerid>
					<name>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</name>
					<bowler-name>Bhuvneshwar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bhuvneshwar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>44</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>592</playerid>
					<name>Praveen Kumar</name>
					<bowler-name>P Kumar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>P Kumar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>40</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>702</playerid>
					<name>Ishant Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Ishant</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ishant</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1844</playerid>
					<name>Karn Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Karn Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Karn Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>28</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1437</playerid>
					<name>Moises Henriques</name>
					<bowler-name>Henriques</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Henriques</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>29</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>571</playerid>
					<name>Ravi Bopara</name>
					<bowler-name>R Bopara</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bopara</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>22</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1739</playerid>
					<name>David Warner</name>
					<bowler-name>Warner</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Warner</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1446</playerid>
					<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhawan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhawan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1599</playerid>
					<name>Naman Ojha</name>
					<bowler-name>N Ojha</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>N Ojha</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>624</playerid>
					<name>Eoin Morgan</name>
					<bowler-name>E Morgan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Eoin Morgan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8424</playerid>
					<name>Hanuma Vihari</name>
					<bowler-name>Vihari</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Vihari</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



