<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14616" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>22nd Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Rajasthan</home>
		<away>Bangalore</away>
		<teamsabbr>JAI vs BLR</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>JAI</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>BLR</awayabbr>
		<homeId>64</homeId>
		<awayId>59</awayId>
		<venue>Sardar Patel Stadium, Ahmedabad</venue>
		<startdate>24 04 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>24 04 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Bangalore</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Bangalore won by 9 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Bangalore</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>9</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Marais Erasmus</Name>
			<Country>RSA</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>S Ravi</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Anil Chaudhary</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Chinmay Sharma</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>14:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150424173306</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>BLR</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>JAI</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>134</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>1</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>16.1</batteamovers>
		<status>Bangalore won by 9 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>370</playerid>
			<name>AB de Villiers*</name>
			<batsman-name>de Villiers</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>de Villiers</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>47</runs>
			<balls-faced>34</balls-faced>
			<fours>6</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>1413</playerid>
			<name>Virat Kohli</name>
			<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Kohli</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>62</runs>
			<balls-faced>46</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>3</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>9427</playerid>
			<name>Deepak Hooda*</name>
			<bowler-name>Deepak Hooda</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Deepak Hooda</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>0.1</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>4</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1451</playerid>
			<name>Dhawal Kulkarni</name>
			<bowler-name>D Kulkarni</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>D Kulkarni</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>26</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>131</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>247</playerid>
<name>Chris Gayle</name>
<player-runs>20</player-runs>
<player-balls>17</player-balls>
<runs>36</runs>
<wicket-nbr>1</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>158</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Watson</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>0</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>5</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>5</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[6 2 1 2 4 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 6 1 1 . 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 1 2 1 . 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/JAI_BLR_APR24/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[That's all we have for you from this game. However, the IPL goes on as we have a double-header coming your way tomorrow. First up, MUM take on HYD at Wankhede and then we have CHN locking horns with PUN at Chepauk. Join us for those two games. Until then, take care and Cya!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Let's have a look at some of the best <b>tweets</b> from this game]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sid Mallya:</b> Yeeeeeeesssssss!!!!! Exactly what was needed to get our season back on track!! Awesome win! #BLR #RAJvBLR #IPL]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Aakash Chopra:</b> #BLR's weaker link won them this game...restricting #RAJ for 130 was commendable. 2 losses in a row after 5 wins. Wake up call for #RAJ. #IPL]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ayaz Memon:</b> Facile but very important win for Bangalore. Also signals perhaps a turnaround in the league. Now for Mumbai to come good tomorrow!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Yohan Blake:</b> Good win @BLRTweets we needed that]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Kaif:</b> Clinical victory by @BLRTweets , they looked completely in control from the moment they won the toss! Congratulations #IPL2015]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Starc:</b> "I wouldn't say 100%, but I am feeling good. I am really happy to be playing for BLR. There is no bowler in the world who is 100%. I don't know, trade secrets (bowling the yorkers at the death). I leaked a few runs at the start, I try to swing the new ball. These are different conditions, but I am bowling well, so I don't need to change too much with my bowling."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Starc</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his bowling figures of <b>4-0-22-3</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kohli:</b> "We wanted that sort of a performance. This might be a momentum change for us. It was a timely win for us. I had to (asked if he had a talk with the team) and told the guys to visualise who you are playing against. The boys responded beautifully. We know we are a team that can play like that, it was the difference today. The intensity was top notch and one that any captain can be proud of. I didn't want to let things go like they were, but it's all about believing that you can go out there and win. Definitely we (himself, Gayle and ABD) are the ones that are batting mainly for BLR. ABD has to come in at No.3, he is the best batsman in the world and was a pleasure batting with him today."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Watson:</b> "We had a really good crack out there (talking about the bowling). We were short on runs. Bangalore were superb today. They outplayed us in all departments. Virat (Kohli) and ABD then finished the game off. 160-170 was a minimum on this wicket. There is no excuse to losing a game. As long as we learn from it and perform better in the next game. We just need to turn this momentum around. We should make sure we get more things right next game."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier in the day, it was Yuzvendra Chahal, who landed decisive blows with his leg-spin. Mitchell Starc followed it up by bowling with unrelenting control in the slog overs and picked up three scalps. Their fielding too was sharp, with Dinesh Karthik taking a splendid catch to send James Faulkner back to the pavilion. The BLR camp would be relieved to get back to winning ways. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[BLR's batsmen backed up their bowlers by putting up a fine performance as the visitors registered a facile win. It was Virat Kohli, who unfurled a series of crunching shots. Kohli's knock can be encapsulated by how he advanced down the track to smack Shane Watson for a six in the 14th over.  AB de Villiers too played an enterprising knock and gave Kohli valuable support. He targeted the main spinner in the opposition, Pravin Tambe, and collected two boundaries in the 9th over.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Both BLR batsmen congratulate each other. Kohli is pumped up with the win. RAJ players shake hands with the batsmen and then walk off the field. The BLR players shake hands with their counterparts as well as the two not-out batsmen.]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>BLR win!</b> Their second of the season. RAJ slip to their second consecutive defeat. It was a juicy full toss from round the wicket, de Villiers had to put it in the gap, he did it with ease through mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Deepak Hooda, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to de Villiers, 1 run, AB shimmies down the track, yorks himself but manages to dig it out to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to de Villiers, no run, full delivery around off, de Villiers mistimes the drive back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Kohli, 1 run, Kulkarni fires a low full toss outside off, Kohli backs away as he advances, reaches out and drives square of the wicket, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Kohli, 2 runs, Kohli gives the charge, Kulkarni digs it in halfway down the pitch, Kohli pulls it in front of square for a couple. BLR one hit away from winning the game]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to de Villiers, 1 run, good length ball on the stumps, de Villiers shuffles across and knocks it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Kohli, 1 run, banged in short, without much venom, Kohli hammers the pull straight to deep square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhawal Kulkarni [3.0-0-20-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Kohli, 1 run, another quicker one around off, Kohli goes hard on the drive, the inside edge rolls to the on-side and the batsmen pick a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Kohli, no run, flatter and on the stumps, Kohli mistimes the punch back down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to de Villiers, 1 run, fired full and outside off, de Villiers drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Kohli, 1 run, Tambe overcompensates and bowls a half tracker, Kohli pulls it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Kohli, <b>SIX</b>, smoked! Flighted delivery on the stumps, Kohli dances down the wicket, gets to the pitch of the ball and sends it sailing into the crowd at long-on. That was a superb shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to de Villiers, 1 run, nice floaty delivery, de Villiers drives to cover, Watson misfields and allows the run to be taken]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pravin Tambe [3.0-0-26-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to de Villiers, 1 run, pitched up outside off, de Villiers opens the bat face and drives square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, smashed! ABD skips down the wicket, converts this into a full length delivery and drills it straight down the ground, bisecting the two fielders at long-on and long-off to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to de Villiers, 2 runs, banged in halfway down the wicket, no real pace on that, de Villiers rocks back and pulls it in front of square, long-on tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Kohli, 1 run, Kohli brings up his <b>second fifty</b> this season. He points his bat towards the dugout and pumps his fists. ABD walks up to him and congratulates him. Coming to the ball, slower delivery on off, Kohli nudges it wide of mid-wicket to get to the landmark]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Kohli, 2 runs, again the duo showing their athleticism. Back of a length delivery, Kohli works it with soft hands in front of square on the leg-side, the call was for two and they get it with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Kohli, <b>SIX</b>, fantastic shot! That is a tremendous hit from the BLR skipper. Watson saw the batsman advance and pulled the length back, Kohli managed to get under it and smacked it straight down the ground for a maximum]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Watson [2.0-0-7-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Kohli, 1 run, Faulkner drifts onto Kohli's pads, he leans forward and clips it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Kohli, no run, fullish and outside off, Kohli drives and picks out cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Kohli, no run, full delivery on the stumps, Kohli works it to mid-wicket, Nair fumbles but the duo don't risk a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to de Villiers, 1 run, slower delivery from Faulkner, de Villiers walks across, is deceived by that and checks the shot, single taken to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Kohli, 1 run, angled across the right-hander, Kohli uses that and steers it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Kohli, 2 runs, once again these two steal a second, on a length close to off, Kohli goes hard on the drive, the ball squirts off the inside edge to the right of mid-wicket, put pressure on the fielder and come back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner [1.0-0-12-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Kohli, 1 run, flighted delivery just outside off, Kohli drives it to long-off and retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Kohli, 2 runs, bit more air on this delivery, Kohli comes down the track and lofts it to the left of long-on, Kulkarni runs across and keeps it to a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Kohli, no run, pushed through outside off, Kohli slashes and the outside edge travels quickly to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Kohli, no run, trifle short and outside off, Kohli cuts and finds Nair at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to de Villiers, 1 run, flatter and around off, de Villiers backs away slightly and punches to deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Kohli, 1 run, quicker, fuller and on the stumps, Kohli whips it along the ground to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pravin Tambe [2.0-0-21-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Kohli, 1 run, another single easily taken, Morris keeps it back of a length, Kohli runs it off the face to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to de Villiers, 1 run, back of a length around off, de Villiers steers it with an open bat face to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Kohli, 1 run, <b>direct-hit and ABD would have been in trouble.</b> The slower delivery, leg-cutter from Morris, Kohli dabs it to the right of the keeper, Samson moves across quickly and fires a throw at the striker's end, ABD was well short of the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Kohli, no run, full delivery, almost a yorker, Kohli squeezes it to Smith at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to de Villiers, 1 run, dugs in short and on leg-stump, de Villiers helps it down to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Kohli, 1 run, good length ball just outside off, Kohli drives it on the up to mid-off, sets off immediately for the single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Morris [2.0-0-18-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Kohli, 1 run, Kohli jumps out of the crease, Kulkarni follows him with a full delivery, eased down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to de Villiers, 1 run, off-cutter that angles in, de Villiers nudges it wide of mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to de Villiers, 2 runs, again, Kulkarni doesn't pitch the ball up, offers width outside off, de Villiers slaps it to deep extra cover, Hooda runs to his right and keeps the batsmen to a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Kohli, 1 run, banged in midway down the wicket, Kohli swivels and pulls it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to de Villiers, 1 run, short of length just outside off, dabbed down to third man with an angled bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Kohli, 1 run, back of a length on the stumps, Kohli shuffles across a touch and flicks it to deep square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhawal Kulkarni [2.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to de Villiers, no run, slower and wider outside off, driven straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, Tambe pushes this one flatter and on AB's pads, he goes back and tucks it very fine, another boundary. BLR are running away with the match]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Kohli, 1 run, flighted delivery and just outside off, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to de Villiers, 1 run, slower and spinning away from outside off, AB comes down the track and works it square past point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, Tambe dragged this one way too short and on the stumps, AB rocked back and pulled it powerfully past mid-wicket, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to de Villiers, no run, tossed up wider outside off, slapped straight to the fielder at extra cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to de Villiers, 1 run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, AB presents the full face of the bat and punches it down towards long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to de Villiers, no run, short of a length and on the stumps, flicked away straight to the fielder at mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Kohli, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, Kohli was looking to pull, changes his mind and dabs it down towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Kohli, 2 runs, back of a length and on Kohli's hips, tucked away behind square on the on-side. Kohli puts the pressure on Tambe who fumbles and allows an extra run]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to de Villiers, 1 run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, eased down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Kohli, 1 run, short of a length and well outside off, Kohli crashes it square on the off-side for a single, he took a step forward there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Watson [1.0-0-1-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to de Villiers, no run, the drifter from Tambe, AB presses forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Kohli, 1 run, pushed through by Tambe, tucked away past mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Kohli, 2 runs, tossed up and on Kohli's pads, nudged away in front of square on the on-side. Kohli runs hard and gets back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Kohli, <b>SIX</b>, that's easy pickings for Kohli, Tambe dropped this one short and on the stumps, Kohli rocks back and pulls it high and over wide mid-wicket for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to de Villiers, 1 run, flighted delivery and well outside off, eased past cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Kohli, 1 run, tossed up and on the stumps, Kohli goes back and punches it down towards long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pravin Tambe, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Kohli, 1 run, this is excellent running from the two batsmen, now AB called Kohli through for a quick single after the batsman dabbed one towards Rahane at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to de Villiers, 1 run, the slower leg-cutter from Faulkner, AB dabs it towards short third man, Kohli calls him through for a quick single and beats the throw from the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, no need to run for these, width on offer from Faulkner, AB was back in his crease and cracks it crisply through extra cover for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to de Villiers, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, AB takes a walk down the track and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, short of a length and well outside off, AB waits on it, opens the face of the bat at the last moment and laces it past point for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to de Villiers, 2 runs, length ball and on AB's pads, tucked away behind square on the on-side. AB is super quick and gets back for the second run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to de Villiers, 1 run, another slower ball from Watson, driven to the left of mid-off where Smith makes a tumbling stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to de Villiers, no run, short of a length and just outside off, AB looks to chop it towards the off-side and gets a bottom edge onto the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to de Villiers, no run, short of a length and on AB's hips, tucked away straight to short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>AB de Villiers, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[AB gets a promotion, the right move, according to me]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Gayle, <b>out</b> Caught by Samson!! That's a soft dismissal for Gayle! This was the slower bouncer from Watson, Gayle got into an almighty tangle as he looked to dab it towards the on-side, gets a top-edge and the ball loops through to the keeper. RAJ needed this wicket, Gayle was threatening to take the match away from them. <b>Gayle c Samson b Watson 20(17) [4s-3 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Watson to Gayle, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Gayle, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, punched towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Gayle, no run, on a good length and slanting across Gayle, dabbed away towards backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Watson, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Kohli, 2 runs, short of a length and just outside off, Kohli plays with an angled bat and runs it very fine. Morris gets across from third man, slides and pulls the ball back in, just a brace for Kohli]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, that's all too easy for Kohli, fraction short and just outside off, Kohli is quick to swivel across and pulls it over mid-wicket for another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Kohli, no run, Kulkarni shortened the length as Kohli gave the charge, he adjusts and defends it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Gayle, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, punched down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Kohli, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Kohli plays with an angled bat and runs it down towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Kohli, no run, short of a length and just outside off, defended with an open face towards backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Gayle, <b>SIX</b>, <b>smashed</b>, length ball from Morris, Gayle clears his left leg and sends this one sailing over the long-on fence. <b>15 runs from the over</b>, the big man has woken up from his slumber]]></line><line><![CDATA[Back over the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Gayle, <b>FOUR</b>, you can't bowl there to Gayle, fraction fuller and just outside off, Gayle stays back and hammers it over extra cover, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[Morris changes to round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Gayle, no run, high full toss from Morris, Gayle is taken by surprise and pushes it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Gayle, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, width on offer from Morris, Gayle stands tall and flashes it square past cover, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Gayle, no run, tad fuller and angling across the left-hander, Gayle is slightly opened up as he defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Kohli, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, dabbed away towards third man for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Gayle, no run, short of a length and well outside off, Gayle cracks it straight to the fielder at cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Gayle, no run, on a good length and just outside off, driven firmly but straight to the fielder at mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Gayle, <b>FOUR</b>, that's the Gayle that has been adored all through the previous seasons of IPL, back of a length and just outside off, Gayle stands tall and flat-bats it over mid-off, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Gayle, leg byes, <b>FOUR</b>, wrong line from Kulkarni, short and on Gayle's pads, he looks to flick and misses, the ball rolls away past the keeper and into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Kohli, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, cramps Kohli for room as he looked to cut, gets an inside edge towards square leg, off strike with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Kohli, no run, short of a length and on Kohli's hips, tucked away towards mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhawal Kulkarni, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Kohli, 1 run, another false shot, this time by Kohli, closed the face of the bat to this inswinger, gets a thick leading edge that rolls past cover, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Gayle, 1 run, that's a cracking yorker from Morris full and shaping back into Gayle, he gets his right leg out of the firing line and just about jams it past mid-wicket for a single. He's smiling, Gayle, wouldn't have if he was cleaned up there]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Gayle, no run, that's a teasing line from Morris, pitches it up and in that corridor outside off, lures Gayle forward on the drive and beats his outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Kohli, 1 run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, driven away through extra cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Gayle, leg byes, 1 run, too straight from Morris, ends up drifting onto Gayle's pads, he looks to tuck it behind square and misses, sneaks in a leg-bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Gayle, no run, short of a length and in that channel outside off, nips back in slighty, Gayle was on the back foot as he defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Gayle and Kohli are at the crease. Gayle is on strike. C Morris will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. BLR's best ever effort with the ball for this season has seen them restrict RAJ to a meagre 130. Can their batsmen complete the chase? New opening combination for BLR. Kohli is walking out to the middle with Gayle. Two slips in place as Morris steams in..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chahal:</b> "I am flighting the ball and varying my pace. Dan (Vettori) and Virat (Kohli) have told me to toss the ball. I basically bowl the leg-spinner, but now and then slip in the googly. You have to assess the conditions and then bowl accordingly. Surely (when asked if they will win today)."]]></line><line><![CDATA[It was Steven Smith, who played with a calm head on his shoulders to compose a fine knock. However, he couldn't pilot them to a good total as he was dismissed by Mitchell Starc. In fact, Starc bowled well in the slog overs and scalped three wickets. The track is helping the spinners a bit. But BLR's batsmen should back themselves to overhaul the home team's score. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[BLR's spinners led by Yuzvendra Chahal put up a disciplined effort to restrict the hosts to a below par total. In particular, Chahal with his flight and guile made an impact and snared a couple of wickets. Iqbal Abdulla too showed his worth by winkling out the dangerous Deepak Hooda. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Kohli has his boys in a huddle as soon as the innings was completed. Something we have not seen before in the tournament. It has been a superb effort with the ball and now upto the batsmen to take them home.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Tambe, 1 run, length delivery on the stumps, Tambe gets behind the line and works it to the on-side. A brilliant last over from the No.1 ODI bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Tambe, no run, how did that miss the stumps? Starc has his hands on his head. On a length around off, Tambe makes room and fails to connect with the drive, the ball almost shaved the off-pole]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to C Morris, 1 run, full toss on the stumps, Morris advances and toe-ends the drive to mid-off, only a single on offer]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Tambe, 1 run, low full toss just outside off, Tambe guides it to the right of backward point and hands the strike back to Morris]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Tambe, no run, fullish and outside off, Tambe drives and is beaten by the pace. This is too good for the veteran]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pravin Tambe, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to D Kulkarni, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Cleaned up! That is a Starc special. Not much Kulkarni could do with that. Starc round the wicket and fires in the yorker, Kulkarni stays leg-side of the ball and fails to squeeze it out, the off-stump is uprooted. RAJ on the verge of being bowled out. That delivery was bowled at <b>143.3kph</b>. <b>D Kulkarni b Starc 1(2)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Starc to D Kulkarni, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to D Kulkarni, 1 run, another off-speed to end the over, Kulkarni is early into the shot, chips it to cover-point and retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhawal Kulkarni, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Faulkner, <b>out</b> Caught by D Karthik!! A stunner from DK. Faulkner can't believe that he has been dismissed. The umpires are going upstairs, but Faulkner is walking back. Looks like they wanted to check for the catch, it is and the batsman has to go. The slower ball from Patel, Faulkner walked across the stumps, scoops it to the left of the keeper, Karthik dives full length and grabs it with one-hand. He anticipated that early which made it easier for him to go for the catch. <b>Faulkner c D Karthik b Harshal Patel 4(5)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Harshal Patel to Faulkner, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to C Morris, 1 run, full and just short of yorker length, Morris drags it off the inside part to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Faulkner, 1 run, slower short ball, Faulkner had to wait for the ball to arrive and pull it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to C Morris, 1 run, length delivery around off, Morris swings hard and drags it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Faulkner, 1 run, low full toss just outside off, Faulkner drives it to mid-off and takes a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel [3.0-0-18-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Faulkner, 1 run, goes back over the wicket, bowls it on the pads, Faulkner flicks and picks out the fielder at backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Morris, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Binny, <b>out</b> Caught by Wiese!! Starc gets another. Second of the over. RAJ losing their way here. Binny could not capitalize on the drop chance. Full and outside off, Binny clears his front leg and slices it off the outer half to sweeper cover, Wiese didn't have to move much to take that. Binny is not pleased, he punches his bat in anger. <b>Binny c Wiese b Starc 20(20) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to Binny, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc goes round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Faulkner, 1 run, back of a length around off, Faulkner dabs it to point and sets off immediately, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Binny, 1 run, full and on the stumps, Binny closes the bat face a bit too early, the outside edge rolls down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Binny, no run, slanted across off, Binny swings hard and connects with thin air]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to S Smith, <b>out</b> Caught by D Karthik!! Starc strikes with the first ball in his second spell. He has given BLR the huge breakthrough as Smith would have been dangerous at this stage of the innings. Full and angled across the right-hander, Smith shuffles across and wanted to go big over long-off, gets a thickish outside edge to the right of the keeper, DK calls for it and takes a simple catch. Smith is not happy with himself. <b>S Smith c D Karthik b Starc 31(28) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Starc to S Smith, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc [2.0-0-16-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Binny, 2 runs, Binny is chancing his luck. Tries to go inside out to the flighted delivery, skips out of the crease, doesn't get to the pitch but still goes through with the shot, the ball balloons over extra cover, who was running back. The batsmen scamper back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to S Smith, 1 run, Chahal slips in the googly as Smith comes down the track, the Australian guides it to cover-point, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Binny, 1 run, second time in the over Binny goes for the reverse sweep, this time he picks out Gayle at short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to S Smith, 1 run, goes straight on after pitching, Smith dabs it to short third man and rotates the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Binny, 1 run, sees the batsman advance and drags the length back, Binny slaps it to deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Binny, <b>FOUR</b>, superb shot! A flighted delivery on off, Binny reverse sweeps it over short third man, though he didn't middle it, he managed to clear the fielder. That was a pre-meditated shot from Binny]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuzvendra Chahal [2.1-0-15-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, once more BLR leak a boundary off the last ball of the over. The off-cutter just outside off, Smith moves across his stumps and pulls it behind square, he beats the man in the deep quite comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Binny, 1 run, Binny backs away to the leg-side, Wiese follows him with a short delivery, Binny manages to flat-bat it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to S Smith, 1 run, again, the length is short, Smith cracks it to sweeper cover, picks out the fielder there]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to S Smith, no run, shortish and outside off, Smith plays the cut and fails to make contact]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Binny, 1 run, slower delivery which is short in length, Binny heaves it to deep mid-wicket, on the bounce to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Binny, 2 runs, <b>dropped!</b> That was a sitter. A back of a length delivery on off, Binny walks down the wicket and lofts it on the up to long-on, he got it off the toe-end and didn't get the timing right, Abdulla steadied himself under it and spilled it. The entire BLR dugout was amassed by that effort]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Binny, leg byes, 1 run, stifled appeal for lbw, angled in from wide of the crease, Binny looked to work it to the on-side, missed and is hit high on the pad, the ball rolls to the off-side and the batsmen sneak in a leg-bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Binny, <b>FOUR</b>, cheeky! RAJ needed this boundary as the runs had dried up. It was a back of a length delivery on off, Binny waited for the ball to arrive, opened the bat face and ran it down to the third man fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Binny, no run, brilliant change of length from Patel, banged in midway down the wicket, Binny backs away and mistimes the pull to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Binny, no run, slower full delivery, Binny was early into the shot, he checks his shot and pushes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to S Smith, 1 run, back of a length on off, Smith punches it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Binny, 1 run, excellent start to the over, inswinging yorker, it was heading straight to the stumps, Binny somehow manages to bring his bat down and jam it to the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel [2.0-0-12-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Binny, 1 run, on a length close to off, Binny guides it to the left of backward point, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Binny, no run, almost dragged on! Another off-speed delivery from Wiese, Binny gives the charge and goes for the expansive drive, the inside edge just bounces over the stumps. He was very lucky there]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to S Smith, 1 run, off-cutter which is short in length, Smith hangs back and punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Binny, 1 run, too straight, on middle and leg, Binny leans forward and flicks it behind square leg, Chahal keeps it to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to S Smith, 1 run, full and angling in on middle, Smith drives it along the ground to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to S Smith, no run, short and well wide of off, Smith goes hard on the cut, under-edges it to Karthik]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese [2.0-0-14-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Binny, no run, again, Chahal not afraid to give air, Binny presses forward and blocks it down the pitch]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Binny, no run, tossed up around off, Binny defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Stuart Binny, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Samson, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Another one goes down. RAJ have now lost half their side. Once again a batsman falls to a poor shot. It was a flighted delivery on off and middle, Samson kneels down and goes for the slog sweep, is early into the shot, missed it completely and heard the sound of ball hitting timber. BLR have their noses in front now. <b>Samson b Chahal 4(7)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chahal to Samson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Samson, 2 runs, drops it short and outside off, Samson slaps it to deep extra cover, Starc had some work to do and he manages to keep the duo to a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Samson, no run, nice loopy delivery, Samson turns it gently to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Samson, no run, floated up around off, Samson defends off the outer half to point, Smith wanted the run but is sent back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuzvendra Chahal [1.1-0-13-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Samson, 1 run, tossed up close to off, Samson drives it neatly to long-off and keeps strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Samson, no run, punched back towards the bowler, Abdulla dives to his right and prevents the run]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to S Smith, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, Smith wrists it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Samson, 1 run, flighted around off, Samson eases it to long-off and opens his account]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sanju Samson, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Deepak Hooda, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Knocked over! This was a nothing shot from Hooda. RAJ in a spot of bother now. Slower through the air and gets it to straighten, Hooda looks to go down town and plays down the wrong line, he misses and the ball crashes into middle-stump. BLR have pulled things back superbly. <b>Deepak Hooda b I Abdulla 1(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[I Abdulla to Deepak Hooda, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Deepak Hooda, <b>wide</b>, expects the batsman to give the charge and fires it wide, easy call for umpire Erasmus]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to S Smith, 1 run, tossed up around off, Smith comes down the track and whips it to deep mid-wicket, they don't risk the second as ABD was the fielder]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Iqbal Abdulla [3.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chahal is back on the field. So, that is good news for BLR.]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to S Smith, 1 run, fuller and outside off, Smith comes on the front foot and drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to S Smith, 2 runs, shortish and outside off, Smith steers it wide of backward point, Gayle dives to his left and parries the ball towards third man, the Jamaican saved a couple there as it was timed really well from Smith]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, fine shot! This was the slower ball, the off-cutter in fact, Smith walks across his stumps, gets inside the line and glances it fine, the fielder was inside the circle and he had no chance of stopping that]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, change of pace from Wiese, Hooda chops it to the left of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Deepak Hooda, no run, on a length just outside off, Hooda leans forward and punches it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to S Smith, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Smith drives it uppishly to sweeper cover, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kohli to S Smith, 1 run, flighted delivery and just outside off, eased down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Deepak Hooda, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kohli to S Smith, <b>out</b> Nair Run Out!! 1 run completed. BLR have struck for the third time. Poor running from Nair though. This was a high full toss from Kohli, Smith drilled it to the right of sweeper cover. He was always coming back for the second run, Nair was late in responding. Harshal fires a superb flat return, Kohli picks up the ball and flicks it onto the stumps. Nair was always struggling. RAJ have lost their third wicket. <b>Nair run out (Harshal Patel/Kohli) 16(14) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Kohli to S Smith, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Appeal for a <b>run-out</b>. Kohli is celebrating and that's because Karun is <b>well short</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kohli to Nair, 1 run, pushed through and just outside off, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kohli to S Smith, 1 run, Kohli keeps it very full and wide outside off, squeezed away behind square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kohli to S Smith, no run, very full and just outside off, driven straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Virat Kohli, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Looks like Chahal has hurt himself as well. It's the little finger on his right hand, the physio is out for some treatment. Not sure what's going on here, Erasmus has a word or two with Kohli. Chahal is walking off, <b>Kohli will complete the over</b>. If Chahal can't bowl anymore, that will be a huge blow to BLR]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Nair, 1 run, <b>that's a chance</b>, but Chahal went one-handed and shelled it, this was tossed up and just outside off, driven to the right of the bowler. He sticks his right hand and drops it, the ball rolls away towards long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to S Smith, no run, back of a length and just outside off, the slower ball from Wiese, slapped straight to Gayle at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Nair, 1 run, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, Nair nudges it past cover-point and settles for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to S Smith, 1 run, width on offer from Wiese, cracked square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Nair, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, punched down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to S Smith, 1 run, tad fuller and well outside off, Smith gets forward and drives it past cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Nair, 1 run, short of a length and angling back into Nair, dabbed away towards third man for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Nair, 1 run, flighted delivery and just outside off, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Nair, no run, shout for LBW, but it looked like it was spinning past off-stump, Nair was down on his knees as he looked to sweep, missed and was struck on the back thigh]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Nair, <b>SIX</b>, <b>massive</b>, this was tossed up and just outside off, Nair goes down on his knees, gets to the pitch of the ball and slog sweeps it, high and over mid-wicket for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to S Smith, 1 run, slower and wider from Abdulla, eased past cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Nair, 1 run, slower and just outside off, Nair plays a checked lofted off-drive, the ball bounces well in front of Mandeep at long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Nair, no run, tossed up and just outside off, pushed towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Iqbal Abdulla [2.0-0-14-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Badrinath is on as a <b>sub</b>. He looks very different with long hair]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Nair, 1 run, another bouncer from Patel, but it's way too short, Nair swivels across and pulls it in front of square on the on-side, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to S Smith, 1 run, on a good length and well outside off, Smith plays with an angled bat and runs it down towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to S Smith, 2 runs, nicely played by Smith, Smith swivels across and pulls it past square leg. Chahal gets across from deep mid-wicket, puts in the slide and keeps them down to a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Nair, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Nair works it in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Nair, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Nair leans forward and drives it straight to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to S Smith, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Smith drops it in front of cover and sets off, Nair was late in responding, but AB can't gather the ball cleanly, allows the single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to S Smith, 1 run, Chahal drifts one on the middle stump line, worked to the left of mid-wicket where the fielder makes a half-stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Nair, 1 run, tossed up and on off, Nair gets forward and drives it down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Karun Nair, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Watson, <b>out</b> Caught by Starc!! That's a big breakthrough for BLR, Chahal gets lucky here. He dropped this one short and just outside off, Watson was quick to rock back on the pull, strikes it hard and flat, he didn't pick the gap though, Starc was placed at deep mid-wicket and he accepts the chance with glee. Watson can't believe it, he stares across towards his partner and walks off. Kohli is pumped up as he hugs his young bowler. <b>Watson c Starc b Chahal 26(22) [4s-4 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chahal to Watson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, more runs for Watson, comes down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and lofts it over mid-on for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Watson, no run, pushed through flatter and just outside off, Watson makes room and chops it to the left of the bowler, he dives and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Watson, <b>SIX</b>, that's a poor start from Chahal, the leg-break goes wrong, drags it way too short, Watson rocks back and pulls it high and over long-on for a maximum]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuzvendra Chahal, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Steven Smith, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Rahane, <b>out</b> Lbw!! That's a big wicket for BLR. RAJ's top-scorer has been dismissed. This was the slower ball from Patel, he rolled his fingers around the seam, Rahane was looking to work it towards the on-side, misses and is struck in front of middle, the height wasn't an issue, the ball must have been going on to hit the middle and leg stump. Easy call for umpire Ravi. <b>Rahane lbw b Harshal Patel 18(12) [4s-2 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Harshal Patel to Rahane, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, that's sloppy from Sarfaraz Khan, this was pitched up and held its line outside off, driven to the right of mid-off. Sarfaraz charges across and puts in the slide, is done in by some extra bounce and the ball beats him to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Watson, 1 run, another slower ball from Patel, Watson makes use of his wrists and works it in front of mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Watson, no run, fuller length delivery and in that channel outside off, driven back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Rahane, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, Rahane doesn't get hold of the pull, gets it to the right of Wiese at mid-on, calls for a quick single and gets it with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Rahane, no run, the slower ball from Patel, he rolled his fingers across it, driven down towards mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Rahane, 1 run, Abdulla gives this one more air, driven to the right of mid-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, nicely played by Rahane, picks up the length early, goes down on his knees and sweeps it over square leg, there's no one in the deep, another boundary for Rahane]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Rahane, no run, this one is given more air by Abdulla, driven straight to the fielder at extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Watson, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, Watson makes room and punches it down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Rahane, 1 run, Abdulla tosses one on the off-stump line, worked to the right of mid-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Rahane, <b>SIX</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, Abdulla dropped this one way too short and just outside off, Rahane is quick to rock back and pulls it high and over long-on, sails into the crowds for the first maximum]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, that's easy pickings for Watson, width on offer from Starc, Watson gets on top of the bounce and cuts it up and over point, the ball races away to the fence in a hurry]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Watson, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, Watson prods across, closes the face of the bat and defends it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Watson, no run, much better from Starc, on a good length and just outside off, Watson prods forward and defends it towards Gayle at silly mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, fraction too short from Starc, Watson is quick to rock back and pulls it in front of square on the on-side, wasn't in complete control, but the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Watson, no run, short of a length and holding its line outside off, Watson drops his gloves and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[Gayle has moved across from 1st slip to a silly mid-off position]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Watson, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Watson presents the full face of the bat and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Watson, 1 run, Abdulla drops this one short and just outside off, punched down towards long-off for a single, just one run from the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Watson, no run, Watson shimmies down the track, gets too close to the pitch of the ball and drives it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Watson, no run, pushed through and just outside off, punched back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Watson, no run, lack of bounce on this one, Abdulla dropped this one slightly shorter and wider outside off, Watson made room for the cut and chops it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Watson, no run, fraction shorter and just outside off, Watson goes back and punches it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Watson, no run, flighted and just outside off, Watson presses forward and drives it towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Iqbal Abdulla, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Rahane, no run, tad fuller and slanting across the right-hander, Rahane went chasing after that and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Watson, 1 run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, draws Watson into the drive, gets a thick edge through gully, a single to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, glorious from Watson, overpitched and well outside off, Watson leans forward, presents the full face of the bat and drives it past extra cover for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[A short mid-wicket is in place now, a slip as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Watson, no run, much better from Starc, on a good length and shaping away from outside off, Watson covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Watson, <b>wide</b>, Starc hasn't got his radar right here, he swings this one down leg-side once again, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Rahane, 1 run, fuller length delivery and a hint of shape back into Rahane, he covers the line and drives it to the right of mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Rahane, <b>wide</b>, another inswinger from Starc, but this one slips down leg-side, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Rahane, no run, loud shout for LBW, but was the ball swinging down leg? Looks like so, the ball might have pitched outside leg as well, Rahane was looking to flick and missed]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rahane and Watson are at the crease. Rahane is on strike. Starc will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to start for BLR. He has a slip in place..]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's time for action. The two umpires are out in the middle. An animated Virat Kohli is in the midst of an inspiring team huddle. The two Rajasthan openers are out in the middle as well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore</b> (Playing XI): Chris Gayle, Mandeep Singh, Virat Kohli(c), Dinesh Karthik(w), AB de Villiers, Sarfaraz Khan, David Wiese, Harshal Patel, Mitchell Starc, Iqbal Abdulla, Yuzvendra Chahal]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajasthan</b> (Playing XI): Ajinkya Rahane, Shane Watson(c), Steven Smith, Sanju Samson(w), Karun Nair, Deepak Hooda, Stuart Binny, James Faulkner, Chris Morris,Dhawal Kulkarni, Pravin Tambe]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Watson:</b> 'We have got a really good squad, have built on the squad from the last season. We had a tough game against Punjab, but have learnt our lessons. BLR have some world class players, but we will play to our strengths. The noise here is incredible, the crowd has been very special. It's going to be a good challenge, playing against these guys. We have got a long batting line-up. Just one change, <b>Dhawal Kulkarni</b> in place of <b>Rahul Tewatia</b>.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kohli:</b> 'We have got good support here, it's a crowd that loves cricket overall. We have played only 4 matches, but we need to turn things pretty soon. Need to get that complete performance. I expect guys to step up themselves and be honest in the changing room, everyone has to give their 100%. We will bowl first, looks like the wicket will stay similar. They are playing a spinner short, dew might come in later as well. We are trying to figure out our best combination. <b>Chris Gayle</b> is playing, <b>Mandeep</b> comes in place of <b>Bisla</b>.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Team News:</b> Chris Gayle is having a net session in the middle. Does it mean he's in the playing XI today? If so, will he replace Rilee Rossouw or David Wiese?]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather Report:</b>  Ahmedabad was baking hot at 43 degrees in the morning and it's expected to be a clear evening. The humdity is just 19% and that should make the players feel a lot more comfortable.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-Head:</b> Rajasthan hold the edge over Bangalore with a 7-6 scoreline. Can Bangalore bounce back from three successive losses and level the scores? Or will the Rajasthan get back to winning ways? We'll find out soon as the toss is round the corner.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chris Gayle opted out of the last game, so that he can be fit for the entire tournament. He was the key when they beat the Kolkata. So, the Challengers would want him back and firing. ABD has once again looked the best batsman for them, even though Virat Kohli scored a fifty in the previous match, it was not a typical Virat innings. The bowling has struggled as there have been too many chop and change in the attack. Mitchell Starc returned to lead the attack, but was not able to provide the early breakthrough. They would want others to support him, if they have to keep the opposition in check.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bangalore started their campaign with a win over defending champions Kolkata, but since then things have gone downward. They played three games at home and lost all of them. The last being against familiar foes, Chennai. Raina and Faf du Plessis powered Chennai to massive score of 181. Ashish Nehra then struck in regular intervals and finished with a 4-wicket haul. In the end, Bangalore lost by 27 runs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Rajasthan look like a well balanced side. Rahane and Smith have been firing with the bat, the former also is the owner of the Orange Cap. Watson returned after a slight niggle and has looked in fine touch as well. Morris, Tambe and Faulkner have been the core of the bowling attack. They have managed to strangle the opposition during crunch situations. Deepak Hooda has also played a vital role in the team, with both bat and ball.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rajasthan had won 5 on the trot before Punjab handed them their first defeat, thanks to a Super Over finish. The Rajasthan were set to win their 6 game of the season, but Shaun Marsh and David Miller had other plans. Both batsmen scored blistering fifties and then Axar Patel and Mitchell Johnson tied the game. In the Super Over, Marsh again belted Morris around and set them a target of 16, Johnson then cleaned up Watson and Saha's brilliance saw Faulkner short of the ground.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:45 Local Time, 13:15 GMT, 18:45 IST:</b> Battle of two contrasting teams, Rajasthan vs Bangalore. One sit pretty on top of the table while the other languish in 7th place, just above Mumbai. Though both have lost their previous games, the Rajasthan seem to be the in-form team. Beating them in their adopted home is not going to be easy.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/>There are many ways to look at the Pepsi Indian Premier League 2015 fixture featuring Rajasthan and Bangalore. To say that one of these teams has been impressive will be an understatement, while the other one is yet to show any signs of encouragement. One side is leading the table whereas the other one is languishing at the bottom. One has continued to win hearts with gritty cricket while the other has seen its big guns misfiring in crunch situations. In all fairness, Rajasthan have been the one to take away all the compliments, while Bangalore have been nowhere near it.<br/><br/>Punjab pushed the Rajasthan to the edge, but it could have been anybody's game. A sixth win was within reach had a forgotten Shaun Marsh not returned to the fold and set it alright for both him and his team, causing Rajasthan to finally experience a lapse after five matches of sheer brilliance. However, all that fails in comparison to how their campaign has been in this year's IPL. They've been the team to watch out for, and will be eyeing a sixth when they face BLR at 'home'.<br/><br/>A batting-heavy BLR unit has failed to deliver so far. Barring their win over defending champions Kolkata, it's been a forgettable three matches for them, so much that they had to drop Chris Gayle out of the playing XI. Virat Kohli and AB de Villiers have shown glimpses of form, but they have not been able to see the side through to the finish- something they will be eager to do if they are to progress up the ladder.<br/><br/><b>Venue:</b> Sardar Patel Stadium, Motera, Ahmedabad<br/><br/><b>Date and Time:</b> April 24, 2015, 20:00 IST<br/><br/><b>Weather:</b> Clear sky with the temperature touching 30 degree Celsius<br/><br/><b>Team News:</b><br/><br/><b>Rajasthan</b><br/><br/>Shane Watson's addition has sorted the opening combination for the Rajasthan and Deepak Hooda batting up the order in place of the struggling Sanju Samson turned out to be a good move against PUN. However, the Rajasthan may be tempted to bring back Dhawal Kulkarni in their attack. Kulkarni was oddly left out after his miserly figures of 2 for 9 against the Hyderabad and going by their policy of rotating the bowlers, it might be the ideal occasion to bring back the nippy medium-pacer in place of Rahul Tewatia.<br/><br/>Probable XI: 1 Ajinkya Rahane, 2 Shane Watson (capt), 3 Steven Smith, 4 Deepak Hooda, 5 Karun Nair, 6 Stuart Binny, 7 Sanju Samson (wk), 8 James Faulkner, 9 Pravin Tambe, 10 Dhawal Kulknarni, 11 Chris Morris<br/><br/><b>Bangalore</b><br/><br/>There is a feeling that Starc's inclusion may have led to Gayle sitting out the game against Chennai, but you simply can't bench the Jamaican in a format like this, especially when he's had so much success for BLR. Gayle coming back should be a no-brainer unless he's nursing an injury. The gamble is Kohli's to take - whether to play David Wiese, who took 4 for 33 against Mumbai and 1 for 46 against CHN or Rossouw, with scores of 14 and 0. It is likely that BLR will go in with Wiese in order to boost their bowling, something that has been a cause of concern for them.<br/><br/>Probable XI: 1 Chris Gayle, 2 Manvinder Bisla, 3 Virat Kohli (capt), 4 Dinesh Karthik (wk), 5 AB de Villiers, 6 Sarfraz Khan, 7 David Wiese, 8 Harshal Patel, 9 Mitchell Starc, 10 Iqbal Abdulla, 11 Yuzvendra Chahal<br/><br/><b>Stats:</b><br/><br/>Ajinkya Rahane, with 305 runs, is the leading run-scorer in IPL 2015, while Yuzvendra Chahal has taken the maximum wickets for BLR - 8.<br/><br/><b>Quotes:</b><br/><br/>Vettori sir had told me beforehand that I will be bowling with the new ball. It was our plan to stifle McCullum with spin early on. I was just trying to bowl accurately with a few subtle variations. I happened to bowl a slow wrong-un and it got me McCullum's wicket - Chahal on his learning from BLR coach Daniel Vettori.<br/><br/>The way we are backing players and playing our cricket is good. In T20, an odd result doesn't go your way; it is important that as team, weplay all the 40 overs with 100 percent commitment - Rahane is not reading too much into the Rajasthan' loss to Punjab.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore</b> (From): Chris Gayle, Manvinder Bisla, Virat Kohli(c), Dinesh Karthik(w), AB de Villiers, Sarfaraz Khan, David Wiese, Mitchell Starc, Iqbal Abdulla, Harshal Patel, Yuzvendra Chahal, Rilee Rossouw, Nic Maddinson, Varun Aaron, Ashok Dinda, Vijay Zol, Abu Nechim, Sandeep Warrier, Yogesh Takawale, Mandeep Singh, S Badrinath, Darren Sammy, Sean Abbott, Sreenath Aravind, Jalaj Saxena, Shishir Bhavane]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajasthan</b> (From): Shane Watson(c), Ajinkya Rahane, Steven Smith, Sanju Samson(w), Karun Nair, Deepak Hooda, Stuart Binny, James Faulkner, Chris Morris, Pravin Tambe, Rahul Tewatia, Rajat Bhatia, Tim Southee, Dhawal Kulkarni, Abhishek Nayar, Ben Cutting, Dishant Yagnik, Vikramjeet Malik, Ankit Sharma, Dinesh Salunkhe, RustyTheron, Pardeep Sahu, Brainder Sran, Sagar Trivedi]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>130</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>9</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Rajasthan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1447</playerid>
					<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
					<batsman-name>A Rahane</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rahane</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>18</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Harshal Patel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8175</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>158</playerid>
					<name>Shane Watson</name>
					<batsman-name>Watson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Watson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>26</runs>
					<balls>22</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Chahal</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7910</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mitchell Starc</fielder>
						<fielderId>7710</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2250</playerid>
					<name>Steven Smith</name>
					<batsman-name>S Smith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Smith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>31</runs>
					<balls>28</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Starc</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7710</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dinesh Karthik</fielder>
						<fielderId>145</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8257</playerid>
					<name>Karun Nair</name>
					<batsman-name>Nair</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nair</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>16</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Harshal Patel</fielder>
						<fielderId>8175</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Virat Kohli</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>1413</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9427</playerid>
					<name>Deepak Hooda</name>
					<batsman-name>Deepak Hooda</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Deepak Hooda</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>I Abdulla</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1830</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8271</playerid>
					<name>Sanju Samson</name>
					<batsman-name>Samson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Samson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Chahal</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7910</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1530</playerid>
					<name>Stuart Binny</name>
					<batsman-name>Binny</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Binny</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>20</runs>
					<balls>20</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Starc</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7710</bowlerId>
						<fielder>David Wiese</fielder>
						<fielderId>8589</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7789</playerid>
					<name>James Faulkner</name>
					<batsman-name>Faulkner</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Faulkner</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Harshal Patel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8175</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dinesh Karthik</fielder>
						<fielderId>145</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8333</playerid>
					<name>Chris Morris</name>
					<batsman-name>C Morris</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>C Morris</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1451</playerid>
					<name>Dhawal Kulkarni</name>
					<batsman-name>D Kulkarni</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>D Kulkarni</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>M Starc</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7710</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9237</playerid>
					<name>Pravin Tambe</name>
					<batsman-name>Tambe</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Tambe</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1447</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>36</runs>
				<overs>4.6</overs>
				<batsman>Ajinkya Rahane</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Rahane</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>158</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>46</runs>
				<overs>5.4</overs>
				<batsman>Shane Watson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Watson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8257</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>72</runs>
				<overs>9.5</overs>
				<batsman>Karun Nair</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Nair</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9427</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>84</runs>
				<overs>11.2</overs>
				<batsman>Deepak Hooda</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Deepak Hooda</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8271</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>89</runs>
				<overs>12.4</overs>
				<batsman>Sanju Samson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Samson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>2250</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>119</runs>
				<overs>17.1</overs>
				<batsman>Steven Smith</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Smith</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1530</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>121</runs>
				<overs>17.5</overs>
				<batsman>Stuart Binny</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Binny</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7789</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>126</runs>
				<overs>18.5</overs>
				<batsman>James Faulkner</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Faulkner</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1451</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>127</runs>
				<overs>19.1</overs>
				<batsman>Dhawal Kulkarni</batsman>
				<batsman-name>D Kulkarni</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>4</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Bangalore">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7710</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
					<bowler-name>M Starc</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Starc</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>22</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1830</playerid>
					<name>Iqbal Abdulla</name>
					<bowler-name>I Abdulla</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>I Abdulla</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>28</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8175</playerid>
					<name>Harshal Patel</name>
					<bowler-name>Harshal Patel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Harshal Patel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>23</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7910</playerid>
					<name>Yuzvendra Chahal</name>
					<bowler-name>Chahal</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chahal</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3.1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8589</playerid>
					<name>David Wiese</name>
					<bowler-name>D Wiese</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Wiese</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>27</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<bowler-name>Kohli</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Kohli</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0.5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>4</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>247</playerid>
					<name>Chris Gayle</name>
					<bowler-name>Gayle</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Gayle</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6319</playerid>
					<name>Mandeep Singh</name>
					<bowler-name>Mandeep</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mandeep</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>145</playerid>
					<name>Dinesh Karthik</name>
					<bowler-name>D Karthik</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>D Karthik</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>370</playerid>
					<name>AB de Villiers</name>
					<bowler-name>de Villiers</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>de Villiers</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9429</playerid>
					<name>Sarfaraz Khan</name>
					<bowler-name>Sarfaraz Khan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sarfaraz Khan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>134</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>1</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>16.1</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Bangalore">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>247</playerid>
					<name>Chris Gayle</name>
					<batsman-name>Gayle</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Gayle</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>20</runs>
					<balls>17</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Watson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>158</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sanju Samson</fielder>
						<fielderId>8271</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Kohli</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>62</runs>
					<balls>46</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>370</playerid>
					<name>AB de Villiers</name>
					<batsman-name>de Villiers</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>de Villiers</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>47</runs>
					<balls>34</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6319</playerid>
					<name>Mandeep Singh</name>
					<batsman-name>Mandeep</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mandeep</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>145</playerid>
					<name>Dinesh Karthik</name>
					<batsman-name>D Karthik</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>D Karthik</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9429</playerid>
					<name>Sarfaraz Khan</name>
					<batsman-name>Sarfaraz Khan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sarfaraz Khan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8589</playerid>
					<name>David Wiese</name>
					<batsman-name>D Wiese</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Wiese</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8175</playerid>
					<name>Harshal Patel</name>
					<batsman-name>Harshal Patel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Harshal Patel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7710</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
					<batsman-name>M Starc</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Starc</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1830</playerid>
					<name>Iqbal Abdulla</name>
					<batsman-name>I Abdulla</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>I Abdulla</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7910</playerid>
					<name>Yuzvendra Chahal</name>
					<batsman-name>Chahal</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chahal</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>247</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>36</runs>
				<overs>4.3</overs>
				<batsman>Chris Gayle</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Gayle</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>0</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>5</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>5</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Rajasthan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8333</playerid>
					<name>Chris Morris</name>
					<bowler-name>C Morris</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>C Morris</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>23</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1451</playerid>
					<name>Dhawal Kulkarni</name>
					<bowler-name>D Kulkarni</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>D Kulkarni</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>26</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>158</playerid>
					<name>Shane Watson</name>
					<bowler-name>Watson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Watson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>23</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7789</playerid>
					<name>James Faulkner</name>
					<bowler-name>Faulkner</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Faulkner</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>17</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9237</playerid>
					<name>Pravin Tambe</name>
					<bowler-name>Tambe</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Tambe</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9427</playerid>
					<name>Deepak Hooda</name>
					<bowler-name>Deepak Hooda</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Deepak Hooda</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0.1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>4</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1447</playerid>
					<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
					<bowler-name>A Rahane</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rahane</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2250</playerid>
					<name>Steven Smith</name>
					<bowler-name>S Smith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Smith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8271</playerid>
					<name>Sanju Samson</name>
					<bowler-name>Samson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Samson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8257</playerid>
					<name>Karun Nair</name>
					<bowler-name>Nair</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nair</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1530</playerid>
					<name>Stuart Binny</name>
					<bowler-name>Binny</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Binny</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



