<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14637" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>44th Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Kolkata</home>
		<away>Punjab</away>
		<teamsabbr>KOL vs MOH</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>KOL</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>MOH</awayabbr>
		<homeId>63</homeId>
		<awayId>65</awayId>
		<venue>Eden Gardens, Kolkata</venue>
		<startdate>09 05 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>09 05 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Punjab</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Kolkata won by 1 wkt</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Kolkata</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>1</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Kumar Dharmasena</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Anil Chaudhary</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Krishnamachari Srinivasan</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Roshan Mahanama</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>10:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150509140557</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>KOL</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>MOH</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>184</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>9</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>19.5</batteamovers>
		<status>Kolkata won by 1 wkt</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>1858</playerid>
			<name>Umesh Yadav*</name>
			<batsman-name>Umesh</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>U Yadav</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>0</runs>
			<balls-faced>0</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>2276</playerid>
			<name>Sunil Narine</name>
			<batsman-name>Narine</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Narine</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>0</runs>
			<balls-faced>1</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1876</playerid>
			<name>Anureet Singh*</name>
			<bowler-name>Anureet Singh</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Anureet Singh</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>3.5</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>56</runs>
			<wickets>2</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>8356</playerid>
			<name>Sandeep Sharma</name>
			<bowler-name>Sandeep Sharma</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Sandeep Sharma</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>35</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>184</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>466</playerid>
<name>Piyush Chawla</name>
<player-runs>18</player-runs>
<player-balls>11</player-balls>
<runs>183</runs>
<wicket-nbr>9</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>1876</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Anureet Singh</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>4</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>3</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[1 1 1 1 W 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>L1 W 1 1 4 4 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 . 1 1 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 W 6 W L1 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/KOL_MOH_MAY09/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[That's it from this game, but there is another on the way. HYD are batting against DEL at Raipur. Hop tabs and follow all the action from that game. For now, take care and Cya!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Russell:</b> "It was a tremendous team effort. The guys believed in themselves. You don't need to be too greedy when you are batting. I have been working on that. It is a bit stiff (shoulder), but I am a warrior. I am loving every minute and thanks to the fans. Hopefully see you all in the final."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his <b>21-ball 51.</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Gambhir:</b> "We just got out of the jail. It was a very important game for us. PUN had nothing to lose and we had everything to lose. We gave away 20 runs more. Unbelievable batting from Russell and if he can keep doing that, then it's a big plus. It is not going to be a same wicket, but we have the team to perform under any conditions. Come Mumbai we will be waiting for it. They (Kolkata's fans) have been the most loyal supporters and it has been our biggest strength. Hopefully, we can see them all on the 24th."]]></line><line><![CDATA[PUN, on the back of Glenn Maxwell's blazing innings, had registered a very good score. The home team dropped a series of catches, which didn't help their cause. However, in the end, Russell's heroics took them to victory.    ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Andre Russell and Yusuf Pathan gave a superb exhibition of power-hitting to take KOL to a thrilling one-wicket win. With this victory, KOL are now placed at the top of the points table. The hosts were in a spot of bother as they required 98 runs from the last eight overs. However, Russell and Yusuf changed the course of the game with their pyrotechnics. It was in the 14th over when Russell and Yusuf walloped Axar Patel for three sixes and a boundary to lift KOL's sagging spirits. Even after Yusuf was dismissed, Russell continued to smack the bowlers to all parts of the ground. He reached his fifty in a mere 19 balls. It got  tense for KOL, before Piyush Chawla landed a meaty blow in the final over and they eventually won by one wicket.  <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>KOL end their home campaign with a win.</b> Russell and Yusuf were seen hugging each other. They were the chief architects of the win. It is once again so close, yet so far for PUN. Both teams congratulate each other as PUN trudge off the field.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Narine, leg byes, 1 run, full delivery on the pads, Narine misses the flick, the ball rolls off the pad to backward square, Umesh calls for the run and Narine was on the bike, the throw comes to his end, but he had made it comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[KOL win! The Eden Gardens erupts.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sunil Narine, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Chawla, <b>out</b> Caught by W Saha!! Is there a twist in the game? We still can have a Super Over. Needless from Chawla. It was short and down leg, would have been called a <b>wide</b>, Chawla decides to glance, the ball gets big on him and gloves to the keeper, Saha moves to his right and takes it easily. <b>Chawla c W Saha b Anureet Singh 18(11) [4s-2 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Anureet Singh to Chawla, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Chawla, <b>SIX</b>, that might be the game. Anureet misses the yorker length, bowls a length delivery on the pads, Chawla makes room and plays the pick-up shot, he middled it beautifully as the ball sailed over deep mid-wicket for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Chawla, <b>out</b> B Hogg Run Out!! Excellent work under pressure from Anureet. It was the yorker on leg-stump, Chawla jams it onto the pad and the ball rolls down the wicket, Hogg was haring across to the striker's end, but Chawla was not interested. Anureet runs forward, picks up the ball and takes down the stumps at the bowler's end. There was no one backing up and the throw needed to be accurate. <b>B Hogg run out (Anureet Singh) 5(5)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Anureet Singh to Chawla, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Once again Bailey changing his field. Third man in now...]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to B Hogg, 1 run, starts with a very full delivery on the stumps, Hogg drives it to the left of the bowler, Anureet bends down in his followthrough and parries it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Anureet Singh [3.0-0-49-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[KOL need 8 off the last over. Who is it going to be for PUN? Axar and Hendricks have finished their quota. Anureet is the man with the ball. He has gone for plenty today, but all that will be forgotten if he defends these 8 runs. Bailey taking his time to get the field right. No sweeper on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to B Hogg, 1 run, yes, he does. Low full toss outside off, Hogg drives to sweeper cover and retains strike for the last over]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Chawla, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Chawla drives it along the ground to deep extra cover, just a single. Can Sandeep Sharma finish it well?]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to B Hogg, 1 run, yorker around off, Hogg squeezes it in front of long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Chawla, 1 run, full and attacking the stumps, Chawla can't get underneath it, drives it to long-on, Miller fumbles but the batsmen don't risk the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Chawla, no run, full and on the stumps, Chawla closes the bat face early and the leading edge goes to cover, Hogg had taken a few paces down the wicket before he was sent back, he had to hurry as Axar under-arms a throw at the bowler's end, Hogg was in though]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to B Hogg, 1 run, low full toss outside off, Hogg eases it to long-off and hands the strike back to Chawla]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sandeep Sharma [3.0-0-30-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The equation now reads <b>13 off 12</b>. It is up to young Sandeep Sharma to bowl the penultimate over]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Chawla, <b>FOUR</b>, back-to-back boundaries and KOL are in it once again. Hendricks provides width outside off, Chawla latches onto it, he slashes it over cover-point and gives the fielder at sweeper no chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Chawla, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely batting from Chawla, it was a short delivery outside off, Chawla leaps up, reaches it and ramps it over short third man. He middled it alright as the ball cleared the fielder with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to B Hogg, 1 run, short and outside off, Hogg hops up and steers it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Chawla, 1 run, off-speed delivery, Chawla chips it straight back over the bowler's head, only a single available]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Brad Hogg, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to J Botha, <b>out</b> J Botha Run Out!! Axar has been magnificent tonight. Two catches, Russell's wicket and now a direct hit. Botha didn't even wait for the third umpire to make the decision. He knew that he was short of the crease. Full delivery just outside off, Botha drives to extra cover, takes off for a risky single, Axar gathers the ball and hits the bulls-eye at the bowler's end. It was just a formality for the TV umpire to make the decision. <b>J Botha run out (A Patel) 2(4)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Beuran Hendricks to J Botha, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Chawla, leg byes, 1 run, good length ball angled into the left-hander, Chawla can't connect with the flick, is rapped on the kneeroll, the ball dribbles towards point and the batsmen sneak in a leg bye]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Beuran Hendricks [3.0-0-25-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>24 needed from 18 balls.</b> In the last 5 overs, KOL scored 74 runs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Chawla, 1 run, quicker and on the pads, Chawla leans forward and nurdles it to the right of short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Piyush Chawla, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to A Russell, <b>out</b> Caught by W Saha!! There's the wicket PUN were looking for. Russell goes after a blistering innings. Has he done enough to take KOL home? Only time will tell. It was short and outside off, Russell goes for the cut and nicks it to the keeper, good take by Saha. He knew that he had hit it and umpire Anil Chaudhary just confirmed that. <b>A Russell c W Saha b A Patel 51(21) [4s-5 6s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A Patel to A Russell, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to J Botha, 1 run, flighted just outside off, Botha eases the drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to A Russell, 1 run, flatter and around off, Russell punches it wide of cover, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to J Botha, 1 run, reverse sweep to short third man, the fielder dives and stops the ball. Saved three runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to A Russell, 1 run, in the air and lands safely. Russell equals the <b>fastest fifty</b> this season. Bhajji had also scored a 19-ball fifty against PUN. It was a short delivery, Russell goes for the pull and top-edges, the ball skies up and drops in no man's land near mid-off. Three fielders converged and it dropped right between them]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Axar Patel [3.0-0-28-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>. From being in a precarious situation at 69/3, KOL are now well ahead in the game. Thanks to power-hitting of Andre Russell and Yusuf Pathan. PUN need Russell's wicket, otherwise another defeat is on the cards]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to A Russell, 1 run, slower ball on the stumps, Russell swipes it across the line, picks out long-on. He missed out on the opportunity to record the fastest fifty this season, he can only equal it now]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to A Russell, <b>SIX</b>, well, Anureet has lost the plot completely. And it is carnage at the Eden Gardens. A freebie, full toss on the stumps, Russell doesn't miss out he sends it sailing over long-on for another six. His 4th of the innings]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to A Russell, <b>FOUR</b>, Anureet misses the yorker and Russell cashes in. A low full toss from round the wicket, Russell gets his front leg out of the way and whips it between deep mid-wicket and long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to J Botha, leg byes, 1 run, full and outside off, Botha gets his front foot across and misses the lap shot, is struck on the pad, but the impact was outside off. He would have been better off playing a conventional shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[Back over the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to A Russell, 1 run, brilliant yorker from round the wicket, Russell falls over as he dug that out to the left of the keeper, Botha calls for a quick single and Russell had to hurry as he was down and the throw came to his end]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to A Russell, <b>SIX</b>, Russell is not happy with the square leg umpire. It was a high full toss, Russell somehow manages to help it on its way over the fine leg fence. He was in all sorts of tangle when he played that. That was a 50-50 call as the ball was dipping and Russell had bent his knee]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Anureet Singh [2.0-0-31-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Johan Botha, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Y Pathan, <b>out</b> Caught by W Saha!! Pathan goes after entertaining the crowd and bringing KOL back in the game. Hendricks provides the much needed wicket for PUN. It was another short ball that rises steeply, Pathan looks to ramp it over the keeper, can't get the elevation and offers a simple catch to Saha. Umpire Anil Chaudhary took a long time before raising his finger. <b>Y Pathan c W Saha b Beuran Hendricks 29(19) [4s-1 6s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Beuran Hendricks to Y Pathan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Y Pathan, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>fifty partnership in just 24 balls.</b> The Eden Gardens erupts with each run. The slower ball goes wrong for Hendricks, down the leg-side, Pathan helps it along the way to the fine leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Y Pathan, no run, takes the pace off the bumper, Pathan sinks under it and allows the ball to sail through to Saha]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to A Russell, 1 run, Russell backs away and Hendricks follows him, mistimed heave to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to A Russell, <b>FOUR</b>, what power! The man at sweeper had a few yards to cover, but he was never getting there. Slower delivery that is short in length, Russell cuts it fiercely square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Y Pathan, 1 run, shortish and outside off, Pathan cracks the cut to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Beuran Hendricks [2.0-0-15-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[KOL have scored 40 in the last 2 overs. Hendricks back to stem the run flow. He is starting from round the wicket..]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to A Russell, <b>FOUR</b>, another huge over for KOL. Pushed through full and outside off, Russell throws his bat at that, the ball takes the outside edge and runs away fine, beats short third man comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to A Russell, <b>wide</b>, fired down the leg-side, Russell misses the flick. He was not balanced for a second and Saha whip the bails off. However, Russell had his foot firmly planted in the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire called for a stumping chance. Russell has his back foot in the crease. He survives]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to A Russell, <b>SIX</b>, Russell now has a piece of Axar. Floated up on the stumps, Russell clears his front leg and tonks it straight down the ground. Clears the rope with ease and goes on to hit the sightscreen]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Y Pathan, 1 run, dabbed in front of point for a single. Sensible batting]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Y Pathan, <b>SIX</b>, smashed! Axar keeps tossing it up and Pathan keeps sending him out of the park. Flighted outside off, Pathan extends his arms and powers it over long-off. Another flat hit from the KOL batsmen]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Y Pathan, no run, beaten! Slower and spin for Axar, Pathan was looking to work to the on-side, is beaten all ends up by the turn]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Y Pathan, <b>SIX</b>, great start to the over. These two can be very dangerous in such situations. Flighted on off, Pathan plants his front foot forward and hammers it straight back over the bowler's head]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to A Russell, no run, too full and outside off, Russell opens himself up and drives to extra cover, that was hit hard and straight to Bailey]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to A Russell, <b>SIX</b>, muscled! Anureet drags the slower delivery short, Russell pulls it off the front foot, it went flat and over deep mid-wicket for a maximum. The fielder was a mere spectator]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to A Russell, <b>FOUR</b>, another streaky boundary for Russell. Short and on the body, Russell shuffles across and pulls, the top-edge flies over the short fine leg fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Y Pathan, 1 run, takes the pace off the ball, it is a short of length delivery, Pathan goes for the heave, gets an inside edge to the right of mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to A Russell, 1 run, low full toss just outside off, Russell drills it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to A Russell, <b>FOUR</b>, edged and four. Fuller and just outside off, it holds its line, Russell is drawn into the drive, the ball takes the outside edge and runs down to the third man fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Anureet Singh [1.0-0-15-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to A Russell, 1 run, fires it full and outside off, Russell drives it through cover, but there is protection in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to A Russell, no run, floated up just outside off, Russell taps it in front of point, wanted the run but Pathan was not interested]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to A Russell, no run, some turn for Axar, Russell defends off the inside half to the right of the bowler, Bailey from mid-wicket tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Y Pathan, 1 run, tossed up on off, Pathan wanted to muscle it out of the park, mistimes it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Y Pathan, no run, flighted around off, Pathan push-drives it to cover, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Y Pathan, no run, shortish and on off, Pathan pulls and picks out mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Axar Patel [1.0-0-2-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to A Russell, no run, flatter and around off, Russell goes back and knocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to A Russell, <b>wide</b>, big turn there, starts on middle and spins away further, wide signalled]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Suryakumar Yadav, <b>out</b> Bowled!! A repeat of Vijay's dimissal. KOL are in trouble now. Suryakumar walks across his stumps, kneels down exposing his leg-stump and misses the sweep, Gurkeerat fires it full and hits the leg-stump. He celebrates with his arms spread wide. <b>Suryakumar Yadav b Gurkeerat Singh 9(9) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Gurkeerat Singh to Suryakumar Yadav, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Y Pathan, 1 run, quicker, fuller and just outside off, Pathan drives it down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, floated up on the stumps, Suryakumar works it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Y Pathan, 1 run, Gurkeerat still not afraid to flight the ball, Pathan walks across and works it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Y Pathan, <b>SIX</b>, first ball Pathan plays off a spinner and he tonks it into the crowd. Tossed up just outside off, Pathan shuffles across and heaves it to wide long-on, the power of Pathan takes it over the rope]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Suryakumar Yadav, no run, low full toss on the off stump, Suryakumar flicks it straight to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Suryakumar Yadav, <b>FOUR</b>, calculated hit from Suryakumar Yadav. Picked the slower ball early, with long-off inside the ring, he lofts it easily over the infield and it bounces just inside the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Y Pathan, 1 run, allows the good length delivery to come and guides it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Y Pathan, no run, short of length delivery on the leg stump, Pathan turns it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Y Pathan, no run, slower delivery, Pathan taps it towards point and sets off but Suryakumar Yadav sends him back because Maxwell quickly got to the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Y Pathan, no run, short delivery on the off stump, Pathan lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Beuran Hendricks [1.0-0-10-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Suryakumar Yadav, no run, big appeal, but the impact was probably just outside off and height was also an issue there. Suryakumar plays across line to this offie, it spins back sharply and hits him above the knee-roll]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Yusuf Pathan, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Gambhir, <b>out</b> Caught by Vijay!! Oh dear! Gautam Gambhir has gifted his wicket. He can't believe it. Short ball from Gurkeerat Singh, it spins away sharply, Gambhir was looking to loft it over extra-cover, but he hit it very straight, long-off ran forward to complete a good catch. KOL have lost 2 wickets in the space of 9 balls now. <b>Gambhir c Vijay b Gurkeerat Singh 24(23) [4s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Gurkeerat Singh to Gambhir, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Gambhir, no run, opens the face of the bat and guides it to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, flighted delivery on the leg stump, Suryakumar steps out and slogs it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Gambhir, 1 run, short and spinning away outside off stump, Gambhir gives himself some room and drives it off the back foot towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, gets down on one knee, takes it on the full and sweeps it behind square on the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, short and spinning back in, Suryakumar pulls it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Gambhir, 1 run, on the leg stump, Gambhir flicks it through square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, flighted delivery just outside off stump, Suryakumar leans forward and flicks it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Suryakumar Yadav, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to M Pandey, <b>out</b> Caught by A Patel!! Another start has been thrown away by Pandey. Flighted delivery from Maxwell, Pandey advances and doesn't get to the pitch of the ball, tries to get a maximum but picks out long-on to perfection. <b>M Pandey c A Patel b Maxwell 22(15) [4s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Maxwell to M Pandey, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Gambhir, 1 run, shortish in length, Gambhir pulls it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to M Pandey, 1 run, mistimed-drive to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Glenn Maxwell, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to M Pandey, 1 run, goes on the back foot and guides it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to M Pandey, no run, no run, shortish and spinning back in, Pandey punches again, probably the ball is stopping, goes uppishly and luckily for Pandey it didn't carry to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to M Pandey, <b>wide</b>, down the leg-side, easy call for the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to M Pandey, no run, very full delivery outside off stump, Pandey mistimes the drive to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Gambhir, 1 run, run, sliced over the infield, the man at sweeper runs to his left but doesn't get there in time]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Gambhir, no run, goes on the back foot and punches, it goes uppishly but doesn't carry to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to M Pandey, 1 run, full from Gurkeerat Singh, Pandey drives it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Gurkeerat Singh Mann, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Gambhir, no run, oh dear! Axar almost took Gamhir out with the throw. Immediately he apologises. Gambhir walks up to him and shakes hands. Gambhir advances and gets an inside edge onto boot, the ball rolls to the right of the bowler, Axar has a shy but fires a wild throw. Gambhir keeps it out with his bat as it came around chest height]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Gambhir, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Gambhir goes for the sweep but picks out backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Gambhir, no run, appeal for LBW as Gambhir misses the sweep, but the ball pitches outside leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to M Pandey, 1 run, very full, pushed to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to M Pandey, no run, big spin for Axar. Flighted delivery pitching around the off stump line and spinning away sharply, Pandey is beaten comprehensively, Saha takes the bails off but Pandey had his back foot grounded]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Gambhir, 1 run, flighted delivery down the leg-side, Gambhir gets an inside edge onto pad as he tries to work it on the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[This is interesting, Axar to operate from round the wicket to the left-hander.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Axar Patel, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[KOL have scored 30 runs in the last two overs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to M Pandey, <b>FOUR</b>, wow! He gets to 18 off just 7 balls. Full and on the off stump, Pandey flicks on one leg, hit well over mid-wicket and it goes for four more. 15 runs off the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to M Pandey, <b>FOUR</b>, looks like he's been batting for 2-3 hours out there. On the walk again is Pandey, nothing wrong with the delivery, good length and just outside off stump, Pandey plays a firm push again and this time sends it to the left of mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to M Pandey, <b>wide</b>, Sandeep Sharma tries the bumper but the umpire doesn't like the height on that]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to M Pandey, <b>FOUR</b>, on the front foot and a lovely punch through cover-point. As always, Pandey takes his front foot away very early, gets into a good position and creams it off the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Gambhir, 1 run, Gambhir walks right across the stumps and whips it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bizarre field placing for Gambhir. Short third man, backward point and a man between the two.]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to M Pandey, 1 run, 'yes, yes' says Pandey, after pushing this short of length delivery to the left of mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to M Pandey, no run, Pandey dances down the track but Sandeep Sharma keeps him calm by dragging the length back, pushed to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, great use of the wrists there from Gambhir. Short of a length delivery just outside off stump, Gambhir hops and turns it through square leg, there was no one in the deep, fine leg gives chase and dives but the ball escapes. Gambhir is looking very good today]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to M Pandey, 1 run, slower delivery on the shorter side, Pandey taps it towards mid-on and takes off for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to M Pandey, <b>FOUR</b>, wow! Just a firm push off the front foot, he was on the move as well as he met the ball but he timed it so well. Width on offer on this short of length delivery and it goes through cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Manish Pandey, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Uthappa, <b>out</b> Caught by A Patel!! Against the run of play, Uthappa has been dismissed. Good length delivery on the off stump, Uthappa looks to flick, it took the outside half of the bat and flew to the left of short mid-wicket, where Axar dived to his left to take it with both hands. Anureet Singh gives PUN a much needed breakthrough. <b>Uthappa c A Patel b Anureet Singh 17(11) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Anureet Singh to Uthappa, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, full delivery and it's a cracking drive off the front foot, he had to reach out for it as it was well outside off stump, the timing was very good and mid-off had no chance as it rocketed past him to his left]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Uthappa, 2 runs, looks like Uthappa doesn't want to let Anureet Singh settle. Straightaway slogs, luckily for him, the inside edge rolls through backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Anureet Singh, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Gambhir, no run, too close to cut but Gambhir is very strong square of the wicket on the off-side, he times it sweetly but picks out backward point. In fact, Bailey has employed backward point, point and cover-point for Gambhir]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Uthappa, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off stump, punched to mid-off for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a front foot pull shot over mid-on, doesn't bother to keep it down, hit deliberately over the infield and it's four more. KOL off to a great start. Sandeep banged that short enough for Uthappa to go for the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Gambhir, 1 run, there is that favourite dab down to third man. Width on offer from Sandeep Sharma, Gambhir sent it from the middle of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, good shot, opens himself up, Sandeep Sharma bowls a juicy full ball, just a hint of outswing on it but Gambhir drove it nicely over cover for this third boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Gambhir, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Gambhir gets on top of the bounce and punches it to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, poor bowling. Not a great first over for Beuran Hendricks in IPL-8. Shortish and down the leg-side again and Uthappa doesn't miss out on the tickle]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Gambhir, 1 run, bumper, rises awkwardly for Gambhir, he takes his eyes off the ball as he pulls, but manages to send it to long leg. The fielder from fine leg runs to his right, slides and saves three. Should have had more than a run there as the fielder had a bit of ground to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, freebie and Gambhir doesn't miss out. Shortish and on the leg stump line, the left-armer's angle from over the wicket makes life very easy for Gambhir, who tickles it fine to the fine leg boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Gambhir, no run, short of length delivery on the off stump, Gambhir tucks it towards square leg and looks for a run, but Uthappa says no]]></line><line><![CDATA[A fly slip for Gambhir as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Uthappa, 1 run, Uthappa opens the face of the bat and guides it with the angle to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Uthappa, no run, fullish and outside off stump, Uthappa drives well but picks out cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Beuran Hendricks, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Gambhir, no run, that's <b>plumb in front</b>, but not given. Sandeep Sharma can't believe it as he walks away to his fielding position. Good length delivery just moving back into the left-hander, Gambhir fails to flick, gets hit in line with middle and it was crashing into middle stump. Probably umpire Anil Chaudhary thought it pitched outside leg stump but it didn't. Lucky escape for the KOL skipper]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Gambhir, no run, good length delivery on the off stump, Gambhir defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, can't bowl leg stump line to this man. He'll thrash you all day. Good length ball on the pads, with fine leg inside the ring, Gambhir glances it fine to the left of the man at backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[One slip in place for Gambhir]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Uthappa, 1 run, maybe he is trying the outswinger but it's not swinging, short of length delivery outside off stump, tapped towards cover-point, Gambhir responds for a quick single and makes his ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Uthappa, no run, no swing on this short of length delivery outside off stump, Uthappa chops the cut and it rolls to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Uthappa, no run, look at that swing. George Bailey, get a slip in mate! Short of a length swinging back in, Uthappa planted his front foot forward, the sharp movement beat him all ends up and beat the inside edge of the bat as he looked to defend and flew over the off stump]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Uthappa and Gambhir are at the crease. Uthappa is on strike. Sandeep Sharma will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Oops! Uthappa pulls out as Sandeep Sharma was running in. Some disturbance behind the bowler's arm and it's sorted.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back for the run chase. Uthappa and Gambhir are out in the middle. Sandeep Sharma has the new ball and surprisingly he doesn't have a slip.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Narine says he was happy that he made a good comeback in this game. Wants to thank the team management for putting the faith in him. Also wants to put the past behind and concentrate on the present (referring to all the scrutiny about his bowling action in recent times). Feels that this is a good score but backs his batters to chase the score down.]]></line><line><![CDATA[For KOL, Sunil Narine, with his box of tricks, flummoxed the opposition ranks and landed crucial blows. He ended up with four wickets to his name. PUN have put runs on the board and it won't be easy for the hosts to overhaul the target. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Glenn Maxwell played a volley of cracking shots as PUN posted a very good total. The hosts though, didn't help their cause by dropping a slew of catches. The ground fielding was sloppy as well. After Murali Vijay and Manan Vohra made decent contributions, Wriddhiman Saha and in particular, Maxwell took over to unleash powerful strokes. Maxwell, with his thrilling artwork of batsmanship, tonked Brad Hogg and Piyush Chawla to all corners of the ground. In fact, he thwacked Hogg for two fours and a six in a single over. David Miller too carted a few hefty blows in the final over. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to D Miller, <b>FOUR</b>, Miller finishes off in style. Low full toss outside off, Miller carves it through the off-side, beats the sweeper on the fence. <b>21</b> off the final over]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to D Miller, <b>FOUR</b>, bad option from Russell to bounce Miller and the South African is a step ahead of the West Indian. Knows the short ball is coming and he hooks it behind square, no-one there and it races away, one bounce over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to D Miller, <b>SIX</b>, flat six. Miller is sitting deep inside his crease and Russell misses the yorker once more, gives a full delivery on leg stump, Miller clears his front leg and heaves it over deep mid-wicket. Powerful!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>George Bailey, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Gurkeerat Singh, <b>out</b> Caught&Bowled!! Too pacy for Gurkeerat Singh Mann and it's an easy return catch. Moved outside off to pull but the bouncer hurried on and he could only lob it up in the air. Russell runs forward and takes the catch. <b>Gurkeerat Singh c and b A Russell 4(7)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A Russell to Gurkeerat Singh, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught&Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to D Miller, 1 run, the slower delivery on the stumps, Miller swivels to pull and gets an inside edge to the thigh pad, they take a single as the ball dribbles away to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to D Miller, <b>SIX</b>, Russell misses the yorker, full outside off and Miller has hit that flat into the policemen standing outside the long-on area. Brutal hit that from Miller]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell [3.0-0-29-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to D Miller, 1 run, high full toss on the stumps, Miller mistimed the heave but it fell safely in front of Botha running in from long-off, on the bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Gurkeerat Singh, 1 run, very full outside off, mistimed drive to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to D Miller, 1 run, another off stump yorker, Miller gets a toe-end on the big hit to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to D Miller, 2 runs, yorker on off, jammed out to deep mid-wicket, the ball went slowly to the man in the deep, gave the chance for the batsmen to come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Gurkeerat Singh, <b>2 wides</b>, fired down leg, Uthappa diving makes a half stop but they take the run as the ball goes away from the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to D Miller, 1 run, low full toss, Miller gets it off the outside half of the bat to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Gurkeerat Singh, 1 run, very full on the stumps, Gurkeerat Singh Mann goes deep in his crease and digs it out to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav [3.0-0-27-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Gurkeerat Singh, 1 run, high full toss, Gurkeerat Singh Mann swings and gets a thick inside edge wide of short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Gurkeerat Singh, no run, another googly, pushed to short cover, no timing on that too]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Gurkeerat Singh, no run, beautiful googly, Gurkeerat Singh Mann is beaten all ends up on the forward push, turns away past the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to D Miller, leg byes, 1 run, good call from the umpire, Hogg fires in the yorker, hits Miller's boot as the batsman went for a big sweep, Miller had got outside the line of off, so Hogg's big appeal went in vain]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Gurkeerat Singh, 1 run, 'catch it' shouted Uthappa as Gurkeerat Singh Mann got forward and sliced the drive uppishly, but well wide of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to D Miller, 1 run, Miller gets outside off and sweeps along the ground to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brad Hogg [3.0-0-27-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Gurkeerat Singh Mann, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to W Saha, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Narine gets his revenge. Tosses this up and beats Saha's slog sweep, timber. Narine ends with a wicket off his last ball. Four wickets for him today and he is delighted - high-fives with Uthappa after getting the wicket. <b>W Saha b Narine 33(25) [6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Narine to W Saha, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to W Saha, <b>SIX</b>, half-tracker and Saha has put it away over mid-wicket. Stayed back to club the pull a long way back into the stands. Hit that right off the middle]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to W Saha, no run, given not out for lbw as Saha shuffled across a bit too much, missed the nudge, may have gone down, not too sure though, Saha had walked out of his crease but gets back before Uthappa whips the bails off]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>David Miller, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Maxwell, <b>out</b> Caught by J Botha!! Taken and Botha kicks the ball away in delight. It was flat and outside off, hurried on slightly and Maxwell top-edged the pull straight down deep mid-wicket's throat. Simple catch and no chance of Botha putting that one down. <b>Maxwell c J Botha b Narine 43(22) [4s-4 6s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Narine to Maxwell, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to W Saha, 1 run, Saha gets outside off and slogs the flat delivery to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Maxwell, 1 run, Maxwell was lining up for the big hit but then pushed the offie to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sunil Narine [3.0-0-11-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to W Saha, no run, Saha has missed out on a leg stump full toss, swung hard at it and it hit the thigh pad before going to Uthappa]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Maxwell, 1 run, now backs away and slices the full delivery outside off, to sweeper cover, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Maxwell, no run, low full toss on the stumps, Maxwell shuffles across a bit and hits it to mid-wicket, says 'no' to the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Maxwell, <b>FOUR</b>, poor delivery, yorker down leg, glanced fine to fine leg, Maxwell getting the much needed bat required]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to W Saha, 1 run, <b>very tough catch and put down by Botha at mid-off.</b> Low full toss outside off, Saha hit it hard and Botha flung to his right with one hand but it didn't stick. Another of those chances that have to stick]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Maxwell, 1 run, very full on off, squeezed out to deep square leg, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav [2.0-0-20-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to W Saha, <b>SIX</b>, Hogg is having a poor day. That is a rarity. Delivers a high full toss, Saha slugs it into the crowd at deep mid-wicket. <b>21</b> off the over and suddenly PUN are motoring towards a big total]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Maxwell, byes, 1 run, Maxwell has missed a full toss outside off, went for the reverse sweep and missed, Uthappa can't gather cleanly and gives away a bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Maxwell, no run, Maxwell is back. Beaten by the wrong 'un as he went for the drive, it turned across his shot and Uthappa was quick, the back foot went out but slid back in, in the nick of time. The third umpire confirms the same. Why did Hogg not bowl the googly till the fourth ball of the over?]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Maxwell, <b>SIX</b>, make that six more. Dragged down very short, gave Maxwell the chance to rock back and murder a pull into the stands at deep mid-wicket. Went a long way back. 14 off the first three balls]]></line><line><![CDATA[Hogg is under pressure]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Maxwell, <b>FOUR</b>, once it is outside off, Maxwell will inevitably go for the reverse sweep, gets a bit of an edge but beats short third to his left, races away]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Maxwell, <b>FOUR</b>, Maxwell with another clean strike, gets to the pitch of the tossed up delivery and biffs it flat over mid-on, one bounce over the ropes]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brad Hogg [2.0-0-7-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Maxwell, 1 run, turns away, Maxwell goes hard on the cut and mistimes it square of the wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Will today be the day when we get to see the real Maxwell standing up?]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Maxwell, <b>SIX</b>, safe shot and Maxwell gets six. Down the track and to the pitch before lofting it flat over long-on, strong wristwork too from the Victorian]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Maxwell, <b>FOUR</b>, that is the Maxwell we know. It was tossed up outside off, he reverse sweeps over short third inside the ring]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to W Saha, 1 run, Saha now comes down the track and slogs wildly, gets a thick inside edge to short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Maxwell, 1 run, very full and Maxwell heaves wildly and gets it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to W Saha, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Saha kneels down and reaches out to slog sweep to deep square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Maxwell, <b>SIX</b>, Maxwell sets up for the pull after Russell bowls the cutter outside off, sat up to be pulled and the Big Show put it over mid-wicket, cleared the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Maxwell, no run, dug in short down leg, Maxwell got inside the line to pull and missed. That was quick from Russell]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to W Saha, 1 run, good length outside off, swiped across the line to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to W Saha, <b>wide</b>, horrid delivery, well down leg and Uthappa dives to save runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Maxwell, 1 run, dabbed to the right of Uthappa, Maxwell was late in setting off but makes it as the throw from the keeper is way wide, a better throw would've got Maxwell]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to W Saha, 1 run, pitched up outside off, driven to mid-off, for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Maxwell, leg byes, 1 run, Maxwell and Russell have a laugh. Friendly chat. Maxwell lifts one leg up to play the flamingo pull, misses, is hit on the thigh pad, they take a quick leg bye]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell [2.0-0-19-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Replays show that Vohra may have actually hit the ball twice when he gave a return catch to Narine]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Maxwell, 1 run, flighted delivery on the stumps, pushed off the front foot to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Maxwell, 2 runs, tossed up outside off, driven to deep extra cover, again Russell with the fielding]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to W Saha, 1 run, very full on the stumps, swept straight to the fielder at deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[Very sloppy from KOL]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to W Saha, 2 runs, Uthappa is the culprit. He isn't near the wicket to collect the throw from Russell. Russell waited to see where to throw to, by then the batsmen had completed two. Gambhir and Ruseell aren't happy]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to W Saha, 2 runs, fraction short outside off, cut hard to deep backward point, Russell runs around and prevents the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to W Saha, 2 runs, Saha comes down the track and flicks along the turf to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Maxwell, no run, three men crowd Maxwell as he faces his first ball. Sharp offie, turns in, Maxwell gets forward to flick and misses, rapped on the pads but going down]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Glenn Maxwell, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Vohra, <b>out</b> Caught&Bowled!! Hit straight back. They are checking for a clean catch. Narine isn't sure too. The umpires signal for the third umpire, the soft signal was not out. But replays prove that it carried cleanly to Narine who bent down and took it near his bootlaces. That hurried onto Vohra who mistimed the flat-batted hit. <b>Vohra c and b Narine 39(34) [4s-1 6s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Narine to Vohra, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught&Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to W Saha, 1 run, trifle short outside off, Saha rocks back and pulls hard, but straight to the fielder at deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Vohra, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Vohra gets forward and flicks to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Vohra, no run, Vohra got a glove on the sweep, Uthappa went up for a big lbw appeal, Vohra was out of his crease for a moment but got back in, Uthappa had to go around Vohra to pick the ball up]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to W Saha, 1 run, dropped with soft hands in front of short cover, quick single taken]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sunil Narine [2.0-0-8-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Vohra, no run, and after such a brilliant shot last ball, plays a slog to the next, quicker and flatter outside off, Vohra slogs and misses. Had no chance of connecting there]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Vohra, <b>SIX</b>, what a beautiful shot that is. When Vohra hits down the ground like this he looks so good. Sees the flighted delivery outside off and then just gets forward to lift it over long-off, cleared the fielder comfortably, lovely timing on that shot too]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to W Saha, 3 runs, good effort from Umesh running around from deep backward square, swept with one hand by Saha and looked to be racing to the fence till Umesh ran and then dived to pull it back. Saves a run for his side]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to W Saha, no run, leggie, Saha opens the face of the bat and guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Vohra, 1 run, Vohra is looking to slog everything now, luckily gets a thick inside edge to short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to W Saha, 1 run, Saha takes a step out and works the full toss down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Piyush Chawla, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to W Saha, 1 run, short and Saha is quick to rock back to pull to deep backward square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to W Saha, no run, googly, almost opens up Saha, who was trying to play to leg initially, pushed awkwardly to short cover in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Vohra, 1 run, spinning into the pads, glanced to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Vohra, no run, turns in, Vohra makes room and guides it straight to the fielder at backward point, looks for the quick single, Saha isn't interested]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Vohra, no run, the wrong 'un, turns the other way, Vohra plays a lame shot across the line and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to W Saha, <b>2 wides</b>, again down leg, Uthappa can't gather cleanly, they take an extra run]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Vohra, leg byes, 1 run, down leg, off the pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Vohra, 1 run, nearly another chance for KOL. Vohra into the walk as the slower delivery stops on him, he chips it in the air near mid-wicket. Yusuf running back doesn't even get a hand on that. It fell just out of his grasp as he lunged out]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Vohra, <b>SIX</b>, finally Vohra connects with a pull/hook. Saw the short ball and hit it sweetly, sending it all the way over deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Vohra, no run, good length outside off, steered with an open face to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Vohra, 2 runs, Vohra makes room and takes a step out of his crease to loft wide of long-off, takes two as the ball is hauled back in]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Vohra, 2 runs, <b>another drop.</b> This time by Uthappa. Short on the stumps, Vohra on one knee looks to pull, is late on the shot, gets a glove and it looped to the right of Uthappa who leapt with one had to his right and could only palm it over, that didn't stick. Russell thought he had his man. More sloppy stuff from KOL]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Vohra, no run, good from Russell, saw Vohra advancing, dug in the short delivery at 142.8ks, followed the batsman, Vohra defends off the splice to point. Got big on Vohra]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell [1.0-0-8-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to W Saha, no run, another wrong 'un, on a fuller length on the stumps, defended to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Vohra, 1 run, flipper, dragged down, short outside off, Vohra punches it in the air, nearly carried to long-off, on the bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Vohra, no run, Vohra isn't picking Hogg, he slogs across the line, this was the wrong 'un, beats the shot and Uthappa flicks the bails off but Vohra had got his back foot back in, was out for a moment but pushed it back in]]></line><line><![CDATA[Uthappa has whipped the bails off, but Vohra is in]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Vohra, no run, spinning in, pitches outside leg and going down, beats Vohra's flick and raps him on the pads. Highly optimistic from Hogg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to W Saha, 1 run, turning in, Saha gets forward and flicks to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Vohra, 1 run, Vohra gets forward and hoicks across the line, but finds deep mid-wicket. Vohra didn't even have a sighter of Hogg, he went hard first up]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brad Hogg, left-arm chinaman, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to W Saha, no run, full on middle and leg, softly defended]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Wriddhiman Saha, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Vijay, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Unnecessary from Vijay and he has thrown it away. Three lives he got but can't make full use of those. Exposes middle and leg as he went down to sweep, missed and the ball clipped leg. Narine has his hands in the air in celebration. Vijay gave himself little chance after exposing his stumps so much. <b>Vijay b Narine 28(21) [4s-4 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Narine to Vijay, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Vijay, no run, Vijay didn't pick that at all, played for the offie, it turned away past his forward defence. Beaten all ends up]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Vijay, <b>FOUR</b>, saw the width on that and opens the face of the bat to guide it wide of slip, was in the air but once he beat the slip it raced away]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Vijay, no run, <b>three attempts and Umesh drops Vijay at short fine.</b> Hogg and Umesh have a smile as the latter shakes his head. Vijay swept that chest high to Umesh who tried to reverse cup it, maybe took it a bit easy and the ball slipped out despite him having three goes at it. Third life for Vijay]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Vijay, no run, leggie, turns away, Vijay pushes it to Russell at point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Vohra, <b>SIX</b>, fabulous shot. Sees the tossed up delivery outside off, gets forward and then lofts it hard and flat over mid-off. Has the legs to go all the way]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Vijay, 1 run, they take on Narine at short fine and make it. Swept to the Trinidadian who was a bit slow and even though he fired in the throw couldn't hit direct. Direct hit would've made Vohra's life uncomfortable]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Vijay, no run, that kept a bit low and Vijay closed the face a bit early, the soft leading edge goes to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Vohra, 1 run, very full on the stumps, jammed out through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Vohra, no run, sliding into middle and leg, worked to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Vijay, 1 run, the call was for two but long-on runs in and keeps it to one]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Johan Botha, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Vijay, 1 run, dropped by <b>Hogg</b> at backward square leg. Vijay shuffled across outside off and swept it hard, couldn't keep it down and Hogg going to his right got both hands but didn't hang on. Must say - it wasn't an easy catch as well. Hogg went with his right hand, best advised to go with two there]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Vijay, no run, stifled shout for lbw but that was going over. Offie, breaks in and raps Vijay above the kneeroll as he was pushing forward to defend]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Vohra, 1 run, may have been the leggie, turned away from off, wristed wide of mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Vijay, 1 run, Vijay shuffles across and gets inside the line to nudge to the right of short fine leg who dives and keeps it to one run]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Vohra, 1 run, that stopped on Vohra who mistimed the loft to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Vohra, no run, normal offie, pitches middle and turns down, Vohra flicks and misses, rapped on the pads, but going down]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sunil Narine, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Vijay, <b>FOUR</b>, 18 off that over. This one is the most classiest of the lot of runs that have come in this over. Length on off and middle, clipped to the right of mid-on, it beats the fielder and races away off the practice wickets. Brilliant timing from Vijay]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Vijay, no run, short of length outside off, punched to cover. Hit that well but straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Vijay, <b>FOUR</b>, Yadav leaks runs. Sliding down and all it needed was a tickle which Vijay gave, glanced to the right of short fine beating the man inside the ring]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Vijay, <b>SIX</b>, that is a magnificent blow. Vijay makes room and crashes the short of length delivery on the stumps over sweeper cover, that was slightly pre-meditated but Vijay pulled it off with great panache]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Vijay, no run, short of length outside off, punched to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Vijay, <b>FOUR</b>, angling into middle and leg, clipped beautifully through square leg and it races away, no-one in the deep and an easy boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Vohra, no run, dug in short outside off, Vohra arches back and watches it go through to Uthappa]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Vohra, <b>FOUR</b>, short fine was inside the ring and he didn't dive, needed to, clipped to his right and he allows the ball to go past him]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Vohra, 2 runs, Vohra comes down the track and then punches the length delivery to mid-off, takes the quick single, there is an overthrow and that doesn't please Gambhir]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Vohra, no run, short of length outside off, punched to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Vijay, 1 run, <b>very tough catch put down by Gambhir at short cover.</b> Vijay drives on the rise and Gambhir leapt with one hand - his right, but could only palm it over. If that had stuck it would've been a great catch. Gambhir with the glasses on wears a disappointed look]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Vohra, 1 run, full outside off, whipped stylishly in the air through mid-wicket but there is Hogg in the deep]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Impressive opening over from Yadav. Even on a slowish wicket he got the ball to hurry onto the batsmen. He certainly looks to be running in with great rhythm in this edition]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Vijay, no run, short of length outside off, pushed to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Vijay, no run, good lifter from Yadav, gets it to rise chest high to Vijay who rises onto his toes and fends it down]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Vohra, 1 run, back of a length outside off, Vohra looks to defend off the back foot and gets a thick outside edge to third man. Went to ground quickly]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Vohra, no run, lovely delivery, slight away movement beats Vohra who was trying to defend that short of length delivery outside off, off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[A lone slip in place which is wide too]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Vohra, no run, short of length outside off, defended solidly off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Vijay, 1 run, a fumble first ball gets Vijay off the mark, tucked straight to the fielder at mid-wicket who lets the ball slip through his grasp]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Vijay and Vohra are at the crease. Vijay is on strike. U Yadav will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players are making their way out to the middle. The countdown is done. We are ready to go]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Punjab</b> (Playing XI): Manan Vohra, Murali Vijay, Wriddhiman Saha(w), Glenn Maxwell, David Miller, George Bailey(c), Gurkeerat Singh Mann, Axar Patel, Beuran Hendricks, Anureet Singh, Sandeep Sharma]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kolkata</b> (Playing XI): Gautam Gambhir(c), Robin Uthappa(w), Manish Pandey, Yusuf Pathan, Andre Russell, Suryakumar Yadav, Johan Botha, Piyush Chawla, Sunil Narine, Umesh Yadav, Brad Hogg]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Gambhir:</b> "Last game was the first time we played four spinners. Having Narine and Hogg in the same side is a luxury. They don't need any assistance from the surface. We are going with the same team."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bailey:</b> "We are going to bat, I think. It certainly worked for KOL last time. Hopefully, we can put the runs on the board. Being a nuisance to the other teams will be a start (when told they can be party spoilers for the other teams). We have pride to claw back and momentum to gain for the next season. We have a couple of changes, Beuran Hendricks gets his first game and Gurkeerat Mann comes in."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Punjab have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-head:</b> The two sides have played 16 matches between them and KOL have the upper hand with 10 wins, while PUN have won 6 of them.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather Update:</b> There have been a few washouts in this edition and one in Eden Gardens as well. The weather is alright for now with temperatures hovering around 32 degree Celsius. However, there are some showers predicted later on. Hopefully, we will get a full game in.]]></line><line><![CDATA[This is the second time these two sides are facing each other this season. In their first meeting, Bailey scored 60 and helped PUN post a decent total of 155. Sandeep Sharma then picked up a 4-wicket haul to reduce KOL to 60/5. However, Russell came out and blasted the bowling apart and went on to score 66 off just 36 balls.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Meanwhile, PUN have plenty of problems. The openers Sehwag, Vijay and Vohra all have had a poor season. Their gun players Maxwell, Miller and Johnson have been woefully out of form. Bailey scored a few runs at the start of the tournament, but now it seems like it has been ages. Sandeep Sharma and Anureet Singh have bowled brilliantly without much support from the their mates. Though they are out of the competition, they will play for pride.]]></line><line><![CDATA[KOL look a formidable side. Gautam Gambhir and Robin Uthappa have provided solid starts. Yusuf Pathan and Andre Russell have used their power to muscle the bowlers around. Manish Pandey and Suryakumar Yadav have not clicked so far, but with the rest of the team contributing, they can afford to carry those two. Umesh Yadav has been impressive with the ball and has found able allies in Russell, Hogg and Chawla. Overall, KOL are a well balanced unit.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>14:45 Local Time, 09:15 GMT, 14:45 IST:</b> Battle of two contrasting teams to start off double-header Saturday. Defending champions Kolkata are up against bottom ranked Punjab. These two sides were the finalists in the previous edition, but things have changed since then. One team has continued from where they had left off last season, while the other is languishing at the bottom of the table. Lets have a quick look as to how they have fared so far.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview</b><br/><br/>Two teams with polar opposite fortunes - Kolkata and Punjab have had contrasting tales to narrate in the Pepsi Indian Premier League 2015. With back-to-back wins, the defending champions have escalated themselves to No 3 in the points-table, while Punjab's campaign this season continues to go from bad to worse. With just two wins in the kitty, last year's runners-up, at the bottom of the pile, are virtually out of the tournament. Their previous outing was their worst, going down to the Bangalore by 138 runs. The enormity of that loss was so huge that all Punjab are left to play for is pride.<br/><br/>However, it won't be easy against a side that has been virtually unstoppable at home. The Kolkata have lost only one out of the six games played at the Eden Gardens and another win will take them to the second spot. KOL's spinners, as evident from the game against the Delhi, have been on the money. Even though Sunil Narine, cleared to bowl by the BCCI Suspect Bowling Action Committee went wicketless, legspinner Piyush Chawla turned on a spectacular show with figures of 4 for 32. Partnering him was Brad Hogg, who has nine wickets from five games. Their batting, though, has been a bit dodgy at times, but it delivered the goods on Thursday with Yusuf Pathan scoring a valuable 42 off 24 deliveries and Johan Botha's five-ball 17 towards the end.<br/><br/>Unlike KOL, on a turning track, Punjab will be hampered by the lack of a premium slow bowler. Barring Axar Patel, no other spinner has been quite up to the mark - Karanveer Singh has had a very ordinary tournament with one wicket from five matches.A demoralised PUN unit will have a big mountain to climb, while KOL will look to end their home-leg on a high.<br/><br/>Venue: Eden Gardens, Kolkata<br/><br/>Date & Time: May 9, 16:00 IST<br/><br/><b>Team News</b><br/><br/><b>Kolkata</b><br/><br/>KOL have won their previous two games with just one change, that of Sunil Narine replacing Ryan ten Doeschate in their previous game. Considering the faith Gambhir has shown in the West Indies spinner lately, the team is likely to remain unchanged for their final home game.<br/><br/>Probable XI: 1 Gautam Gambhir (capt), 2 Robin Uthappa (wk), 3 Manish Pandey, 4 Yusuf Pathan, 5 Andre Russell, 6 Suryakumar Yadav, 7 Johan Botha, 8 Piyush Chawla, 9 Sunil Narine, 10 Umesh Yadav, 11 Brad Hogg<br/><br/><b>Punjab</b><br/><br/>Every combination that Punjab have tried, has resulted in a disaster. Both Manan Vohra and Virender Sehwag have been flops at the top and there have been far too many players getting few or no games at all. Since they have nothing to lose, Gurkeerat Singh Mann, Rishi Dhawan and Yogesh Golwalkar can be given a try, with the left-arm spinner replacing Karanveer Singh as PUN's second spinning option. Beuran Hendricks is another likely replacement for the under-performing Mitchell Johnson.<br/><br/>Probable XI: 1 Murali Vijay, 2 Gurkeerat Singh Mann/Manan Vohra/Virender Sehwag, 3 Wriddhiman Saha (wk), 4 Glenn Maxwell/Shaun Marsh, 5 David Miller, 6 George Bailey (c), 7 Axar Patel, 8 Beuran Hendricks, 9 Anureet Singh, 10 Yogesh Golwalkar, 11 Sandeep Sharma<br/><br/><b>Stats and Trivia</b><br/><br/>KOL lead 3-2 over Punjab at Eden Gardens<br/><br/>George Bailey is 15 runs shy of 500 runs for Punjab<br/><br/><b>Quotes</b><br/><br/>I don't believe in momentum. You have to take every game as they come. We play PUN next, they are going to come hard at us. We need to play well and come out on top - KOL skipper Gautam Gambhir ahead of the clash against Punjab.<br/><br/>We have been working so hard to turn it around, but it's not quite happening. Somehow, we aren't quite getting the balance right. We are out of it and we probably can do well in the future - a disappointed George Bailey reflects on his side's miserable campaign.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Punjab</b> (From): Manan Vohra, Murali Vijay, Wriddhiman Saha(w), Glenn Maxwell, George Bailey(c), David Miller, Axar Patel, Mitchell Johnson, Anureet Singh, Karanveer Singh, Sandeep Sharma, Beuran Hendricks, Gurkeerat Singh Mann, Parvinder Awana, Rishi Dhawan, Shardul Thakur, Shaun Marsh, Shivam Sharma, Thisara Perera, Virender Sehwag, Nikhil Naik, Yogesh Golwalkar]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kolkata</b> (From): Gautam Gambhir(c), Robin Uthappa(w), Manish Pandey, Yusuf Pathan, Andre Russell, Suryakumar Yadav, Johan Botha, Piyush Chawla, Sunil Narine, Umesh Yadav, Brad Hogg, Morne Morkel, Pat Cummins, Ryan ten Doeschate, Veer Pratap Singh, Kuldeep Yadav, Azhar Mahmood, Sumit Narwal, Sheldon Jackson, Aditya Garhwal, Kishan Cariappa, Vaibhav Rawal]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>183</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>5</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Punjab">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1597</playerid>
					<name>Murali Vijay</name>
					<batsman-name>Vijay</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Vijay</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>28</runs>
					<balls>21</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Narine</bowler>
					<bowlerId>2276</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8358</playerid>
					<name>Manan Vohra</name>
					<batsman-name>Vohra</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Vohra</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>39</runs>
					<balls>34</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Narine</bowler>
					<bowlerId>2276</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Narine</fielder>
						<fielderId>2276</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1465</playerid>
					<name>Wriddhiman Saha</name>
					<batsman-name>W Saha</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>W Saha</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>33</runs>
					<balls>25</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Narine</bowler>
					<bowlerId>2276</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7662</playerid>
					<name>Glenn Maxwell</name>
					<batsman-name>Maxwell</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Maxwell</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>43</runs>
					<balls>22</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Narine</bowler>
					<bowlerId>2276</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Johan Botha</fielder>
						<fielderId>487</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6349</playerid>
					<name>David Miller</name>
					<batsman-name>D Miller</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>D Miller</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>27</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8298</playerid>
					<name>Gurkeerat Singh Mann</name>
					<batsman-name>Gurkeerat Singh</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Gurkeerat Singh</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>A Russell</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7736</bowlerId>
						<fielder>A Russell</fielder>
						<fielderId>7736</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1440</playerid>
					<name>George Bailey</name>
					<batsman-name>Bailey</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bailey</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8808</playerid>
					<name>Axar Patel</name>
					<batsman-name>A Patel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>A Patel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9490</playerid>
					<name>Beuran Hendricks</name>
					<batsman-name>B Hendricks</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Beuran Hendricks</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1876</playerid>
					<name>Anureet Singh</name>
					<batsman-name>Anureet Singh</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Anureet Singh</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8356</playerid>
					<name>Sandeep Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Sandeep Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sandeep Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1597</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>45</runs>
				<overs>5.5</overs>
				<batsman>Murali Vijay</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Vijay</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8358</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>78</runs>
				<overs>10.5</overs>
				<batsman>Manan Vohra</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Vohra</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7662</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>143</runs>
				<overs>16.3</overs>
				<batsman>Glenn Maxwell</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Maxwell</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1465</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>149</runs>
				<overs>16.6</overs>
				<batsman>Wriddhiman Saha</batsman>
				<batsman-name>W Saha</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8298</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>169</runs>
				<overs>19.3</overs>
				<batsman>Gurkeerat Singh Mann</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Gurkeerat Singh</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>1</byes>
			<wides>5</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>3</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>9</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Kolkata">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1858</playerid>
					<name>Umesh Yadav</name>
					<bowler-name>Umesh</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>U Yadav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7736</playerid>
					<name>Andre Russell</name>
					<bowler-name>A Russell</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>A Russell</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>50</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2276</playerid>
					<name>Sunil Narine</name>
					<bowler-name>Narine</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Narine</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>19</runsoff>
					<wickets>4</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>487</playerid>
					<name>Johan Botha</name>
					<bowler-name>J Botha</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>J Botha</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>9</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>140</playerid>
					<name>Brad Hogg</name>
					<bowler-name>B Hogg</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>B Hogg</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>30</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>466</playerid>
					<name>Piyush Chawla</name>
					<bowler-name>Chawla</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chawla</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>308</playerid>
					<name>Gautam Gambhir</name>
					<bowler-name>Gambhir</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Gambhir</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>527</playerid>
					<name>Robin Uthappa</name>
					<bowler-name>Uthappa</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Uthappa</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1836</playerid>
					<name>Manish Pandey</name>
					<bowler-name>M Pandey</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M Pandey</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>790</playerid>
					<name>Yusuf Pathan</name>
					<bowler-name>Y Pathan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Y Pathan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7915</playerid>
					<name>Suryakumar Yadav</name>
					<bowler-name>Suryakumar Yadav</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Suryakumar Yadav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>184</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>9</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>19.5</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Kolkata">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>527</playerid>
					<name>Robin Uthappa</name>
					<batsman-name>Uthappa</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Uthappa</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>17</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Anureet Singh</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1876</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Axar Patel</fielder>
						<fielderId>8808</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>308</playerid>
					<name>Gautam Gambhir</name>
					<batsman-name>Gambhir</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Gambhir</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>24</runs>
					<balls>23</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Gurkeerat Singh</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8298</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Murali Vijay</fielder>
						<fielderId>1597</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1836</playerid>
					<name>Manish Pandey</name>
					<batsman-name>M Pandey</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M Pandey</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>22</runs>
					<balls>15</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Maxwell</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7662</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Axar Patel</fielder>
						<fielderId>8808</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7915</playerid>
					<name>Suryakumar Yadav</name>
					<batsman-name>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Gurkeerat Singh</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8298</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>790</playerid>
					<name>Yusuf Pathan</name>
					<batsman-name>Y Pathan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Y Pathan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>29</runs>
					<balls>19</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>B Hendricks</bowler>
					<bowlerId>9490</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Wriddhiman Saha</fielder>
						<fielderId>1465</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7736</playerid>
					<name>Andre Russell</name>
					<batsman-name>A Russell</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>A Russell</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>51</runs>
					<balls>21</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>4</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>A Patel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8808</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Wriddhiman Saha</fielder>
						<fielderId>1465</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>487</playerid>
					<name>Johan Botha</name>
					<batsman-name>J Botha</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>J Botha</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Axar Patel</fielder>
						<fielderId>8808</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>466</playerid>
					<name>Piyush Chawla</name>
					<batsman-name>Chawla</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chawla</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>18</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Anureet Singh</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1876</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Wriddhiman Saha</fielder>
						<fielderId>1465</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>140</playerid>
					<name>Brad Hogg</name>
					<batsman-name>B Hogg</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>B Hogg</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>5</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Anureet Singh</fielder>
						<fielderId>1876</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1858</playerid>
					<name>Umesh Yadav</name>
					<batsman-name>Umesh</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>U Yadav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2276</playerid>
					<name>Sunil Narine</name>
					<batsman-name>Narine</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Narine</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>527</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>31</runs>
				<overs>3.3</overs>
				<batsman>Robin Uthappa</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Uthappa</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1836</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>63</runs>
				<overs>7.3</overs>
				<batsman>Manish Pandey</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Pandey</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>308</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>69</runs>
				<overs>8.5</overs>
				<batsman>Gautam Gambhir</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Gambhir</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7915</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>83</runs>
				<overs>10.5</overs>
				<batsman>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>790</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>136</runs>
				<overs>14.6</overs>
				<batsman>Yusuf Pathan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Y Pathan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7736</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>159</runs>
				<overs>16.5</overs>
				<batsman>Andre Russell</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Russell</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>487</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>161</runs>
				<overs>17.2</overs>
				<batsman>Johan Botha</batsman>
				<batsman-name>J Botha</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>140</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>177</runs>
				<overs>19.2</overs>
				<batsman>Brad Hogg</batsman>
				<batsman-name>B Hogg</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>466</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>183</runs>
				<overs>19.4</overs>
				<batsman>Piyush Chawla</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Chawla</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>4</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>3</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Punjab">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8356</playerid>
					<name>Sandeep Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Sandeep Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sandeep Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9490</playerid>
					<name>Beuran Hendricks</name>
					<bowler-name>B Hendricks</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Beuran Hendricks</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1876</playerid>
					<name>Anureet Singh</name>
					<bowler-name>Anureet Singh</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Anureet Singh</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3.5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>56</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8808</playerid>
					<name>Axar Patel</name>
					<bowler-name>A Patel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>A Patel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>33</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8298</playerid>
					<name>Gurkeerat Singh Mann</name>
					<bowler-name>Gurkeerat Singh</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Gurkeerat Singh</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>17</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7662</playerid>
					<name>Glenn Maxwell</name>
					<bowler-name>Maxwell</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Maxwell</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>5</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8358</playerid>
					<name>Manan Vohra</name>
					<bowler-name>Vohra</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Vohra</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1597</playerid>
					<name>Murali Vijay</name>
					<bowler-name>Vijay</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Vijay</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1465</playerid>
					<name>Wriddhiman Saha</name>
					<bowler-name>W Saha</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>W Saha</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6349</playerid>
					<name>David Miller</name>
					<bowler-name>D Miller</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>D Miller</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1440</playerid>
					<name>George Bailey</name>
					<bowler-name>Bailey</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bailey</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



