<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14619" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>25th Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Kolkata</home>
		<away>Rajasthan</away>
		<teamsabbr>KOL vs JAI</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>KOL</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>JAI</awayabbr>
		<homeId>63</homeId>
		<awayId>64</awayId>
		<venue>Eden Gardens, Kolkata</venue>
		<startdate>26 04 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>26 04 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner></winner>
			<decision></decision>
		</toss>
		<state>abandon</state>
		<status>Match abandoned without a ball being bowled</status>
		<result type="abandon">
			<winningteam></winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Richard Illingworth</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Rajesh Deshpande</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Vineet Kulkarni</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Ranjan Madugalle</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>10:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150426135017</actualendGMT>
	</match>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[Well, the first match of the Super Sunday was a bit of a dampener with heavy rain playing spoilsport. Both teams will not be complaining though, having pocketed one point each. There's another big match coming up. It's DEL against BLR at the Feroz Shah Kotla. Change tabs and enjoy all the action. For now, cheers and bye..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>19:15 Local Time, 13:45 GMT, 19:15 IST:</b> It was inevitable. The match has been <b>abandoned</b> and both teams share one point each. Rajasthan move to the top of the table with 11 points while Kolkata stay third with 7 points.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>19:02 Local Time, 13:32 GMT, 19:02 IST:</b> I saw Gambhir and Watson shake hands. That means this match might just be <b>abandoned</b>. We might get the official news shortly.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:53 Local Time, 13:23 GMT, 18:53 IST:</b> The super sopper is still moving across the boundary ropes. The umpires are out for another inspection. Umpire Illingworth looks concerned with the bowler run-up area. The three umpires are in the midst of a chat now. The chief curator is also involved in the chat now. Illingworth is now having a serious talk with both the teams.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:43 Local Time, 13:13 GMT, 18:43 IST:</b> The umpires are out for another inspection. Sawdust is being applied across the outfield. The super sopper is moving across the boundary ropes and there's still plenty of water there. The umpires are chatting with both the captains and team management now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:25 Local Time, 12:55 GMT, 18:25 IST:</b> We have got some news. There will be another inspection at <b>6:45 PM</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>17:50 Local Time, 12:20 GMT, 17:50 IST:</b> 'It's going to take at least 45 minutes to remove the covers. We will have another look at <b>6:30 PM</b>. We aren't sure about the match, there's plenty of water, we will chat with the groundsmen. The cut-off time for a 5 over match is <b>7:30 PM</b>,' say the umpires.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The umpires are now chatting with Paddy Upton, the coach of Rajasthan. There's still plenty of water on the covers. Gautam Gambhir is involved in an intense chat with KOL coach, Trevor Bayliss. Richard Illingworth has a chat with the KOL camp now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>17:35 Local Time, 12:05 GMT, 17:35 IST:</b> The umpires are out for the inspection. Is the outfield dry enough? We should be getting more news shortly. The pitch has been uncovered. They are now checking the bowler's run-up. Morrison says there's no breeze and they are plenty of wet areas across the outfield, he reckons they need more time to get this match going.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>17:20 Local Time, 11:50 GMT, 17:20 IST:</b> The floodlights have taken full effect. It is still very gloomy and there's plenty of water on the covers. The cut-off time for a 5-overs-a-side match is <b>19:20</b>. That leaves us with two more hours. The IPL T20 site has stated that there will be an official inspection at <b>17:35</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>17:00 Local Time, 11:30 GMT, 17:00 IST:</b> Some good news, the <b>rain has stopped</b> and the covers are being removed. We still have a long way to go for the start of the match though.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>16:45 Local Time, 11:15 GMT, 16:45 IST:</b> Here's what <b>Aakash Chopra</b> has tweeted: Sorry to disappoint but nothing good to share from Kolkata...in fact, it's raining harder now and the ground-staff has disappeared #KOLvRAJ]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>16:40 Local Time, 11:10 GMT, 16:40 IST:</b> <b>David Lloyd</b> has tweeted that it's still pouring at the ground. We will only start losing overs after <b>5:15 PM IST</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>16:20 Local Time, 10:50 GMT, 16:20 IST:</b> It looked promising for a while but the rain is back. This will be frustrating for all concerned.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>16:00 Local Time, 10:30 GMT, 16:00 IST:</b> Two super-soppers are in action and the excess water on the covers are being removed. As always, Gautam Gambhir, who's standing near the team dug-out wears a pensive look. We might still have some play today.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>15:50 Local Time, 10:20 GMT, 15:50 IST:</b> Rain is lashing down at the Eden Gardens. It poured yesterday night and it continues to do so today. The ground has taken quite a battering already. Scratch the earlier update, it looks like the <b>rain is easing out</b>. But the groundsmen haven't started mopping up as yet.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>15:30 Local Time, 10:00 GMT, 15:30 IST:</b> It should have been toss time but all we see on TV is Danny Morrison with an umbrella over his head. Needless to say, it is still pouring at the Eden Gardens.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>15:20 Local Time, 09:50 GMT, 15:20 IST:</b> We had live visuals from the ground and the scenes are pretty murky. The entire ground has been covered. The forecast is for more showers in the evening.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The return of Shane Watson has forced the team management to make changes to their winning squad. Lead bowler, Tim Southee, lost his place and Chris Morris has found form deserting him. With James Faulkner struggling, the bowling suddenly looks short of class. Pravin Tambe has been average and the bench-strength doesn't look good either. This team plays as an unit though and under the calming influence of coach Paddy Upton and mentor Rahul Dravid, the Rajasthan will be hoping to get back to their best.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rajasthan started off in a superb fashion - winning their first five matches. Since then, some of their cracks have shown and they went down twice in succession at Ahmedabad, their adopted home ground. The batting rests heavily on the top-3 and Rahane, Watson and Steven Smith haven't disappointed. It is their middle order that's under the scanner though. Karun Nair and Sanju Samson haven't lived up to expectations and that has put enormous pressure on their top-order.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The batting hasn't fired in unison either. Last year's orange cap owner, Robin Uthappa, hasn't converted his starts into something more useful. Gambhir has been the bulwark of this batting unit while Manish Pandey and Suryakumar Yadav have shone in patches. They lost their last match against Hyderabad - a rain affected encounter and can't afford more such reversals. If the batting hasn't been consistent, the bowlers have more than not held on to their own. Morne Morkel has been their best performer so far while Umesh Yadav has blown hot and cold. With Narine missing, will chinaman spinner, Kuldeep Yadav, get his opportunity so far or will KOL revert to Brad Hogg?]]></line><line><![CDATA[Coming to the two teams, it has been a mixed bag for Kolkata. They have won 4 out of their 6 matches so far, but the wins haven't been convincing. Their ace spinner, Sunil Narine, has been reported for suspect action once again and <b>he will be missing today's match</b> - with the team management deciding to send him once again to the bio-mechanics lab of the Sri Ramachandra University in Chennai for further tests on his bowling action. While the wily West Indian mystery spinner wasn't at his best so far in the competition, his absence is bound to be a huge blow to Gautam Gambhir's team.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>14:50 Local Time, 09:20 GMT, 14:50 IST:</b> Hello and a warm welcome to Match 25 of the Indian Premier League. Before going any further, let me start with some bad news. It is <b>raining in Kolkata</b> right now and the covers are well in place. A prompt start looks doubtful as of now. Barring a small patch, the entire ground has been covered and the skies look pretty grey and angry.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/>Kolkata' stop-start IPL campaign has suffered another blow ahead Sunday's afternoon fixture against Rajasthan with Sunil Narine likely to sit out after being reported for a suspect bowling action. Despite the latest blow to their campaign, Kolkata return to their home turf to get their campaign back on track in familiar conditions.<br/><br/>Rajasthan, on the other hand, have suffered two successive defeats after winning five matches in a row and despite the two losses at home in Ahmedabad, they remain on top of the standings and will look to get back to winning ways. One of their defeats - to Punjab - was after a Super Over finish, which wouldn't have sent any shockwaves, but the team would still be on guard against a third consecutive defeat, as a similar streak last year had thrown their campaign off track.<br/><br/>The defending champions haven't had the smoothest start to the season but still lie third on the points table with three victories and two losses after five games. Their worry ahead of this match, however, is not only the near-certain absence of Narine, but how the weather in Kolkata would hold up. There are possibilities of thunderstorms and rain, and after a truncated fixture in Vizag resulted in a loss in their previous game, another disruption could impact the game on Sunday as well.<br/><br/><b>Venue:</b> Eden Gardens, Kolkata<br/><br/><b>Date:</b> April 26, 2015<br/><br/><b>Time:</b> 16:00 IST<br/><br/><b>Weather:</b> A high of 33 degrees Celcius with a possibility of thunderstorms and showers<br/><br/><b>Team news</b><br/><br/><b>Kolkata</b><br/><br/>There couldn't have been a bigger blow to Kolkata than losing their premier spinner. Narine's unavailability during the last year's Champions League T20 after being reported resulted in the team losing the final, there is a similar threat to their campaign this time as well. Narine's absence will impact the combination of the team as well, as in the last game they could afford playing three spinners at once.<br/><br/>Johan Botha made an impressive start for Kolkata against Hyderabad and is likely to retain his place, which will keep out Ryan ten Doeschate again. Kolkata do have a variety of spin bowling options in their ranks but how they make that change would be the interesting bit.<br/><br/>A straight swap for an overseas player could mean 44-year-old Australian chinaman bowler Brad Hogg making his debut for the side, while other options include local talents like KC Cariappa and Kuldeep Yadav, which would mean sacrificing an Indian player and bringing in another overseas batsman or a bowler in his place.<br/><br/>Probable XI: 1. Robin Uthappa (wk), 2. Gautam Gambhir (capt), 3. Manish Pandey, 4. Suryakumar Yadav, 5. Yusuf Pathan, 6. Andre Russell, 7. Johan Botha, 8. Piyush Chawla, 9. Brad Hogg, 10. Morne Morkel, 11. Umesh Yadav<br/><br/><b>Rajasthan</b><br/><br/>After reeling off five straight wins, Rajasthan lost their last two matches to Punjab and Bangalore, the second of which was a comprehensive one. Some of their local players haven't fired as well as they would have liked, and while there isn't a cause for worry yet, they may be looking to alter their combination a little ahead of their next match.<br/><br/>Rajasthan' middle order hasn't clicked much in the recent fixtures with the openers doing the bulk of the scoring. Even though Stuart Binny held the innings together during the previous match against BLR, he hasn't contributed enough with either bat or ball, indicating he could make way in a like-for-like replacement with Rajat Bhatia, who earlier played for Kolkata. Familiarity with the conditions and variations in his bowling could see Bhatia getting the nod ahead of Binny.<br/><br/>Probable XI: 1. Ajinkya Rahane, 2. Shane Watson (capt), 3. Steven Smith, 4. Karun Nair, 5. Sanju Samson, 6. Deepak Hooda, 7. Rajat Bhatia/Stuart Binny, 8. James Faulkner, 9. Chris Morris, 10. Pravin Tambe, 11. Dhawal Kulkarni<br/><br/><b>Stats and trivia</b><br/><br/>Rajasthan got the better of Kolkata in both their fixtures last season, with the Rajasthan winning the first leg in Super Over.<br/><br/>The second league game saw Kolkata suffering a batting collapse that saw them lose by 10 runs following a dramatic collapse, losing 10 wickets for 39 runs after being 121 for no loss. Pravin Tambe took a hat-trick in that fixture, while Kolkata resurrected their campaign after that defeat, and went on an unbeaten streak to lift the tournament.<br/><br/><b>Quotes</b><br/><br/>"We just need to turn this momentum around. We should make sure we get more things right next game," - Rajasthan captain Shane Watson doesn't mince words after the defeat to Bangalore.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajasthan</b> (From): Shane Watson(c), Ajinkya Rahane, Steven Smith, Karun Nair, Deepak Hooda, Sanju Samson(w), Stuart Binny, James Faulkner, Chris Morris, Dhawal Kulkarni, Pravin Tambe, Rajat Bhatia, Tim Southee, Abhishek Nayar, Ben Cutting, Dishant Yagnik, Vikramjeet Malik, Ankit Sharma, Rahul Tewatia, Dinesh Salunkhe, RustyTheron, Pardeep Sahu, Brainder Sran, Sagar Trivedi]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kolkata</b> (From): Gautam Gambhir(c), Robin Uthappa(w), Manish Pandey, Suryakumar Yadav, Yusuf Pathan, Andre Russell, Johan Botha, Piyush Chawla, Sunil Narine, Morne Morkel, Umesh Yadav, Pat Cummins, Ryan ten Doeschate, Veer Pratap Singh, Kuldeep Yadav, Azhar Mahmood, Brad Hogg, Sumit Narwal, Sheldon Jackson, Aditya Garhwal, Kishan Cariappa, Vaibhav Rawal]]></line>		
		</commentary>
</scorecard>



