<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14614" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>20th Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Bangalore</home>
		<away>Chennai</away>
		<teamsabbr>BLR vs CHN</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>BLR</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>CHN</awayabbr>
		<homeId>59</homeId>
		<awayId>58</awayId>
		<venue>M.Chinnaswamy Stadium, Bengaluru</venue>
		<startdate>22 04 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>22 04 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Bangalore</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Chennai won by 27 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Chennai</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>27</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Johanes Cloete</Name>
			<Country>RSA</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Chettithody Shamsuddin</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Pashchim Pathak</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Javagal Srinath</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>14:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150422182520</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>BLR</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>CHN</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>154</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>8</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>20</batteamovers>
		<status>Chennai won by 27 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>7710</playerid>
			<name>Mitchell Starc*</name>
			<batsman-name>M Starc</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Starc</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>9</runs>
			<balls-faced>6</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
			<batsman>
				<name />
				<runs />
				<balls-faced />
				<fours />
				<sixes />
			</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>8181</playerid>
			<name>Mohit Sharma*</name>
			<bowler-name>Mohit Sharma</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Mohit Sharma</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>39</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>242</playerid>
			<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
			<bowler-name>DJ Bravo</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>3</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>25</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>182</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>8589</playerid>
<name>David Wiese</name>
<player-runs>22</player-runs>
<player-balls>20</player-balls>
<runs>154</runs>
<wicket-nbr>8</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>242</bowlerid>
<bowlername>DJ Bravo</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>1</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>5</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>6</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[W W . . . 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. . 4 L4 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 1 . 1 1 6 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 1 1 . 4 W ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/BLR_CHN_APR22/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[This is <b>Sidhant Maheshwari</b>, saying goodbye on behalf of <b>Krishna, Raju, Bharath, Sriram</b> and my co-commentators, <b>Akshay Maanay</b> and <b>Pradeep</b>. See you tomorrow!]]></line><line><![CDATA[That brings us to the end of our coverage of double-header Wednesday. Tomorrow, <b>Delhi</b> will host the <b>Mumbai.</b> Don't forget to join us then.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Let's take a look at some of the best <b>tweets</b> from this game:]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Virender Sehwag:</b> Wow nehra ji ne aaj phir kamaal kar diya .. old is gold .]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dean Jones:</b> @BLRTweets have problems.. @henrygayle not playing and they spend 10 Crore on @DineshKarthik who has only made 43 runs..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sanjay Manjrekar:</b> Ashish Nehra's wickets are Bravery Awards. One of the few bowlers brave enough to keep bowling fuller length deliveries.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravi Bopara:</b> Wow. @henrygayle not selected for Bangalore. Never thought I'd ever see that.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>G Rajaraman:</b> Second time in a few weeks that Dhoni has had a hand in running out AB de Villiers!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sid Mallya:</b> Hard loss to take.. Congrats #CHN on the win. Need to bounce back strong next game..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Raina:</b> 'We have worked really hard with Flem (Stephen Fleming). He asked me to enjoy and I did that. I had a good partnership with Smith and Dhoni out there. I should have probably stayed on for two more overs. My plan was to be positive and it really worked for me. I thought we were 20 runs short. We bowled really well, Nehra has been brilliant for us for the last two years. I think BLR are the favourites with the crowd. With Virat in the team, they have the biggest support in the tournament.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his <b>32-ball 62</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhoni:</b> 'I felt we could have done better in a few situations where the application was wrong, in both batting and bowling. We need to dominate. The spinners need to pull up their socks, our spinners haven't done so well. He (Faf) has been brilliant. Mid-off is a crucial position and we have stationed Faf there. Being one of the experienced players, he can always talk to the bowlers from there. There are a few fielders who are not that quick, but they also try. That run-out was crucial. It was a good throw, if I would have gone with the gloves, he would have made it in. AB is a fantastic player and if you can get him run-out, it's a great thing. His wicket helped us perform better.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kohli:</b> 'It's disappointing. I can't really say much for now. We have been very disappointed with ourselves. We have failed to perform as a group. We need to sit down and find the issues. Hopefully, we can fix them. It's about putting up partnerships as individual performances don't matter much. We keep losing wickets after 20-25 runs and it never helps. We need to put in good partnerships and set a platform for the other batsmen later on, but once again we failed in that area. Having Mitchell (Starc) back in the squad is great for us. Harshal (Patel), Chahal and Iqbal (Abdulla) bowled well too.']]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier in the day, the fulcrum of CHN's batting line-up,  Suresh Raina, played a powerful knock and Faf du Plessis essayed a fine hand. However, the visitors lost the plot in the end overs.  The CHN camp would be pleased to get back to winning ways after losing to RAJ in their previous game.]]></line><line><![CDATA[BLR put up a listless show as they slipped towards their third defeat of the tournament. None of their batsmen were able to up the scoring rate. Even Virat Kohli struggled to find gaps and unfurl shots. It was the veteran left-arm seamer Ashish Nehra, who kept the opposition on their toes by bowling with unrelenting control and picked up four wickets. Ishwar Pandey backed him up by giving a good account of himself. CHN's fielding too was sharp. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Virat Kohli leads his men out onto the field as they exchange handshakes with their counterparts. The CHN boys look extremely happy after beating BLR in their den. On the other hand, this is BLR's <b>third consecutive loss at home</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, <b>out</b> Caught by Dwayne Smith!! <b>CHN win by 27 runs</b>, a dominant performance from MSD's men. They take a wicket off the last ball too. It was the slower ball from Bravo, Wiese goes for a slog and gets a leading edge that goes high in the air. Smith from sweeper cover runs in and takes a simple catch. <b>Wiese c Dwayne Smith b Dwayne Bravo 22(20) [4s-2 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, <b>FOUR</b>, that's thumped to the fence, it was short and slightly wide outside off once again. Wiese goes for the cut once again and this time makes a good connection, sends it to the left of backward point and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, no run, bowls this slightly wide outside off, Wiese reaches out and looks to cut, the ball goes past the blade. It was inside the tramline and hence, can't be called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Starc, 1 run, Starc goes right across this time and he clips this full delivery from Bravo to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, 1 run, Wiese goes for a big pull, but completely mistimes it. The ball goes off the outside half of the bat and rolls away to long-off. The lack of pace was the reason why he couldn't hit it properly]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Starc, 1 run, banged halfway down the wicket, Starc pulls it down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Bravo comes round the wicket to Starc]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Wiese, <b>SIX</b>, Mohit pays the price for bowling way too many slower balls. Wiese was expecting that as he waited for the ball to arrive and then he hammered it over the cow corner fence for a mighty six]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Starc, 1 run, another short delivery from Mohit, Starc rocks back and pulls it on the bounce to deep mid-wicket, just the single on this occasion]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Wiese, 1 run, slower short ball from Mohit, Wiese mistimes the pull from deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Wiese, no run, slower ball from Mohit, Wiese was looking to hoick it over mid-wicket but misses it by a long way. Mohit lets out a grunt as he delivered that ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mohit comes over the wicket to Wiese]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Starc, 1 run, angles this one in on off, Starc mistimes the heave towards long-on, the batsmen were thinking about the second there but it's not available]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Starc, <b>FOUR</b>, banged in short and at the batsman, Starc pulls it to the right of short fine leg and the ball hurries across the turf and runs away]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Mohit comes round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma [3.0-0-26-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Starc, 1 run, Starc also tries a big slog, but gets an inside edge onto the pad. The ball rolls away towards point and the batsmen sneak in a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, 1 run, clears his front leg this time as he chips this fuller delivery on the bounce to long-on, only a single available]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, leg byes, <b>FOUR</b>, angles this one in on the pads, Wiese tries to help it on the on-side and misses, the ball goes to the left of the short third man fielder off the pad, Nehra dives but the ball escapes and runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, <b>FOUR</b>, one too many slower balls from Bravo, Wiese was expecting that as he flat-bats it over the bowler and long-off couldn't stop it running to his right]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, no run, Wiese comes charging down the track and wanted to hoick this delivery angling in around off over the on-side, but he fails to connect once again. The ball wasn't that far away from the off stump either]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, no run, slower delivery slightly wide outside off, Wiese looks to cut but the lack of pace beats him once again]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo [1.0-0-12-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nehra finishes a brilliant spell. His figures: <b>4-0-10-4</b>. A Man of the Match performance? I guess so. He also becomes the owner of the <b>Purple cap</b> now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Wiese, 1 run, full delivery on off, Wiese drives it down to long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Wiese, no run, Wiese was aiming for a big hit over the on-side, but gets an inside edge onto the pad, the ball falls to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Wiese, no run, slower ball outside off, Wiese tries to cut it hard, but the ball again goes past his blade]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Wiese, no run, length delivery angled across off, Wiese tries to run it down to third man, but fails to connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hat-trick</b> ball coming up]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Harshal Patel, <b>out</b> Caught by Dwayne Bravo!! Nehra <b>on a hat-trick.</b> Even last time in this fixture, Nehra picked up 4 wickets and today also he has 4. It was a short of length delivery on the stumps, Patel backs away and top-edges the pull over the bowler, Bravo moves to his right from mid-on and takes it comfortably. He also does a little dance step. <b>Harshal Patel c Dwayne Bravo b Nehra 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nehra to Harshal Patel, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, <b>out</b> Caught by Dwayne Smith!! Is that the match for CHN? Kohli departs after scoring a fifty. It was a full delivery on middle stump line, Kohli flicks it in the air and Smith at deep mid-wicket stays calm and takes a good catch over his head. He made sure that he doesn't fall over, well judged catch by the West Indian. BLR are in tatters here. <b>Kohli c Dwayne Smith b Nehra 51(42) [4s-4 6s-2]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Nehra to Kohli, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashish Nehra [3.0-0-9-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[BLR need <b>59 from 24 balls</b>. Change of bat for Kohli, he might have chosen the heavier one now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, 1 run, gives this one more air, Kohli comes down the track and takes it on the full, drives it wide of long-off for another single, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, <b>SIX</b>, <b>Kohli reaches his fifty with a six</b>, it was tossed up on the stumps, Kohli clears his front leg and tonks it straight down the ground for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Wiese, 1 run, rounarmish from Jadeja, Wiese cuts it square of the wicket, the batsmen take a single before the sweeper runs to his left and tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, 1 run, leans forward and drives this flighted delivery to deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, 2 runs, drifting in on leg, Kohli leans forward and nudges it past mid-wicket, the batsmen come back for the second too as the fielder in the deep had a fair distance to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Wiese, 1 run, bowled fuller and on off, Wiese drives it down to long-off and gets off strike]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, on a good length and outside off, Kohli comes on the front foot and drives it past the diving fielder at extra cover, the fielder from sweeper cover too runs to his right, but the ball was way out of his reach. <b>12 runs came off the over</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, 1 run, length delivery outside off, Wiese opens the face of the bat and pushes it towards the point region, the batsmen hurry across for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Kohli, 1 run, yorker on middle stump line, Kohli jams it out to short third man. Don't know what Bravo was appealing for there as the ball didn't hit any part of the pad or the boot]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, short and slightly wide outside off, Kohli reaches out and cuts it to the deep extra cover fence, the fielder at sweeper cover was a spectator there]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Kohli, no run, angling in on middle stump line, Kohli goes for the drive, but gets an inside edge that drops right next to the off stump, it wasn't that far away from the stumps, it was the slower ball from Bravo]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhoni is standing up to the stumps for Bravo]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Kohli, 2 runs, full delivery on the stumps, Kohli drills the drive past the bowler, Baz runs to his left from long-on, puts in the dive and saves two runs for his team]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, 1 run, another one that's fuller and outside off, Kohli drives it to deep extra cover and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, no run, floated up outside off, Kohli drives it hard, but picks out cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Wiese, 1 run, flatter outside off, Wiese punches it to sweeper cover off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sarfaraz Khan, <b>out</b> Caught by Mohit Sharma!! That was hit fiercely but straight to the fielder at deep mid-wicket. It was the tossed up delivery, Sarfaraz kneels down and smashes the slog sweep towards deep mid-wicket, where Mohit was standing in the way. The ball was travelling but Mohit takes it easily. <b>Sarfaraz Khan c Mohit Sharma b Ravindra Jadeja 11(7) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ravindra Jadeja to Sarfaraz Khan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sarfaraz Khan, 2 runs, goes across slightly and nudges this delivery on middle stump line past mid-wicket, good running ensures that the batsmen come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sarfaraz Khan, <b>SIX</b>, shimmies down the track and lofts this flighted delivery inside-out over the deep extra cover fence. What a shot from the youngster there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic timeout</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Kohli, no run, bowls this one slightly wide outside off, Kohli went chasing after that, but mistimes the drive back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Kohli, no run, length delivery on middle stump line, Kohli drives it towards mid-wicket, who runs to his left, puts in the dive and prevents the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Sarfaraz Khan, 1 run, angling in on middle and leg, Sarfaraz goes across and glances it to fine leg for another single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Kohli, 1 run, nudges this shortish delivery on middle stump line towards mid-wicket and calls for a quick single, makes it in time even though the throw comes in at the non-striker's end]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Kohli, no run, full and on the stumps, Kohli squeezes out the drive back on the pad, he almost falls over after playing that shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Sarfaraz Khan, 1 run, opens the face of the bat and looks to guide it down to third man, he just about gets it past the keeper and the batsmen take a single, it wasn't far away from the off stump there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, no run, looks to defend, the ball turns away and beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sarfaraz Khan, 1 run, shortish and outside off, Sarfaraz cuts it to deep backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Sarfaraz Khan, no run, tries to play the lap it past the keeper, but fails to connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, <b>out</b> de Villiers Run Out!! 1 run completed. BLR have lost their biggest striker! It was a flatter delivery outside off, Kohli punches it towards deep extra cover. Kohli turned back for the second run there, but decides against it after taking a few steps and de Villiers was charging to the other end. Smith had quickly ran across to his right to stop the ball and then fires in a quick throw too. AB had to stop midway on the pitch and needs to rush back in as the throw from the deep arrives. Dhoni collects the throw away from the stumps, but intelligently parries it towards the stumps and catches de Villiers short. <b>de Villiers run out (Dwayne Smith/Dhoni) 14(10) [6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Has AB been run-out here? The third umpire is taking a look. He is short of his crease and that's a huge wicket for CHN. AB has to make the long way back and it's a huge disappoinment for the BLR fans as he was looking in great touch.]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, no run, shortish and slightly wide outside off, Kohli goes for the cut but the ball beats the blade]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, no run, flatter delivery just outside off, Kohli backs away and guides it towards backward point, who slips to his left but doesn't allow the ball to escape past him]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Villiers, <b>SIX</b>, <b>hammered!</b> AB gets another six off the last ball of the over. It was full and outside off, AB gets under it and lofts it easily over the long-off fence, that went quite the distance]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Kohli, 1 run, full delivery angling in on middle, Kohli flicks it uppishly past short mid-wicket, the ball rolls away to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Villiers, 1 run, yorker just outside off, AB jams it out towards long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhoni is standing up to the stumps for both these batsmen here]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Villiers, no run, shortish and slightly wide outside off, AB reaches out for it but can't connect, the umpire deems it to be a legal delivery as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Villiers, no run, yorker on the stumps, AB squeezes it towards short mid-wicket, can't get the single away]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Kohli, 1 run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Kohli punches it to mid-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to de Villiers, <b>SIX</b>, AB gets into the groove, he kneels down and slog sweeps this magnificently over the deep mid-wicket fence. That went right off the meat of the bat and made a cracking sound as he connected with it]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, 1 run, flicks this delivery on middle stump line to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to de Villiers, 1 run, flatter on middle and leg, AB whips it through mid-wicket and takes a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to de Villiers, no run, slower through the air, AB pushes at it, gets an inside edge onto the pad and the ball falls right next to the off stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, 1 run, knocks this flighted delivery outside off to deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, flatter and outside off, Kohli cuts it to the left of backward point, Nehra moves across and lets the ball escape through his legs, Kohli gets a boundary for that and that effort from the veteran bowler wouldn't please his captain]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Villiers, no run, AB comes down the track and Pandey bowls a full toss on the pads, AB misses the clip and the ball rolls away into the off-side. There was an appeal from the keeper and the bowler, but it was definitely going down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Villiers, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, AB tries to slap it hard, but mistimes it towards cover once again]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Villiers, no run, full delivery outside off, AB leans forward and mistimes the drive to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[The keeper has gone back for AB]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Kohli, 1 run, full delivery outside off, Kohli drives it off the inside half of the bat past the non-striker, the batsmen take a single before mid-off runs to his right and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>AB de Villiers, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>. ABD walks in.]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to D Karthik, <b>out</b> Caught by Dwayne Bravo!! Bravo takes a sensational catch and does a little jig. BLR lose a wicket just when a partnership was building. It was a back of a length delivery, Karthik goes for the pull, gets it high on the bat and hits it to long-on, Bravo runs forward and takes a good low catch. <b>D Karthik c Dwayne Bravo b I Pandey 10(11) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[I Pandey to D Karthik, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to D Karthik, no run, back of a length around off, Karthik punches and picks out backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ishwar Pandey [1.0-0-8-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Kohli, no run, conventional offie from Ash, Kohli comes half-forward and knocks it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, classy shot! That is his favourite shot. Another leg-spinner which is pitched up, Kohli presses forward and drills the drive wide of long-off, Pandey had no chance near the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Kohli, <b>wide</b>, leg-spinner bowled well wide of off, easy call for the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Kohli, <b>SIX</b>, superb shot! Pressure straightaway on Ashwin. It was trifle short and Kohli latches onto it, he stands tall and pulls it into the crowd at deep mid-wicket. That went a long way]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to D Karthik, 1 run, opens the bat face and drives the tossed up delivery square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to D Karthik, <b>FOUR</b>, wrong line from Ashwin, pitched on middle and spun away further, Karthik shuffles across and sweeps it very fine, beats short fine to his right as well as the fielder in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Kohli, 1 run, flighted on off, Kohli skips out of the crease and smashes it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kohli, 1 run, off-speed delivery, keeps a bit low as well, Kohli nurdles it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to D Karthik, 1 run, short of length around off, Karthik stands up and punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kohli, 1 run, keeps a shade low around off, Kohli dabs it off the toe-end to the left of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to D Karthik, 1 run, back of a length close to off, Karthik drops it near his feet and the ball rolls back, Kohli calls for a sharp run and he had to hurry as Dhoni tried to kick the ball onto the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to D Karthik, 2 runs, this was not all that short, but the pace of Mohit allowed Karthik to pull it in front of square, Bravo runs to his right from long-on and keeps it to a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[Karthik backs away as Mohit was about to deliver. He points to something behind the bowler.]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to D Karthik, no run, back of a length on off, Karthik jams it onto the pad, the ball rolls towards point, he wanted the run but Kohli sends him back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to D Karthik, 1 run, on a length close to off, Karthik brings his bat down at an angle and the outside edge rolls down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, 1 run, takes the pace off the ball, Kohli taps it in front of cover and takes off immediately, DK was a bit casual but made it even as Baz fires a throw at the striker's end]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, no run, short of length on off, Kohli shuffles across and knocks it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, no run, back of a length around off, Kohli hangs back and defends it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, no run, fullish and just outside off, Kohli push-drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, 2 runs, full and tailing into the pads, Kohli flicks it to deep backward square leg, Mohit slips and concedes the second run. That might have been because of the dew]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to D Karthik, no run, good comeback over from Mohit after being hit for 19 in his first over. Length ball right on off-stump, Karthik presses forward and defends it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to D Karthik, no run, lovely outswinger from Mohit, he lands it on a length and gets it to shape away, Karthik plays inside the line and lets it go through to Dhoni]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhoni goes back for DK]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kohli, 1 run, too straight, on middle and leg, Kohli clips it behind square leg, Mohit not happy with himself as he let Kohli get off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kohli, no run, good length ball outside off, Kohli's feet went nowhere as he was looking to drive, was beaten off the inside edge. Good take by MS standing up to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kohli, no run, on a length just outside off, Kohli opens the bat face and drives it to cover-point, can't pierce the packed off-side field]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kohli, no run, back of a length on off, Kohli gets right behind the line and defends to the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dinesh Karthik, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhoni up to the stumps for Mohit]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rossouw, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Nehra blows a kiss after knocking over Rossouw. It was a harmless length delivery on the stumps, Rossouw stays rooted to the crease and misses it completely. He makes an indication as to the ball kept low. But, it didn't seem like it did as it hit the middle of middle stump. BLR rocked back with those two dismissals. <b>Rossouw b Nehra 14(9) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nehra to Rossouw, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, 1 run, shortish and just outside off, Kohli cuts it to third man and opens his account]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rossouw, 1 run, full and slanting into the pads, Rossouw leans forward and flicks it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Virat Kohli, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Bisla, <b>out</b> Caught by du Plessis!!<b> A stunner from Faf!</b> He might have hurt himself even more as he catches the shoulder after completing the catch. Bisla once again gives the charge, doesn't get close enough to the pitch of the ball, toe-ends the loft towards mid-off, Faf runs back and takes it with one (right) hand over his head, he tumbles over but still manages to hold onto the ball. <b>Bisla c du Plessis b Nehra 17(14) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nehra to Bisla, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Bisla, no run, probing stuff from Nehra, angled across the right-hander, Bisla pokes at it even though there is a slip in place. The ball zips past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Bisla, no run, on a length close to off, Bisla defends it towards point off the back foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rossouw, <b>FOUR</b>, an expensive over from Mohit Sharma. Once more drags the length short, Rossouw skips down the wicket and flat-bats it to the right of mid-on, one bounce and into the fence. <b>19 runs</b> came off the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rossouw, no run, slower delivery outside off, Rossouw lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rossouw, <b>SIX</b>, monster hit! Rossouw advances down the wicket, converts it into a length delivery, gets under it and hammers it over long-on for the first six of the innings. "Fetch that" reads the giant screen]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rossouw, 2 runs, shorter and just outside off, Rossouw fetches it from there and pulls it to deep mid-wicket, the substitute fielder tidies up in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Bisla, 3 runs, super effort from McCullum to save a run. Bisla charges down and slices the length delivery over point, Baz gives chase, dives full length and hauls it in for Jaddu. That is what you can expect from the New Zealand skipper, 100% commitment]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Bisla, <b>FOUR</b>, not the best of starts from Mohit. Banged in halfway down the wicket, Bisla goes on the back foot and pulls it over mid-wicket, didn't middle it but he will pick up four]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rossouw, no run, short of length on the fourth stump line, Rossouw stands tall and punches it towards cover-point, Baz moves quickly to his left and saves some runs for the team]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Bisla, 1 run, again, Bisla comes down the track and mistimes the pull wide of mid-on, another sharp run taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rossouw, leg byes, 1 run, fuller and on leg-stump, Rossouw gives the charge and misses the flick, the ball thuds into the pad and lobs to the off-side, Jaddu fires a throw at the bowler's end but Rossouw makes it with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Bisla, 1 run, shortish from Nehra, Bisla walks down the wicket and pulls it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Bisla, no run, fuller and on off, Bisla comes half-forward and pushes it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rossouw, 1 run, nips back in from short of length, Rossouw goes for the short-arm pull, gets an inside edge onto the pad, the ball drops to the off-side and Bisla calls for a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashish Nehra, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Bisla, no run, back of a length around off, Bisla gets right behind the line and defends to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Bisla, <b>FOUR</b>, in the air but in the gap. For a moment he would have thought that he picked out the fielder. Fraction short and outside off, Bisla flays it wide of cover, Baz can't get there to stop the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Bisla, no run, good length ball on the stumps, the ball didn't seem to come on to the bat, Bisla checks his shot and chips it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Bisla, no run, some movement for Pandey, short of length and shaping away outside off, Bisla takes a step forward and pokes at it, the ball beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[The second slip has been removed. Pandey is stopped in his run-up as there was some disturbance near the sightscreen.]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Bisla, <b>FOUR</b>, Bisla off the mark in style. Banged in midway down the wicket, no real pace on that, Bisla was quick to rock back and pull it in front of square, one bounce and into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Bisla, no run, back of a length just outside off, Bisla punches it to backward point and calls "waiting, waiting" for the single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Bisla and Rossouw are at the crease. Bisla is on strike. I Pandey will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back... The Chennai players are in a huddle. Rossouw and Bisla make their way out to the middle. Will Gayle's absence harm BLR's chances? Ishwar Pandey is marking his run-up. He has a couple of slips in place. The countdown begins and we are all set for the run-chase...]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Starc:</b> "I need to go and practice under-arm throwing. Chahal bowled really well to pick up 3 wickets. We just said that we will assess as the game goes on (referring to the plan to open with Chahal), it was a bit of a plan with Dan (Vettori). We have plenty of firepower with the bat and hopefully we can chase it down. Hopefully not (when asked if he is ready to have a bat)."]]></line><line><![CDATA[On their part, Chahal and Abdulla came back rather well. Chahal even snared three wickets and that included Raina's prized scalp. Mitchell Starc also made an impact by bowling parsimoniously. On expected lines, it is another of those flat decks at the Chinnaswamy stadium and the hosts have every chance of overhauling the target. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Suresh Raina's blazing innings helped CHN post a very good score. Raina was in imperious touch and took a heavy toll on spin twins, Iqbal Abdulla and Yuzvendra Chahal. It was in the 13th over when he walloped Chahal for three sumptuous sixes. Dwayne Smith too played a key role  with a sterling knock. In the slog overs, Faf du Plessis showed improvisation to collect crucial runs.  <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to du Plessis, 3 runs, short and outside off, du Plessis upper cuts it to third man, the batsmen take on the fielder and come back for the second, the one backing up DK also missed the ball and the extra run was conceded, Kohli is not at all happy with the effort. du Plessis had to dive in to make his ground while coming back for the third run and he <b>probably hurt his shoulder</b>. The physio is out there tending to him as he walks back grimacing in pain]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Nehra, byes, 1 run, poor from Starc. Full and outside off, Nehra can't squeeze it out, Faf calls him for the run, DK throws the ball to Starc, he rolls the ball towards the stumps at the non-striker's end, he misses and Nehra makes it in]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashish Nehra, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Mohit Sharma, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Castled! This was bound to happen. It was just a matter of time before it did. A length delivery bowled at 144.6kph, Mohit backed away to the leg-side, exposed his stumps and was beaten for pace, the off-stump gets uprooted. <b>Mohit Sharma b Starc 2(6)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to Mohit Sharma, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Mohit Sharma, no run, excellent change of length from Starc, shortish and outside off, Mohit can't seem to lay bat on ball. Faf is itching to go to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Mohit Sharma, no run, fullish and outside off, Mohit swings and misses. He is keeping Faf at the other end. The South African walks up and has a word with Mohit]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc changes to round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Mohit Sharma, no run, good start to the over, yorker just outside off, Mohit gives charge and fails to lay bat on that]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc [3.0-0-21-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to du Plessis, <b>SIX</b>, nice way to finish the over. It was once again the change of pace, du Plessis spots it early, clears his front leg out of the way and tonks it over long-on for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Mohit Sharma, 1 run, pulls the slower ball back, Mohit mistimes the pull to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to du Plessis, 1 run, slower short ball, du Plessis waits for it and taps it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Mohit Sharma, 1 run, fullish and just outside off, Mohit drives it to sweeper cover and hands the strike back to Faf]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Ashwin, <b>out</b> Caught by Bisla!! Chennai losing their way. It was another off-speed delivery, full and just outside off as well, Ashwin makes room and has to reach for it, he ends up slicing it to short third man, Bisla didn't have to move to take that. <b>Ashwin c Bisla b Wiese 5(3) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Wiese to Ashwin, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Ashwin, <b>wide</b>, splays it down leg, wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Ashwin, <b>FOUR</b>, drops the slower ball halfway down the pitch, Ashwin backs away and cuts it behind point, third man was inside the circle and it was easy pickings for the off-spinner]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese [3.0-0-32-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, drilled! It was a flighted delivery on middle and leg, du Plessis jumps out of the crease, gets to the pitch and smashes it past the non-striker, ABD at long-on had no chance of cutting that]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Ashwin, 1 run, tossed up on off, Ashwin uses his wrists to work it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to du Plessis, 1 run, flatter and on the pads, du Plessis works it to backward square leg, wanted the second but he slipped while turning]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to du Plessis, <b>wide</b>, fired well wide of off, easy call for the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Dwayne Bravo, <b>out</b> Caught by de Villiers!! That is the 5th wicket by a spinner today. Again it was slowed up by Abdulla, Bravo wanted to go inside out, he gets it off the inside part of the bat, the ball skies towards mid-on, ABD runs in from long-on and hangs onto it quite easily. <b>Dwayne Bravo c de Villiers b I Abdulla 5(4) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[I Abdulla to Dwayne Bravo, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Dwayne Bravo, no run, slower through the air, Bravo jams it onto the pad, the ball rolls back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to du Plessis, 1 run, skips out of the crease, takes it on the full and wrists it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Bravo, <b>FOUR</b>, an expensive over from Starc. <b>15 runs off it</b>. A low full toss on middle and leg, Bravo leans forward and flicks it handsomely in front of square, no chance for the fielder in the deep to stop that]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc goes round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to du Plessis, 1 run, fullish and on the stumps, du Plessis drills it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, Starc misses the yorker and pays the price for that, a high full toss outside off, du Plessis goes deep in the crease, opens the bat face and slices it to the deep backward point fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Bravo, 1 run, low full toss around off, Bravo squeezes the drive square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to du Plessis, 1 run, angled across the right-hander, du Plessis slices it on the bounce to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, poor start from Starc, short and on the ribs, du Plessis shuffles across, gets inside the line and glances it fine, Bisla runs across and dives, but can't save the boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc [2.0-0-6-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to du Plessis, 1 run, flighted outside off, du Plessis drives it to long-off and keeps strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, bad delivery from Abdulla, short and on the stumps, Faf had all the time in the world to pick his spot, he goes back and pulls it between deep mid-wicket and long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to du Plessis, no run, comes down the track and looks to work it to the on-side, closes the bat face early, the leading edge rolls to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to du Plessis, no run, flatter and around off, du Plessis guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Ravindra Jadeja, <b>out</b> Caught by Kohli!! Another big wicket for the home side. They have now picked up 3 in the last 4 overs. Jadeja tries to hit it with the turn, doesn't get under it, gets the elevation but not the distance, picks out Kohli at long-on. Chennai slightly losing their way here. <b>Ravindra Jadeja c Kohli b I Abdulla 8(8) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[I Abdulla to Ravindra Jadeja, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to du Plessis, 1 run, pushed through on off, Faf taps it between cover and point for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Iqbal Abdulla [2.0-0-22-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to du Plessis, 1 run, skids on after pitching, du Plessis backs away and pushes it to the left of cover, Kohli swoops in and fires a throw at the striker's end, he missed and that allowed Jadeja to get in. A direct-hit would have made things interesting]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to du Plessis, no run, slider that turned away a bit, du Plessis looks to work it to the on-side, ekes out an inside edge onto the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to du Plessis, no run, du Plessis walks across and wrists it to the on-side, Chahal moves across quickly and keeps the batsmen at their respective ends]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, nudges the flighted delivery to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, flatter and close to off, Jadeja defends it back down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Faf du Plessis, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dhoni, <b>out</b> Caught by de Villiers!! That is a huge wicket for BLR. Dhoni goes trying to score quickly. Chahal after getting some pasting has got both Raina and Dhoni. This was tossed up outside off, Dhoni goes for the inside out loft, he gets it squarer than he wanted, picks out one of the best fielders in the world. ABD never looked like dropping that at deep extra cover. <b>Dhoni c de Villiers b Chahal 13(13) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Chahal to Dhoni, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, sharp bouncer to end the over, Jadeja sways away from the line of the delivery]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dhoni, 1 run, back of a length off-cutter, Dhoni punches it to the right of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, again, the length is short, Jadeja pulls it to deep mid-wicket, bit closer to the fielder this time]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Ravindra Jadeja, <b>FOUR</b>, fine shot! Harshal bangs it in short at his pace, it sat up nicely for Jadeja, he transfers his weight on the back foot and pulls it in front of square, beat the man in the deep comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, Jadeja missed out there, it was on the leg-stump, asking to be put away, Jadeja misses the flick and wears it on the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Ravindra Jadeja, 2 runs, too straight, on middle and leg, Jadeja nurdles it to square leg, the call was for two and they make it easily in the end]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel [3.0-0-20-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dhoni, no run, slower through the air and around off, Dhoni guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Raina, <b>out</b> Caught by Rossouw!! Finally, some respite for Chahal. Raina got a bit greedy there. He wanted to hit this for the fourth consecutive six in this over and perished in the process. This was pushed wider from Chahal, Raina came down the track, had to reach for it and he lofts it towards long-off, Rossouw runs to his right and takes it cleanly. <b>Raina c Rossouw b Chahal 62(32) [4s-4 6s-6]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chahal to Raina, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Raina, <b>SIX</b>, a hat-trick of sixes for Raina. Kohli looks a worried man. Floated up around off, Raina goes down on one knee and slog sweeps, it was a top-edge and the small ground helps Raina to collect another six]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Raina, <b>SIX</b>, back-to-back maximums for Raina. This was dragged halfway down the wicket, Raina is quick to rock back and pull it over deep mid-wicket, he connected well this time around]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Raina, <b>SIX</b>, Raina reaches yet another <b>IPL fifty</b>. Even a mishit carries the distance at this ground. Tossed up on off and middle, Raina comes down the track, doesn't get to the pitch but still goes through with the shot, the ball clears the long-on fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dhoni, 1 run, nice floaty delivery, a bit too full, Dhoni drags the drive to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuzvendra Chahal [2.0-0-19-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Raina, 2 runs, comes down the track and takes it on the full, eases it wide of long-on, a slight fumble from Wiese allows the batsmen to sneak a second]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Raina, <b>SIX</b>, fabulous shot! Fantastic footwork from Raina once again, he takes a couple of steps down the wicket, gets to the pitch of the ball and sends it sailing over deep mid-wicket for his third six]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Dhoni, 1 run, trifle short around off, Dhoni pulls it to deep square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Dhoni, <b>wide</b>, Abdulla tries to outthink Dhoni, darts it outside off as the batsman thought of giving the charge, but it was well wide of off, wide given]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Raina, 1 run, again, comes down the track and drills the drive down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Raina, no run, Raina gives charge, yorks himself and squeezes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, Abdulla expected Raina to come down the wicket and fired it outside off, Raina stays put and slaps it square of the wicket, the ball travelled to the fence in no time]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, 1 run, pitched up just outside off, Raina drives it along the carpet to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Dhoni, 1 run, wicket-to-wicket from Wiese as DK comes up to the stumps, Dhoni works it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Dhoni, <b>FOUR</b>, hammered! Full and outside off, Dhoni shimmies down the wicket and drills it to deep extra cover, Sarfaraz runs to his right, dives but still can't stop the ball from reaching the fence. Such was the power behind that shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, 1 run, slanted across off, Raina opens the face of the bat and steers it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[Change of bat for Raina]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Dhoni, 1 run, Dhoni gives the charge for the full delivery, he sets off for the single, Raina was struggling and had there been a direct-hit, it would have been a touch-and-go decision. Harshal was the fielder and he fails to hit timber. Raina had to put in the dive to try and make his ground there]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, 1 run, fullish and outside off, Raina drags the loft to long-on, he got it off the inside half of the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese [2.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Dhoni, no run, good comeback from Abdulla, slows down the pace on this one, Dhoni was looking to sweep and is hit on the glove, the ball rolls to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Dhoni, no run, tossed up and wider outside off, driven to the left of cover where Kohli makes a good stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Dhoni, no run, flighted and just outside off, Dhoni plays with an open face and guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Dhoni, no run, pushed through flatter and just outside off, Dhoni makes room and mistimes the cut towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Raina, 1 run, low full toss from Abdulla, drilled down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Raina, <b>SIX</b>, <b>massive</b>, nice way to greet the left-arm spinner, skips down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and sends it high and deep into the mid-wicket stands]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Iqbal Abdulla, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dhoni, <b>FOUR</b>, that's not a bad way to get going, pitched up and just outside off, Dhoni leans forward and caresses it past point, the fast outfield takes care of the rest]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>MS Dhoni, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[MS promotes himself to number four, gets a big ovation from the Chinnaswamy crowd, a slip is in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dwayne Smith, <b>out</b> Caught by D Karthik!! Edged and caught! That's a huge wicket for Harshal, Smith was starting to take the game away from BLR. This was short of a length and held its line outside off, Smith was looking to run it down towards third man, is cramped for room, extra bounce as well, he ends up getting a thick edge. Karthik moves across to his right and gobbles the chance. <b>Dwayne Smith c D Karthik b Harshal Patel 39(29) [4s-3 6s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Harshal Patel to Dwayne Smith, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dwayne Smith, no run, quick bumper from Patel, Smith ducks under it and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, 1 run, on a length and just outside off, Raina makes room and punches it to the right of mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, Smith looks to pull and mistimes it past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Patel, full and on Smith's pads, he waits on it and tucks it very fine, the man at fine leg is very square and the ball beats him to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, <b>17 runs from the over</b>, on a length and just outside off, nudged in front of mid-wicket for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Dwayne Smith, no run, the slower bouncer from Wiese, Smith ducks under it and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, Wiese is leaking runs here, low full toss and well outside off, Smith leans forward and caresses it past extra cover for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Dwayne Smith, <b>SIX</b>, this is even better from Smith, fraction short and just outside off, Smith swivels across and pulls it over mid-wicket for another maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Dwayne Smith, <b>SIX</b>, <b>5000 T20 runs for Smith</b>, this was pitched up and well outside off, Smith gets underneath and lofts it back over the bowler's head, sends it sailing into the stands]]></line><line><![CDATA[It has started drizzling again]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Dwayne Smith, no run, another shovel and miss from Smith, the slower off-cutter from Wiese, Smith swung hard and missed]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, no run, that's excellent from Patel, bangs one short and gets it to angle across Raina, he looks to pull and is beaten. The ball gains height after crossing the batsman, Karthik leaps and stops a certain boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, fuller length delivery and angling onto Smith's pads, shovelled away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dwayne Smith, no run, tad fuller and holding its line outside off, Smith prods forward and gets a thick inside edge onto his thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dwayne Smith, no run, half appeal for LBW, but there were two sounds there, replays indicate a thick inside edge, Smith was half forward on the push]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, 1 run, fuller length delivery and on Raina's pads, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, no run, short of a length and on Raina's hips, he was shuffling across a long way on the flick, misses and the ball goes over the top of leg-stump]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Dwayne Smith, no run, on a good length and angling back into Smith, defended towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, leg byes, 1 run, another loud shout for LBW, but the umpire reckoned that it pitched outside leg, Raina was looking to flick and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, <b>SIX</b>, <b>massive</b>, pitched up and in that channel outside off, Raina gets a good stride forward, presents the full face of the bat and launches it back over Wiese's head, into the sightscreen]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, no run, Raina missed out there, another slower and wider delivery from Wiese, cut straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, no run, Wiese slips in the slower delivery, Raina prods forward and defends it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, no run, short of a length and just outside off, cracked straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, leg byes, 1 run, another shout for LBW, but the ball pitched outside leg and hit Raina high on the thigh pad, he was shaping for the pull and missed by a long way]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, no run, on a good length and on the off-stump line, Raina was setting himself up for the big shot, makes the late adjustment and dabs it straight to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[Patel changes to over the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, Patel isn't learning his lessons here, too much width once again, Raina goes up and over point for another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, overpitched and well outside off, Raina leans forward and caresses it square past point, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, no run, loud shout for LBW, but there were plenty of things going against the bowler, he came from wide of the crease and gets this one to angle back into Raina, rapped him high on the pads as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, no run, the slower delivery from Patel, it's pretty wide as well, Raina went chasing after that and misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dwayne Smith, <b>SIX</b>, that ruins the over for Chahal! Drops this one horridly short and on the stumps, Smith rocks back and pulls it high and over square leg for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dwayne Smith, no run, pushed through quicker by Chahal, Smith goes down on his knees on the sweep, finds the man at short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dwayne Smith, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, blocked towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Raina, 1 run, tossed up and on the stumps, Raina goes back and works it past mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, another false shot! This was pushed through by Chahal, Smith went for the big drive, drags it towards deep mid-wicket, drops well in front of the man in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, Smith gets lucky! This was tossed up and spun away from outside off, the leg-break, Smith was looking to go over mid-on, gets a thick edge that loops over point and races away to to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Raina, no run, that's a lovely delivery from Starc, gets the ball to wobble in the air, nips back before shaping away from outside off, Raina is drawn into a loose drive, beaten on the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Smith plays with an open face and guides it down towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, no run, on a good length and nipping away from outside off, Smith covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, no run, Starc keeps it full and gets it to shape away from outside off, draws Smith into a half-hearted poke and beats his outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, no run, low full-toss and just outside off, Smith driven straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, no run, on a good length and shaping away from outside off, left alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, even Superman AB can't get to the ball, this was tossed up and just outside off, Raina came charging down the track, goes for the lofted off-drive, doesn't get hold of the shot, the ball stays in the air for a long time. AB charges across from long-on, puts in the dive but the ball drops away from him]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Brendon McCullum, <b>out</b> Caught by Rossouw!! Chahal strikes! A short stay for McCullum, this was dropped short and just outside off, skidded through after pitching, McCullum was perhaps done in by some extra bounce, can't keep his cut down and finds Rossouw at cover-point. Just the kind of start BLR wanted, CHN have lost one of their gun players early. <b>Brendon McCullum c Rossouw b Chahal 4(6) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chahal to Brendon McCullum, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Brendon McCullum, no run, flighted and on the stumps, McCullum stays behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Brendon McCullum, no run, the slider from Chahal, pushed through and turns away slightly, McCullum plays inside the line and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, tossed up and on the stumps, punched down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dwayne Smith, 2 runs, flighted delivery and on Smith's pads, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a brace]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuzvendra Chahal, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Change of strategy from BLR. Chahal will share the new ball.. A slip is in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, Starc gets his radar wrong, this is full and well outside off, McCullum slices it away over point, almost went all the way, bounces just in front of the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Brendon McCullum, no run, the toe-crushing yorker from Starc, swings back into McCullum, he watches it all along and jams it out. Starc has a smile]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Brendon McCullum, leg byes, <b>FOUR</b>, wrong line from Starc, drifts one onto McCullum's pads, he looks to flick and misses, the ball races away off the pads and into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[Its Starc v Brendon McCullum now..]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, another low full-toss from Starc, Smith drives and gets a thick edge towards third man. The fielder gets across, puts in the dive and saves a certain boundary, keeps the batsmen down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, no run, another full-toss from Starc, Smith pushes at that tentatively, gets a thick edge and to the right of 1st slip, Bisla tumbles across and saves a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, no run, Starc starts his IPL with a low full toss, he was searching for the yorker, Smith jams his bat down and gets an inside edge onto the pads]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Smith and Brendon McCullum are at the crease. Dwayne Smith is on strike. Starc will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Right, the players are in the middle. Starc has the ball in his hand. One slip in place..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>20:16 Local Time, 14:46 GMT, 20:16 IST:</b> OK, we have got more news. Match will start at <b>8:25 PM</b>. It is still a 20-overs-a-side match.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>20:13 Local Time, 14:43 GMT, 20:13 IST:</b> Rain is playing hide and seek in Bengaluru. The covers are being removed once again.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>20:09 Local Time, 14:39 GMT, 20:09 IST:</b> It is still spitting at the stadium. More covers are being brought on, we might have a longer delay.]]></line><line><![CDATA[History has been made at the IPL as well. At 17 years and 177 days, Sarfaraz Khan becomes the youngest ever cricketer to make his IPL debut. How will the young boy respond to the situation? He beats the record of Pradeep Sangwan, by a matter of just two days.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The big news from the BLR camp is the axing of Chris Gayle. Match at Chinnaswamy and Gayle getting axed from the playing XI - that was unthinkable. But that's exactly what the team management has done. Remember, Gayle pottered around for a 24-ball 10 in the previous match against MUM. A huge vote of confidence for South Africa's Rilee Rossouw. I presume, he will be opening with MS Bisla. As I type, the rain has stopped and the covers are being removed. We should have action soon.. Scratch that, rain has returned but it hasn't dampened the spirits of the massive crowd assembled at the Chinnaswamy.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>20:00 Local Time, 14:30 GMT, 20:00 IST:</b> Play is due to start now, but there was a streak of lightning and there's some light rain as well. The covers are in place. We will have a delayed start for sure.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams</b>:]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore</b> (Playing XI): Manvinder Bisla, Rilee Rossouw, Virat Kohli(c), Dinesh Karthik(w), AB de Villiers, Sarfaraz Khan, David Wiese, Mitchell Starc, Harshal Patel, Yuzvendra Chahal, Iqbal Abdulla]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai</b> (Playing XI): Brendon McCullum, Dwayne Smith, Suresh Raina, Faf du Plessis, Dwayne Bravo, MS Dhoni(w/c), Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Mohit Sharma, Ashish Nehra, Ishwar Pandey]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather Report:</b> It rained in Vizag and it was threatening to do so in Bengaluru as well. Fortunately, the rain gods have abated as of now. It's a cool and breezy evening - conditions that should make the players feel like home.]]></line><line><![CDATA[CHN's bowling hasn't been the best either. Ravindra Jadeja has been carried by the rest of the team so far. Will Dhoni risk him against the likes of Chris Gayle, AB de Villiers, Virat Kohli, Dinesh Karthik and David Wiese? Will Matt Henry/Kyle Abbott get a chance today?]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Team News:</b> BLR are badly missing a bowling leader and would gladly welcome the return of Mitchell Starc, the World's No.1 bowler. He is likely to take the place of Rilee Rossouw, who was dimissed for a first ball duck in the match against Mumbai. Aaron and Abu Nechim were very expensive in the last match and one of them could well sit out.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-Head Record:</b> One of the most competitive contests in the IPL, CHN hold a 9-7 winning advantage with one match washed out. Chinnaswamy hasn't been a happy hunting ground this season for Kohli's men. Can they change the script today?]]></line><line><![CDATA[We are going to witness few interesting battles today, it's the Indian ODI skipper vs the Test skipper. Its MSD vs VK. It's fiery Starc vs blazing McCullum. Men from the Caribbean, Gayle and Smith will be the key for their sides. Will it be the Captain Cool's day? Or will it be the young and charming VK's day? We are all set for a run-carnival as Chinnaswamy is always known to produce high scoring thrillers. Stay tuned as we update you with the toss and teams in a little while.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Going by the strengths, CHN looks a more stable side with a mix of good international players. BLR looked ordinary in both the departments (batting and bowling) and also looked sloppy in the field. However, with the return of Mitchell Starc, their bowling looks solid with David Wiese filling the void of a handy all-rounder. Wiese picked up four wickets in the last game and nearly won the game for BLR, with the bat. Chahal has been the most impressive bowler so far and BLR desperately need Starc to make a mark as they cannot afford more losses.]]></line><line><![CDATA[CHN, who have stuck to the same side so far, would most likely make a few changes as RAJ outclassed their bowling attack. One of Ravindra Jadeja and Ishwar Pandey would most likely have to sit out as neither of them have been effective. Even though it's a friendly battle, one should also remember that Karnataka and Tamil Nadu were the most consistent sides during the recently concluded Ranji Trophy season.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:45 Local Time, 13:15 GMT, 18:45 IST:</b> BLR vs CHN, It can't get any better than this, the South Indian rivals are all set to lock horns at the Chinnaswamy Stadium  in the Garden city, Bengaluru. It hasn't been a great tournament so far for the hosts as they are sitting at the bottom of the table with only one win against their name. On the other hand, CHN also tasted a defeat in their last game against RAJ, this being their only loss of the tournament so far. BLR are yet to register a win at their home ground and with the return of Mitchell Starc, Virat Kohli's side would be very keen to turn the tables around.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/><br/>It promises to be an exciting contest. Bangalore are aiming to turn the tide after back-to-back losses. They are placed at the bottom of the points table currently and will be seeking inspiration to stem the rot. Chennai were jolted by a thumping loss to Rajasthan two days ago. They too will no doubt be gunning to get their campaign back on track quickly. They will be the more confident side though and it should be easier for them to shake off one defeat after three straight wins that put them at second in the points table.<br/><br/>The M Chinnaswamy stadium in Bangalore is notorious for its short boundaries. With power-hitters packed on either side, viewers and fans will expect to get their share of thrill by seeing the ball being carted around. A run-fest is high on the cards but with quality pacers adorning both teams, one cannot rule out a game-changing spell either.<br/><br/><b>Venue:</b> M Chinnaswamy stadium, Bangalore<br/><b>Date:</b> April 22,2015<br/><b>Time:</b> 2000 Hrs IST<br/><br/><b>Team news</b><br/><br/><b>Bangalore</b><br/><br/>The arrival of Mitchell Starc is bound to be a huge boost for a dispirited BLR. The Australian pacer, recently crowned Man-of-the-Series in the World Cup, will be high on confidence and could prove talismanic given his recent run of form. His improved proficiency with yorkers makes him a good leader of the attack and someone capable of making a difference. BLR's biggest worry has been the bowling department but David Wiese's standout show amidst the carnage unleashed by Mumbai is something that they will take heart from. The likes of Varun Aaron and Yuzvendra Chahal will have to step up and play to their potential for BLR's bowling unit to become a potent combination.<br/><br/>The batting department of BLR has always looked good on paper but getting people to fire together has been a problem. A side containing Chris Gayle, Virat Kohli and AB de Villiers threaten to blow away oppositions before every game but the story unfolding on the ground is often a different one. Gayle has been misfiring a lot more than usual. His wait-before-exploding approach at the top is adding pressure on the middle order, particularly when he falls after eating up too many deliveries. An unabashed approach will be particularly gainful in this format. Dinesh Karthik, one of the most expensive buys in the auction, should be made accountable after repeated failures. He plays a key part in the team and BLR will be greatly strengthened if he finds form soon, adding to the promise shown by Wiese.<br/><br/><b>Probable XI:</b> 1. Chris Gayle, 2. Manvinder Bisla (wk), 3. Virat Kohli (capt), 4. Dinesh Karthik, 5. AB de Villiers, 6. Mandeep Singh, 7. David Wiese, 8. Mitchell Starc, 9. Iqbal Abdulla, 10. Yuzvendra Chahal, 11. Varun Aaron<br/><br/><b>Chennai</b><br/><br/>The advantage of having a settled combination is one of the biggest assets for Chennai. MS Dhoni is not someone who will be looking to chop and change the squad after just one defeat. Ravindra Jadeja's form is a cause of concern, especially so with Irfan Pathan waiting in the wings but it is unlikely that CHN cut the rope early. A rejuvenated Ashish Nehra has taken over the mantle of leading the attack and has struck crucial blows giving CHN's bowling a lot more teeth. They failed collectively against Rajasthan but Rajasthan will be clinging on to the confidence gained from previous games.<br/><br/>Dwayne Smith and Brendon McCullum have forged, arguably, the most dangerous opening combination in IPL 2015. Both men have been brutally aggressive and effective. That Suresh Raina, Faf du Plessis, MS Dhoni and Dwayne Bravo have made significant contributions with the bat so far makes the batting unit stable. CHN will want nothing but more of the same from their batsmen.<br/><br/><b>Probable XI:</b> 1. Dwayne Smith, 2. Brendon McCullum, 3. Suresh Raina, 4. Faf du Plessis, 5. MS Dhoni (capt/wk), 6. Dwayne Bravo, 7. Ravindra Jadeja, 8. Ravichandran Ashwin, 9. Mohit Sharma, 10. Ishwar Pandey, 11. Ashish Nehra<br/><br/><b>Quotes</b><br/><br/>"It was warming to see Bravo do well. If he continues this way, I can come in at four and express myself early." - <b>MS Dhoni</b> talks team work and strategy.<br/><br/>"I was pretty disappointed not to be here from the start but now I am here and I will try to catch up, pick some wickets when I get the chance." - <b>Mitchell Starc</b> is fit and raring to go.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai</b> (From): Brendon McCullum, Dwayne Smith, Suresh Raina, Faf du Plessis, Dwayne Bravo, MS Dhoni(c/w), Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Mohit Sharma, Ashish Nehra, Ishwar Pandey, Baba Aparajith, Matt Henry, Mithun Manhas, Pawan Negi, Samuel Badree, Ronit More, Michael Hussey, Rahul Sharma, Kyle Abbott, Ankush Bains, Irfan Pathan, Pratyush Singh, Andrew Tye, Eklavya Dwivedi]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore</b> (From): Manvinder Bisla, Chris Gayle, Virat Kohli(c), Dinesh Karthik(w), AB de Villiers, David Wiese, Mandeep Singh, Iqbal Abdulla, Mitchell Starc, Yuzvendra Chahal, Varun Aaron, Nic Maddinson, Ashok Dinda, Harshal Patel, Vijay Zol, Abu Nechim, Sandeep Warrier, Yogesh Takawale, Rilee Rossouw, S Badrinath, Darren Sammy, Sean Abbott, Adam Milne, Sarfaraz Khan, Jalaj Saxena, Shishir Bhavane]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>181</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>8</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Chennai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Smith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>39</runs>
					<balls>29</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Harshal Patel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8175</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dinesh Karthik</fielder>
						<fielderId>145</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Brendon McCullum</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Chahal</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7910</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Rilee Rossouw</fielder>
						<fielderId>2244</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Raina</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>62</runs>
					<balls>32</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>6</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Chahal</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7910</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Rilee Rossouw</fielder>
						<fielderId>2244</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhoni</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>13</runs>
					<balls>13</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Chahal</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7910</bowlerId>
						<fielder>AB de Villiers</fielder>
						<fielderId>370</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<batsman-name>R Jadeja</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>8</runs>
					<balls>8</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>I Abdulla</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1830</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Virat Kohli</fielder>
						<fielderId>1413</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7825</playerid>
					<name>Faf du Plessis</name>
					<batsman-name>du Plessis</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>du Plessis</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>33</runs>
					<balls>18</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>242</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
					<batsman-name>DJ Bravo</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>5</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>I Abdulla</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1830</bowlerId>
						<fielder>AB de Villiers</fielder>
						<fielderId>370</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<batsman-name>Ashwin</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ashwin</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>5</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>D Wiese</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8589</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Manvinder Bisla</fielder>
						<fielderId>1901</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Mohit Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mohit Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>M Starc</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7710</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>269</playerid>
					<name>Ashish Nehra</name>
					<batsman-name>Nehra</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nehra</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8665</playerid>
					<name>Ishwar Pandey</name>
					<batsman-name>I Pandey</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>I Pandey</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>201</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>12</runs>
				<overs>1.5</overs>
				<batsman>Brendon McCullum</batsman>
				<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>255</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>70</runs>
				<overs>8.5</overs>
				<batsman>Dwayne Smith</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>413</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>124</runs>
				<overs>12.5</overs>
				<batsman>Suresh Raina</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>265</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>132</runs>
				<overs>14.1</overs>
				<batsman>MS Dhoni</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>587</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>135</runs>
				<overs>15.2</overs>
				<batsman>Ravindra Jadeja</batsman>
				<batsman-name>R Jadeja</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>242</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>156</runs>
				<overs>17.3</overs>
				<batsman>Dwayne Bravo</batsman>
				<batsman-name>DJ Bravo</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1593</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>168</runs>
				<overs>18.2</overs>
				<batsman>Ravichandran Ashwin</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Ashwin</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8181</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>177</runs>
				<overs>19.4</overs>
				<batsman>Mohit Sharma</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mohit Sharma</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>1</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>6</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>10</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Bangalore">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7710</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
					<bowler-name>M Starc</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Starc</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>24</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7910</playerid>
					<name>Yuzvendra Chahal</name>
					<bowler-name>Chahal</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chahal</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>40</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8175</playerid>
					<name>Harshal Patel</name>
					<bowler-name>Harshal Patel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Harshal Patel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>28</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8589</playerid>
					<name>David Wiese</name>
					<bowler-name>D Wiese</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Wiese</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>46</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1830</playerid>
					<name>Iqbal Abdulla</name>
					<bowler-name>I Abdulla</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>I Abdulla</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1901</playerid>
					<name>Manvinder Bisla</name>
					<bowler-name>Bisla</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bisla</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2244</playerid>
					<name>Rilee Rossouw</name>
					<bowler-name>R Rossouw</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rossouw</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<bowler-name>Kohli</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Kohli</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>145</playerid>
					<name>Dinesh Karthik</name>
					<bowler-name>D Karthik</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>D Karthik</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>370</playerid>
					<name>AB de Villiers</name>
					<bowler-name>de Villiers</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>de Villiers</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9429</playerid>
					<name>Sarfaraz Khan</name>
					<bowler-name>Sarfaraz Khan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sarfaraz Khan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>154</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>8</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Bangalore">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1901</playerid>
					<name>Manvinder Bisla</name>
					<batsman-name>Bisla</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bisla</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>17</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Nehra</bowler>
					<bowlerId>269</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Faf du Plessis</fielder>
						<fielderId>7825</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2244</playerid>
					<name>Rilee Rossouw</name>
					<batsman-name>R Rossouw</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rossouw</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>14</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Nehra</bowler>
					<bowlerId>269</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Kohli</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>51</runs>
					<balls>42</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Nehra</bowler>
					<bowlerId>269</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dwayne Smith</fielder>
						<fielderId>255</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>145</playerid>
					<name>Dinesh Karthik</name>
					<batsman-name>D Karthik</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>D Karthik</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>10</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>I Pandey</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8665</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dwayne Bravo</fielder>
						<fielderId>242</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>370</playerid>
					<name>AB de Villiers</name>
					<batsman-name>de Villiers</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>de Villiers</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>14</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dwayne Smith</fielder>
						<fielderId>255</fielderId>
						<fielder2>MS Dhoni</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>265</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9429</playerid>
					<name>Sarfaraz Khan</name>
					<batsman-name>Sarfaraz Khan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sarfaraz Khan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>11</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>R Jadeja</bowler>
					<bowlerId>587</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mohit Sharma</fielder>
						<fielderId>8181</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8589</playerid>
					<name>David Wiese</name>
					<batsman-name>D Wiese</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Wiese</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>22</runs>
					<balls>20</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>DJ Bravo</bowler>
					<bowlerId>242</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dwayne Smith</fielder>
						<fielderId>255</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8175</playerid>
					<name>Harshal Patel</name>
					<batsman-name>Harshal Patel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Harshal Patel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Nehra</bowler>
					<bowlerId>269</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dwayne Bravo</fielder>
						<fielderId>242</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7710</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
					<batsman-name>M Starc</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Starc</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7910</playerid>
					<name>Yuzvendra Chahal</name>
					<batsman-name>Chahal</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chahal</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1830</playerid>
					<name>Iqbal Abdulla</name>
					<batsman-name>I Abdulla</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>I Abdulla</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1901</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>31</runs>
				<overs>3.3</overs>
				<batsman>Manvinder Bisla</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Bisla</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>2244</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>33</runs>
				<overs>3.6</overs>
				<batsman>Rilee Rossouw</batsman>
				<batsman-name>R Rossouw</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>145</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>61</runs>
				<overs>8.2</overs>
				<batsman>Dinesh Karthik</batsman>
				<batsman-name>D Karthik</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>370</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>85</runs>
				<overs>11.3</overs>
				<batsman>AB de Villiers</batsman>
				<batsman-name>de Villiers</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9429</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>97</runs>
				<overs>13.3</overs>
				<batsman>Sarfaraz Khan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Sarfaraz Khan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1413</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>123</runs>
				<overs>16.1</overs>
				<batsman>Virat Kohli</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8175</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>123</runs>
				<overs>16.2</overs>
				<batsman>Harshal Patel</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Harshal Patel</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8589</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>154</runs>
				<overs>19.6</overs>
				<batsman>David Wiese</batsman>
				<batsman-name>D Wiese</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>1</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>5</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>6</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Chennai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8665</playerid>
					<name>Ishwar Pandey</name>
					<bowler-name>I Pandey</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>I Pandey</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>21</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>269</playerid>
					<name>Ashish Nehra</name>
					<bowler-name>Nehra</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nehra</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>10</runsoff>
					<wickets>4</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Mohit Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mohit Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>39</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<bowler-name>Ashwin</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ashwin</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>17</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<bowler-name>R Jadeja</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>37</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>242</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
					<bowler-name>DJ Bravo</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<bowler-name>B McCullum</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Brendon McCullum</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<bowler-name>Dwayne Smith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Smith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<bowler-name>Raina</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Raina</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7825</playerid>
					<name>Faf du Plessis</name>
					<bowler-name>du Plessis</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>du Plessis</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhoni</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhoni</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



