<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14617" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>23rd Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Mumbai</home>
		<away>Hyderabad</away>
		<teamsabbr>MUM vs HYD</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>MUM</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>HYD</awayabbr>
		<homeId>62</homeId>
		<awayId>255</awayId>
		<venue>Wankhede Stadium, Mumbai</venue>
		<startdate>25 04 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>25 04 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Mumbai</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Mumbai won by 20 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Mumbai</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>20</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Kumar Dharmasena</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Chris Gaffaney</Name>
			<Country>NZ</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Simon Fry</Name>
			<Country>Aus</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Roshan Mahanama</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>10:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150425140847</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>HYD</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>MUM</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>137</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>8</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>20</batteamovers>
		<status>Mumbai won by 20 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>1844</playerid>
			<name>Karn Sharma*</name>
			<batsman-name>Karn Sharma</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Karn Sharma</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>2</runs>
			<balls-faced>5</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>1726</playerid>
			<name>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</name>
			<batsman-name>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>6</runs>
			<balls-faced>4</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>111</playerid>
			<name>Lasith Malinga*</name>
			<bowler-name>Malinga</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Malinga</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>1</maidens>
			<runs>23</runs>
			<wickets>4</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1449</playerid>
			<name>Vinay Kumar</name>
			<bowler-name>Vinay</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Vinay</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>31</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>158</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>508</playerid>
<name>Dale Steyn</name>
<player-runs>0</player-runs>
<player-balls>1</player-balls>
<runs>127</runs>
<wicket-nbr>8</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>111</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Malinga</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>2</wides>
			<noballs>1</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>5</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[1 N1 2 . 1 . 4 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. 1 1 W 1 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>W . W W . L1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>2 L1 . 4 . 2 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/MUM_HYD_APR25/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[That ends the first match of today's double-header. The second game is about to start in a few minutes. Change tabs and continue enjoying all the IPL action. For now, cheers and bye..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Malinga:</b> 'It came out nicely. After my ankle surgery, I was struggling for rhythm. It came out well today, I am enjoying this moment, need to do well in the next few matches. I was happy that my plan to Warner worked. Me and McClenaghan work well as a partnership. We will work harder in the next few games as well. It was a good batting track, but when the ball became soft, it became tougher to time the ball well.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga</b> is the MoM for his 4/23]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit Sharma:</b> 'This is the kind of performance we have been talking about. This is the character of Mumbai - which we lacked in the last few games. I should give a lot of credit to the bowlers. This wasn't an easy pitch to defend scores, they showed what they could do. All the players took responsibility - either with the bat or with the ball. I am glad we could send the kids back home with a win, need to continue playing this way in the future as well.']]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier in the day, HYD's bowlers made an impact by landing crucial blows. Dale Steyn, Praveen Kumar and Bhuvneshwar Kumar took seven wickets between them. However, it wasn't enough to prevent MUM from emerging victorious.]]></line><line><![CDATA[HYD's batsmen put up a disappointing show to hurtle towards a defeat. Shikhar Dhawan played with precise metre of timing to essay a flurry of fine shots. However, once he was dismissed, HYD lost momentum. KL Rahul and Ravi Bopara struggled to up the tempo and that didn't help  the visitors' cause. Lasith Malinga, Mitchell McClenaghan and Jagadeesha Suchith bowled with good control for the hosts. Malinga went on to pick four wickets.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The crowd erupts and the Wankhede looks like a sea of blue. Plenty of MUM flags are seen at the ground. The players shake hands. Sachin is very happy in the dugout. A few glum faces in the HYD dugout.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Bhuvneshwar, 2 runs, <b>MUM win by 20 runs!</b> It is their second win of the season. Full delivery, Bhuvneshwar charges down and toe-ends the drive to deep extra cover for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Bhuvneshwar, no run, leg-cutter, Bhuvneshwar once more misses out on the scoop. No chance to steal a bye as well as PP is quick to get his gloves off and collect the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Bhuvneshwar, <b>FOUR</b>, fantastic shot! It was the slower one that was short in length, Bhuvneshwar stands tall and lofts it over extra cover, he generated enough power on the shot to pick up four]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Bhuvneshwar, no run, leg-cutter outside off, Bhuvneshwar walks across his stumps and tries the scoop, he can't connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Karn Sharma, leg byes, 1 run, again, it is fuller and on the pads, Karn goes for the hoick, misses and the ball goes off the pad to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Karn Sharma, 2 runs, full delivery on leg-stump, Karn makes room and chips it straight back over the bowler's head, gets back comfortably for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Vinay Kumar [3.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Karn Sharma, leg byes, 1 run, back of a length slower delivery, Karn pulls and misses, the ball hits him on the back thigh and rolls to the off-side. It is a <b>triple-wicket maiden</b> for Malinga, he finishes with: <b>4-1-23-4</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Karn Sharma, no run, full toss outside off, Karn doesn't get bat on that, PP collects and Malinga tells him not to throw the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bhuvneshwar Kumar, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Hat-trick ball coming up...]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Steyn, <b>out</b> Caught by Pollard!! HYD falling apart like a pack of cards. Malinga is <b>on a hat-trick</b>. His third in the over, fourth overall. Another slower delivery, Steyn backs away and mistimes the loft, the ball skies over the bowler's head, Pollard calls for it from long-on and takes it with his bucket hands. <b>Steyn c Pollard b Malinga 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Malinga to Steyn, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dale Steyn, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to P Kumar, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Cleaned up! Malinga exults and the Wankhede erupts. Once more it was the change of pace that brings about the downfall, Praveen shimmies down the track and looks to send it out of the park, he fails to get bat and the ball knocks the bails off. <b>P Kumar b Malinga 0(2)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Malinga to P Kumar, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to P Kumar, no run, off-speed delivery outside off, Praveen goes for a wild swing, misses it by a distance]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Praveen Kumar, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Vihari, <b>out</b> Caught by Parthiv Patel!! HYD falling apart here. Malinga's slower one does the trick, it was well outside off, Vihari goes for a mighty heave towards cow corner, the outside edge goes low to PP, who takes a good low catch to his right. MUM inch closer towards victory. <b>Vihari c Parthiv Patel b Malinga 16(10) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Malinga to Vihari, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Karn Sharma, no run, full ball on the stumps, Karn moves away to the leg-side and squeezes it back down the wicket, McClenaghan fields in his followthrough. He finishes an excellent spell, his figures: <b>4-0-20-3</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Vihari, 1 run, follows the batsman with a full delivery, Vihari manages to flick it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Karn Sharma, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Bopara, <b>out</b> Caught by (sub)Pandya!! Bopara departs! Is that the match for MUM? The slower delivery that is dragged short, Bopara waits for the ball to arrive and pulls it to deep mid-wicket, Pandya who's on as a substitute for Simmons, runs forward and takes a good catch. Third wicket for McClenaghan and he has been very impressive today. <b>Bopara c (sub)Pandya b McClenaghan 23(27) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[McClenaghan to Bopara, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Vihari, 1 run, low full toss on leg stump, Vihari makes room and drives it to mid-off, picks up a quick single. The fielder hits the timber at the non-striker's end, but Vihari had made it in. The third umpire was called upon needlessly]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Bopara, 1 run, dug in midway down the wicket, Bopara pulls it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Bopara, no run, Bopara fails to connect with a full toss, McClenaghan goes for the yorker and bowls a freebie outside off, Bopara was early into the drive, missed it completely]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [3.0-0-17-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Vihari, <b>FOUR</b>, excellent shot! That is a terrific shot under pressure. Malinga misses the yorker by a couple of inches and he has been put away, Vihari shuffles across the stumps and flicks it behind square leg, the timing on that takes it to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Vihari, no run, change of pace outside off, Vihari goes for a swipe across the line, is nowhere close to the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Bopara, 1 run, full and outside off, Bopara drives to extra cover and takes off immediately, Rohit fires a throw at the bowler's end, misses and Bopara would have been a goner. He is disappointed with himself as he hits the ground hard with his hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Bopara, no run, yorker length just outside off, Bopara fails to jam it out, goes on the bounce to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Bopara, 2 runs, full and outside off, Bopara backs away and slices it square of the wicket, that ball was travelling towards the rope before Pandya intercepts, he dives full length, sticks out his left hand, stops it and hauls it in before sliding into the rope. Saved a couple of crucial runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Vihari, <b>no ball</b>, 1 run, oh dear! Malinga has broken the stumps at his end while delivering the ball. Slower short ball outside off, Vihari chops it towards point. No free-hit for HYD as it was not a front foot no-ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Bopara, 1 run, full and outside off, Bopara throws the kitchen sink at it, the outside edge flies down to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga [2.0-0-13-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>. The break will give the teams a breather for the upcoming 4 overs. It is still anybody's game. Another wicket for MUM and they will be into the bowlers, but if these two batsmen get 2 good overs, then HYD will be ahead. Buckle up folks as we are in for a tight finish.]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Vihari, <b>FOUR</b>, edged and four! A good over for HYD. Those two boundaries helped them to keep up with the asking rate, full and outside off, Vihari goes hard and the outside edge runs down to the third man fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Vihari, no run, Vinay watches the batsman back away to the leg-side, bowls it full and outside off, just inside the tramline, Vihari can't reach that]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Vihari, <b>FOUR</b>, a much needed boundary for HYD. Vinay bowls it short and around off, not much pace on that delivery, Vihari rocks back and pulls it in front of square, splits the two fielders in the deep to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Bopara, 1 run, slower delivery that is dragged short, Bopara pulls it wide of long-on, Pollard keeps it to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Bopara, no run, leg-cutter outside off, Bopara misses out on the cut shot, he was deceived by the lack of pace]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Vihari, 1 run, back of a length around off, Vihari opens the bat face and runs it to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Vinay Kumar [2.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[There was plenty of discussion as to who has to bowl. Malinga was ready to steam in, but Rohit decides against it and gives it to Vinay.]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Bopara, no run, pitched up outside off, Bopara drives it straight to extra cover, Rohit keeps the batsmen at their respective ends]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hanuma Vihari, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Rahul, <b>out</b> Caught by Rayudu!! Rahul's dodgy innings comes to an end. McClenaghan has his hands aloft. Rahul is unhappy with himself as he smacks his bat onto his pad. Full delivery outside off, Rahul wanted to go over extra cover, the bat turned in his hands, skies it to long-off, Rayudu runs to his left and takes a good catch. <b>Rahul c Rayudu b McClenaghan 25(27) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[McClenaghan to Rahul, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Bopara, 1 run, short of length on off, Bopara pulls it to long-on, didn't middle it and hence couldn't find the gap]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Rahul, 1 run, too full and almost a yorker outside off, Rahul squeezes it to extra cover, Rohit sees that the batsmen get only one]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Bopara, 1 run, Bopara gives the charge to McClenaghan, converts it into a fuller length delivery, lofts it on the bounce to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Bopara, 2 runs, brilliant running, Bopara always wanted two. McClenaghan comes round the wicket, slips in the slower one, Bopara opens the bat face and runs it to square third man, takes on the fielder and sprints back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [2.0-0-12-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Simmons is walking off the field. Seems like he has injured himself while saving the boundary in the last over. Hopefully, it is nothing serious as MUM have lost plenty of players already. They would not want another one added to the list.]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Rahul, no run, Rahul comes down the track and clips it to mid-wicket, can't beat the fielder there]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Bopara, 1 run, Bopara is not picking him, once more plays for the turn, closes the bat face little early and the leading edge goes to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Bopara, no run, flighted close to off, Bopara turns it softly to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Bopara, no run, slider just outside off, Bopara plays for the turn, the ball goes straight and beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Rahul, 3 runs, fraction short and on the stumps, Rahul pulls it square of the wicket on the leg-side, Simmons runs across to his left, dives and pulls it in back in, but the ball was rolling back, he again dives forward and keeps it in play. Top effort from the West Indian]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Bopara, 1 run, Harbhajan drags the length back, Bopara has time to go back and push it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Rahul, no run, Rahul tries to be too smart, goes for the reverse paddle, gets a toe-end to the left of the bowler. A fine spell from Suchith comes to an end, his figures: <b>4-0-25-1</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Bopara, 1 run, flatter and on off, punched down the ground to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Bopara, <b>FOUR</b>, Suchith not afraid to toss it up even after getting hit, he throws it up around off, Bopara stays on leg-stump and lofts it inside-out, Pollard runs to his right from long-off, dives but the ball is too far away from him. It goes on the bounce and hits the ad cushions]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Rahul, 1 run, bit more air this time, Rahul nurdles it wide long-on. Sensible batting from Rahul]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Rahul, <b>SIX</b>, just over the rope. Flighted delivery on off and middle, Rahul goes down on one knee and slog sweeps it to deep mid-wicket, he didn't middle it but had enough to get it over the leaping Vinay Kumar]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Bopara, 1 run, tossed up on middle, Bopara comes down the track, takes it on the full and drives to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Bopara, 1 run, flighted on off, Bopara wrists it powerfully to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Bopara, 2 runs, nice floaty delivery, Bopara works it with the turn to deep square leg, he called for two and got it with ease. He placed it right between the two fielders]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Bopara, no run, slower through the air, Bopara turns it gently to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Bopara, no run, flatter and just outside off, Bopara punches and finds cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Rahul, 1 run, trifle short and close to off, Rahul pulls it to long-on, for only a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Rahul, no run, tossed up around off, Rahul kneels down and goes for the reverse sweep, misses and is struck on the thigh pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harbhajan Singh [2.0-0-27-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Rahul, 1 run, Rahul uses his feet, gets to close to the ball and whips it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Bopara, 1 run, flighted outside off, Bopara skips out of the crease and drives to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Rahul, 1 run, straight delivery on the stumps, Rahul nudges it to deep mid-wicket, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Rahul, no run, backs away and cuts to extra cover, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Rahul, no run, tossed up and on the leg-stump line, Rahul was looking to sweep and misses, the ball rolls away towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Rahul, no run,]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Rahul, 1 run, length ball and on Rahul's pads, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Rahul, 2 runs, <b>just over cover</b>, on a good length and just outside off, Rahul makes room and looks to go over cover, just about gets it over the fielder at cover. He leaps and just about getshis fingertip on that, harsh to call it as a chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Rahul, 2 runs, on a good length and just outside off, Rahul dabs it down towards third man, he takes on the fielder and comes back for the seconds run. Parthiv Patel whips the bails off but Rahul makes it in with a dive]]></line><line><![CDATA[The third umpire has been called for a run-out chance. Rahul is SAFE]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Rahul, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Rahul gets half forward and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Bopara, 1 run, short of a length and well outside off, cracked away square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Bopara, no run, on a good length and just outside off, defended towards point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Rahul, no run, Suchith drifts one outside off, Rahul gets a big stride forward and pushes it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Rahul, no run, tossed up and just outside off, Rahul lunges forward and defends it back at the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravi Bopara, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to N Ojha, <b>out</b> Caught by Pollard!! Suchith strikes for MUM! Ojha was looking to up the tempo, comes down the track, Suchith held this one back slightly. As a result, Ojha's timing goes awry, he was looking to go over extra cover, ends up slicing it high and towards long-off. Pollard doesn't drop those, HYD have lost their third wicket. <b>N Ojha c Pollard b Jagadeesha Suchith 9(9)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Jagadeesha Suchith to N Ojha, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to N Ojha, 2 runs, tossed up and on off, Ojha drives it to the left of long-off and comes back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to N Ojha, 2 runs, Ojha shimmies down the track, doesn't get to the pitch of the ball, looks to go over extra cover and gets a thick outside edge over point, comes back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to N Ojha, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Ojha pushes forward and gets an inside edge towards the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to N Ojha, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, Ojha makes room and steers it square behind point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Rahul, 1 run, short of a length and well outside off, Rahul reaches out and slaps it wide of sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Rahul, <b>wide</b>, Vinay attempts the slower ball, it loops over the batsman's head, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to N Ojha, 1 run, short and wide from Vinay, Ojha flashes at that and gets a thick edge, goes to third man on the bounce, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Rahul, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, dabbed away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to N Ojha, 1 run, width on offer from Vinay, steered to the right of point where the fielder makes a tumbling half-stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Rahul, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, Rahul cracks it in front of square on the off-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Vinay Kumar, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Rahul, 1 run, pushed through by Suchith, Rahul goes back and punches it towards wide long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to N Ojha, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, eased down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Rahul, 1 run, Rahul shimmies down the track to a well flighted delivery and works it in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to N Ojha, 1 run, the slider from Suchith, Ojha pushes forward and gets an inside edge past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Rahul, 1 run, fraction short and on the stumps, worked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Rahul, no run, flighted and just outside off, Rahul presses forward and defends it back at the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jagadeesha Suchith, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Naman Ojha, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dhawan, <b>out</b> Caught by Malinga!! That's a big wicket, Dhawan was batting like a dream, his innings has been cut short. This was banged in short and just outside off, Dhawan swivelled across on the pull, nails the shot but hits it straight to Malinga at mid-wicket. The Lankan speedster doesn't drop those, HYD have lost both openers now. <b>Dhawan c Malinga b McClenaghan 42(29) [4s-7 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[McClenaghan to Dhawan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dhawan, 2 runs, McClenaghan shortens his length on off, Dhawan closed the face of the bat on the flick, gets a soft leading edge past cover for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dhawan, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Dhawan presses half-forward and defends it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dhawan, no run, short of a length and just outside off, steered away straight to Pollard at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dhawan, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Dhawan chops it off the toe-end, the ball rolls away towards gully]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dhawan, <b>wide</b>, McClenaghan slips this one down leg-side, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, that's nicely played by Dhawan, back of a length and just outside off, Dhawan waits on it, opens the face of the bat at the last moment and runs it past the lone slip, third man is very square and the ball races away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [1.0-0-5-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Lokesh Rahul, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Warner, <b>out</b> Caught by Rayudu!! Catching practice for Rayudu! MUM needed this wicket badly. This was short and just outside off, Warner was looking to help it on its way, hits it off the middle of the bat, doesn't get the placement right. Rayudu didn't need to move an inch at third man, takes the catch gleefully, HYD have lost their first wicket. Malinga gives a send-off to the departing batsman, first time I have ever seen him giving a send-off. <b>Warner c Rayudu b Malinga 9(7) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Malinga to Warner, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dhawan, 1 run, on a good length and well outside off, Dhawan goes hard on the drive and gets a bottom edge past point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, Dhawan is looking in terrific touch, fraction fuller and just outside off, Dhawan presents the full face of the bat and drives it past mid-off. Vinay gives the chase, slides and drags the ball back in, but it rolls back and hits the ad cushions]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dhawan, no run, Malinga slips in a slower one, Dhawan plays with an open face and guides it straight to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dhawan, no run, another full toss from Malinga, Dhawan takes half-a-step down the track and drives it straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Warner, 1 run, low full toss from Malinga, Warner drives it to the left of extra cover where the fielder makes a tumbling half-stop, saves three runs for his team as he parries the ball towards mid-off with the dive]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dhawan, no run, slower and just outside off, Dhawan lunges forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dhawan, <b>SIX</b>, Dhawan has taken a liking to Harbhajan, this was floated and just outside off, Dhawan goes down on his knees and sweeps it high and over square leg, goes all the way and over the ropes for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, this is even better! Dhawan shimmies down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and whips it against the spin, clears mid-wicket and races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, fraction short and wide outside off, Dhawan makes room and threads the gap between point and cover-point with the cut, another boundary for Dhawan]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dhawan, no run, nicely bowled by Harbhajan, slower and just outside off, drags Dhawan forward before spinning and bouncing past the outside edge. Parthiv Patel is quick to whip the bails off, Dhawan was out of his crease for a while but gets it back in the nick of time]]></line><line><![CDATA[Appeal for a <b>stumping</b>. Is Dhawan's feet in the air? NO, he's got it down in time.. Should be NOT-OUT and it is]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>improvisation from Dhawan</b>, gets down on his knees, uses the pace of Harbhajan, reverses his stance and gets the sweep very fine, beats McClenaghan at short third man and races away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harbhajan Singh [1.0-0-9-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a gift from Malinga, goes for the wide yorker and ends up offering a full toss, Warner reaches out and drills it past cover-point, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Warner, no run, Malinga slips in the slower ball now, on a good length and in that channel outside off, Warner was way too early on the slash and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dhawan, 1 run, very full and just outside off, driven to the left of mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dhawan, no run, <b>how did that miss the leg stump?</b> Cracker of a delivery from Malinga, gets this one to swing back into Dhawan, beats him for pace and whizzes past the leg-stump, Malinga can't believe he didn't get a wicket there]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dhawan, 2 runs, too straight from Malinga, once again drifts onto Dhawan's pads, nudged away past mid-wicket for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dhawan, no run, length ball and on Dhawan's pads, tucked towards square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dhawan, 1 run, McClenaghan tumbles on his followthrough once again, the line is fraction short, Dhawan drops it in front of cover-point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, nicely played by Dhawan, tad fuller and in that corridor outside off, Dhawan leans forward, presents the full face of the bat and drives it past mid-off for a boundary, McClenaghan takes a tumble on his followthrough and is on all fours]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dhawan, no run, tad fuller and on the off-stump line, Dhawan gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dhawan, no run, on a good length and coming back with the angle, Dhawan was cramped for room, gets an inside edge onto the pads, the ball rolls adjacent to the batsman]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dhawan, no run, fuller length delivery and in that channel outside off, Dhawan covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dhawan, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Dhawan goes hard on the cut and mistimes it towards point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Warner, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, driven straight to the fielder at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Warner, no run, pushed through by Harbhajan, Warner was caught on the shuffle, gets struck high on the pads, the impact was in front of leg-stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Harbhajan, drops this one way too short and well outside off, Warner makes room and cracks it square past point, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dhawan, 1 run, this one is given more air, Dhawan comes down the track and drives it towards long-off, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dhawan, no run, pushed through and just outside off, chopped straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, this was tossed up and well outside off, Dhawan gets a big stride forward and drives it sweetly through extra cover. Pollard runs across a long way from long-off, puts in the dive, but can't haul it back in]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhawan and Warner are at the crease. Dhawan is on strike. Harbhajan will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. Harbhajan Singh will open the bowling for MUM. A slip is in place..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Steyn:</b> "Good to be on the field and I really enjoyed it out there. To get Pollard off the first ball in the last over made a big difference. Their batters got in and got out, overall it was good bowling. I think it is a pretty par score."]]></line><line><![CDATA[For HYD, Dale Steyn prised out a couple of batsmen, including the dangerous Simmons.  Praveen Kumar and Bhuvneshwar Kumar bowled with good control and were rewarded with wickets. The outfield is lightning fast and it is a placid pitch, so HYD have every chance of overhauling the target. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Lendl Simmons' crunching innings piloted MUM to a decent total. Simmons, with his pyrotechnics, mainly looked to hoick it across the line and unfurled a series of boundaries. He then completed a fine half-century. Rohit Sharma looked in fine touch during his brief stay at the crease before he lost his wicket to Karn Sharma. It was Kieron Pollard, who cracked a few thunderous shots to give MUM's bowlers something to bowl at. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Jagadeesha Suchith, 2 runs, back of a length just outside off, Suchith advances down the wicket and smacks it to long-on, McClenaghan was always coming back for the second, the throw goes to the striker's end, but Suchith had made it in with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire called for a run-out chance. Suchith is the batsman in question. He has made his ground. Two to finish the innings for MUM.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Jagadeesha Suchith, 2 runs, Bhuvneshwar went for the yorker, bowls a low full toss, Suchith clears his front leg and drills it to the bowler's left, the long-on fielder tidies up and McClenaghan comes back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Jagadeesha Suchith, 2 runs, slanted across the left-hander, Suchith slices it over backward point, hurries back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Jagadeesha Suchith, <b>wide</b>, takes the pace off the ball and sprays it outside off, wide given]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to McClenaghan, 1 run, McClenaghan survives, full toss around off, McClenaghan drags the drive to long-on off the inner part of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Hat-trick ball coming up...]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Vinay, <b>out</b> Caught by N Ojha!! Bhuvi is <b>on a hat-trick.</b> This is excellent stuff from the bowler, another off-speed delivery, it was outside off, Vinay goes for the cut, the outside edge goes to the right of the keeper, Ojha dives full length and plucks it out with one hand. <b>Vinay c N Ojha b Bhuvneshwar 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bhuvneshwar to Vinay, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Vinay Kumar, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Pollard, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Knocked him over! Great start to the final over of the innings. Pollard could have caused damage, if he had stayed there. The slower delivery from Bhuvi, it was the leg-cutter, Pollard was early into the shot, missed it completely and the ball hits the top of leg-stump. This wicket can make a difference of 10 runs in the final total. <b>Pollard b Bhuvneshwar 33(24) [4s-3 6s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Bhuvneshwar to Pollard, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bhuvneshwar Kumar [3.0-0-18-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Pollard, 1 run, wide yorker outside off, Pollard squeezes it off the toe-end to point. That would have been a wide, if he had let that go. Nevertheless, it was an excellent over from Boult, just the <b>8 runs</b> off it]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Pollard, 2 runs, no pace on the ball whatsoever for Pollard, he has to generate all the power, pulls it to deep mid-wicket and comes back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[Boult switches to round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Jagadeesha Suchith, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Suchith stays leg-side of the ball and slices it towards backward point, the fielder gets a hand and parries it to sweeper cover, saved some runs there]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Jagadeesha Suchith, 2 runs, full and speared on the stumps, Suchith plays the pick-up shot over mid-wicket, goes on the bounce to the right of Bopara, Pollard sprints back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Pollard, 1 run, short and just outside off, Pollard fetches it and pulls it to deep mid-wicket, Dhawan keeps Pollard at the non-striker's end]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Pollard, <b>wide</b>, fires it well wide of off, it was outside the tramline, Pollard lets it go and the umpire signals wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Pollard, no run, shortish and just outside off, Pollard makes room and fails to connect with the cut]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Trent Boult [3.0-0-19-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Change of gloves for Pollard.]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Pollard, 1 run, full delivery on the stumps, Pollard eases it to long-on and keeps the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Pollard, <b>wide</b>, this time the slower delivery is sprayed down leg, umpire Dharmasena stretches his arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Pollard, <b>SIX</b>, that was put away with ease. It was a full toss on the pads, Pollard leans forward and flicks it over mid-wicket, the strength of Pollard takes it over the rope. MUM need plenty more of these]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Pollard, <b>wide</b>, fires the yorker down leg, easy call for the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Pollard, <b>FOUR</b>, Praveen is in disbelief. A low full toss on middle and leg, Pollard was early into the flick, closes the bat face and the leading edge balloons over cover-point, no one in the deep to stop the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jagadeesha Suchith, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Harbhajan, <b>out</b> Caught by Bhuvneshwar!! Another batsman holes out in the deep. MUM losing wickets in pursuit of quick runs. It was an off-speed delivery from Praveen, bowled well wide of off, Harbhajan had to reach for it, mistimes it and hits it to long-off, where Bhuvi claims his second catch. <b>Harbhajan c Bhuvneshwar b P Kumar 0(4)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[P Kumar to Harbhajan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Harbhajan, no run, leg-cutter which is short in length, Harbhajan cuts it and picks out backward point, Dhawan fires a needless throw at the bowler's end, Praveen is not impressed with that]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Pollard, 1 run, fullish and on off, Pollard eases the drive to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Pollard, <b>wide</b>, Praveen can't get the yorker right, splays it down leg, Pollard can't lay bat on that, wide called]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Praveen Kumar [3.0-0-20-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Harbhajan, no run, back of a length around off, Harbhajan fails to connect with the cut, it was too close to the body for him to be playing the cut]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Harbhajan, no run, low full toss on the stumps, Harbhajan flicks it to mid-wicket, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Harbhajan Singh, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rayudu, <b>out</b> Caught by Boult!! Rayudu holes out and MUM slip further. It was a nice juicy full toss from Bhuvi, Rayudu could have hit it anywhere, but he smacks it straight to long-on, Boult tracks back a bit, jumps in the air and takes it over his head. That was a well judged catch from the Kiwi. HYD picking wickets at regular intervals. <b>Rayudu c Boult b Bhuvneshwar 7(7) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bhuvneshwar to Rayudu, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rayudu, no run, change of pace from Bhuvneshwar, Rayudu misses the dab down to third man, he was deceived for pace there]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Pollard, 1 run, good length just outside off, Pollard eases it square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Pollard, <b>FOUR</b>, top shot! It looked like a mistimed shot from Pollard. On a length just outside off, Pollard drives it past the diving extra cover fielder, the power of the man beats the fielder at sweeper cover as well]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Bhuvneshwar Kumar [2.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Rayudu, <b>FOUR</b>, another short delivery and this time Rayudu is not holding back, he goes for the pull and gets a top-edge, the ball flies over the keeper's head and almost travels the distance. Steyn bowls out, his figures: <b>4-0-38-2</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Rayudu, no run, bouncer just outside off, Rayudu was looking to pull, but doesn't go through with the shot. Nice carry to Ojha who collects it over his head]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Pollard, 1 run, full and angling into the pads, Pollard whips it down to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Pollard, 2 runs, too straight, on off and middle, Pollard clips it off his hips behind square leg, Bopara runs to his right, dives and saves a couple of runs for HYD]]></line><line><![CDATA[Steyn loses his run-up and pulls out of the delivery stride. He didn't land properly.]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Rayudu, 1 run, <b>direct-hit would have had Pollard in trouble.</b> Good length delivery around off, Rayudu backs away and drops it in front of backward point, Dhawan runs forward, collects the ball and fires a throw at the striker's end, he missed and Pollard made it in]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Pollard, 1 run, short of length around off, Pollard eases it to the right of backward point and gets to the other end]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dale Steyn [3.0-0-29-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Pollard, 1 run, Pollard walks forward, gets inside the line to the back of a length delivery and flicks it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Pollard, no run, another off-speed delivery, Pollard was early into the pull, misses it by a long way, the ball almost shaves the off-pole]]></line><line><![CDATA[Boult goes round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Rayudu, 1 run, full and outside off, Rayudu backs away and opens the bat face to drive it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Pollard, 1 run, that is a new delivery from Boult, never seen him bowling the leg-spinner, Pollard waits for it and guides it behind point, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Pollard, no run, slower delivery close to off, Pollard watches it carefully and knocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Rayudu, 1 run, angled across the right-hander, Rayudu uses the angle and steers it to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Trent Boult [2.0-0-15-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Pollard, no run, floated up around off, Pollard prods forward and defends to the off-side. Karn finishes his spell, his figures read: <b>4-0-30-1</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ambati Rayudu, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rohit, <b>out</b> Caught by Bhuvneshwar!! Huge wicket for HYD. They have sent back the MUM skipper. Nicely tossed up delivery just outside off, Rohit takes a couple of steps down the wicket and mistimes the inside-out loft, he want to go over extra cover, but gets it a lot straighter, picks out Bhuvi at long-off, who takes a comfortable catch. With just over 6 overs to go, that is a big scalp for HYD. <b>Rohit c Bhuvneshwar b Karn Sharma 24(15) [4s-2 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Karn Sharma to Rohit, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Pollard, 1 run, skids on after pitching, Pollard crouches low and nudges it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rohit, 1 run, loopy delivery outside off, Rohit drives it along the ground to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Pollard, 1 run, drifts onto Pollard's pads, flicked away to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rohit, 1 run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Rohit whips it between deep mid-wicket and long-on, Steyn runs to his right from long-on and keeps it to a single. Rohit wanted two but was sent back rightly]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Pollard, <b>FOUR</b>, fine shot! Steyn follows the short ball with a yorker, but gets the line wrong, bowls it on the pads, Pollard glances it fine and beats the man at 45. Steyn's pace took it to the fence with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Pollard, no run, short of length delivery rising steeply towards the batsman, Pollard drops it to the off-side rather awkwardly. He looked in discomfort while playing that delivery]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Pollard, no run, good length ball around off, Pollard presses forward to defend, the ball takes the inside part and dribbles to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kieron Pollard, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Simmons, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Steyn gets his man. Simmons throws it away after reaching his fifty, but he has done his job and that is to set a platform for the final onslaught. It was a back of a length delivery, Simmons moves away and goes for a wild slog towards cow corner, misses and the ball crashes into middle-stump. He is disappointed and he wanted to smack the stumps with his bat. <b>Simmons b Steyn 51(42) [4s-6 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Steyn to Simmons, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, Simmons registers his <b>5th IPL fifty</b>. Gets to the milestone which a cracking shot. Backs away to the leg-side and drills the length delivery to the right of mid-off, the ball travelled to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>that was almost taken.</b> Full delivery in the slot, Simmons gets his front leg out of the way and lofts it towards long-on, Boult moves to his left, dives full length and gets both hands, but couldn't hang onto it. That would have been a stunner]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dale Steyn [2.0-0-17-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Simmons, 1 run, good cricket all-round, Simmons gives the charge, Karn bowls it wide of off, the batsman stretches, reaches for it and drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rohit, 1 run, sees the batsman advance and slows it up, Rohit eases it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Simmons, 1 run, fraction short and outside off, Simmons cuts square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rohit, 1 run, comes down the track and works it to long-on, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, cracking shot! Karn drops it short and outside off, Rohit waits for it, goes deep in the crease and cuts it to deep backward point, no chance for the sweeper cover to stop that]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Simmons, 1 run, nice floaty delivery outside off, Simmons backs away, has to reach for it and he squeezes it off the inside edge, the ball bounces overs the sticks and goes to short fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Simmons, 1 run, slower delivery to end the over, Simmons nudges it to deep square leg and retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Rohit, 1 run, full and on off, Rohit clears his front leg and wrists it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Rohit, <b>SIX</b>, super shot! It was an effortless shot from the MUM skipper. Length delivery just outside off, Rohit comes forward and hammers it straight back over the bowler's head to pick up his first six]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Simmons, 1 run, banged in halfway down the pitch, Simmons pulls to deep mid-wicket. It was in the air and goes on the bounce to Dhawan]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Rohit, 1 run, keeps it just outside off, Rohit presses it to sweeper cover after coming forward]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Simmons, 1 run, back of a length on off, Simmons pulls it in front of square on the leg-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Simmons, 1 run, flatter and on leg, Simmons nudges it through mid-wicket for another single, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Simmons, <b>SIX</b>, <b>hammered!</b> It was bowled fuller and on the stumps, Simmons clears his front leg and tonks it over the cow corner fence. That went well back into the crowd]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Simmons, no run, Simmons gives the charge and was looking for the big heave over mid-wicket there, he gets an inside edge onto the pad and the ball rolls away to his right]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rohit, 1 run, drifting on the pads once again, Rohit clips it down to long-on and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Simmons, 1 run, touch quicker and on middle and leg, Simmons clips it to deep mid-wicket off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rohit, 1 run, floated up and turning away just outside off, Rohit leans forward and drives it to wide long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic timeout</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Simmons, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Simmons hangs back and punches it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Simmons, no run, full delivery outside off, Simmons leans forward and drives it hard, but picks out mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Rohit, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off, Rohit opens the face of the bat and guides it to the left of backward point, the batsmen pinch a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, short of length delivery on off and middle stump line, Rohit waits for it and helps it to the deep backward square leg fence. At Praveen's pace, that was a freebie. Fine leg runs to his left but the ball beats him to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Simmons, 1 run, banged in short this time, Simmons goes for the pull and gets a top-edge that goes high in the air, the fielder from deep backward square leg runs forward but the ball drops in front of him]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Simmons, no run, short and slightly wide outside off, Simmons gently cuts it towards backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Simmons, 1 run, fuller in length and on the stumps, Simmons drives it off the inside half of the bat towards the bowler, who tries to deflect the ball back on the stumps. Lucky for Rohit, the ball goes over the stumps. <b>Had it hit the stumps, Rohit was out as he was well out of his crease there</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Simmons, no run, flighted delivery outside off, Simmons stays back, opens the face of the bat and guides it towards short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four!</b> That would have carried to the slip fielder if he was there in place. For now, Karn gives this one more air outside off, Simmons looks to drive and gets a thick outside edge that runs away to the left of short third man and crashes into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rohit, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Rohit comes on the front foot and drives it down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rohit, no run, bowls it slower on the stumps, Rohit leans forward and tries to push it down to long-on, closes the bat face a little too early and gets a soft leading edge that rolls away towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Simmons, 1 run, floated up on middle stump line, Simmons drives it down to long-on to get off strike]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Karn Sharma, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit Sharma, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Chand, <b>out</b> Caught by Dhawan!! Chand bites the dust now and PK is jubilant after taking the wicket. It was the slower short ball from PK, Chand went for the pull but completely mistimed it, the bat too turned in his hands while he went for that shot. He ends up offering a simple catch to Dhawan at mid-wicket, who takes it without much fuss. Two in two overs for HYD now. <b>Chand c Dhawan b P Kumar 5(4) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[P Kumar to Chand, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Simmons, 1 run, gets this to tail in on a yorker length, Simmons squeezes it out towards the cover-point region and gets off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Simmons, no run, PK bowls a leg-cutter once again and bowls it slightly wide once again, Simmons fails to connect on the cut once more]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Simmons, no run, slower widish ball outside off, Simmons was early into the cut and was through the shot by the time the ball went past him]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Chand, 1 run, back of a length delivery on off, Chand drops it to the right of backward point and sets off, the fielder runs to his right and fails to collect it cleanly, the batsmen make it comfortably in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Simmons, 1 run, starts off with a shortish delivery slightly wide outside off, Simmons cuts it to the right of third man, the batsmen take a single before the fielder gets around the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Praveen Kumar, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[PK replaces Bhuvi now]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Chand, no run, fuller delivery on the stumps, Chand defends it to mid-on, Steyn has something to say to Chand after he finished bowling that ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Chand, <b>FOUR</b>, brilliant shot to get off the mark, it was bowled on a length and swinging away just outside off, Chand leans forward and gently pushes at it. It was bowled at 146.1kph and the pace on the ball takes it to the left of mid-off and the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Unmukt Chand, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Parthiv Patel, <b>out</b> Caught by Vihari!! Steyn gets the first breakthrough. He sends Parthiv on his way back. It was a short of length delivery on the stumps, Parthiv tries to play the pick-up shot once again and he connected well this time around. There was however protection in the deep at backward square leg, who takes a well judged catch in the end. He walks back disappointed and Steyn has his arms up in joy. <b>Parthiv Patel c Vihari b Steyn 17(17) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Steyn to Parthiv Patel, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Parthiv Patel, <b>FOUR</b>, short of length delivery on middle and leg, Parthiv goes deep in the crease and pulls it to the right of short fine leg, the ball hurries across the turf and crashes into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Simmons, 1 run, Steyn drags his length back even further this time around, Simmons goes for the pull but mistimes it to the right of mid-on, another single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Parthiv Patel, 1 run, just short of a good length and on the stumps, Parthiv stays back and plays the pick up shot over backward square leg, there was protection in the deep and the batsmen can only take a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Parthiv Patel, leg byes, 1 run, Parthiv backs away slightly and wanted to heave this over mid-wicket, but he fails to connect. He wears it high on the pad and the batsmen sneak in a leg bye as the ball rolls away into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Parthiv Patel, no run, angling away outside off, Patel mistimes the slog towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Parthiv Patel, <b>FOUR</b>, length delivery outside off, Parthiv goes across and whips it hard, he didn't time it that well and the ball went to the left of mid-on, where Warner dives and gets a hand on it. However, it wasn't enough to stop the ball from reaching the fence and Parthiv collects four]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Simmons, 1 run, full and slightly wide outside off, Simmons slashes hard and the ball runs away down to third man off a thickish outside edge, the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Simmons, no run, Bhuvi offers a little more width this time around, Simmons stays on the back foot and cuts it, picks out backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Simmons, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Simmons stands tall and punches it to short cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Bhuvneshwar Kumar [1.0-0-8-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Parthiv Patel, no run, Parthiv gives a little shimmy down the track to try and loft Steyn inside-out over cover, Steyn bowls it fuller and slightly wide outside off, Parthiv misses and the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Simmons, 1 run, back of a length delivery around off, Simmons hops in the crease and drops it in front of mid-off, he was a little late to take off for the single but makes it in time]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, that's very well played by Simmons, it was on a length and outside off, Simmons opens the face of the bat and gently guides it to the right of first slip, third man was squarer and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Parthiv Patel, 1 run, full and swinging in towards the left-hander's off stump, Parthiv leans forward and drives it to the left of the bowler off the inside half of the bat, Steyn tries to stop the ball with his left boot and parries it to the right of the keeper, the batsmen cross over]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Parthiv Patel, no run, angles this one across off, Parthiv opens the face of the bat and pushes it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Simmons, 1 run, full and swinging away just outside off, Simmons looks to drive, the ball goes uppishly to the left of backward point, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dale Steyn, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Steyn replaces Bhuvi. A slip in place for Simmons]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Simmons, 1 run, bowls this on middle and leg, Simmons wrists it to the right of the bowler and sets off, the batsmen take a comfortable single before Boult runs across and fields the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Simmons, no run, slower length delivery outside off, Simmons lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Parthiv Patel, 1 run, angling in on the pads, Parthiv works it past mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Simmons, 1 run, short of length delivery angled across off, Simmons drops it in front of cover-point and sets off, the fielder runs to his left and fires in the throw at the striker's end. Parthiv was struggling there and <b>a direct-hit would have caught him short</b>. Luckily, Bopara misses and Parthiv makes it in]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Simmons, no run, back of a length delivery on off, Simmons opens the face of the bat and pushes it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Parthiv Patel, 1 run, back of a length delivery on off, Parthiv goes across and nudges it through square leg for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place for the left-hander]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Parthiv Patel, 1 run, Bhuvi drags his length back and bowls it across off, Parthiv rocks back and pulls it on the bounce to deep square leg, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Parthiv Patel, <b>wide</b>, <b>back-to-back wides</b> from Bhuvi as he drifts another delivery down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Parthiv Patel, <b>wide</b>, another one down the leg-side, Parthiv fails to tickle it fine and the keeper collects, the umpire exercises his arms again]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Parthiv Patel, no run, back of a length delivery on top of off, Parthiv gets behind the line and defends solidly]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Parthiv Patel, <b>wide</b>, swinging down the leg-side, Parthiv fails to glance it fine and the umpire calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Parthiv Patel, <b>FOUR</b>, great use of the wrists there from Parthiv, it was full and on the stumps, Parthiv goes sliglty across and flicks it over mid-wicket and collects four]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Parthiv Patel, no run, bowls this one on a length and on the stumps, Parthiv fails to clip it through the on-side and wears it on the pad, there was an appeal for lbw, but the ball pitched outside leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Parthiv Patel, no run, back of a length delivery angling away just outside off, the ball keeps a tad low as well, Parthiv gets his bat down in time and defends it towards short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Parthiv Patel, no run, full and swinging away just outside off, Parthiv leans forward and defends it into the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Bhuvneshwar Kumar, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bhuvi starts with two slips in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Simmons, no run, back of a length delivery on the stumps, Simmons defends it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, Simmons is looking in great touch here, it was full and swinging in on the pads, Simmons clips it through square leg and the ball runs away to the fence in a jiffy]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Simmons, no run, length delivery holding its line outside off, Simmons pokes at it, the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Simmons, <b>wide</b>, Boults slips a low full toss trying to bowl a yorker slightly wide outside off, Simmons leaves it and the umpire calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, full and shaping in on middle and leg, Simmons clips it past a diving mid-wicket and the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Simmons, 2 runs, full delivery just outside off, Simmons leans forward and drives it wide of mid-off, the bat turns in his hands and that's why he didn't get the perfect timing on that, the batsmen take two before the ball is hunted down]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Simmons, no run, back of a length delivery swinging in on middle, Simmons turns it towards mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Simmons and Parthiv Patel are at the crease. Simmons is on strike. Boult will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place for Boult]]></line><line><![CDATA[The umpires make their way out to the middle. HYD players stride out to the centre, followed by the Mumbai openers. Simmons will take the strike first up. Boult will open the bowling.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hyderabad</b> (Playing XI): Shikhar Dhawan, David Warner(c), Lokesh Rahul, Naman Ojha(w), Ravi Bopara, Hanuma Vihari, Karn Sharma, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Praveen Kumar, Dale Steyn, Trent Boult]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mumbai</b> (Playing XI): Lendl Simmons, Parthiv Patel(w), Unmukt Chand, Rohit Sharma(c), Kieron Pollard, Ambati Rayudu, Jagadeesha Suchith, Harbhajan Singh, Vinay Kumar, Mitchell McClenaghan, Lasith Malinga]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mumbai have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Warner:</b> 'I think I am short and small, it has to stick (on being called Pocket dynamite). We need to keep going with this momentum from the last game. When teams are down, they come firing at you. We need to restrict them. He (Dhawan) is a clever guy, if i am firing, he keeps himself back. We would have batted as well. The heat looks ridiculous though. It is a great opportunity for the 17,000 kids to enjoy the game. It was great to get a win last game and it is important to do well with the bat and ball here. We have two changes, <b>Trent Boult</b> and <b>Hanuma Vihari</b> come in for Henriques and Bipul Sharma.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit:</b> 'It's a must-win game. We are just taking it as another game. We are under pressure to perform. We need to perform to the best of our capabilities. We need to play fearless cricket, we have spoken about this. Not sure whether the heat will have an effect on the pitch, but it might turn a little. <b>We are going to bat first</b>. We need to get the basics right. It is a high scoring ground and anything above 170 should be a good total. We also have two changes, <b>Jagadeesha Suchith</b> and <b>Vinay Kumar</b> replace Bumrah and Hardik Pandya.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Toss time!</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The toss is not far away from now. Stay tuned for the team updates.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather Report:</b> Expect humid conditions with the sun shining bright. The maximum temperature is expected to hover around the 32-33 degree Celsius mark. With no chance of rain, we should get a full game in.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-Head:</b> Both teams have met each other on four occasions before today's game. There's nothing to separate both the teams on this count as they have won two games each.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dale Steyn, who replaced Boult in the team two games back, has looked good with the ball. It will be interesting to see whether the Hyderabad decide to have both Boult and Steyn for this game. With the likes of Bhuvneshwar and Praveen in the team, the HYD bowling attack looks one of the best on paper. Let's see if they can continue their impressive show with the ball.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hyderabad</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Hyderabad started their campaign with a loss against the formidable CHN. In their second game against BLR, fifties from both Warner and Dhawan helped them overhaul the target. A low-scoring game against the Rajasthan went right down to the wire, but HYD ended up on the losing side after Faulkner hit a boundary off the last ball of the match. They were close to notching up another win when they needed 10 runs off the last over against the Delhi. In the end, a brilliant final over from Coulter-Nile saw them lose the game by 4 runs. A David Warner special against defending champions KOL, was enough to give them their second win this season after the game was cut short by rain. Not to forget, HYD bowlers were magnificent during the final overs of the game.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mumbai</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mumbai were comprehensively beaten in their opening day encounter with KOL. Harbhajan's pyrotechnics saved them from an embarrassing loss, but they still fell short by 18 runs. Their next two games were against the form sides of the tournament, RAJ and CHN and both those teams showed why they are on top of the points table for now. In their game against BLR, fifties from Unmukt Chand and Lendl Simmons helped MUM reach 209. Eventually, they restricted BLR to 191 and got their first points of the season. In their last game, blazing knocks from Duminy and Mumbai-born Shreyas Iyer took the wind out of MUM's sails, helping the Delhi win by a comfortable margin of 37 runs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[After losing 5 of their first 6 matches, Mumbai find themselves at the bottom of the table. Their counterparts today, Hyderabad are currently in fifth position and they have played a game less than Mumbai. With two wins in 5 matches, HYD are tied on points with PUN and BLR, but are above them because of a superior net run-rate. Hello and welcome to the 23rd match of the Indian Premier League. Before we go forward, let's take a look at the form guide.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hyderabad</b> (From): Shikhar Dhawan, David Warner(c), Lokesh Rahul, Naman Ojha(w), Ravi Bopara, Moises Henriques, Karn Sharma, Bipul Sharma, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Praveen Kumar, Dale Steyn, Trent Boult, Parvez Rasool, Ashish Reddy, Ricky Bhui, Chama Milind, Kane Williamson, Kevin Pietersen, Eoin Morgan, Hanuma Vihari, Prasanth Padmanabhan, Siddarth Kaul, Ishant Sharma]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mumbai</b> (From): Lendl Simmons, Parthiv Patel(w), Unmukt Chand, Rohit Sharma(c), Kieron Pollard, Ambati Rayudu, Harbhajan Singh, Hardik Pandya, Mitchell McClenaghan, Lasith Malinga, Pawan Suyal, Jasprit Bumrah, Colin Munro, Aditya Tare, Marchant de Lange, Shreyas Gopal, Pragyan Ojha, Abhimanyu Mithun, Aiden Blizzard, Akshay Wakhare, Nitish Rana, Siddhesh Lad, Jagadeesha Suchith, Vinay Kumar]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>157</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>8</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Mumbai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>599</playerid>
					<name>Lendl Simmons</name>
					<batsman-name>L Simmons</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Simmons</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>51</runs>
					<balls>42</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Steyn</bowler>
					<bowlerId>508</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>74</playerid>
					<name>Parthiv Patel</name>
					<batsman-name>Parthiv Patel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Parthiv Patel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>17</runs>
					<balls>17</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Steyn</bowler>
					<bowlerId>508</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Hanuma Vihari</fielder>
						<fielderId>8424</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7904</playerid>
					<name>Unmukt Chand</name>
					<batsman-name>Chand</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chand</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>5</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>P Kumar</bowler>
					<bowlerId>592</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Shikhar Dhawan</fielder>
						<fielderId>1446</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>576</playerid>
					<name>Rohit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Rohit</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rohit</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>24</runs>
					<balls>15</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Karn Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1844</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</fielder>
						<fielderId>1726</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>657</playerid>
					<name>Kieron Pollard</name>
					<batsman-name>K Pollard</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Pollard</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>33</runs>
					<balls>24</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Bhuvneshwar</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1726</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6311</playerid>
					<name>Ambati Rayudu</name>
					<batsman-name>Rayudu</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rayudu</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>7</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Bhuvneshwar</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1726</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Trent Boult</fielder>
						<fielderId>8117</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>75</playerid>
					<name>Harbhajan Singh</name>
					<batsman-name>Harbhajan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Harbhajan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>P Kumar</bowler>
					<bowlerId>592</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</fielder>
						<fielderId>1726</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10357</playerid>
					<name>Jagadeesha Suchith</name>
					<batsman-name>Jagadeesha Suchith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Jagadeesha Suchith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1449</playerid>
					<name>Vinay Kumar</name>
					<batsman-name>Vinay</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Vinay</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Bhuvneshwar</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1726</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Naman Ojha</fielder>
						<fielderId>1599</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7624</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell McClenaghan</name>
					<batsman-name>McClenaghan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>McClenaghan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>111</playerid>
					<name>Lasith Malinga</name>
					<batsman-name>Malinga</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Malinga</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>74</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>42</runs>
				<overs>5.4</overs>
				<batsman>Parthiv Patel</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Parthiv Patel</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7904</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>49</runs>
				<overs>6.6</overs>
				<batsman>Unmukt Chand</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Chand</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>599</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>100</runs>
				<overs>12.3</overs>
				<batsman>Lendl Simmons</batsman>
				<batsman-name>L Simmons</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>576</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>108</runs>
				<overs>13.5</overs>
				<batsman>Rohit Sharma</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rohit</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6311</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>126</runs>
				<overs>16.4</overs>
				<batsman>Ambati Rayudu</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rayudu</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>75</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>128</runs>
				<overs>17.3</overs>
				<batsman>Harbhajan Singh</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Harbhajan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>657</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>149</runs>
				<overs>19.1</overs>
				<batsman>Kieron Pollard</batsman>
				<batsman-name>K Pollard</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1449</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>149</runs>
				<overs>19.2</overs>
				<batsman>Vinay Kumar</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Vinay</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>9</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>10</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Hyderabad">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8117</playerid>
					<name>Trent Boult</name>
					<bowler-name>T Boult</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Boult</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>27</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1726</playerid>
					<name>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</name>
					<bowler-name>Bhuvneshwar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bhuvneshwar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>26</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>4</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>508</playerid>
					<name>Dale Steyn</name>
					<bowler-name>Steyn</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Steyn</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>38</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>592</playerid>
					<name>Praveen Kumar</name>
					<bowler-name>P Kumar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>P Kumar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1844</playerid>
					<name>Karn Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Karn Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Karn Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>30</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1446</playerid>
					<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhawan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhawan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1739</playerid>
					<name>David Warner</name>
					<bowler-name>Warner</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Warner</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8733</playerid>
					<name>Lokesh Rahul</name>
					<bowler-name>Rahul</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rahul</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1599</playerid>
					<name>Naman Ojha</name>
					<bowler-name>N Ojha</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>N Ojha</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>571</playerid>
					<name>Ravi Bopara</name>
					<bowler-name>R Bopara</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bopara</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8424</playerid>
					<name>Hanuma Vihari</name>
					<bowler-name>Vihari</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Vihari</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>137</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>8</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Hyderabad">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1446</playerid>
					<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhawan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhawan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>42</runs>
					<balls>29</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>McClenaghan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7624</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Lasith Malinga</fielder>
						<fielderId>111</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1739</playerid>
					<name>David Warner</name>
					<batsman-name>Warner</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Warner</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Malinga</bowler>
					<bowlerId>111</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ambati Rayudu</fielder>
						<fielderId>6311</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8733</playerid>
					<name>Lokesh Rahul</name>
					<batsman-name>Rahul</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rahul</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>25</runs>
					<balls>27</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>McClenaghan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7624</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ambati Rayudu</fielder>
						<fielderId>6311</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1599</playerid>
					<name>Naman Ojha</name>
					<batsman-name>N Ojha</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>N Ojha</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Jagadeesha Suchith</bowler>
					<bowlerId>10357</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Kieron Pollard</fielder>
						<fielderId>657</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>571</playerid>
					<name>Ravi Bopara</name>
					<batsman-name>R Bopara</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bopara</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>23</runs>
					<balls>27</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>McClenaghan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7624</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Hardik Pandya</fielder>
						<fielderId>9647</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8424</playerid>
					<name>Hanuma Vihari</name>
					<batsman-name>Vihari</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Vihari</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>16</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Malinga</bowler>
					<bowlerId>111</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Parthiv Patel</fielder>
						<fielderId>74</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1844</playerid>
					<name>Karn Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Karn Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Karn Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>592</playerid>
					<name>Praveen Kumar</name>
					<batsman-name>P Kumar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>P Kumar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Malinga</bowler>
					<bowlerId>111</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>508</playerid>
					<name>Dale Steyn</name>
					<batsman-name>Steyn</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Steyn</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Malinga</bowler>
					<bowlerId>111</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Kieron Pollard</fielder>
						<fielderId>657</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1726</playerid>
					<name>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</name>
					<batsman-name>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8117</playerid>
					<name>Trent Boult</name>
					<batsman-name>T Boult</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Boult</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1739</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>45</runs>
				<overs>4.6</overs>
				<batsman>David Warner</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Warner</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1446</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>52</runs>
				<overs>5.6</overs>
				<batsman>Shikhar Dhawan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dhawan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1599</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>68</runs>
				<overs>8.4</overs>
				<batsman>Naman Ojha</batsman>
				<batsman-name>N Ojha</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8733</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>104</runs>
				<overs>14.5</overs>
				<batsman>Lokesh Rahul</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rahul</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>571</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>126</runs>
				<overs>17.4</overs>
				<batsman>Ravi Bopara</batsman>
				<batsman-name>R Bopara</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8424</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>127</runs>
				<overs>18.1</overs>
				<batsman>Hanuma Vihari</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Vihari</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>592</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>127</runs>
				<overs>18.3</overs>
				<batsman>Praveen Kumar</batsman>
				<batsman-name>P Kumar</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>508</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>127</runs>
				<overs>18.4</overs>
				<batsman>Dale Steyn</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Steyn</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>2</wides>
			<noballs>1</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>5</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Mumbai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>75</playerid>
					<name>Harbhajan Singh</name>
					<bowler-name>Harbhajan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Harbhajan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7624</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell McClenaghan</name>
					<bowler-name>McClenaghan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>McClenaghan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>20</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>111</playerid>
					<name>Lasith Malinga</name>
					<bowler-name>Malinga</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Malinga</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>23</runsoff>
					<wickets>4</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10357</playerid>
					<name>Jagadeesha Suchith</name>
					<bowler-name>Jagadeesha Suchith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Jagadeesha Suchith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1449</playerid>
					<name>Vinay Kumar</name>
					<bowler-name>Vinay</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Vinay</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>31</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>599</playerid>
					<name>Lendl Simmons</name>
					<bowler-name>L Simmons</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Simmons</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>74</playerid>
					<name>Parthiv Patel</name>
					<bowler-name>Parthiv Patel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Parthiv Patel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7904</playerid>
					<name>Unmukt Chand</name>
					<bowler-name>Chand</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chand</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>576</playerid>
					<name>Rohit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Rohit</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rohit</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>657</playerid>
					<name>Kieron Pollard</name>
					<bowler-name>K Pollard</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Pollard</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6311</playerid>
					<name>Ambati Rayudu</name>
					<bowler-name>Rayudu</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rayudu</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



