<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14644" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>51st Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Mumbai</home>
		<away>Kolkata</away>
		<teamsabbr>MUM vs KOL</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>MUM</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>KOL</awayabbr>
		<homeId>62</homeId>
		<awayId>63</awayId>
		<venue>Wankhede Stadium, Mumbai</venue>
		<startdate>14 05 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>14 05 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Kolkata</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Mumbai won by 5 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Mumbai</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>5</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Richard Illingworth</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Vineet Kulkarni</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Rajesh Deshpande</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Rajendra Jadeja</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>14:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150514181555</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>KOL</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>MUM</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>166</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>7</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>20</batteamovers>
		<status>Mumbai won by 5 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>1858</playerid>
			<name>Umesh Yadav*</name>
			<batsman-name>Umesh</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>U Yadav</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>5</runs>
			<balls-faced>2</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>466</playerid>
			<name>Piyush Chawla</name>
			<batsman-name>Chawla</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Chawla</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>1</runs>
			<balls-faced>7</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>111</playerid>
			<name>Lasith Malinga*</name>
			<bowler-name>Malinga</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Malinga</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>31</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>657</playerid>
			<name>Kieron Pollard</name>
			<bowler-name>K Pollard</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Pollard</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>1</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>6</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>172</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>790</playerid>
<name>Yusuf Pathan</name>
<player-runs>52</player-runs>
<player-balls>37</player-balls>
<runs>160</runs>
<wicket-nbr>7</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>657</bowlerid>
<bowlername>K Pollard</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>1</byes>
			<wides>7</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>8</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[4 1 4 4 1 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>W . 4 1 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 . B1 6 1 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>W 4 1 Wd . . . ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/MUM_KOL_MAY14/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[<b>Hardik Pandya</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his <b>31-ball 61</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit:</b> 'It was a nerve-wracking game. It went down to the last ball, but we held out nerves. A great game for the supporters to watch but extremely happy with the way things turned out today. I think 170 was a good score, the odd ball was stopping and gripping. We didn't know how much was a good score. We have played here before and 180 off is usually the par total. During the strategic timeout, Pollard has handled the situation before and I went with my instinct to bowl him. His body language was confident and I threw the ball to him. We want to concentrate on what we have been doing as a team. Our training sessions have been good and precise, the guys are putting in a lot of effort. We have one final game against HYD, it is going to be a different challenge but we are up for that challenge.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Gambhir:</b> 'I always felt that we gave away too many runs in the end. Not a great effort by the bowlers at that time. Taking it to the last over was a good effort, but we needed to be more sensible with the bat. The wicket wasn't doing too much, but we kept losing wickets at crucial junctures. Yusuf played an unbelievable knock and letting them score 170 odd was probably the game changer. The first 15 overs we were pretty much in the game. You can't let anyone score 70 in the last five. A little more sense in the last two overs with the bat would have probably got us home. Hopefully, we can turn up well against Rajasthan and win the game.']]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, Hardik Pandya's buccaneering knock took MUM to a good total. Pollard struggled to make an impact, but gave Pandya valuable support. With this victory, MUM have kept their hopes of qualifying for the playoffs alive. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Despite Yusuf Pathan's heroics, KOL slipped towards a gut-wrenching defeat. For most part of the innings, Yusuf played with composure to put the visitors in a pole position. However, in the final over, Kieron Pollard snared Yusuf's wicket and MUM registered a thrilling victory. It has to be said that Piyush Chawla didn't pick any of the slower deliveries bowled by Pollard in the last over. Lasith Malinga, Harbhajan Singh and Mitchell McClenaghan all bowled decent spells for the hosts. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pollard runs away as he pumps his chest hard. What a brilliant finish to the game, Chawla walks back dejected and Gambhir and the rest of the KOL players are stunned in the dugout. Chawla could only finish with 1 off 7 balls. Rohit Sharma too was extremely happy as he ran in towards Pollard from the boundary rope. With this win, MUM stay in contention for the playoffs and the race to the top four gets even tighter now. The MUM support staff is delighted as well.Ricky Ponting, Jonty Rhodes and the others were seen hugging each other after the win. Sachin Tendulkar too looks jubilant.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to Chawla, no run, MUM are on the run, they have won this from nowhere. <b>They stay alive in the tournament</b>. It was another slower ball angling away well outside off, Chawla comes dancing down the track and looks to go big on the on-side, fails to connect for the Nth time in this innings]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>6 needed from 1 ball</b>. Can Chawla hit a six here? He has only got 1 off 6 balls]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to Chawla, no run, Gambhir is biting his nails in the dugout. Another slower ball outside off and Chawla fails to connect with the slog, has to rush back in as Patel was quick to charge towards the stumps with the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to Chawla, no run, fuller delivery angling away just outside off, Chawla goes for a slog, but fails to connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to Chawla, <b>wide</b>, bowls this one slower and well outside off, Chawla leaves and the umpire calls it a wide as it was well outside the tramline]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to U Yadav, 1 run, reaches out and drags this slower ball down to long-on, gets a single this time]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to U Yadav, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>ohh dear!</b> That's poor fielding from Malinga, it was on middle and leg, Yadav helps it behind square on the on-side, Malinga at short fine leg fails to get down in time and stop it, the turn probably did him in and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to Y Pathan, <b>out</b> Caught by Parthiv Patel!! Pollard strikes with the first ball and that gets the crowd going. Pathan walks back dejected. It was the slower short ball from Pollard, Pathan goes for the pull but can only manage to get a top-edge, Patel moves to his left and takes a simple catch. Don't know why but Pathan stood in his crease, he should have at least crossed there. <b>Y Pathan c Parthiv Patel b Pollard 52(37) [4s-5 6s-2]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Pollard to Y Pathan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kieron Pollard, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>12 needed from 6 balls</b>. Pollard will bowl the final over.]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Chawla, no run, Chawla once again has been fooled by the lack of pace, it was a slower ball outside off, Chawla pushes at it and the ball goes past the blade and on the bounce to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Y Pathan, 1 run, yorker just outside off, Pathan squeezes it out, the ball goes to the right of the bowler, who can't stop it with his right hand and the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Y Pathan, <b>SIX</b>, <b>what a way to get to your fifty!</b> His 9th in IPL. This was full and on the stumps, Pathan knew this was coming and smokes it over the deep mid-wicket fence for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Chawla, byes, 1 run, another slower ball and once again Chawla is early into the shot and fails to connect. Patel too fails to collect it cleanly and allows the batsmen to sneak in a bye to get Pathan back on strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Chawla, no run, slower delivery spinning away outside off, Chawla goes early into the slog and fails to connect. Good change of pace there from the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Y Pathan, 1 run, full delivery on the stumps, Pathan clips it to deep mid-wicket and it will only be a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga [3.0-0-23-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>21 needed from 12 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Y Pathan, 1 run, that's excellent fielding from Rayudu at deep backward square leg, saved three runs for his team there. It was a shortish delivery on leg stump line, Pathan helps it on its way behind square, Rayudu had a lot of distance to cover from deep square leg, he slides to his right and stops the ball with his right hand. Great effort from him and McClenagahan too applauds the effort]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Chawla, 1 run, just short of a good length and on top of off, Chawla drops it in front of point and gets off the mark with a quick single, gives the strike back to Pathan]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Y Pathan, 1 run, that was poor running from these two, it was another short delivery at the batsman, Pathan pulls it behind square on the on-side, there was a chance for the batsmen to take the second as the fielder had some ground to cover from deep square leg, but they decide against it]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Y Pathan, <b>FOUR</b>, that's intelligently played by Pathan, this was a back of a length delivery outside off, Pathan stays back and upper cuts it late, gets it over a leaping short third man and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Y Pathan, no run, banged in short and on the stumps, Pathan decides to play the ramp shot a little too late and fails to connect, the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Piyush Chawla, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Suryakumar Yadav, <b>out</b> Caught by Rayudu!! Rayudu is on the run after taking a good catch. Yadav's little stay at the crease comes to an end. It was bowled on middle stump line, Yadav goes across and flicks it in the air, he hit it quite well but it didn't have enough to clear the fence. Rayudu from deep square leg runs to his right and takes a good catch. McClenaghan is delighted to pick his first wicket of the night. <b>Suryakumar Yadav c Rayudu b McClenaghan 11(5) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[McClenaghan to Suryakumar Yadav, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [3.0-0-24-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>28 runs needed from 18 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Y Pathan, no run, bowls this one fuller and outside off, Pathan jams out the drive to the left of mid-off, who quickly gets across and fields it. Yadav was looking for the single there, but Pathan sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, full toss angling in on middle stump line, Yadav pushes it down to long-on and gets off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Suryakumar Yadav, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>back-to-back boundaries for Yadav</b>. Vinay bowls a back of a length delivery well outside off, Yadav slashes hard and gets it over backward point, third man was finer and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Suryakumar Yadav, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>deft touch!</b> That's a super shot at this stage. This was bowled well wide outside off, Yadav waits inside the crease, opens the face of the bat very late and gets it to the right of the keeper, who dives in vain. Third man was inside the circle and it was always going away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Y Pathan, 1 run, on a length and outside off, Pathan knocks it down to long-off and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mid-off goes back and square leg comes in now]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Y Pathan, <b>FOUR</b>, that's been smashed! It was a short of length delivery outside off, Pathan waits on the back foot and punches it wide of mid-off, who dives but it goes in vain. The ball crashes into the fence in a jiffy]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Suryakumar Yadav, 2 runs, full toss on the stumps, Yadav checks his clip and ends up spooning it on the on-side, just about clears the man at mid-wicket, who was running back and leaping up to try and take the catch. The batsmen take two before the ball is fielded]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Suryakumar Yadav, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to A Russell, <b>out</b> Caught by Parthiv Patel!! Malinga is jubilant as the dangerman Russell is gone. It was full and outside off, Russell went chasing after the drive, gets an outside edge as Malinga outfoxed him with a slower one. Parthiv bends forward and takes a good low catch slightly to his right. <b>A Russell c Parthiv Patel b Malinga 2(4)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Malinga to A Russell, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Y Pathan, 1 run, banged in short and at the batsman, Pathan goes for the pull and miscues it completely, gets hit high on the bat and the ball was in the air for some time, but drops in no man's land at backward square leg, short fine leg gets around and the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Y Pathan, no run, bumper from Malinga this time, Pathan is happy to sit under it and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Y Pathan, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a nice looking shot, it was full and just outside off, it was the slower one as well, Pathan drills it to the right of the bowler, the umpire had to duck for cover. Pollard from long-on runs to his left, puts in the dive but fails to stop the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to A Russell, 1 run, slower delivery slightly wide outside off, Russell was through the drive a little early, ends up pushing it a little uppishly through the covers for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga [2.0-0-15-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to A Russell, 1 run, full delivery outside off, Russell drives it to mid-off and sets off for the single, it was the slower one as well. The fielder fires in the throw at the non-striker's end, he misses but Russell was anyway in]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to A Russell, no run, in the blockhole this time, Russell gets it to the right of short fine leg off the inside half of the bat, short fine leg moves to his right and prevents the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Y Pathan, 1 run, another one that's back of a length and angling away well outside off, Pathan reaches out and mistimes the flat-batted loft, gets it to the left of extra cover, only a single on this occasion]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Y Pathan, 2 runs, short and slightly wide outside off, Pathan flat-bats it over extra cover and comes back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Shakib, <b>out</b> Caught by Pandya!! Pandya holds onto the catch and looks relieved. Shakib backed away this time and Vinay Kumar followed him and cramped him for room, Shakib goes for the pull but miscues it completely as it hit him high on the bat. Pandya charges in from deep mid-wicket and takes a good catch. <b>Shakib c Pandya b Vinay 23(15) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Vinay to Shakib, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Shakib, 2 runs, slower back of a length delivery angling in on the stumps, Shakib helps it behind square on the on-side, the fielder at deep square leg runs to his left, picks the ball and fires the throw at the striker's end. Shakib had to put in the dive to make his ground. Don't know why the third umpire was even called for that decision as Shakib was well in]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Vinay Kumar [2.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Shakib, 1 run, low full toss outside off, Shakib goes hard on the drive, but picks out the man at sweeper cover. His bottom hand came off the bat as he played that shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Shakib, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a great shot from Shakib, it was a length ball angling in towards the batsman, Shakib heaves it over square leg and the ball runs away to the fence in a jiffy]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Shakib, <b>wide</b>, bowls this one well wide outside off, easy call for the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Y Pathan, 1 run, on the pads, Pathan nudges it to the right of short fine leg, where Malinga dives and prevents the batsmen from taking any more runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Y Pathan, <b>wide</b>, McClenaghan is not happy with that call. It was a slower ball bumper from him, Pathan doesn't offer a shot and the ball sails over his head, the umpire exercises his arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Shakib, 1 run, short delivery from McClenaghan, Shakib pulls it hard and to the right of deep backward square leg, who runs to his right, puts in the dive and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Shakib, no run, good change of pace from McClenaghan, he rolled his fingers over this one as Shakib stays leg-side and looks to slog it hard, fails to connect and the ball goes to the left of the keeper off the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Y Pathan, 1 run, that's a good short for just a single, banged in short and at the batsman, Pathan pulls it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [2.0-0-14-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Shakib, no run, that's drilled but straight to the man at mid-off. It was a length delivery from Pandya, Shakib comes down the track and punches it hard]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Shakib, 2 runs, Pandya once again bowls this short, Shakib transfers his weight on the back foot and pulls, doesn't get it off the meat of the bat, but it had enough to go over the fielder at mid-wicket, who was running back. The batsmen run for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Y Pathan, 1 run, shortish delivery outside off, Pathan plays a whippy pull to deep mid-wicket, gets off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Shakib, 1 run, short and wide outside off, Shakib stays back and cuts it to sweeper cover, only a single on this occasion]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Shakib, 2 runs, this time Pandya angles this one across off, Shakib hoicks it past square leg and the batsmen take two before the ball is hunted down]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Shakib, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a brilliant shot to welcome Pandya to the bowling crease, it was short and there was enough width on offer, Shakib stays back and cuts it to the right of backward point, the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Hardik Pandya, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Shakib, 1 run, once again Shakib gives the charge to this flighted delivery, drives it down to long-on and will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Y Pathan, 1 run, nudges this delivery on middle and leg stump line towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Shakib, 1 run, comes down the track and drives this to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Shakib, <b>FOUR</b>, drops this one short, Shakib goes deep in the crease and looks to cut, the ball flies off the outside half of the bat and goes to the left of slip, runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Shakib, no run, tossed up on off, Shakib leans forward and defends it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Y Pathan, 1 run, flatter delivery just outside off, Pathan pushes it towards cover-point and sets off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Gambhir, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Looks like Pandya's prayers after that dropped chance have been answered. Gambhir comes down the track this time to the ball that was turning in towards him, stays leg-side and goes for a big shot, ends up yorking himself and the ball hits the leg stump. Suchith is pumped after taking that wicket and Pandya too can be seen his hands close together, breathing a sigh of relief. <b>Gambhir b Jagadeesha Suchith 38(29) [4s-5]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Jagadeesha Suchith to Gambhir, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Gambhir, 2 runs, <b>dropped!</b> How costly is that going to be? It was a flighted delivery outside off, Gambhir once again steps out and hoicks it over mid-wicket, doesn't get the desired distance. Pandya runs to his right in the deep, gets both hands to it, but shells it]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, Gambhir too is not holding back, he gives the charge this time around and heaves it to the deep mid-wicket fence. That almost carried the distance, bounces just short of the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Y Pathan, 1 run, flatter and outside off, Pathan goes back in the crease and bunts it wide of long-off and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Y Pathan, <b>SIX</b>, <b>that's smashed!</b> It was floated up well outside off, Pathan reaches out and lofts it handsomely over the long-off fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Gambhir, 1 run, tossed up on off, Gambhir comes down the track and heaves it on the bounce to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Gambhir, 1 run, "catch" was the shout from PP. But the ball lands short of the fielder, short and outside off, Gambhir cuts it in the air to backward point, the fielder dives forward, but the ball drops in front of him]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Gambhir, no run, nice floaty delivery on off, Gambhir defends it down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Y Pathan, 1 run, slower and around off, Pathan gets a thickish outside edge to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Y Pathan, no run, tossed up on the stumps, Pathan kneels down and misses the sweep, it was going down leg, the ball lobs up and PP runs forward and takes a diving catch. It was not required as there was no wood on that]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Gambhir, 1 run, flighted on the stumps, Gambhir nudges it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, this was not all that short, Gambhir uses the depth of the crease, goes right back and cut its square of the wicket, the timing on that didn't give the sweeper fielder any chance]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Gambhir, 1 run, trifle short and outside off, Gambhir stays leg-side of the ball and guides it to deep backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Y Pathan, 1 run, quicker and on leg-stump, Pathan goes for the paddle sweep, gets it off the glove and rolls back past the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Y Pathan, <b>FOUR</b>, beaten on the previous ball and four on the next, that's Pathan for you. Tossed up outside off, Pathan makes room and lofts it inside out to wide long-off, it was in the air, Pollard runs to his left, dives and gets a hand, but can't cling on. That would have gone into the list of spectacular catches had he taken it]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Y Pathan, no run, beaut! Turn and bounce for Suchith, pitched on middle and turns away, Pathan looks to force it off the back foot, is undone by the extra bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Gambhir, 1 run, flighted delivery on off, Gambhir comes down the track and whips it in the air, wide of the mid-wicket fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Gambhir, 2 runs, drifting on the pads, Gambhir nudges it to deep square leg, places it in the gap and gets a comfortable two]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jagadeesha Suchith, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Y Pathan, no run, slower through the air, Pathan knocks it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Y Pathan, no run, push-drives the flighted delivery to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Y Pathan, <b>wide</b>, quicker and fired down leg, Pathan can't lay bat on that, PP doesn't collect it cleanly, the ball rolls to short fine, GG wanted the run but is sent back. They missed out on a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Y Pathan, no run, quicker and outside off, Pathan waits for the ball to arrive and cuts it late to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Y Pathan, no run, floated on the stumps, Pathan defends to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Gambhir, 1 run, flighted outside off, Gambhir drives it down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Y Pathan, 1 run, tossed up on off, Pathan leans forward and wrists it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Y Pathan, <b>wide</b>, darted down the leg-side, Pathan looks to help it on the way, misses and wide given]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Y Pathan, 1 run, good length ball on off, Pathan defends in front of cover and takes off immediately, good response from GG]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Gambhir, 1 run, back of a length outside off, Gambhir steers it with an angled bat to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Gambhir, no run, bumper angling into the batsman, Gambhir goes for the pull, misses as the ball sails over the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Y Pathan, 1 run, back of a length close to off, Pathan punches it to the left of mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Y Pathan, no run, good length ball around off, Pathan bunts it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Gambhir, 1 run, starts from round the wicket, on middle and leg, Gambhir gets inside the line and glances it to fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Vinay Kumar [1.0-0-9-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Y Pathan, <b>FOUR</b>, Pathan off and running. Fraction short and outside off, Pathan uses the pace on the ball and cuts it behind point, Simmons can't stop that and it races away to the fence. An adventurous first over from Bhajji comes to an end. It had everything six, wickets and four]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Yusuf Pathan, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Gambhir, <b>out</b> M Pandey Run Out!! A wicket gifted away by KOL. Once again brilliance in the field from Simmons. Pushed through on leg-stump, Gambhir glances it to short fine, Pandey calls for a needless run, he knew he was struggling, puts in the dive, but Simmons hits the bull's eye. MUM are back in the game in just 3 balls. <b>M Pandey run out (Simmons) 1(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Harbhajan to Gambhir, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[TV umpire pressed into service. MUM players think they have their man. Pandey might be struggling. He is short and has to make his way back to the pavilion.]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to M Pandey, 1 run, tossed up around off, Pandey wrists it to long-on and opens his account]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Manish Pandey, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Uthappa, <b>out</b> Caught by Malinga!! Harbhajan has his man. That is a good comeback after being hit off the first ball. It was a nothing shot really from Uthappa. Quicker and on the stumps, Uthappa goes down on one knee, plays the lap shot to short fine, didn't get the elevation to clear Malinga, who juggled a couple of times before taking it. <b>Uthappa c Malinga b Harbhajan 25(20) [4s-3 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Harbhajan to Uthappa, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Uthappa, no run, pushed through outside off, Uthappa steers it to short third man, wants the single but is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Uthappa, <b>wide</b>, fired down the leg-side, Uthappa can't connect with the paddle, an extra added to the total]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Uthappa, <b>SIX</b>, Bhajji welcomed to the attack with a massive hit. Flighted delivery on middle and leg, Uthappa kneels down and middles the slog sweep, the ball sails away over deep square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harbhajan Singh, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Uthappa, 1 run, slants the length delivery into the batsman, Uthappa goes for the hoick, gets a thickish inside edge to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Gambhir, 1 run, good length ball on the stumps, Gambhir drops it near his feet, the ball rolls adjacent to the pitch, Uthappa calls for the run and makes it with ease, McClenaghan runs forward and can't flick the ball onto the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Gambhir, <b>wide</b>, bouncer angling into the batsman, Gambhir sways away from the line of the delivery, the umpire does not like the height on that]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Uthappa, 1 run, Uthappa backs away and chops the back of a length delivery to cover-point, the duo go through for a risky single. Suchith fires a throw at the bowler's end, he missed but Uthappa would have just made his ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket now]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Uthappa, no run, too full and just outside off, Uthappa toe-ends the drive to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, back of a length on off, Uthappa plants his front foot forward and pulls it over the leaping mid-wicket fielder, he got it right off the meat as the ball reached the fence in a jiffy]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Gambhir, 1 run, on a length just outside off, Gambhir hops across and dabs it to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [1.0-0-5-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Uthappa, no run, good length ball on the stumps, Uthappa drives it down the wicket, Vinay reaches out to his right and makes a fine stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, fabulous shot! After a couple of awful shots, Uthappa connects with one. Banged in halfway down the wicket, he was expecting it, rocks back and nails the pull to deep mid-wicket, it almost went the distance. The third umpire confirmed that it went on the bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Uthappa, no run, Uthappa doesn't want his state team's mate to settle. Advances down the wicket and wanted to go over mid-off, Vinay keeps it back of a length, Uthappa misses the shot and the ball flies over the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Uthappa, no run, good length ball just outside off, Uthappa goes for a cross-batted heave, mistimes it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Gambhir, 1 run, Vinay goes round the wicket, angles it in on the pads, Gambhir flicks it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, cracking shot! Vinay is greeted to the attack with a superb shot. Gambhir makes room as he gives the charge, converts it into a length delivery, opens the bat face and drills the drive in the air wide of cover-point, Suchith dived but it was well wide of him]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Vinay Kumar, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Uthappa, no run, shortens the length around off, Uthappa plays it with soft hands and guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Gambhir, 1 run, low full toss on the stumps, Gambhir works it to deep mid-wicket, was looking for two but decides against it]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Gambhir, no run, excellent comeback, the slower ball dips in, Gambhir is early on the drive, the ball sneaks under the bat and goes on the bounce to Parthiv]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, super shot! Just a few inches short of yorker length, Gambhir leans forward and flicks it handsomely in front of square, no fielder at mid-wicket and the ball rockets to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Gambhir, 2 runs, Malinga misses the yorker, bowls a full toss on the pads, Gambhir whips it behind square leg, McClenaghan runs to his right from fine leg, slides and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Uthappa, 1 run, change of pace, low full toss, Uthappa flicks it to deep mid-wicket and crosses over]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Gambhir, no run, fuller and just outside off, Gambhir drives and picks out short cover, he had middled that but couldn't hit the gap]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Gambhir, no run, drags the length back, Gambhir tries to force it off the back foot, the extra bounce does him in. The ball beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, Gambhir is very strong in that area. Fraction short and hint of width, he gets on top of the bounce and cuts it to the right of backward point, Pollard dives in vain. He did well to find the gap there]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Gambhir, no run, back of a length on off, Gambhir knocks it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[A wide slip in place for Gambhir]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Uthappa, 1 run, short and cramps the batsman for room, Uthappa is hurried on the pull, mistimes it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Uthappa, no run, short of length on off, Uthappa drops it in front of point, Pollard gets to the ball quickly]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Gambhir, no run, Malinga gets away with a full toss, Gambhir's feet went nowhere as he pushed it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Uthappa, 1 run, good length ball on off, Uthappa wrists it wide of mid-on and takes a sharp run]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Uthappa, no run, slower ball, it was a low full toss, dipped on the batsman, Uthappa spotted it late, but adjusted well to defend back to the bowler, both the batsman and bowler have a smile on their faces]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Uthappa, no run, on a length just outside off, Uthappa presses it to cover after coming forward, calls "wait" for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! Malinga goes straight and drifts it onto the pads, Uthappa presses forward and flicks it elegantly over the infield, the ball races away to the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Uthappa, 2 runs, some movement for Malinga, it was back of a length and outside off, shaping away as well, Uthappa leans forward, opens the bat face and guides it to square third man, easy two]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Uthappa and Gambhir are at the crease. Uthappa is on strike. Malinga will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back... It is a must win game for MUM and the batters have done the job. Now, it is upto their bowlers. Can they defend this target? We'll find out soon as the players stride out to the middle. Uthappa makrs his guard. Malinga has the new ball and already the crowd are chanting "Malinga, Malinga". One slip and a floating third slip in place...]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pollard had his fair share of problems against the spinners, but strung together a sparkling partnership with Pandya. In fact, it was the partnership between Pandya and Pollard that lifted MUM's sagging morale. Pandya showed his class by thwacking Umesh Yadav for four boundaries in the 17th over. For KOL, Shakib picked up two scalps. The track is offering a bit of help for the spinners and it won't be easy to chase down the target. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[On the back of a sterling partnership between Hardik Pandya and Kieron Pollard, MUM registered a good total. Initially, Sunil Narine, Morne Morkel and Shakib Al Hasan all chipped in with wickets to put the visitors in the ascendancy. It was Shakib, who picked up the wicket of Parthiv Patel to put the lid on the scoring rate. Rohit Sharma tried to up the ante, but was dismissed by a crackerjack of a delivery from Narine. It was the knuckle ball that accounted for the wicket of Rohit.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Pollard, 1 run, Umesh gets away with one, full toss at a nice height, Pollard can only hammer it to long-on. That was there to be put away, but he couldn't get it off the meat]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Pandya, 1 run, yorker outside off, Pandya digs it out the drive to extra cover, quick single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Pollard, 1 run, too full and around off, Pollard squeezes it to long-off, once more the bottom hand comes off the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Pollard, 2 runs, pitched up outside off, Pollard drives to wide of long-off, Manish tidies up but the batsmen have enough time to come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Pandya, 1 run, short and outside off, Pandya goes for the pull, the thick outside edge flies down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Free-hit</b> coming up..]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Pandya, <b>no ball</b>, 2 runs, this is just poor from Umesh. Another full toss outside off, Pandya drives to the right of sweeper cover, Russell runs cross, slides and saves a couple of runs. Umesh has overstepped though and it is a big one]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Pandya, <b>FOUR</b>, great start to the over, rubbish delivery from Umesh, full toss outside off, Pandya slices it over backward point, the bottom hand came off the bat, but had connected well]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav [2.0-0-24-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pandya, 1 run, low full toss on leg-stump, Pandya went for the lap shot, the ball hits the toe-end and rolls down to long-on. Another big over for MUM, <b>17 runs</b> came off it]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pandya, no run, fuller and on off, Pandya drives down the wicket, Russell does well to stop it in his followthrough]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pandya, <b>SIX</b>, Pandya registers his <b>maiden IPL fifty</b>. The whole MUM dug-out stands up and applauds the young man's effort. Pandya just raises his bat and acknowledges it. Back of a length, Pandya was expecting it, pulls it over deep mid-wicket to reach the landmark in style]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pandya, <b>FOUR</b>, well directed short delivery, Pandya takes it on, the top-edge flies over the keeper's head, that's more for Pandya and MUM]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pandya, <b>FOUR</b>, full delivery just outside off, Pandya lofts it inside out over extra cover, the fielder at long-off was inside the ring, Umesh gives chase but comes second]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pandya, <b>no ball</b>, beamer. Both the bowler and batsman have a smile on the face. Russell apologised immediately. It was the attempted yorker that slipped out of the hands, Pandya did well to get inside the line and let it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pollard, 1 run, short and just outside off, Pollard swats it straight to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell [3.0-0-20-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pandya, no run, tossed up on off, Pandya defends it down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pandya, <b>wide</b>, offie turns down leg, Pandya falls over as he misses the flick, his back foot was raised but he got back before Uthappa whipped the bails off. That was some neat glovework from Uthappa]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire called for a stumping chance. Uthappa seemed confident. Pandya has lifted his back foot. Is it in the air? He might have just got back in time.]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pandya, <b>SIX</b>, clean strike! Full and in the slot, on middle and leg, Pandya comes forward, gets under that and tonks it over cow corner. The ball went flat and a long way into the stands]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pollard, 1 run, quicker and outside off, Pollard dabs it to short third man, calls for the run and gets the desired response from Pandya]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pandya, 1 run, off-break turns back in, Pandya makes room and punches to deep extra cover, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pollard, 1 run, flatter and around off, Pollard knocks it off the back foot to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pandya, 1 run, flighted on off, Pandya lofts it to long-on, Suryakumar runs forward and the ball drops in front of him, he did well to get his body behind]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Pandya, 1 run, pitched up just outside off, Pandya hammers the drive down the wicket, Yadav gets his boot in the way and saves some runs. An expensive over after the strategic break, <b>18 runs from the over</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Pandya, <b>FOUR</b>, this was a poor ball from Yadav, short and plenty of width on offer, Pandya doesn't bother to keep it down the ground, cuts it up and over backward point to collect his fourth boundary in the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Australian coach Darren Lehmann is in the house.]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Pandya, <b>FOUR</b>, streaky! But Pandya and MUM will take that. It is the third boundary of the over. Short and on off, Pandya gets an inside edge on the short-arm pull, goes past the stumps and beats short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Pandya, <b>FOUR</b>, back-to-back boundaries for Pandya. Yorker ends up being a low full toss, Pandya goes low, opens the bat face and steers it to third man, Narine slides, the ball hits his body and rolls away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Pandya, <b>FOUR</b>, top shot! This young man can bat. Short and on off, Pandya rocks back and plays the short-arm pull, split the fielders at deep square and deep mid-wicket to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Pollard, 1 run, fullish and on off, Pollard drives it down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav [1.0-0-6-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pollard, 1 run, knuckle ball outside off, Pollard lunges forward and eases it towards point, retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pandya, 1 run, pushed through, Pandya punches it down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pollard, 1 run, another run taken behind square on the off-side, guided to Morne at short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pandya, 1 run, knuckle ball outside off, Pandya dabs it to the left of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pandya, <b>wide</b>, another off-break goes down leg, easy call for umpire Illingworth]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pollard, 1 run, flatter and just outside off, Pollard steers it to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pollard, <b>wide</b>, offie turning down leg, Pollard can't get bat on the glance, wide given]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pollard, <b>SIX</b>, fabulous shot! First signs of aggression from Pollard. Flighted just outside off, Pollard dances down the wicket, doesn't get to the pitch, still goes through with the loft, clears long-on with ease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sunil Narine [2.0-0-14-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pollard, 1 run, Russell goes for the yorker, bowls a low full toss, drilled down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pollard, no run, takes the pace off the ball, Pollard hangs back and defends it to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pandya, 1 run, short and on the stumps, Pandya pulls it in front of square, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pandya, 2 runs, short of length on off and middle, Pandya plays the short-arm pull to fine leg, scampers back for the second before Morkel gets to the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pandya, no run, off-speed delivery outside off, Pandya covers the line, shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pandya, <b>FOUR</b>, super shot! It was just a steer and the ball raced away to the fence. Back of a length and on off, Pandya uses the pace on the ball and guides it behind point, the timing was excellent]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Pollard, no run, fires it around off, Pollard chops it to Uthappa, who collects it on the bounce. Shakib has a fantastic return to the team, he ends with very impressive figures: <b>4-0-22-2</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Goes over the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Pandya, 1 run, floated up just outside off, Pandya presses it wide of cover and sets off for the run]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Pandya, <b>wide</b>, darted down the leg-side, an extra added to the total]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Pollard, 1 run, tossed up close to off, Pollard drags the drive to long-on, came off the inner part of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Pandya, 1 run, flighted around off, Pandya wrists it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Pollard, 1 run, flatter and just outside off, Pollard pulls hard towards long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Pollard, no run, pushed through on the pads, Pollard misses the clip and wears it on the pad, going down leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan [3.0-0-17-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pollard, 1 run, again, nothing in Pollard's arc, short and on off, Pollard mistimes the pull to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pollard, no run, Uthappa went up for a caught behind appeal, but nothing from Russell. Back of a length and nips in, Pollard is cramped for room, ball hits the thigh pad and goes to Uthappa. There was no inside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pandya, 1 run, too straight, on middle and leg, Pandya flicks it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pollard, 1 run, short and outside off, Pollard fetches the pull and the top-edge balloons wide of the short fine fielder. Russell was interested for a while as the ball eluded Morkel]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pollard, 2 runs, dug in short and aimed at the body, Pollard tucks it with soft hands to mid-wicket, hares back for the second before the ball is hunted down]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pandya, 1 run, short of length around off, steered away to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pandya, leg byes, 1 run, flighted on leg-stump, Pandya leans forward and misses the nudge, ball goes off the pad to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[A silly point and slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pandya, no run, pushed through on off, Pandya defends to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hardik Pandya, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Rohit, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Cleaned up! That ball would have got any right-hander in the world. Even Narine enjoyed it as he pumps his fists. The knuckle ball once more, pitched on middle and straightened, Rohit played down the wrong line, is beaten in defence and the ball hits the top of off-stump. Gambhir was also delighted with the wicket. <b>Rohit b Narine 30(21) [4s-5]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Narine to Rohit, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, knuckle ball from Narine, short in length and turning away, Rohit read it well, goes back and cuts it square of the wicket, Chawla runs to his left from sweeper cover, gets a hand but can't stop it]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pollard, 1 run, flatter and on off, Pollard whips it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Rohit, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Rohit nudges it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pollard, no run, again, short and just outside off, Pollard dabs it to point and wanted the run, but is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pollard, <b>FOUR</b>, finally, Pollard decided to take on the short delivery, it was bowled at a good height from Russell, Pollard rocked back and pulled it in front of square on the leg-side, Chawla ran to his left and had no chance of stopping the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pollard, no run, back of a length around off, Pollard knocks it towards point, no chance for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pollard, no run, fuller and outside off, Pollard drives and picks out cover, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Rohit, 1 run, shortens the length on off, Rohit opens the bat face and glides it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Pollard, 1 run, banged in halfway down the wicket, Pollard drops it with softs hands between cover and point, quick single taken]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pollard is on the ground, working on his boot. Seems like there was some extra mud stuck in the spikes. All sorted out now and he is ready to get going.]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, Narine gives this one more air, Rohit gets a big stride forward and drives it through cover, beats the fielder running across from long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pollard, 1 run, this one is given more air, driven to the left of mid-wicket where the fielder makes a partial stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pollard, 2 runs, pushed through and just outside off, Pollard was looking to nudge it towards the on-side, gets a leading edge towards backward point. Umesh dives over the ball and allows an extra run]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pollard, no run, Narine slows down the pace as Pollard came down the track, defended in front of cover. He was almost committed to a single, sent back in time by Rohit]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Pollard, no run, tossed up and just outside off, Pollard prods forward and defends it back at the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Rohit, 1 run, flighted and on Rohit's pads, worked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sunil Narine, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Pollard, no run, <b>loud shout for LBW</b>, it was the wrong 'un from Chawla, Pollard didn't read it one bit, went back and missed, the impact was in front of leg-stump. The ball would have been going down leg as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Rohit, 1 run, flighted delivery and just outside off, driven square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, this one is given more air by Chawla, Rohit gets down on his knees and sweeps it powerfully past square leg, the ball races away to the fence for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, fraction too short and wide outside off, Rohit makes room and cracks it square behind point, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Rohit, no run, this one is given more air, driven back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Rohit, no run, flighted delivery and on Rohit's pads, worked towards mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Piyush Chawla, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Pollard, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Pollard comes down the track and defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Pollard, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Pollard walks down the track and defends it with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Pollard, no run, Morkel shortens his length as Pollard walked down the track, he gets his bat and gloves out of the way and allows the ball to hit his thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[A FSL in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Pollard, <b>wide</b>, short of a length and angling down leg-side, Pollard gets his bat and glove out of the way, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Pollard, no run, that's a nasty bouncer from Morkel, Pollard hops across and plays with soft hands, ends up fending it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Rohit, 1 run, on a good length and angling into Rohit, he was early in closing the face of the bat, gets a thick leading edge behind square on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Rohit, no run, short of a length and angling into Rohit, he shuffles across and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Pollard, no run, pushed through and on Pollard's pads, he comes down the track and misses the flick, the ball rolls away off the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[A gully is in now]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Pollard, no run, slower and drifting into Pollard, he watches it all along and dabs it towards first slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[A silly point is in place, a slip as well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, 1 run, flighted delivery and on off, punched down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kieron Pollard, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rayudu, <b>out</b> Caught by A Russell!! Another wicket goes in waste! Rayudu has thrown it away here, this was flighted and well outside off, Rayudu comes down the track and was looking to go inside out over cover. The bat turned in his hands and he ends up slicing it high and towards long-off. Russell doesn't drop those, MUM have lost their third wicket. <b>Rayudu c A Russell b Shakib 2(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shakib to Rayudu, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rayudu, no run, this one is given more air, pushed to the right of the bowler, he dives and saves some runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, 1 run, tossed up and just outside off, driven past cover for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Rayudu, 2 runs, good start from Rayudu, full and on Rayudu's pads, whipped away behind square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Rohit, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, steered away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Rohit, <b>wide</b>, Morkel shortens the length and sprays this one wide outside off, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ambati Rayudu, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Simmons, <b>out</b> Caught by M Pandey!! Another waste of a wicket for MUM. This was banged in short and just outside off, Simmons made room for the cut, the ball got big on him, he ended up getting a top-edge and the ball went high in the air, Manish settled underneath the skier at point and holds onto the dolly. MUM have lost both openers now. <b>Simmons c M Pandey b M Morkel 14(16) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[M Morkel to Simmons, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Simmons, <b>SIX</b>, Simmons makes the most of the free-hit, this was the slower length ball from Morkel, Simmons cleared his left leg, went deep inside the crease and lofts it high and over long-on for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Free-Hit</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Simmons, <b>no ball</b>, Morkel keeps it full and on the stumps, Simmons made room outside leg and squeezed it straight to the fielder at backward point. Morkel has overstepped though]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Simmons, no run, Morkel bangs one short and on the stumps, Simmons was way too early on the pull, gets an inside edge onto the body]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Rohit, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Rohit plays with an open face and guides it down towards third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, 1 run, flighted and just outside off, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Shakib, he dropped this one short and wide outside off, Rohit made room and cracked it to the left of cover-point. Pathan dives over the ball and concedes a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, no run, pushed through and on Rohit's pads, he looks to nudge it towards the on-side, hits him high on the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rohit, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Rohit gets forward and drives it back at the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit Sharma, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Parthiv Patel, <b>out</b> Caught by M Pandey!! Parthiv has thrown away yet another start! Shakib slows down the pace as Parthiv came down the track, the ball dipped onto him, he wasn't there to the pitch, he ended up shovelling it over mid-wicket. Manish came in from the deep and holds onto the simple chance. MUM have lost their first wicket after a positive start. <b>Parthiv Patel c M Pandey b Shakib 21(14) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shakib to Parthiv Patel, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Parthiv Patel, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, Parthiv shimmies down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and goes back over the non-striker's head, a couple of bounces and over the ropes]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Simmons, no run, on a length and on Simmons' pads, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Simmons, no run, the slower bouncer from Morkel, Simmons charges down the track and is beaten by the change of pace as he went for the pull]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Parthiv Patel, 1 run, <b>Umesh nearly pulled off a stunner</b>! This was short and on the stumps, Parthiv swivels across on the pull, gets it to the right of short fine. Umesh moved across, goes one-handed and the ball slipped out after hitting his palms. Could he have gone two-handed?]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Parthiv Patel, 2 runs, too straight from Morkel, ends up drifting onto Parthiv's pads, clipped away behind square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Parthiv Patel, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, Parthiv shimmies down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and drills it up and over cover for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Parthiv Patel, 2 runs, short of a length and on Parthiv's pads, he nudges it in front of mid-wicket, runs hard and gets back for the second run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a lovely shot from Simmons, this was tossed up and just outside off, Simmons gets a big stride forward and drills it past cover, the ball races away to the fence in a jiffy]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Parthiv Patel, 1 run, tossed up and on the stumps, Parthiv gets down on his knees and sweeps it past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Parthiv Patel, no run, poor ball from Shakib, Patel makes room and goes hard on the cut, mistimes it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Parthiv Patel, no run, Shakib drops one short and well outside off, Parthiv makes room and cracks it straight to the fielder at extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Simmons, 1 run, slower and on the stumps, eased towards mid-on for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Simmons, no run, <b>was it a stumping chance?</b> Simmons came down the track on the flick, the ball rolled away off the pads and to the left of the keeper. Uthappa fumbled with the take, Simmons was miles down the track and has enough time before Uthappa can collect the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Simmons, 1 run, short of a length and holding its line outside off, flicked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Parthiv Patel, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, Parthiv hops across and drops it in front of cover-point for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Simmons, 1 run, tad fuller and in that corridor outside off, Simmons makes room and gets a thick inside edge on the drive, the fielder at mid-on gets across and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Simmons, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Simmons goes hard on the drive and mistimes it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Simmons, no run, short of a length and holding its line outside off, Simmons has a lame poke at that and is beaten by a long way]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Parthiv Patel, 1 run, tad fuller and just outside off, Parthiv presents the full face of the bat and pushes it to the left of mid-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Morne Morkel, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Parthiv Patel, 1 run, too straight from Yadav, Parthiv whips it in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Parthiv Patel, <b>FOUR</b>, poor effort from Morne at square third man, back of a length and in that channel outside off, Parthiv plays with an open face and guides it behind square on the off-side. Morne gets across from the deep and drags the ball onto the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Parthiv Patel, no run, Yadav shortens his length outside off, Parthiv gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Simmons, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Simmons gets forward and drives it towards short extra cover. The fielder leaps and gets a hand onto it, keeps the batsmen down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Simmons, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping onto Simmons' pads, he looks to flick and misses, the ball rolls away towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Simmons, no run, short of a length and shaping away from outside off, Simmons covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Simmons and Parthiv Patel are at the crease. Simmons is on strike. U Yadav will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players are out in the middle. It's a huge match for both teams, the pitch looks pretty flat and should be a high scoring encounter.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit:</b> 'Good toss to lose, we wanted to bat first anyway. It's a must-win game, but we will not focus on what happens elsewhere, we would look to focus on our game. One change for us, <b>Vinay Kumar</b> replaces <b>Jasprit Bumrah</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Gambhir:</b> "We would like to bowl first. Looks like a good wicket, we would like to restrict them. We need to play well in this match. Two changes for us. <b>Morne Morkel</b> comes in place of <b>Brad Hogg</b> and <b>Shakib Al Hasan</b> replaces <b>Johan Botha</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mumbai</b> (Playing XI): Parthiv Patel(w), Lendl Simmons, Rohit Sharma(c), Hardik Pandya, Ambati Rayudu, Kieron Pollard, Harbhajan Singh, Jagadeesha Suchith, Vinay Kumar, Mitchell McClenaghan, Lasith Malinga]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kolkata</b> (Playing XI): Robin Uthappa(w), Gautam Gambhir(c), Manish Pandey, Suryakumar Yadav, Yusuf Pathan, Shakib Al Hasan, Andre Russell, Piyush Chawla, Morne Morkel, Umesh Yadav, Sunil Narine]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kolkata have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather Report:</b>  It was another hot and humid morning in Mumbai but the conditions are much more pleasant at the moment. It's the last home match for MUM and they wouldn't like to be knocked out in front of their home fans.]]></line><line><![CDATA[After their trouncing against BLR, Mumbai might well rethink about their team combination. Vinay Kumar was surprisingly left out in the last match and should be back, in place of Jasprit Bumrah.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Team News:</b> Shakib Al Hasan has rejoined KOL and is expected to feature today. He will most likely replace Johan Botha. On a Wankhede track which assists the pacers, KOL might also play Morne Morkel, in place of chinaman bowler, Brad Hogg.]]></line><line><![CDATA[KOL come into the match after their exploits against PUN, registering the first ever one-wicket victory in the history of IPL. Gautam Gambhir's men have reposed confidence in their spinners, playing as many as four of them. The batting has been consistent with the middle-order amongst the runs. Andre Russell has been a revelation and there have been useful contributions down the order. They have 15 points from 12 matches and a win today will take them to number one in the points table.]]></line><line><![CDATA[After a horrendous start to the tournament, Mumbai reeled off five wins in a row before their momentum came to a grinding halt against the Bangalore in their last match at the Wankhede Stadium. It wasn't just the loss, the margin of defeat came as a crushing blow to MUM's hopes. Their bowlers had no clue against the rampaging AB de Villiers and Virat Kohli, allowing BLR to pile up 235/1 in their allotted 20 overs. Barring Lasith Malinga, none of the other bowlers showed any discipline and were left clueless as the two batsmen ran amok. The batting was much better though, with Simmons anchoring the chase and Kieron Pollard opening his shoulders. Someone needed to replicate ABD's knock if MUM were to pull off a miracle. That didn't happen and they were left licking their wounds after a 39-run loss.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:45 Local Time, 13:15 GMT</b> It's do or die for Mumbai. A win and their hopes of qualifying for the playoffs will be alive. On the other hand, a loss and they will join Delhi and Punjab amongst the sidelines. It's an important match for Kolkata as well. A victory will improve their chances of a top two finish. All to play for then. Hello, and a warm welcome to one and all to Match 51 of the 2015 edition of the Indian Premier League.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview</b><br/><br/>It is the final week of IPL 2015 and no team is confirmed in the playoffs. It is safe to say that this edition of the IPL has been the most open tournament ever. After Chennai squandered their opportunity to seal their place, it gives Kolkata a chance to seal their spot in the knock-outs while it gives a potential lifeline to Mumbai.<br/><br/>The scenario is not so simple for Mumbai. They will have to win against both Kolkata and Hyderabad and hope Rajasthan lose their last game. Having lost at a crucial time to Bangalore, Mumbai have an uphill task against a team that is peaking at the right time.<br/><br/>The equation is simple for Kolkata. If they win their next game against Mumbai, they will be through. Should they lose, they will have to defeat Rajasthan in their last league game to secure their passage.<br/><br/>Venue: Wankhede Stadium, Mumbai<br/><br/>Date: May 14, 2015<br/><br/>Time: 20:00 IST<br/><br/>Weather: Low of 31 degrees with 25 percent chances of rain<br/><br/><b>Team news</b><br/><br/><b>Mumbai</b><br/><br/>The team's bowling was taken to the cleaners in their game against Bangalore. The batting came under pressure chasing 236 but the real worry will be the bowling. Jasprit Bumrah, who finished with figures of 4-0-52-0, could be replaced by R Vinay Kumar for this crucial match.<br/><br/>Probable XI<br/><br/>1 Parthiv Patel (wk), 2 Lendl Simmons, 3 Rohit Sharma (c), 4 Kieron Pollard, 5 Ambati Rayudu, 6 Hardik Pandya, 7 Harbhajan Singh, 8 R Vinay Kumar, 9 Jagadeesha Suchith, 10 Mitchell McClenaghan, 11 Lasith Malinga<br/><br/><b>Kolkata</b><br/><br/>Sunil Narine returned to form by finishing with wonderful figures of 4-0-19-4. His form, combined with the depth in the team's bowling, gives them a boost for this game. Considering that the Wankhede wicket might not favour spin, the team could replace Johan Botha with Morne Morkel.<br/><br/>Probable XI<br/><br/>1 Robin Uthappa (wk), 2 Gautam Gambhir, 3 Manish Pandey, 4 Suryakumar Yadav, 5 Yusuf Pathan, 6 Andre Russell, 7 Johan Botha/Morne Morkel, 8 Piyush Chawla, 9 Brad Hogg, 10 Umesh Yadav, 11 Sunil Narine<br/><br/><b>Stats</b><br/><br/>Gautam Gambhir needs three more runs to become the first Kolkata batsman to reach 2000 runs in IPL.<br/>Sunil Narine has the most four-wicket hauls in IPL. He has six four-wicket hauls to go with one five-wicket haul.<br/><br/><b>Quotes</b><br/><br/>"We just got out of jail." - Kolkata skipper Gautam Gambhir admits that Punjab gave them a rude jolt.<br/><br/>"With the table so tight, we need to continue playing well." - Mumbai skipper Rohit Sharma emphasises the need to win consistently.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kolkata</b> (From): Gautam Gambhir(c), Robin Uthappa(w), Manish Pandey, Suryakumar Yadav, Yusuf Pathan, Andre Russell, Johan Botha, Piyush Chawla, Brad Hogg, Umesh Yadav, Sunil Narine, Shakib Al Hasan, Morne Morkel, Pat Cummins, Ryan ten Doeschate, Veer Pratap Singh, Kuldeep Yadav, Azhar Mahmood, Sumit Narwal, Sheldon Jackson, Aditya Garhwal, Kishan Cariappa, Vaibhav Rawal]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mumbai</b> (From): Lendl Simmons, Parthiv Patel(w), Rohit Sharma(c), Hardik Pandya, Ambati Rayudu, Kieron Pollard, Harbhajan Singh, Jagadeesha Suchith, Mitchell McClenaghan, Lasith Malinga, Jasprit Bumrah, Vinay Kumar, Ben Hilfenhaus, Corey Anderson, Unmukt Chand, Siddhesh Lad, Nitish Rana, Akshay Wakhare, Aiden Blizzard, Abhimanyu Mithun, Pragyan Ojha, Shreyas Gopal, Pawan Suyal, Marchant de Lange, Aditya Tare, Colin Munro]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>171</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>4</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Mumbai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>599</playerid>
					<name>Lendl Simmons</name>
					<batsman-name>L Simmons</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Simmons</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>14</runs>
					<balls>16</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Morkel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>608</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Manish Pandey</fielder>
						<fielderId>1836</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>74</playerid>
					<name>Parthiv Patel</name>
					<batsman-name>Parthiv Patel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Parthiv Patel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>21</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Shakib</bowler>
					<bowlerId>544</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Manish Pandey</fielder>
						<fielderId>1836</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>576</playerid>
					<name>Rohit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Rohit</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rohit</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>30</runs>
					<balls>21</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Narine</bowler>
					<bowlerId>2276</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6311</playerid>
					<name>Ambati Rayudu</name>
					<batsman-name>Rayudu</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rayudu</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Shakib</bowler>
					<bowlerId>544</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Andre Russell</fielder>
						<fielderId>7736</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>657</playerid>
					<name>Kieron Pollard</name>
					<batsman-name>K Pollard</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Pollard</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>33</runs>
					<balls>38</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9647</playerid>
					<name>Hardik Pandya</name>
					<batsman-name>H Pandya</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Pandya</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>61</runs>
					<balls>31</balls>
					<fours>8</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>75</playerid>
					<name>Harbhajan Singh</name>
					<batsman-name>Harbhajan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Harbhajan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10357</playerid>
					<name>Jagadeesha Suchith</name>
					<batsman-name>Jagadeesha Suchith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Jagadeesha Suchith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1449</playerid>
					<name>Vinay Kumar</name>
					<batsman-name>Vinay</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Vinay</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7624</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell McClenaghan</name>
					<batsman-name>McClenaghan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>McClenaghan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>111</playerid>
					<name>Lasith Malinga</name>
					<batsman-name>Malinga</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Malinga</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>74</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>29</runs>
				<overs>4.2</overs>
				<batsman>Parthiv Patel</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Parthiv Patel</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>599</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>42</runs>
				<overs>5.4</overs>
				<batsman>Lendl Simmons</batsman>
				<batsman-name>L Simmons</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6311</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>47</runs>
				<overs>6.3</overs>
				<batsman>Ambati Rayudu</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rayudu</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>576</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>79</runs>
				<overs>11.4</overs>
				<batsman>Rohit Sharma</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rohit</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>6</wides>
			<noballs>3</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>10</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Kolkata">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1858</playerid>
					<name>Umesh Yadav</name>
					<bowler-name>Umesh</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>U Yadav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>37</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>608</playerid>
					<name>Morne Morkel</name>
					<bowler-name>M Morkel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M Morkel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>27</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>544</playerid>
					<name>Shakib Al Hasan</name>
					<bowler-name>Shakib</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shakib</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>22</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>466</playerid>
					<name>Piyush Chawla</name>
					<bowler-name>Chawla</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chawla</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>9</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2276</playerid>
					<name>Sunil Narine</name>
					<bowler-name>Narine</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Narine</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>38</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7736</playerid>
					<name>Andre Russell</name>
					<bowler-name>A Russell</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>A Russell</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>37</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>527</playerid>
					<name>Robin Uthappa</name>
					<bowler-name>Uthappa</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Uthappa</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>308</playerid>
					<name>Gautam Gambhir</name>
					<bowler-name>Gambhir</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Gambhir</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1836</playerid>
					<name>Manish Pandey</name>
					<bowler-name>M Pandey</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M Pandey</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7915</playerid>
					<name>Suryakumar Yadav</name>
					<bowler-name>Suryakumar Yadav</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Suryakumar Yadav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>790</playerid>
					<name>Yusuf Pathan</name>
					<bowler-name>Y Pathan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Y Pathan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>166</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>7</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Kolkata">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>527</playerid>
					<name>Robin Uthappa</name>
					<batsman-name>Uthappa</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Uthappa</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>25</runs>
					<balls>20</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Harbhajan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>75</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Lasith Malinga</fielder>
						<fielderId>111</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>308</playerid>
					<name>Gautam Gambhir</name>
					<batsman-name>Gambhir</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Gambhir</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>38</runs>
					<balls>29</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Jagadeesha Suchith</bowler>
					<bowlerId>10357</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1836</playerid>
					<name>Manish Pandey</name>
					<batsman-name>M Pandey</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M Pandey</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Lendl Simmons</fielder>
						<fielderId>599</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>790</playerid>
					<name>Yusuf Pathan</name>
					<batsman-name>Y Pathan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Y Pathan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>52</runs>
					<balls>37</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>K Pollard</bowler>
					<bowlerId>657</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Parthiv Patel</fielder>
						<fielderId>74</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>544</playerid>
					<name>Shakib Al Hasan</name>
					<batsman-name>Shakib</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shakib</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>23</runs>
					<balls>15</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Vinay</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1449</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Hardik Pandya</fielder>
						<fielderId>9647</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7736</playerid>
					<name>Andre Russell</name>
					<batsman-name>A Russell</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>A Russell</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Malinga</bowler>
					<bowlerId>111</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Parthiv Patel</fielder>
						<fielderId>74</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7915</playerid>
					<name>Suryakumar Yadav</name>
					<batsman-name>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>11</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>McClenaghan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7624</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ambati Rayudu</fielder>
						<fielderId>6311</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>466</playerid>
					<name>Piyush Chawla</name>
					<batsman-name>Chawla</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chawla</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1858</playerid>
					<name>Umesh Yadav</name>
					<batsman-name>Umesh</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>U Yadav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>5</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>608</playerid>
					<name>Morne Morkel</name>
					<batsman-name>M Morkel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M Morkel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2276</playerid>
					<name>Sunil Narine</name>
					<batsman-name>Narine</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Narine</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>527</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>45</runs>
				<overs>5.3</overs>
				<batsman>Robin Uthappa</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Uthappa</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1836</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>46</runs>
				<overs>5.5</overs>
				<batsman>Manish Pandey</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Pandey</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>308</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>88</runs>
				<overs>10.6</overs>
				<batsman>Gautam Gambhir</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Gambhir</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>544</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>118</runs>
				<overs>14.2</overs>
				<batsman>Shakib Al Hasan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Shakib</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7736</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>128</runs>
				<overs>15.5</overs>
				<batsman>Andre Russell</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Russell</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7915</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>144</runs>
				<overs>17.1</overs>
				<batsman>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>790</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>160</runs>
				<overs>19.1</overs>
				<batsman>Yusuf Pathan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Y Pathan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>1</byes>
			<wides>7</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>8</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Mumbai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>111</playerid>
					<name>Lasith Malinga</name>
					<bowler-name>Malinga</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Malinga</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>31</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7624</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell McClenaghan</name>
					<bowler-name>McClenaghan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>McClenaghan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>31</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1449</playerid>
					<name>Vinay Kumar</name>
					<bowler-name>Vinay</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Vinay</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>33</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>75</playerid>
					<name>Harbhajan Singh</name>
					<bowler-name>Harbhajan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Harbhajan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>31</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10357</playerid>
					<name>Jagadeesha Suchith</name>
					<bowler-name>Jagadeesha Suchith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Jagadeesha Suchith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>23</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9647</playerid>
					<name>Hardik Pandya</name>
					<bowler-name>H Pandya</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Pandya</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>10</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>657</playerid>
					<name>Kieron Pollard</name>
					<bowler-name>K Pollard</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Pollard</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>6</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>74</playerid>
					<name>Parthiv Patel</name>
					<bowler-name>Parthiv Patel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Parthiv Patel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>599</playerid>
					<name>Lendl Simmons</name>
					<bowler-name>L Simmons</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Simmons</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>576</playerid>
					<name>Rohit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Rohit</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rohit</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6311</playerid>
					<name>Ambati Rayudu</name>
					<bowler-name>Rayudu</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rayudu</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



