<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14599" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>6th Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Delhi</home>
		<away>Rajasthan</away>
		<teamsabbr>DEL vs JAI</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>DEL</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>JAI</awayabbr>
		<homeId>61</homeId>
		<awayId>64</awayId>
		<venue>Feroz Shah Kotla, Delhi</venue>
		<startdate>12 04 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>12 04 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Rajasthan</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Rajasthan won by 3 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Rajasthan</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>3</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Simon Fry</Name>
			<Country>Aus</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Chris Gaffaney</Name>
			<Country>NZ</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Nandan</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Graeme Labrooy</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>10:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150412135456</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>JAI</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>DEL</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>186</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>7</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>20</batteamovers>
		<status>Rajasthan won by 3 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>8333</playerid>
			<name>Chris Morris*</name>
			<batsman-name>C Morris</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>C Morris</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>13</runs>
			<balls-faced>6</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>1</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>1057</playerid>
			<name>Tim Southee</name>
			<batsman-name>Southee</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Southee</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>7</runs>
			<balls-faced>4</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>6667</playerid>
			<name>Imran Tahir*</name>
			<bowler-name>Tahir</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Tahir</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>28</runs>
			<wickets>4</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1629</playerid>
			<name>Angelo Mathews</name>
			<bowler-name>Mathews</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Mathews</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>42</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>185</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>7789</playerid>
<name>James Faulkner</name>
<player-runs>17</player-runs>
<player-balls>11</player-balls>
<runs>173</runs>
<wicket-nbr>7</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>6667</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Tahir</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>5</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>6</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[. 2 1 2 Wd 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 1 4 Wd 2 1 4 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>W 6 . 1 W . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 2 1 4 1 4 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/DEL_JAI_APR12/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[So, that's all we have for you from this game. It's time you switch tabs and follow the second game today as <b>Mumbai are bowling first against Punjab</b>. It should be a cracking encounter. So, don't miss out on the action there.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Deepak Hooda</b>: It's been 2 years and I have improved (when asked about how he was not hitting such huge sixes in the Under-19 World Cup). Rajasthan put up camps before the IPL and they made me play the role of an aggressor during that time, I did the same out there today. Rahane was telling me what to do, he told me to believe. Obviously, I need to develop my off-spin bowling as well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Deepak Hooda spoke in Hindi. We have transcribed his interview for you.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Deepak Hooda</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his match-winning knock of <b>54 from just 25 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Smith:</b> 'It just shows that in this game, you are not getting buried. The way the boys played is magnificent. The way the youngster Hooda played is sensational. Faulkner and Morris also struck a few good ones. It's the thing with Rajasthan, we like to blood young Indians and we will keep doing that. It's good to take 2 wins out of 2 and hopefully, we can take this momentum forward.']]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, it was Mayank Agarwal, who kick-started the innings with a quick-fire knock. Shreyas Iyer, JP Duminy and Angelo Mathews all played their parts to give their bowlers a good score to defend. Pravin Tambe and Hooda seemed to have pulled the batting side back, but just in the nick of time, Mathews lifted Delhi's sagging spirits with a late cameo. In the end though, Delhi lost yet another game and now their losing streak in the IPL extends to 11 matches.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Deepak Hooda essayed a sparkling fifty as Rajasthan registered a thrilling win in the final over. In the last over, Tim Southee and Chris Morris held their nerve to win the game for them. It was Southee, who hit the winning runs with a boundary. In fact, Delhi's spin twins, Mishra and Tahir used the googly to outfox the opposition. But Hooda plundered the opposition bowlers and took the game away from their grasp. Hooda landed some crunching blows over the long on region. He also showed good wrist-work. It has to be said that Delhi's fielding was below par. Yuvraj missed a chance to run out Hooda and Manoj Tiwary also dropped a catch to give the 19-year old a reprieve.]]></line><line><![CDATA[DEL's players can't believe their luck. After that four, they were standing there in disbelief. The dug-out was also looking extremely disappointed. On the other hand, RAJ's dug-out was going crazy. Out of all people, Rahul Dravid was looking so enthusiastic and was extemely happy, he exchanges high-fives with everyone around and hugs them as well. What a win for RAJ! But, take a moment to think about Mathews, who did well throughout the game, only to falter right at the very end. But, it was his third over that opened the floodgates for Rajasthan and gave them a glimmer of hope. You have to appreciate the kind of effort Rajasthan put up, especially the youngster Hooda, who played a match-winning knock today. They were behind the eight-ball, but Hooda's magnificent fifty got them back right into it. So, <b>RAJ now have 2 wins in 2 games</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Southee, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>Southee wins it for Rajasthan!</b> DEL can't believe their luck, their losing streak continues. This is their 11th consecutive loss, <b>equalling Pune record for most number of successive losses</b>. Coming back to the ball, it was full and on off, Southee was expecting that and he drove it magnificently after clearing his front leg, he got it to the right of cover and long-off also had no chance of cutting that off. The ball rolls away to the fence in a flash.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Duminy and Mathews discuss about the field placements. Deep mid-wicket is coming slightly inside the rope. So is deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to C Morris, 1 run, good ball from Mathews, almost a yorker on the stumps, Morris digs it out to extra cover and Morris can only take the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to C Morris, <b>FOUR</b>, Morris gets a four, Mathews wanted to bowl a yorker and misses his length by a fraction, Morris goes down after taking a stride, converts it into a low full toss and just helps it down to the fine leg fence. The fielder at fine leg was inside the circle]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rajasthan need <b>8 from 3 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Southee, 1 run, full delivery on the stumps, Southee drills the drive straight down to long-on, only a single available]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Southee, 2 runs, full delivery angling away outside off, Southee carves it over backward point, he didn't time it that well though, the batsmen take two before the sweeper runs to his left and collects the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to C Morris, 1 run, good ball from Mathews first up. It was right in the blochoke, Morris squeezes it out to point and Yuvi misfields a little, but it will only be a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Angelo Mathews [3.0-0-29-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mathews to bowl the final over of this game. The Rajasthan need 12 to win. 11 runs will take it to the Super Over. Mathews will come from round the wicket now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Southee, no run, quicker one on the stumps, Southee was backing away there and mistimes the drive back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Tim Southee, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Faulkner, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Tahir is running around the park as he has taken the big wicket of Faulkner. His fourth wicket of the innings. It was another googly from Tahir, Faulkner was down on his knees, trying to play the slog sweep. The ball goes under his bat and crashes into the stumps. Tahir has brought the Delhi back into the game. <b>Faulkner b Tahir 17(11) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Tahir to Faulkner, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to C Morris, 1 run, Tahir drags his length back a little, Morris goes for another big shot on the on-side, he mistimes it and the ball bounces well in front of the fielder at long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to C Morris, no run, tossed up just outside off, Morris drills the drive back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to C Morris, <b>SIX</b>, <b>Morris opens his account with a six!</b> It was the googly from Tahir, Morris goes down on one knee, slog sweeps it over the deep square leg fence, brilliant shot first up from the all-rounder]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Morris, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Deepak Hooda, <b>out</b> Caught by Mathews!! Tahir is ecstatic after picking up the big wicket of Hooda. It was a poor ball from Tahir though and he got lucky on this occasion. He goes on his celebratory run as Hooda went after this short and wide delivery, he wanted to dispatch it over the long-on fence, but couldn't quite get it off the middle as he had to reach out for it. In the end, he offers a simple catch to Mathews at long-on, who reverse cups it! <b>Deepak Hooda c Mathews b Tahir 54(25) [4s-3 6s-4]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Tahir to Deepak Hooda, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Imran Tahir [3.0-0-21-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Faulkner, <b>FOUR</b>, slice of luck for Faulkner and he wouldn't mind it. It was the french cut from Faulkner as he backed away and wanted to go on the on-side. He though gets an inside edge on this and the ball runs past to the left of the keeper and crashes in to the fine leg fence, <b>17 runs came off the over</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, Hooda goes across to this fullish delivery angled across off, he just drives it down to long-on to get off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Deepak Hooda, 2 runs, low full toss from the bowler on the pads of Hooda, who flicks it towards deep square leg. The fielder from deep mid-wicket runs to his right, fires in the throw, but the batsmen take two easily in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Deepak Hooda, <b>wide</b>, bowls this one well down the leg-side and Hooda fails to connect with the tickle, called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[Coulter-Nile comes round the wicket. There's a kite on the ground and there's a little delay because of that]]></line><line><![CDATA[Faulkner and Hooda have a chat in the middle. Hooda now goes back to the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Deepak Hooda, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>that's a brilliant fifty from the youngster!</b> This was so well played. It was a back of a length delivery just outside off, Hooda waits for it, opens the face of the bat and runs it down to the third man fence, he knew that the third man was inside the circle and placed it to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Faulkner, 1 run, Faulkner makes room once again and Coulter-Nile follows him with a length ball, Faulkner works it through square leg and takes the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Faulkner, <b>FOUR</b>, Faulkner makes room and wanted to go inside-out over cover, but he gets a thick edge and since third man was inside the circle, the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Nathan Coulter-Nile [3.0-0-25-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Faulkner, 1 run, Faulkner knocks this last delivery from Mishra through the covers and settles for the strike, it was the googly from Mishra]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, Hooda goes for the reverse sweep this time and he connects with this flighted delivery just outside off off the back of his bat, the ball goes over the keeper's head and the batsmen sneak in a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Deepak Hooda, <b>wide</b>, bowled well wide outside off, Hooda went chasing after it, but fails to connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Deepak Hooda, 2 runs, Hooda goes down on one knee and looks to slog sweep it, but the ball takes the toe-end of the bat and goes on the off-side through the covers, the batsmen take two on that count]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Faulkner, 1 run, tossed up around off, Faulkner drives it past the diving bowler and the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Faulkner, 2 runs, this time Faulkner connects with the cut square of the wicket, <b>a direct-hit from the deep and Faulkner would have been out</b>, don't know what was Yuvraj doing trying to collect the throw from the deep, must have put the keeper off as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Faulkner, no run, touch shortish and spinning away just outside off, Faulkner was looking to cut it through the off-side, but fails to connect]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Amit Mishra [3.0-0-24-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Faulkner, 1 run, Faulkner hangs back and steers it towards point for an easy single, it was the leg-spinner from Tahir]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Faulkner, 2 runs, Faulkner clips this delivery on middle and leg through mid-wicket, good running between both of them ensures that they come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, Hooda was down the track once again, but Tahir slips in the quicker one on the pads, he gets an inside edge onto the pad and the ball rolls away to short fine leg, the batsmen sneak in a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Deepak Hooda, <b>SIX</b>, <b>that's absolutely sensational!</b> Hooda just doesn't give enough respect to anyone. It was floated up, Hooda comes down the track and clobbers it over the long-on fence. He is definitely very powerful]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Faulkner, 1 run, drifting on middle and leg, Faulkner works it to deep mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Rahane, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Tahir is on the run as he catches Rahane off guard. Rahane has been bowled here. It's another googly from Tahir and Rahane falls just short of his fifty. He came charging down the track and the ball was spinning in towards him, he missed it and the ball crashes into the leg stump. <b>Rahane b Tahir 47(39) [4s-2 6s-3]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Tahir to Rahane, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Imran Tahir [2.0-0-10-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Unadkat to Deepak Hooda, <b>SIX</b>, <b>Hooda has been dropped!</b> Manoj Tiwary is the culprit at deep mid-wicket. It was another full toss from Unadkat, Hooda swings across the line and Tiwary had it covered, he moves across to his right, takes the catch but parries it over the fence. Unadkat can't believe his luck here and Hooda survives]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Unadkat to Deepak Hooda, <b>SIX</b>, Hooda is playing brilliantly here. Unadkat misses his length and bowls another full toss, Hooda was back and across his stumps, he tonks this over the long-on fence for another maximum, great hit from the youngster]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Unadkat to Rahane, 1 run, that's a good ball from Unadkat, almost a yorker just outside off, Rahane squeezes it out to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Unadkat to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, Hooda gives the charge and has a swipe at a widish full toss, the ball goes on the bounce to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Unadkat to Deepak Hooda, no run, was that a wide? Certainly the umpire doesn't think so. It was another low full toss well wide outside off, Hooda can't connect with it and looks at the umpire, was a little disappointed that it was not called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Unadkat to Rahane, 1 run, comes down the track and has a wild swing at a full toss that was bowled well outside off, Rahane's hand also came off the bat as the ball goes towards long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jaydev Unadkat [2.0-0-15-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to Rahane, 1 run, works this one past square leg and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to Rahane, <b>SIX</b>, Yuvi pays for the mistake last ball! Rahane hangs back to this shortish delivery and pulls it over the cow corner fence with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, ohh dear! <b>Yuvi has missed out on a run-out chance!</b> It was bowled in the channel just outside off, Hooda cuts it to backward point and Rahane was charging towards the other end. Hooda was late to get off the blocks as the fielder fired in a throw right in the hands of Yuvraj, who was standing besides the stumps at the non-striker's end. Yuvraj makes a mess of the take and Hooda makes his ground. The crowd is not happy either]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to Rahane, 1 run, Rahane gives the charge this time and knocks this flatter delivery to deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, bowls this slower and drags his length back as well, Hooda was looking to give the charge and in the end he can only push it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to Rahane, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Rahane leans forward and drives it through the covers for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Starts from round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuvraj Singh, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the batting side to take the <b>strategic timeout</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Deepak Hooda, <b>FOUR</b>, back-to-back boundaries to end the over, it was a length delivery outside off, Hooda hangs back, opens the face of the bat and drives it past a diving backward point, the ball hurries through the lightning outfield, <b>this was the big over the Rajasthan needed as 19 runs came off it</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Deepak Hooda, <b>FOUR</b>, now a boundary to bring the team 100, Hooda walks right across his stumps, Mathews tries to bowl a low full toss on the stumps and Hooda just works it away behind square on the on-side, the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Deepak Hooda, <b>SIX</b>, <b>what a shot!</b> This man definitely packs a punch! Beautifully timed from him. It was fuller and on middle and leg, Hooda just uses his wrists to flick it over wide long-on fence, his first six of the night]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Rahane, 1 run, Mathews bowls this one closer and on the stumps, Rahane drives it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Rahane, <b>wide</b>, is that a harsh call from the umpire? Didn't look outside the tramline as Rahane came charging down the track, it was slightly wide outside off and Rahane couldn't connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, angling in on middle and leg, Hooda chips it in the air, the ball goes on the bounce to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Deepak Hooda, 2 runs, back of a length delivery on the stumps, Hooda stays rooted to the crease and tucks it away behind square on the on-side, comes back for the second before the fielder from fine leg runs to his left and tidies up]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Angelo Mathews [2.0-0-10-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Duminy is holding Tahir back as Mathews comes into the attack]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, floated up outside off, Hooda leans forward and drives it to sweeper cover, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Deepak Hooda, no run, pushed through outside off, Hooda goes across and chops it towards backward point off the bottom edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Deepak Hooda, 2 runs, Hooda comes down the track to this flighted delivery just outside off, he works it through mid-wicket and good running ensures they come back for the second even though the throw from the deep arrives at the non-striker's end]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Rahane, 1 run, googly on the stumps, Rahane stays back, clears his front leg and punches it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, flatter and quicker on the stumps, Hooda mistimes the punch through square leg and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Deepak Hooda, no run, googly from Mishy just outside off, Hooda makes room, opens the face of the bat and picks out backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Deepak Hooda, <b>wide</b>, bowls this down the leg-side, called a wide]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Rahane, no run, bowls it quicker and just outside off, Rahane hangs back and defends it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, tossed up from Tahir, Hooda leans forward and wrists it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Deepak Hooda, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Binny, <b>out</b> Lbw!! ohh dear! Binny is gone! Tahir has outfoxed him and Tahir is jubilant. It was the googly from Tahir, Binny didn't pick it up and missed it completely as he was trying to push at it, he misses and the ball hits him on the pad in line with the middle stump. Doesn't get easier than this for the umpire, who raises his finger in a flash. <b>Binny lbw b Tahir 1(2)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Tahir to Binny, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Rahane, 1 run, bowled quicker and on the stumps, Rahane eases it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Rahane, <b>wide</b>, way outside off stump, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Binny, 1 run, on the stumps, Binny works it away to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Rahane, 1 run, flighted delivery on the stumps, flicked to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Stuart Binny, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Nair, <b>out</b> Stumped!! One shot too many from Nair and he falls. Pretty needless having already got 11 runs off the over. Googly again from Mishy, Nair races down the track and looks to go through the off-side, misses the ball completely. Easy stumping chance for the keeper and he makes no mistake. Mishra is a delighted man and why not. Second wicket for him. <b>Nair st K Jadhav b Mishra 20(12) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mishra to Nair, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Stumped!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Nair, <b>FOUR</b>, googly from Mishra, but Nair has reverse-swept that very fine, Mathews gives chase but the ball beats him to the third man boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Nair, 2 runs, advances and flicks this along the ground to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Nair, no run, plays the reverse sweep but picks out backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Nair, <b>FOUR</b>, down the track, inside-out, good shot. It was in the air for a while, but it was just wide of Tiwary at short extra-cover. Nair didn't try to hit it hard, just drove it nicely from the middle of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Rahane, 1 run, nice and full, Rahane punches it to the right of the bowler and beats Mishra's dive]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b> time. Few words from Duminy in the huddle]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Rahane, leg byes, 1 run, big cryyyy from Tahir but that was pretty optimistic from the bowler. Rahane gets inside the line of this flighted delivery and looks to glance it fine, but misses and gets hit on the pad, the ball was going down the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Rahane, no run, very close to the off stump, defended off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Nair, 1 run, very full from Tahir, Nair flicks it through mid-wicket, Yuvraj fumbles a bit but they don't go for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Nair, no run, leggie from Tahir, Nair taps it towards cover-point and looks for a run, but Rahane sends him back, Duminy fires a throw to the keeper but before the bails were whipped off, Nair made his way back into the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[Run-out check sent upstairs. Nair is the man in question. He's in though!]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Nair, 2 runs, another googly, much straighter this time, Nair flicks it to deep mid-wicket, Unadkat runs to his right from long-on and makes a good diving save]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Nair, 2 runs, starts off with a googly on the leg stump, flicked to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Imran Tahir, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Leg spin from both ends now]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Rahane, 2 runs, goes on the back foot and turns this short ball through mid-wicket, calls for two and makes his ground easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Nair, 1 run, taps this to point and takes off for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Nair, <b>FOUR</b>, nice hit from Nair. Flighted delivery spinning away, Nair gets down on one knee and sweeps it along the ground through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Nair, no run, slider on the leg stump, defended off the front foot into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Karun Nair, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to S Smith, <b>out</b> Caught by M Agarwal!! Googly, not hit well and it's caught at long-on. As always, Smith uses his feet and tries to take the attack to the spinner, he goes for the loft but the bat turns in his hands. No timing on that and long-on had it easy. Big wicket for the Delhi. What a start for Mishra! <b>S Smith c M Agarwal b Mishra 10(9) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mishra to S Smith, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to S Smith, no run, advances and takes it on the full, driven back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Amit Mishra, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for spin]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, 1 run, advances and pushes the short of length delivery towards mid-off, the ball hit the outside half of the bat on that occasion]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, short and outside off stump, Smith makes a bit of room and cuts it to the right of backward point. It was in the air but in the gap]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Rahane, 1 run, short of length delivery on the off stump, Rahane glances it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to S Smith, 1 run, Smith looks to drive, but gets an inside edge that goes through square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Rahane, 1 run, short of length delivery on the stumps, Rahane pulls it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Rahane, no run, good length delivery on the stumps, Rahane tucks it to mid-wicket. The ball again keeps a bit low]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, great way to open the account. Full and in the slot, Smith nails the drive to perfection, it was in the air for a while, but there was no one at extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to S Smith, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Smith mistimes the cut to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to S Smith, no run, this is interesting, Smith is going for it straightaway. Slower ball full and outside off stump, Smith looks to go over mid-on but misses. The ball doesn't bounce much as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to S Smith, no run, on the leg stump, played to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Rahane, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off stump, dabbed to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Rahane, no run, full and outside off stump, Rahane drives and picks out cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Samson, <b>out</b> Caught by Yuvraj!! He's picked the fielder out to perfection. Good length delivery on the leg stump, Samson flicks it nicely, it looked very good for a while but Duminy had a man stationed at deep square leg and it was an easy catch. Yuvraj was initially going back but he realised that it wasn't travelling and made the adjustment to come forward to complete the catch. The bowling change has worked for the Delhi. <b>Samson c Yuvraj b Mathews 11(12) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mathews to Samson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Rahane, 1 run, mistimes the pull shot, it was a shortish ball from Mathews, Rahane gets away with it as it clears the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Rahane, no run, huge appeal for LBW. Short of a length delivery from Mathews, Rahane goes for the pull and misses as it keeps low, again it was too high for the umpire to raise the finger]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Samson, 1 run, on the off stump, worked away through to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Samson, no run, plays across the line to a ball that is well outside off stump and gets beaten. Short of a length delivery outside off stump, Samson looks for mid-wicket but doesn't make contact]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Samson, no run, good length delivery on the stumps, Samson defends it to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Angelo Mathews, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The keeper is up to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[This is just the start the Rajasthan wanted chasing 185. What is Duminy going to do now?]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Samson, 1 run, good length delivery on the leg stump, Samson flicks it to deep mid-wicket and keeps strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Rahane, 1 run, slower delivery outside off stump, Rahane dabs it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, short and wide outside off stump, can't bowl there to this man, Rahane rocks back and cuts fiercely, the fielder at backward point flies to his left as it was in the air but it went well wide of him]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Rahane, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, bit of extra bounce on that, Rahane cuts and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Rahane, <b>SIX</b>, top shot! Good length delivery right in the slot, Rahane hits through the line and lofts it high over wide long-on. He's looking very good today]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Rahane, no run, big shout for LBW but not given. This short ball keeps low, Rahane goes on the back foot to pull, is beaten by the lack of bounce, gets hit in line with off stump but it was too high]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Unadkat to Rahane, 1 run, excellent front foot punch on the move but Duminy dives to his right and saves three at mid-off. Unadkat overpitched the ball on that occasion and got away with it]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Unadkat to Samson, 1 run, on the leg stump, gently worked away to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Unadkat to Rahane, 1 run, Rahane calls for two after clipping this short of length delivery through backward square leg but the fielder quickly got to the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Unadkat to Rahane, no run, could be a run-out, but Shreyas Iyer misses. Anyway, Rahane would have been in as he dived full length to make his ground. Rahane tapped this towards cover-point and set off, but Samson sent him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Unadkat to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, classy drive from Rahane. Full and in the slot, Rahane leans forward, waits for the ball to come and crashes it between mid-off and extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Unadkat to Rahane, <b>SIX</b>, that's a top shot from Rahane. Not sure why Unadkat opted to take pace off the ball. Rahane was struggling with the left-armer's angle across him. Rahane steps out and pulls handsomely over deep square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Samson, no run, good length delivery outside off stump, pushed into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Samson, 2 runs, it's a leading edge but it's safe again. Good length delivery just outside off stump, Samson looks to play more towards mid-on, gets a leading edge and it flies over cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Samson, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Samson cuts and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Samson, 2 runs, chipped awkwardly and I tell you what, had mid-on been on the edge of the circle, it would have been an easy catch. Shortish from Coulter-Nile, Samson hops and lifts awkwardly, luckily for him the fielder was well inside the ring. Samson was surprised by the pace and bounce on that one]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Samson, no run, good length delivery on the stumps, Samson defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Samson, <b>FOUR</b>, poor start from both the bowler and the fielder. Short of a length delivery down the leg-side, Samson glances it nicely to fine leg, Tahir runs to his right from fine leg but overruns the ball and it goes for four. That should have been just one]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Nathan Coulter-Nile, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Unadkat to Rahane, 2 runs, the change of pace from Unadkat. Slower delivery on the stumps, Rahane glances it away to fine and opens his account with a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Unadkat to Rahane, no run, short of length and very close to the off stump, Rahane defends with soft hands to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Unadkat to Rahane, no run, this time he leans forward and drives the length ball to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Unadkat to Rahane, no run, appeal for caught behind, the keeper and the fielder at slip were very confident, but Unadkat wasn't fully sure. Again the angle away from the right-hander is troubling Rahane. He feels for the ball, this short of length delivery just leaves him and beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Unadkat to Rahane, no run, goes for a loose drive and gets beaten. Back of a length ball angling away from the right-hander, Rahane plays away from the body and gets beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Unadkat to Rahane, no run, short of length delivery just swinging back in, Rahane watchfully defends it towards point, looks for a run but decides against it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rahane and Samson are at the crease. Rahane is on strike. Unadkat will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back... The pitch is good to bat on, but the Rajasthan need to manage their run chase well. Meanwhile, wickets at regular intervals will be the key for the Delhi.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shreyas Iyer:</b> "I think it is a good score to defend. I knew I was going to cover up later on and it was a good stand with Agarwal. We are going to bank on our two spinners Imran Tahir and Amit Mishra."]]></line><line><![CDATA[However, Rajasthan's spinners, Pravin Tambe and Deepak Hooda, with subtle variations of flight and drift were able to stem the run flow to some extent.  In fact, it was Tambe, who deceived Mayank in the flight to take his wicket. For a while, even the likes of Duminy and Yuvraj Singh had to prod and push for quick singles. Eventually, Yuvraj upped the scoring rate by taking a heavy toll off James Faulkner. Yuvraj, with his majestic swing of the bat, played a couple of thunderous strokes down the ground. Once Yuvraj was dismissed, Angelo Mathews and Duminy landed mighty blows to bring the packed house to its feet. It was definitely a domineering innings from Mathews.  Rajasthan would rue the fact that Ajinkya Rahane dropped Mathews. On a flat pitch coupled with a lightning fast outfield, Rajasthan still can chase down this target. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shreyas Iyer, JP Duminy and Angelo Mathews checked in a series of fine shots as Delhi ended up with a good total. Iyer played some crunching lofted strokes. The highlight of his innings was the way he got inside the line of the ball to play a pull shot over fine leg off Chris Morris for a six. Iyer's opening partner, Mayank Agarwal, also played his part with a breezy innings. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Duminy, <b>SIX</b>, Duminy finishes it off in style. Morris misses the yorker, offers a full toss, leathered into the stands. Duminy made room and carted it into the crowd. Two bad balls in the over and Morris gives away <b>17</b> off the final over]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Mathews, 1 run, that is a magnificent yorker. On middle. Mathews had no room to work with, just about dug that out. Top, top bowling]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Duminy, leg byes, 1 run, tries to repeat the stroke, but can't connect. Hit outside leg on the pad. Again Morris missed the yorker and got lucky with a length ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Duminy, <b>SIX</b>, Morris misses his yorker, it was a slower delivery, Duminy heaves it over mid-wicket, just about clears the man in the deep. Duminy cleared his front leg and swung well]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Duminy, 2 runs, yorker length on the stumps, clipped wide of Smith at wide long-on, they take a quick two]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Mathews, 1 run, very full on the stumps, jammed out to long-on, just a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Morris [3.0-0-19-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Mathews, 1 run, Mathews skips out but can't get under that yorker length, dug out to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Duminy, 1 run, low full toss, dragged to square leg, quick single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Mathews, 1 run, very full outside off, driven to extra cover, who is at the edge of the circle]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Mathews, <b>FOUR</b>, a slower delivery from Southee, but down leg, Mathews clips it very fine and beats fine leg who had a bit of ground to cover. Poor bowling from Southee, but Mathews is turning it on at the Kotla]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Duminy, 1 run, full outside off, drilled hard, but Smith at mid-off goes to his left to field]]></line><line><![CDATA[Faulkner was Man of the Match last match. Today he has got his most expensive figures in the IPL. Cricket - what a game!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Mathews, 1 run, from round the wicket and down leg, clipped away fine, but fine leg is there, so just a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tim Southee [3.0-0-27-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, 1 run, short on the stumps, pulled hard, but straight to the fielder at deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, <b>SIX</b>, Mathews is going now. Duminy punches gloves with Mathews. Another length ball and swung away over mid-wicket. Connected cleanly and the fielder at the fence was just a mere spectator]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, <b>FOUR</b>, now Mathews gets a four. Waits for the slower delivery, shuffles across a little and then clips it behind square, beats short fine inside the ring. Jinks wears a sad expression on his face]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, 2 runs, <b>dropped by Jinks at long-on.</b> Brutalised by Mathews, but straight at Jinks who drops it despite getting both hands to it. Tried to take it on the rebound, failed to do so. They take two too]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, no run, pushes it further wide of off, Mathews went for another big hit over cover, but failed to make contact. That was bowled much quicker]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Mathews, <b>FOUR</b>, now Mathews smashes Faulkner. Length delivery outside off, blasted over the head of Faulkner]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Mathews, 1 run, full outside off, driven hard and wide of long-off, retains the strike with that run]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Mathews, <b>wide</b>, short and down leg, Mathews can't connect on the pull]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Mathews, no run, full and clipped straight to the fielder at mid-wicket. There is a fumble from Faulkner, but they don't take the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Replays show that Nair just about hung on]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Duminy, 1 run, low full toss on the stumps, clipped wide of long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Angelo Mathews, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Yuvraj, <b>out</b> Caught by Nair!! Yuvraj is gone. The crowd are disappointed. Short from Morris, top-edged pull and Nair running in from fine leg, slides and completes an excellent catch. Kept his eyes on the ball all the way and took it well. <b>Yuvraj c Nair b C Morris 27(17) [6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[C Morris to Yuvraj, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Duminy, 1 run, the call was for two but they take just a single straight down the ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Yuvraj, 1 run, full and outside off, lofted but no real timing as the weight was back, down to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Morris [2.0-0-14-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Yuvraj, 1 run, wanted to repeat the stroke, but it was a pacy back of a length delivery on the stumps, Yuvraj defends to long-on and takes the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Yuvraj, <b>SIX</b>, Yuvraj picks the back of the hand slower delivery and goes over long-on. Waits for it and stays deep in his crease, lofted high into the crowd. The crowd have suddenly come to life at the Kotla]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Duminy, 1 run, back of the hand slower delivery outside off, cut to point, quick single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[Duminy applauded that six hit by Yuvraj. He liked it]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Yuvraj, 1 run, back of the hand slower delivery, punched to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Yuvraj, 2 runs, short now and pulled to deep backward square leg, for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Yuvraj, <b>SIX</b>, that is Yuvraj at his very best. Length delivery on the stumps, Yuvraj stands and delivers. Clean swing of the bat and it goes all the way, bounces in front of the sightscreen]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner [2.0-0-21-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Yuvraj, 1 run, superb yorker on off, dug out to cover and a quick single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third man up, mid-wicket back]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Duminy, 1 run, short of length outside off, cutter, dabbed down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Duminy, no run, Duminy shuffles across outside off and then eyes mid-wicket, but he can't connect on the swipe to a wide length ball outside off]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Yuvraj, 1 run, low full toss on the pads, clipped to deep square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Yuvraj, 2 runs, now Karun Nair saves two with a dive at long-on. Low full toss, pushed past mid-off, but Nair running across was good enough]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Duminy, 1 run, Duminy comes down the track and tries to smash that through the off-side, but gets an inside edge onto the pads, the ball rolls towards the keeper, they take a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tim Southee [2.0-0-21-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Yuvraj, no run, Yuvraj punches that towards long-off, cover comes across to field]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Duminy, 1 run, Duminy goes on the back foot and works that through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Duminy, <b>wide</b>, fired way outside off, wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Yuvraj, 1 run, Yuvraj is on the walk and works it through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Yuvraj, 2 runs, what fielding from Morris at long-off. It was a full toss that was smashed by Yuvraj, was heading for the boundary, but Morris dived full length and pushed it back, saved two]]></line><line><![CDATA[Yuvraj is sorting his gear out. Slight delay]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Duminy, 1 run, shortish on the stumps, whipped off the back foot to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Yuvraj, 1 run, floated up outside off, Yuvraj gets forward and drives to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Duminy, no run, back of the hand slower delivery outside off, Duminy wants to cut that late, but misses out]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Duminy, no run, yorker on off, dug out to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Duminy, <b>SIX</b>, he plays that shot really well. It was slightly short on the stumps, Duminy gets inside the line and pulls, manages to send it over the ropes at fine leg. Delhi needed that for the runs weren't coming in the last over or so]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Duminy, 2 runs, short outside off, cut in the air, but wide of the diving point, to the left of the man, for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Duminy, no run, back of a length outside off, pushed to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Duminy, no run, Duminy is a disappointed man after he is early into the clip and misses a length ball on the hips]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner [1.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Yuvraj, no run, very full outside off, carved straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Duminy, 1 run, goes for a big drive, gets an inside edge onto the boot, the ball rolls away after that into the covers, easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Duminy, no run, pushed back to Deepak Hooda]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Duminy, <b>wide</b>, what was that? Fired way outside off and Samson did well to grab the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Yuvraj, 1 run, defended to cover, and off goes Yuvraj]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Duminy, leg byes, 1 run, down leg, Duminy misses the clip but takes a leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Yuvraj, 1 run, driven with a closed bat face to long-off, Yuvraj is off the mark]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Deepak Hooda [2.0-0-9-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuvraj Singh, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Shreyas Iyer, <b>out</b> Caught by Southee!! The slower delivery does it for Morris. Shreyas Iyer got it right off the toe end as he went for the lofted hit, it lobs high and Southee settles under that skier at mid-off. Takes it with fingers pointing up. <b>Shreyas Iyer c Southee b C Morris 40(30) [4s-3 6s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[C Morris to Shreyas Iyer, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Shreyas Iyer, <b>wide</b>, way down leg, Morris missed his radar totally]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Duminy, 1 run, length delivery outside off, square driven hard, but straight to the fielder at sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, another slower delivery, whipped to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Shreyas Iyer, no run, that is a wild slog. Slower ball from Morris, Shreyas Iyer makes room and swings, is beaten. The ball goes on the bounce to Samson]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Shreyas Iyer, no run, that is a quick bouncer from C Morris, whizzes past the head of Shreyas Iyer who was looking for an encore, the ball was too quick for him]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Shreyas Iyer, <b>SIX</b>, now pulls and gets six. It was short down leg, Shreyas Iyer helped it on its way over fine leg. Cleared the fence with ease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Morris [1.0-0-5-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, a mistimed shot from Shreyas Iyer as he went for another biggie, down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Duminy, 1 run, full on the stumps, clipped to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Duminy, no run, well bowled. Slowed it down, the googly, draws Duminy into the push and is beaten, the ball turned away past the edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, shortish on the stumps, Shreyas Iyer shuffles across and whips it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, smashed! Too full from Tambe, Shreyas Iyer drills that flat past the stumps and gives the boundary riders no chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Shreyas Iyer, <b>SIX</b>, that is a massive hit. Got under that ball and then slog-swept it way back into the stands at long-on. It was a 95-metre hit]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pravin Tambe [2.0-0-5-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, another slower delivery, back of the hand again, punched wide of the diving Faulkner, single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Shreyas Iyer, <b>wide</b>, back of the hand slower delivery, down leg, called wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Shreyas Iyer, <b>SIX</b>, now Shreyas Iyer is going. Makes room slightly and goes over mid-off. Hit well to go all the way. Faulkner bowled a length ball and Shreyas Iyer got under that well]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Shreyas Iyer, no run, short of length on the stumps, Shreyas Iyer defends to the left of backward point, no chance of a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, half-volley on the pads, flicked wide of mid-wicket and that will be a boundary for Shreyas Iyer. Once he hit the gap it was enough]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Duminy, 1 run, just in front of Tambe running forward from sweeper cover. Duminy used his feet and carved it high over cover, Tambe was a bit slow to react and the ball doesn't reach him by the time he gets there]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Duminy, no run, short of length on the stumps, Duminy defends solidly]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Shreyas Iyer, no run, confusion but Shreyas Iyer is back home, it was driven to point, Shreyas Iyer was sent back by Duminy and he made it, beating the throw which was wide to Samson]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Shreyas Iyer, <b>wide</b>, fired down leg, Samson does well to get his body behind it]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Shreyas Iyer, no run, short and wide outside off, was there for the cut, but Shreyas Iyer finds point. Missed out there]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Shreyas Iyer, no run, flatter on the stumps, nudged to short fine, Duminy sends Shreyas Iyer back]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Duminy, 1 run, punched to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Duminy, 2 runs, darted down as he sees Duminy using his feet, Duminy works it to deep square leg, placed in the gap and they come back for a quick two]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Duminy, no run, shortish outside off, Duminy cuts late and finds point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Shreyas Iyer, no run, very full and it's driven straight back to Tambe. Just the 3 singles off the over. Another top over from Tambe]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Shreyas Iyer, no run, makes room and drills it but finds short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Duminy, 1 run, very full outside off, squeezed out to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, leans forward and clips it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Shreyas Iyer, no run, was that down leg? The umpire suggests the same. Shreyas Iyer is on the walk and he misses the flick to a very full ball, going down with the angle]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Duminy, 1 run, Duminy kneels down and pre-meditates a paddle down to fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Duminy, 1 run, sliding onto middle and leg, Duminy gets an inside edge onto the pads, the ball rolls to square leg, single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, low full toss on the pads, flicked to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Shreyas Iyer, no run, shortish, was there to be hit, but Shreyas Iyer finds mid-off with a flat-batted shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Duminy, 1 run, very full, driven hard to wide long-off, Morris fields and prevents the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, from round the wicket, on the pads, flicked to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[Replays show that Tambe bowled that wicket taking delivery from well behind the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Duminy, 1 run, driven hard and straight to Binny at cover, who fumbles and gives away the single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Deepak Hooda, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Duminy, 1 run, on the pads, flicked to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Duminy, no run, pushed off the front foot to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jean-Paul Duminy, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to M Agarwal, <b>out</b> Caught&Bowled!! Agarwal gives it away. Credit to Tambe for drawing the false stroke too. Agarwal made room to go big, but the ball wasn't there for the lofted shot, he goes through with the hit and can only tamely lob it back to Tambe. Another promising innings nipped in the bud. That's Agarwal's IPL career in short. So much promise, so little results to show for. <b>M Agarwal c and b Tambe 37(21) [4s-6 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Tambe to M Agarwal, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught&Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to M Agarwal, no run, a front foot punch from Agarwal, timed well, but straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, very full on the stumps, Iyer gets forward and drives to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Shreyas Iyer, no run, shortish, but keeps a bit low, skidded on too, Iyer cuts and misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pravin Tambe, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to M Agarwal, <b>FOUR</b>, finesse! It was close to his off stump, but he opened the face at the very last moment and then let it run off the bat face, beats Tambe to his left, the ball scooted away to the fence. 18 off the over and Agarwal has got off to a flier]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to M Agarwal, 2 runs, good length outside off, Agarwal opens the face of the bat and steers it to square third man, Tambe this time runs around and cuts it off. Just a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to M Agarwal, <b>FOUR</b>, that's the best shot of the lot. Pure timing, back of a length outside off, Agarwal opens the face of the bat and just dabs that past point, beats Tambe from third man who had no chance. The timing was top notch and that's why it kept running away from Tambe]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to M Agarwal, <b>FOUR</b>, short fine is in and Agarwal uses that to glance it wide of him, poor delivery as it was down leg, Agarwal needed to get bat on that and he just did that]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to M Agarwal, <b>FOUR</b>, that is a flat-batted mistimed bunt straight down the ground. Hit high on the bat but well over Kulkarni and then it races away. Kulkarni didn't even put his hand up to try and catch it]]></line><line><![CDATA[Just a slip in. Square leg back]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to M Agarwal, no run, gentle outswinger from Kulkarni first up, Agarwal had a look and let it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhawal Kulkarni, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to M Agarwal, 1 run, back of a length outside off, Agarwal dabs that down to third man, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, Southee digs it in short, Shreyas Iyer rocks back and plays a controlled pull to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, magnificent shot. A bit of Jinks in that drive from Shreyas Iyer. Hit on the rise and all timing as the ball is threaded through cover. Elegantly done by the young man]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to M Agarwal, 1 run, short of length on the stumps, Agarwal stays beside the line and dabs it down to third man, played it from the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to M Agarwal, no run, tight length delivery on the stumps, Agarwal defends it back to Southee]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to M Agarwal, <b>SIX</b>, he has connected that well. Even though the bat face closed, the timing on that meant that it carried all the way over wide long-off. Very full from Southee and Agarwal skewed the loft, but got six]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Shreyas Iyer, no run, that perhaps kept a bit low, Shreyas Iyer was trying to cut that away, but the ball went under his bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Shreyas Iyer, no run, short of length outside off, Shreyas Iyer lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to M Agarwal, 1 run, one hand comes off the bat as he tries to drive and the thick outside edge runs away to third man, went through the vacant gully region]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to M Agarwal, no run, this is a strange innings from Agarwal. After a good shot he is beaten again. Next ball we may see a boundary. That's how his innings has panned out so far. This time he is late in getting forward and then pushes out at the length delivery outside off, is beaten neck and crop]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now square leg goes back. Still two slips in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to M Agarwal, <b>FOUR</b>, too straight, in fact on middle and leg, Agarwal clips that wide of square leg and the fast outfield does the rest]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to M Agarwal, no run, swing for Morris too. Pitches it on a good length after angling it in, it hits the seam and then seams away past the iffy forward push of Agarwal]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Morris, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to M Agarwal, 1 run, lovely outswinger, lures Agarwal into the drive, a thick outside edge but again through that vacant gully region for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to M Agarwal, <b>FOUR</b>, that is a good stroke. Dug in short, probably Agarwal was waiting for it I guess, is quick to rock back and pulls over mid-wicket. The short ball didn't rise high enough to trouble the batsman]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to M Agarwal, no run, poor shot. This was a good length delivery outside off, swinging away, Agarwal went for a big drive on-the-up and missed. The feet didn't get to the ball and he just used his hands, which didn't work]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to M Agarwal, no run, Jinks at point saves four! That is a super stop. Square driven off the front foot and Jinks dives to his right and stops it cleanly with both hands, gets a pat from Binny for that effort]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, on middle, Shreyas Iyer shuffles across slightly and clips it to the right of mid-on for a comfortable single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Shreyas Iyer, <b>wide</b>, slides down leg, Shreyas Iyer can't meet with the glance]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to M Agarwal, 1 run, swing straightaway for Southee, Agarwal gets lucky as he closes the face of the bat to a middle stump swinging delivery and gets a leading edge, in the air, but no gully and it runs away through that region for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>M Agarwal and Shreyas Iyer are at the crease. M Agarwal is on strike. Southee will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Will be interesting to see whether Southee can get some swing. Here we go...]]></line><line><![CDATA[No news on why Watson isn't available. Even Smith didn't say anything at the toss or to put it this way he wasn't asked why Watson wasn't playing. The umpires walk out to the middle. The Rajasthan stroll forward too. Out come the Delhi openers. Tim Southee is marking his run. Iyer and Agarwal are the openers]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Delhi</b> (Playing XI): Mayank Agarwal, Shreyas Iyer, Jean-Paul Duminy(c), Yuvraj Singh, Manoj Tiwary, Angelo Mathews, Kedar Jadhav(w), Nathan Coulter-Nile, Amit Mishra, Imran Tahir, Jaydev Unadkat]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajasthan</b> (Playing XI): Ajinkya Rahane, Sanju Samson(w), Steven Smith(c), Karun Nair, Deepak Hooda, Stuart Binny, James Faulkner, Chris Morris, Tim Southee, Dhawal Kulkarni, Pravin Tambe]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajasthan have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[No Watson, it is <b>Smith:</b> "It was a good start for us, but it is another day and we will look to continue on. <b>We are going to have a bowl.</b> Looks a good wicket, we batted first last game, something different this time and we will see how we go. Same side from last game"]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Duminy:</b> "It's a game of small margins. We will take a lot out of it. Our bowling performance in the last game especially in the back half of the innings was pretty good. We have got a point to prove at our home venue and hopefully we can start off well today. We will keep building on our team culture which has been important to us and the results will come. It is probably what we would've done anyway, so pretty happy. There is <b>three changes</b> - Gautam, Morkel and Joseph are out. Mathews in for Morkel, Unadkat and Manoj Tiwary are in too"]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Toss time!</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Is Shane Watson fit? That is big question at the moment. If he returns, it is most likely that Chris Morris will sit out. If Watson returns, the Rajasthan will look even stronger as he adds a great value with the bat. Are Delhi thinking of bringing in Angelo Mathews, Quinton de Kock? We'll get the answers very shortly. The toss isn't too far away, stay tuned...]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather</b>: The temperature is expected to hover around 23-24 degrees, which is pleasant for cricket. However, the humidity is in the mid 80s, which means that it could drain the players a bit. They would want to make sure that they take enough fluids. It's a bit cloudy for now, but let's hope that rain doesn't disrupt proceedings.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Tim Southee was outstanding in the World Cup and on a surface that had a bit of grass, he didn't disappoint with the new ball. In fact, he removed Virender Sehwag first ball with a lovely outswinger. Dhawal Kulkarni hit the right lengths and kept things quiet, while James Faulkner, after a good time with the bat, mixed it up nicely to pick three wickets and ruin PUN's run chase.]]></line><line><![CDATA[On the other hand, Rajasthan are fresh from a fantastic win against a strong Punjab side in their first game. The Rajasthan always have the knack of unearthing excellent domestic talent and we saw Deepak Hooda grab eyeballs with his aggressive style of play. Stand-in-skipper Steve Smith continued his good form from the World Cup, but it was Finisher Faulkner, who provided the much needed impetus lower down the order to give the Rajasthan a competitive total. However, they would want Ajinkya Rahane, Sanju Samson, Karun Nair and Stuart Binny to bat more responsibly.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Yuvraj Singh too was held back and the move did not work for the Delhi as both Yuvraj and Duminy failed to bail the side out of trouble. Although Albie Morkel took a lot of time to get going, he got the boundaries towards the end and almost took DEL past the line. The youngsters at the top of the order though need to shoulder more responsibility and give some stability to the side. In the bowling department, Domnic Joseph impressed everyone on IPL debut with his accurate bowling, while Amit Mishra bowled good variations to bowl an economic spell. Australian pacer Nathan Coulter-Nile's performance will be key to DEL if they are to do well with the ball.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>14:45 Local Time, 09:15 GMT, 14:45 IST:</b> We move to the national capital today for Match 6 of the 2015 Indian Premier League. It's Delhi hosting Rajasthan at the Feroz Shah Kotla. After revamping their side in the auctions, the Delhi hoped to get off to a good start, but lost their season opener to the Chennai. However, they put up a much improved show as they ran CHN very close, only to lose the thriller by 1 run. Last year we debated about JP Duminy batting too low down the order. If you thought the issue would be settled with himself being the captain for this season, it wasn't to be as he came at No. 7 in the first game when the asking rate was very high.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview</b><br/>Delhi return to their home ground when they take on Rajasthan in Match 6 of IPL 2015 on Sunday. They haven't won a match here in their last seven matches and their last victory at Kotla was against the Mumbai in April 2013.<br/><br/>Delhi' plans of resurrecting their torrid IPL record went pear-shaped against Chennai. The side looked a bit different as compared to what they've in the past couple of seasons. The way they managed their batting-order surprised a few.<br/><br/>One of the few sides not to have undergone much transformation, RAJ's performance against Punjab was impressive. On a pitch that seemed two-paced, their batsmen recovered from early jitters and posted a competitive total. IPL debutant Deepak Hooda (30) and Faulkner (46) got together for a quick-fire 51-run stand to give the RAJ innings some momentum, and the Australia allrounder backed it with a fantastic spell to ensure his team got off to a winning start.<br/><br/>Keeping all that in mind, RAJ certainly have the advantage, but DEL will take a lot of confidence from their CHN game the other day and will not be easy to get away with.<br/><br/>Venue: Feroz Shah Kotla, New Delhi<br/><br/>Date: April 12<br/><br/>Time: 16:00 IST<br/><br/>Weather: Bright and sunny with a maximum of 33 degrees Celsius<br/><br/><b>Delhi</b><br/><br/>Still early in the season, DEL would like to stick to the side they played against CHN. Albie Morkel's bowling would have benched him, but he later made amends with the bat and will surely take the field against RAJ. That being said, the batting-line up may be altered with the management likely to send Yuvraj Singh and JP Duminy a bit up the order. Despite looking a little patchy, Yuvraj will be itching to have a go and giving him more deliveries will help DEL's case.<br/><br/>Probable XI: 1 Mayank Aggarwal, 2 CM Gautam (wk), 3 JP Duminy (capt), 4 Yuvraj Singh, 5 Kedar Jadhav, 6 Shreyas Iyer, 7 Albie Morkel, 8 Nathan Coulter-Nile, 9 Imran Tahir, 10 Amit Mishra, 11 Domnic Muthuswami<br/><br/><b>Rajasthan</b><br/><br/>Shane Watson is the only possible candidate for a change in the RAJ line-up. The Australia allrounder missed the opening match due to a bruised hip. If he recovers in time, Chris Morris, who played against PUN, will have to sit out.<br/><br/>Probable XI: 1 Karun Nair, 2 Ajinkya Rahane, 3 Steven Smith, 4 Sanju Samson, 5 Stuart Binny, 6 Deepak Hooda, 7 James Faulkner, 8 Shane Watson/Chris Morris, 9 Tim Southee, 10 Dhawal Kulkarni, 11 Pravin Tambe<br/><br/><b>Quotes:</b><br/><br/>It's a game of small margins, but I am proud of the boys. We will take a lot of learning out of this game. We didn't have big partnerships but still got close. One or two balls more and we would have won it: JP Duminy after his side's one-run loss to CHN.<br/><br/>Every time I bat in a T20 game, I try and contribute to the best of my ability. Playing as an allrounder there is always a chance of having a bad day, with both bat and ball, but I've worked hard on my game and hopefully I'll be able to keep this going for the rest of the tournament: James Faulkner on his match-winning knock against PUN.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajasthan</b> (From): Ajinkya Rahane, Sanju Samson(w), Shane Watson(c), Steven Smith, Karun Nair, Deepak Hooda, James Faulkner, Stuart Binny, Tim Southee, Dhawal Kulkarni, Pravin Tambe, Abhishek Nayar, Chris Morris, Rajat Bhatia, Ben Cutting, Dishant Yagnik, Vikramjeet Malik, Ankit Sharma, Rahul Tewatia, Dinesh Salunkhe, RustyTheron, Pardeep Sahu, Brainder Sran, Sagar Trivedi]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Delhi</b> (From): Mayank Agarwal, Chidhambaram Gautam(w), Shreyas Iyer, Yuvraj Singh, Jean-Paul Duminy(c), Kedar Jadhav, Albie Morkel, Nathan Coulter-Nile, Imran Tahir, Mohammed Shami, Amit Mishra, Quinton de Kock, Manoj Tiwary, Shahbaz Nadeem, Saurabh Tiwary, Jayant Yadav, Angelo Mathews, Jaydev Unadkat, Gurinder Sandhu, Travis Head, Srikar Bharat, Marcus Stoinis, Zaheer Khan, Domnic Joseph, KK Jiyas]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>184</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>3</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Delhi">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>2195</playerid>
					<name>Mayank Agarwal</name>
					<batsman-name>M Agarwal</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M Agarwal</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>37</runs>
					<balls>21</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Tambe</bowler>
					<bowlerId>9237</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Tambe</fielder>
						<fielderId>9237</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9428</playerid>
					<name>Shreyas Iyer</name>
					<batsman-name>S Iyer</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shreyas Iyer</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>40</runs>
					<balls>30</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>C Morris</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8333</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Tim Southee</fielder>
						<fielderId>1057</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>211</playerid>
					<name>Jean-Paul Duminy</name>
					<batsman-name>Duminy</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Duminy</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>44</runs>
					<balls>38</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>69</playerid>
					<name>Yuvraj Singh</name>
					<batsman-name>Yuvraj</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Yuvraj</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>27</runs>
					<balls>17</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>C Morris</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8333</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Karun Nair</fielder>
						<fielderId>8257</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1629</playerid>
					<name>Angelo Mathews</name>
					<batsman-name>Mathews</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mathews</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>27</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>694</playerid>
					<name>Manoj Tiwary</name>
					<batsman-name>M Tiwary</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M Tiwary</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1851</playerid>
					<name>Kedar Jadhav</name>
					<batsman-name>K Jadhav</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>K Jadhav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7774</playerid>
					<name>Nathan Coulter-Nile</name>
					<batsman-name>Coulter-Nile</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Coulter-Nile</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1454</playerid>
					<name>Amit Mishra</name>
					<batsman-name>A Mishra</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mishra</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6667</playerid>
					<name>Imran Tahir</name>
					<batsman-name>Tahir</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Tahir</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6327</playerid>
					<name>Jaydev Unadkat</name>
					<batsman-name>Unadkat</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Unadkat</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>2195</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>45</runs>
				<overs>4.4</overs>
				<batsman>Mayank Agarwal</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Agarwal</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9428</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>93</runs>
				<overs>10.6</overs>
				<batsman>Shreyas Iyer</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Iyer</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>69</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>138</runs>
				<overs>16.3</overs>
				<batsman>Yuvraj Singh</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Yuvraj</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>7</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>9</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Rajasthan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1057</playerid>
					<name>Tim Southee</name>
					<bowler-name>Southee</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Southee</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8333</playerid>
					<name>Chris Morris</name>
					<bowler-name>C Morris</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>C Morris</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1451</playerid>
					<name>Dhawal Kulkarni</name>
					<bowler-name>D Kulkarni</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>D Kulkarni</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>18</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9237</playerid>
					<name>Pravin Tambe</name>
					<bowler-name>Tambe</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Tambe</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>18</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9427</playerid>
					<name>Deepak Hooda</name>
					<bowler-name>Deepak Hooda</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Deepak Hooda</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>20</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7789</playerid>
					<name>James Faulkner</name>
					<bowler-name>Faulkner</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Faulkner</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>55</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1447</playerid>
					<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
					<bowler-name>A Rahane</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rahane</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8271</playerid>
					<name>Sanju Samson</name>
					<bowler-name>Samson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Samson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2250</playerid>
					<name>Steven Smith</name>
					<bowler-name>S Smith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Smith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8257</playerid>
					<name>Karun Nair</name>
					<bowler-name>Nair</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nair</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1530</playerid>
					<name>Stuart Binny</name>
					<bowler-name>Binny</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Binny</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>186</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>7</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Rajasthan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1447</playerid>
					<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
					<batsman-name>A Rahane</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rahane</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>47</runs>
					<balls>39</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Tahir</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6667</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8271</playerid>
					<name>Sanju Samson</name>
					<batsman-name>Samson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Samson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>11</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mathews</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1629</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Yuvraj Singh</fielder>
						<fielderId>69</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2250</playerid>
					<name>Steven Smith</name>
					<batsman-name>S Smith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Smith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>10</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>A Mishra</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1454</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mayank Agarwal</fielder>
						<fielderId>2195</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8257</playerid>
					<name>Karun Nair</name>
					<batsman-name>Nair</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nair</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>20</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[stumped]]></status>
					<bowler>A Mishra</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1454</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Kedar Jadhav</fielder>
						<fielderId>1851</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1530</playerid>
					<name>Stuart Binny</name>
					<batsman-name>Binny</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Binny</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Tahir</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6667</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9427</playerid>
					<name>Deepak Hooda</name>
					<batsman-name>Deepak Hooda</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Deepak Hooda</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>54</runs>
					<balls>25</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>4</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Tahir</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6667</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Angelo Mathews</fielder>
						<fielderId>1629</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7789</playerid>
					<name>James Faulkner</name>
					<batsman-name>Faulkner</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Faulkner</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>17</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Tahir</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6667</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8333</playerid>
					<name>Chris Morris</name>
					<batsman-name>C Morris</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>C Morris</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>13</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1057</playerid>
					<name>Tim Southee</name>
					<batsman-name>Southee</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Southee</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>7</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1451</playerid>
					<name>Dhawal Kulkarni</name>
					<batsman-name>D Kulkarni</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>D Kulkarni</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9237</playerid>
					<name>Pravin Tambe</name>
					<batsman-name>Tambe</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Tambe</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8271</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>37</runs>
				<overs>4.6</overs>
				<batsman>Sanju Samson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Samson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>2250</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>50</runs>
				<overs>7.2</overs>
				<batsman>Steven Smith</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Smith</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8257</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>74</runs>
				<overs>9.6</overs>
				<batsman>Karun Nair</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Nair</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1530</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>78</runs>
				<overs>10.4</overs>
				<batsman>Stuart Binny</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Binny</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1447</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>130</runs>
				<overs>15.1</overs>
				<batsman>Ajinkya Rahane</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Rahane</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9427</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>166</runs>
				<overs>18.1</overs>
				<batsman>Deepak Hooda</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Deepak Hooda</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7789</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>173</runs>
				<overs>18.5</overs>
				<batsman>James Faulkner</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Faulkner</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>5</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>6</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Delhi">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>6327</playerid>
					<name>Jaydev Unadkat</name>
					<bowler-name>Unadkat</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Unadkat</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>30</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7774</playerid>
					<name>Nathan Coulter-Nile</name>
					<bowler-name>Coulter-Nile</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Coulter-Nile</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>42</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1629</playerid>
					<name>Angelo Mathews</name>
					<bowler-name>Mathews</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mathews</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>42</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1454</playerid>
					<name>Amit Mishra</name>
					<bowler-name>A Mishra</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mishra</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>32</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6667</playerid>
					<name>Imran Tahir</name>
					<bowler-name>Tahir</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Tahir</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>28</runsoff>
					<wickets>4</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>69</playerid>
					<name>Yuvraj Singh</name>
					<bowler-name>Yuvraj</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Yuvraj</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>11</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2195</playerid>
					<name>Mayank Agarwal</name>
					<bowler-name>M Agarwal</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M Agarwal</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9428</playerid>
					<name>Shreyas Iyer</name>
					<bowler-name>S Iyer</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shreyas Iyer</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>211</playerid>
					<name>Jean-Paul Duminy</name>
					<bowler-name>Duminy</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Duminy</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>694</playerid>
					<name>Manoj Tiwary</name>
					<bowler-name>M Tiwary</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M Tiwary</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1851</playerid>
					<name>Kedar Jadhav</name>
					<bowler-name>K Jadhav</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>K Jadhav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



