<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14605" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>11th Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Hyderabad</home>
		<away>Rajasthan</away>
		<teamsabbr>HYD vs JAI</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>HYD</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>JAI</awayabbr>
		<homeId>255</homeId>
		<awayId>64</awayId>
		<venue>Dr. Y.S. Rajasekhara Reddy ACA-VDCA Cricket Stadium, Visakhapatnam</venue>
		<startdate>16 04 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>16 04 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Rajasthan</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Rajasthan won by 6 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Rajasthan</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>6</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>S Ravi</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Pashchim Pathak</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Chettithody Shamsuddin</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Manu Nayyar</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>14:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150416180021</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>JAI</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>HYD</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>131</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>4</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>20</batteamovers>
		<status>Rajasthan won by 6 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>1530</playerid>
			<name>Stuart Binny</name>
			<batsman-name>Binny</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Binny</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>16</runs>
			<balls-faced>14</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>7789</playerid>
			<name>James Faulkner</name>
			<batsman-name>Faulkner</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Faulkner</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>6</runs>
			<balls-faced>5</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>592</playerid>
			<name>Praveen Kumar</name>
			<bowler-name>P Kumar</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>P Kumar</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>30</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>8117</playerid>
			<name>Trent Boult</name>
			<bowler-name>T Boult</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Boult</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>31</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>128</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>1447</playerid>
<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
<player-runs>62</player-runs>
<player-balls>56</player-balls>
<runs>118</runs>
<wicket-nbr>4</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>8117</bowlerid>
<bowlername>T Boult</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>1</byes>
			<wides>4</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[1 4 . . 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 . 4 1 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 . 1 W 1 4 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 1 . L1 1 4 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/HYD_JAI_APR16/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[This is <b>Sidhant Maheshwari</b>, signing off on behalf of <b>Krishna, Raju, Bharath, Sriram</b> and my co-commentators, <b>Ramakrishnan</b> and <b>Pradeep</b>. See you tomorrow, folks!]]></line><line><![CDATA[So, that's all we have for you from this game. Tomorrow, <b>Mumbai</b> will be up against the formidable <b>Chennai</b>. Don't forget to join us then.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Let's take a look at some of the interesting <b>tweets</b> from this game:]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@sidmallya:</b> Gotta love these last ball finishes!! Well played #RAJ, but well fought #HYD to get it so close....pure drama!!! #HYDvRAJ #IPL]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@nikhilchinapa:</b> Jimmy!!! Well done @rajasthanroyals but whhhyyyyyyyy would you leave it till the last ball!!?? #bestillmybeatingheart #RAJvHYD]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@fwildecricket:</b> Clinical from #RAJ; but #HYD didn't score enough runs, they need more from their Indian batsmen. #IPL #HYDvRAJ]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@holdingwilley:</b> A  very precious dot ball, outgambitting Faulkner at the crease.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@bhogleharsha:</b> Was sheer quality this innings from Ajinkya Rahane. But needed to take his team home....]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rahane:</b> 'Good to be back home. Really happy with the way I am batting right now. I am very confident. Happy that the team won once again, we did really well as a team today. It (the pitch) was a little bit  on the slower side. I just wanted to keep it simple there because I knew that if we took our time, it would be easier for us in the end. We are just playing well. One game at a time, so looking forward to the next game.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ajinkya Rahane</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his knock of <b>62</b>. He also becomes the new <b>Orange cap</b> holder]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Smith:</b> 'I think the boys are playing some good cricket. Got a bit tight in the end, but it's good to go over the line once again. The Indian contingent is exciting. The pitch played pretty similar throughout the game. It would have been nice to have got these runs a little bit quicker though.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Smith:</b> 'I think the boys are playing some good cricket. Got a bit tight in the end, but it's good to go over the line once again. The Indian contingent is exciting. The pitch played pretty similar throughout the game. It would have been nice to have got these runs a little bit quicker though.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Warner:</b> 'Great game, the boys dug in deep there. It was great, it was nail-biting in the end there, but they played well. We were a bit below par there. We thought it was a 150-160 wicket. Well, if a few decisions had gone our way, it could have been different. Definitely, it's great to see these guys come out and turn up here. We hope to see them (crowd) in the next game as well.']]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, it was teamwork that helped Rajasthan to restrict the opposition to a modest total. The likes of Dhawal Kulkarni and Pravin Tambe bowled with discipline and were rewarded with wickets. Eoin Morgan played a useful knock. However, Tambe prised out both Morgan and Naman Ojha and despite a couple of hefty blows from Bopara, the hosts just couldn't up the tempo.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ajinkya Rahane and Sanju Samson played with a calm head on their shoulders as Rajasthan won a low-scoring thriller. On a deck that was offering the bowlers encouragement, Rahane and Samson twinned caution with aggression to keep the scorecard moving. Even after Samson lost his wicket, Rahane found the gaps with needlepoint precision. In the end, it got tense for the visitors, before James Faulkner held his nerve to steer them home with cracking a boundary off the final ball of the innings. For the hosts, Ravi Bopara and Karn Sharma bowled well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Faulkner, <b>FOUR</b>, it was a low full toss outside off, Faulkner opens the face of the bat and drives it to the right of backward point and the ball runs away to the fence. Praveen misses his length this time around and paid the price for it. He was unhappy with himself there]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Faulkner finishes it off with a boundary</b>. Rajasthan win by 6 wickets in the end. Praveen Kumar got every ball right in this over, except the last one. Faulkner shakes hands with the Hyderabad' players.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Another big discussion between Warner and Praveen. Ojha comes up to the stumps now. Warner has decided to bring everyone inside the circle. They all are looking to save the single here. <b>1 needed in 1 ball</b>. Here we go then...]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Binny, 1 run, full delivery around off, Binny comes down the track and drives it past the bowler, the batsmen take a single and Binny was looking for the second there, but Faulkner sends him back after seeing the throw come in towards the non-striker's end]]></line><line><![CDATA[Can we have a super over here? 2 needed off 2 balls]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Faulkner, leg byes, 1 run, a yorker on the legs of Faulkner, who fails to work it through the on-side, the ball rolls away behind square on the off-side off the pad and the batsmen take a leg bye. Praveen appealed for the lbw, but it was going down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[Big discussion between Warner and Praveen going on regarding the field placements. Third man has gone back and fine leg is inside the ring now]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Faulkner, no run, yorker outside off, Faulkner makes room and looks to carve it over the off-side, he fails to connect and the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Binny, 1 run, <b>run-out chance missed!</b> It was full and outside off, Binny squeezes out the drive towards backward point, where Morgan dives to his left and makes a stunning stop. He quickly throws the ball at the non-striker's end as Binny was struggling. A direct-hit would have meant curtains for Binny, the man running in towards the stumps from mid-on too fails to collect the ball cleanly, otherwise it could have been close on the second attempt too]]></line><line><![CDATA[Fine leg has gone back now]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Faulkner, 1 run, Faulkner makes room and Praveen follows him with a yorker, Faulkner squeezes it out onto his pad, the ball rolls away in front of point and the batsmen take a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Praveen Kumar [3.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>5 runs needed off 6 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Binny, <b>FOUR</b>, lucky boundary but RAJ will take it. It was a short delivery outside off, Binny went for the big pull, ends up slicing and the ball runs away to the square third man region. Streaky, but all these runs count]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Faulkner, 1 run, Faulkner comes charging down the track and flat-bats this back of a length delivery towards cover, where Bopara dives to his right and parries the ball towards mid-off, saved a few runs for his team there]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Rahane, <b>out</b> Bowled!! <b>Is there a twist in the tale?</b> Rahane, the set batsman is gone. It was a short of length delivery outside off, Rahane advances forward and goes for a big slog over the leg-side, he gets an inside edge and the ball rams into the off stump. Big wicket for HYD at this stage. Can they pull off a miraculous victory here? We will know in a short while. <b>Rahane b Boult 62(56) [4s-9]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Boult to Rahane, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Binny, 1 run, banged in short and at the batsman, Binny pulls it, but can't time it right. The fielder from deep mid-wicket runs forward, but the ball bounces in front of him. Only a single available this time as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Binny, no run, length delivery outside off, Binny goes for a big hit over extra cover, but only connects with thin air. Rahane has a chat with him after the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Rahane, 1 run, bangs this one short, Rahane pulls it down to long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Comes from round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Trent Boult [3.0-0-24-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>RAJ need 12 runs in 12 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, 1 run, low full toss on off, Rahane goes across and clips it to mid-wicket, the batsmen charge across to the other end and Rahane will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Binny, 1 run, Binny comes forward after giving himself room, he almost yorks himself there, but did well to squeeze it out towards point, who dives to his right and makes a half stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, 1 run, great shot from Rahane, but Warner keeps them down to a single. It was full and outside off, Rahane lofts it past the bowler, Warner at long-off runs to his right, picks the ball and fires in a direct-hit at the bowler's end. The batsmen can only take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, one bounce and into the deep mid-wicket fence, this was timed superbly by Rahane, Bhuvi dragged his length back and bowled it on middle and leg stump line, Rahane just picks it off his pads and hits it towards the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, no run, yorker outside off, Rahane was on the front foot and squeezes it out towards point, can't take the single as the ball went straight towards the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Binny, 1 run, splays this one on the pads, Binny tucks it away towards deep mid-wicket for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Bhuvneshwar Kumar [3.0-0-17-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Binny, 1 run, angles this in on off, Binny stays inside the crease, opens the face of the bat at the last moment and steers it to the left of backward point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Rahane, 1 run, slower short ball from Bopara, Rahane waits for it and pulls it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Rahane, no run, Rahane comes down the track once again and Bopara drags it slightly wide outside off, Rahane tries to run it down to third man, but ends up chopping it towards the keeper, can't get the single away]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Rahane, no run, full delivery outside off, Rahane comes forward and drives it straight back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, Rahane comes down the track and he flicks this length delivery on middle stump line to the cow corner fence, great use of the wrists there from him]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Binny, 1 run, full delivery on off, Binny walks across and was looking to go over the on-side, closes the bat face a little too early, gets a leading edge that falls well short of the man at sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashish Reddy to Binny, 1 run, Binny takes a step forward to this length delivery outside off, he cracks it hard, but straight to the fielder at sweeper cover, only a single available and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashish Reddy to Rahane, 1 run, Rahane reaches his <b>14th IPL fifty</b> with this single, it was angled in on the pads, Rahane nudges it to the right of mid-wicket and sets off, completes the single easily in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashish Reddy to Rahane, no run, length delivery shaping in from outside off, Rahane gets behind the line and defends it towards short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashish Reddy to Binny, 1 run, bowls this one in the channel just outside off, Binny knocks it down to long-off to get off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashish Reddy to Binny, no run, just short of a good length and on middle, the ball keeps a touch low as well, Binny checks his drive and the ball goes a little uppishly towards the bowler, but bounces in front of him]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashish Reddy to Binny, 2 runs, back of a length delivery angling in on the pads, Binny tucks it away behind square on the on-side and comes back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashish Reddy, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, Rahane is playing a superb knock here, this time it was short and wide again from Bopara, Rahane waits inside the crease and cuts it very late, he gets it towards the square third man region and the ball runs away to the fence. The third man fielder ran to his right there, but dives in vain as the ball was far away from him]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Binny, 1 run, back of a length delivery slightly wide outside off, Binny glides it down to third man from the crease, gets off the mark with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Stuart Binny, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Nair, <b>out</b> Caught&Bowled!! Bopara picks his second of the night and this time it's Nair, who has to go. It was a length delivery around off, Nair pushes at it after coming forward, he checks his push and the bat also turns in his hands as he makes contact with the ball. He ends up chipping it towards the bowler, who dives in front and to his right to take the catch. <b>Nair c and b Bopara 1(5)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bopara to Nair, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught&Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Nair, no run, drags his length back slightly, Nair comes forward and pushes it down to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Nair, no run, full delivery on off and middle, Nair goes across and drives it wristily back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Rahane, 1 run, full delivery angling in from outside off, Rahane drives it down to long-off after coming forward]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for the batting team to take their <b>strategic timeout</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Nair, no run, slower through the air and on off, Nair gets on the front foot and defends solidly]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rahane, 1 run, floated up on the stumps, Rahane turns it towards mid-wicket and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a <b>cracking shot!</b> It was tossed up and outside off, Rahane leans forward and drives it magnificently past a diving cover, the ball runs away to the fence and the man at sweeper had no chance of stopping that]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Nair, 1 run, flatter and outside off, Nair hangs back and cuts it square of the wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place for Nair]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Karun Nair, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Smith, <b>out</b> Caught by Warner!! Big wicket for HYD. Karn gets the dangerous Smith out. He bowled this one slower and tosses it slightly wide outside off. Smith reaches out and goes for the lofted drive once again, but this time he picks out Warner at cover, who takes a simple catch. Warner throws the ball in the air in delight too. <b>S Smith c Warner b Karn Sharma 13(10) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Karn Sharma to S Smith, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, Smith gives the charge, reaches to the pitch of the ball and lofts it inside-out over extra cover, he played it with the turn there and that's why it was so pleasing to the eye]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Karn Sharma [2.0-0-9-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to S Smith, 1 run, angles it in on middle stump line, Smith punches it towards deep backward square leg off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Rahane, 1 run, full delivery on off, Rahane goes slightly across and drives it down to long-on, he was looking for the second there, but it's not there]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Rahane, no run, length delivery on off, Rahane goes across and turns it towards square leg, where the mid-wicket fielder runs to his right and prevents the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Rahane, no run, full and just outside off, Rahane comes forward and pushes it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to S Smith, 1 run, length ball on leg stump that keeps slightly low, Smith goes across, adjusts to the bounce and pushes it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to S Smith, no run, comes down the track and drives this full delivery to extra cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, 1 run, opens the face of the bat and guides it down to third man, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, Smith thumps Boult down to the long-on fence. It was full and just outside off, Smith makes room after clearing his front leg, drills it to the left of mid-on and the ball hurries across the turf and crashes into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, no run, Smith plays away from the body this time and gets beaten, it was the pace of the ball that beat his outside edge there as he poked at it]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Rahane, 1 run, touch fuller and closer to the off stump this time, Rahane leans forward and drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, that's been <b>smashed!</b> It was short, it was wide and Rahane latches onto it, he cuts it fiercely over backward point and the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[Comes round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, 1 run, goes fuller and angles it across off, Smith shuffles across and looks to drive it through the off-side, the ball rolls away to deep mid-wicket off the inside half of the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Smith, <b>wide</b>, bumper from Boult, Smith ducks under it and the umpire calls it a wide for height]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Trent Boult [2.0-0-12-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Rahane, no run, just short of a good length and shaping away once again, Rahane has a waft at it, but fails to make contact]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Rahane, no run, <b>beaten!</b> It was the length delivery shaping away outside off, Rahane goes for the drive, but the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Rahane, no run, fullish delivery outside off, Rahane pushes it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to S Smith, 1 run, goes across and clips this fullish delivery off the inside half of the bat to mid-wicket, the batsmen take a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Steven Smith, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Samson, <b>out</b> Caught by N Ojha!! What a brilliant catch! Bopara, the wicket-taker has the breakthrough. It was bowled on a length and outside off, Samson opens the face of the bat and looks to guide it past the keeper, who dives full length to his right and takes a sensational catch with the tip of his mitts. The umpires check whether that was a clean catch and replays show that Ojha had his fingers around the ball. <b>Samson c N Ojha b Bopara 26(30) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bopara to Samson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Rahane, 1 run, angling in on off and middle, Rahane goes across and works it to deep square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravi Bopara, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rahane, 1 run, Karn Sharma drops one short and just outside off, Rahane rocks back and pulls it wide of long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rahane, 2 runs, that's excellent running from Rahane, tad fuller and on off, Rahane nudges it towards the vacant mid-wicket regions, wants two and gets back with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rahane, no run, flighted and just outside off, Rahane prods forward defensively]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rahane, no run, that's a lovely leg-break from Karn Sharma, tossed up on off, draws Rahane forward before spinning past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rahane, 2 runs, overpitched and well outside off, Rahane gets forward and drills it past cover for another couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Samson, 1 run, the googly from Karn Sharma, Samson gets to the pitch of the ball and punches it towards long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Samson, 1 run, another of those wristy pulls from Samson, gets a single to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Samson, no run, back of a length and just outside off, dabbed in front of point. Rahane wants a single and is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Samson, 2 runs, length ball and on Samson's pads, flicked away past square leg for another easy brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Samson, no run, short of a length and just outside off, flicked towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Samson, 2 runs, too short from Praveen, can't do so with his pace, pulled away behind square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Rahane, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, Rahane plays a half-arm jab towards deep mid-wicket for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Samson, no run, huge turn for Karn Sharma, but the line was from well outside off, Samson was lunging forward, watches the ball turn square and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rahane, 1 run, Karn Sharma drifts one on off, Rahane goes back and works it behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rahane, no run, flighted and just outside off, Rahane prods forward and defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Samson, 1 run, Karn Sharma drops one short and on the stumps, Samson goes back and works it in front of square on the on-side, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rahane, 1 run, pushed through quicker by Karn Sharma, Rahane rocks back and mistimes the pull towards long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Rahane, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Rahane lunges forward defensively]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Karn Sharma, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Karn Sharma is in, a slip is in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Samson, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Samson prods across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Samson, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four</b>, more luck for Samson, fraction shorter and a hint of shape away from Praveen, draws Samson half-forward and into the defensive push, the edge is found, but there's no one at slip and the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Samson, 2 runs, that would have been a fine catch had Ashish completed it! This was short and just outside off, Samson went for the half arm-jab pull, gets a lot of height and over mid-wicket. Ashish runs in from the deep, dives forward but doesn't get to the ball, reprieve for Samson]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Samson, <b>FOUR</b>, that's what he was trying to do last ball! Fraction short and just outside off, Samson shuffles across and pulls it over mid-on for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in now]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Samson, no run, that's a wild hack from Samson! This was short and shaped away slightly, Samson went for a wild swoosh and missed it completely]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Rahane, 1 run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Rahane throws his bat at that and gets a thick edge towards third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Rahane, <b>wide</b>, the bouncer from Praveen, but it's too short and well down leg-side, given as a wide]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, 1 run, Bhuvneshwar keeps it full and gets the ball to wobble in the air, Rahane shuffles across and flicks it to the right of mid-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Samson, 1 run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Samson leans forward and caresses it through cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, byes, 1 run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, left alone. Ojha can't collect it cleanly and allows a bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>Rahane gets lucky</b>, this was pitched up and just outside off, Rahane used the bottom hand as he looked to flick it past mid-on, looked like he checked his shot at the last moment, spoons it in the air and is lucky that the ball went over the head of Boult at mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, 2 runs, tad fuller and shaping away from outside off, driven through cover for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, no run, Rahane comes down the track, covers for the swing and defends it towards cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Bhuvneshwar Kumar [2.0-0-9-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Change of ends for Bhuvneshwar. One slip still in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Samson, no run, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, Samson steps down the track and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Samson, no run, the inswinger from Praveen, Samson covers for the movement and defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Rahane, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, Rahane wristily works it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Rahane, no run, on a good length and just outside off, dabbed with an open face and towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Samson, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, nudged in front of square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Samson, 2 runs, that's nicely played by Samson, gentle outswinger from Praveen, Samson takes a step down the track and caresses it past extra cover for a brace]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Samson, <b>wide</b>, Kumar swings one well down leg-side, given as a wide]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Praveen Kumar, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, wrong line from Boult, too straight and onto Rahane's pads, flicked away past the keeper for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Rahane, no run, that's loose from Rahane, this was pushed across the batsman, the outswinger from Boult, he went feeling for that and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Rahane, 2 runs, too straight from Boult, ends up drifting onto Rahane's pads, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Rahane, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, punched towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Rahane, <b>wide</b>, Boult slips one down leg-side, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Samson, 1 run, Samson takes a step down the track, covers for the movement and drops it in front of mid-off. He calls for a quick single, almost bumped into the bowler, has to get around Boult and makes his ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Samson, no run, fuller length delivery and in that corridor outside off, Samson plays away from his body and gets an inside edge, the ball rolls back towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, no run, on a good length and just outside off, stayed a tad low as well, Rahane chops it onto the ground, thinks about a single and decides against it]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Samson, 1 run, fuller length delivery and a hint of shape back into Samson, driven off the inner half of the bat and to the right of mid-on for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Samson, no run, width on offer from Samson, slapped straight to short point where Rahul makes a smart stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Samson, no run, Bhuvneshwar shortens his length and gets this one to shape away from outside off, Samson has a loose dab at that and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Samson, 2 runs, tad fuller and well outside off, Samson leans forward and drives it on the up, gets it in the gap between cover-point and point, comes back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Samson, no run, on a good length and well outside off, Samson presses forward and defends it towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[A slip and a gully in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Rahane, no run, tad fuller and on the stumps, Rahane presses across and turns it towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Rahane, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Rahane prods half-forward and blocks it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Rahane, no run, <b>loud shout for LBW</b>, the umpire has a good look at that and says NO. That looked very close, pitched around middle and nipped back into Rahane, he was caught on the shuffle as he looked to flick, gets struck low on the pads. The impact was on middle. Rahane is very lucky to survive, Boult isn't impressed one bit]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Rahane, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Rahane prods across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, poor line from Boult, short and on Rahane's pads, he gets inside the line and gets an inside edge onto the flick, the ball runs away past the keeper and into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Samson, leg byes, 1 run, too straight and on Samson's pads, he was looking to work it towards the on-side, misses and the ball rolls away off the thigh pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Trent Boult, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, no run, much better from Bhuvneshwar, tad fuller and a hint of shape back into Rahane, he was prodding forward and with loose hands, gets an inside edge and the ball rolls away towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>short, wide and four</b>, width on offer from Bhuvneshwar, Rahane gets on top of the bounce and cracks it square past point for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Samson, 1 run, on a good length and a hint of nip back into Samson, he plays with an open face and guides it towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Samson, no run, short and wide from Bhuvneshwar, Samson reaches out and slaps it straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Samson, no run, tad fuller and well outside off, Samson leans forward and gets an inside edge on the defensive push, the inside edge rolls towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Rahane, 1 run, short of a length and shaping away from outside off, worked away behind square on the off-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rahane and Samson are at the crease. Rahane is on strike. Bhuvneshwar will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. Two slips in place for Bhuvneshwar..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Warner</b>: "I don't think the score reflects what the wicket is like. 150-160 would have been good, but credit to them. They bowled really well. We've got to come out and take wickets. We've got to be clinical. We can win this game."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Morgan checked in fine shots to lift their sagging spirits to some extent. Ojha gave Morgan good support. However, Pravin Tambe outfoxed both of them to take their wickets and put the visitors in the ascendancy. The deck is offering a bit of help for the bowlers, but Rajasthan would back themselves to overcome the modest target and win their fourth game in a row in this year's IPL.  ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Despite Eoin Morgan and Naman Ojha stitching a fine partnership, Hyderabad ended up with a below par total. For most part of the innings, Rajasthan bowled with relentless control and precision to put the home team under pressure. It was Dhawal Kulkarni, who generated enough swing to snaffle the wickets of Lokesh Rahul and Shikhar Dhawan. Stuart Binny and Tim Southee also bowled fine spells up front. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Ashish Reddy, 2 runs, full and on the stumps, Reddy slogs it wide of long-on, Smith runs to his left from deep mid-wicket and saves two]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Bopara, 1 run, short ball again and another mistimed pull from Bopara and this time it goes to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Ashish Reddy, 1 run, Southee follows Ashish Reddy as he backs away a long way, it would have been a wide if a left-hander was batting, Reddy drives it straight to extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Bopara, 1 run, pacy bumper this time, Bopara mistimes the pull, luckily for him it doesn't carry to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Ashish Reddy, byes, 1 run, shortish slower ball, Reddy goes for the pull but misses. Samson fumbles and they get a bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Ashish Reddy, <b>SIX</b>, Faulkner takes the catch, but he's crossed the rope. Slower ball outside off stump, Reddy backs away and smashes the loft, long-off runs to his left, jumps and takes the catch, but his left foot landed beyond the boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tim Southee [3.0-0-19-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Tambe ends 4-0-21-2.]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Ashish Reddy, 1 run, full and outside off stump, Reddy mistimes the drive to extra-cover, where Smith dives to his right and saves a few]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Bopara, 1 run, and again, driven hard to deep extra-cover but only for a single though]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Bopara, 2 runs, after being hit for a six, Tambe fires it flat and short, Bopara crashes it very hard to deep extra-cover, Ashish Reddy races back for the second and the dive saves him]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire called for a run-out check. Ashish Reddy is the man in question. He's crossed the line with the dive. Oh has the bat bounced when Tambe took the bails off? Very difficult to tell. Will the benefit of doubt go the batsman? Yes, it does!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Bopara, <b>SIX</b>, <b>that's gone out of the ground</b>. What a hit! Tambe bowls this flighted delivery too full, Bopara waits and absolutely gives it all, the ball sails over long-on. That was hit very hard by Bopara]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Bopara, no run, flighted delivery well outside off stump, Bopara lets it go looking for a wide but it was just inside the line]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Ashish Reddy, 1 run, on the leg stump, Reddy flicks it to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Bopara, no run, slower ball outside off stump, cut straight to backward point. A couple of yards either side of the fielder would have been four]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Bopara, <b>FOUR</b>, oh he's smashed that! Morris misses the yorker by a distance and bowls a juicy full ball, Bopara drills it very hard to the left of the bowler and mid-off had no chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Ashish Reddy, 1 run, pushed away to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Bopara, 1 run, races towards the bowler again, Bopara goes for the pull, gets an under edge that goes past the stumps to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Bopara, no run, <b>dropped</b>, but a tough chance. Short of a length delivery cramping for room as he came down the track, Bopara looks to flat-bat it for four, hits it in the air, the bowler had to move to his right a bit in his followthrough, got both hands to it but couldn't hold on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Bopara, no run, short of length delivery just outside off stump, Bopara defends off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Morris [2.0-0-17-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Bopara, 1 run, cut square of the wicket and he'll keep strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Ashish Reddy, 1 run, shortish and outside off stump, Reddy drives it along the ground to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Ashish Reddy, no run, punched to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashish Reddy, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Eoin Morgan, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Oh the umpire almost in a funny manner quickly raises his left index finger as soon as Tambe appealed for LBW. Big wicket for RAJ. Flighted delivery on the stumps, Morgan goes for the fancy little reverse sweep and gets hit on the pad. The impact was on middle and it would have crashed into the stumps. <b>Eoin Morgan lbw b Tambe 27(30) [4s-2 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Tambe to Eoin Morgan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Eoin Morgan, no run, <b>stumping chance missed</b>! Googly outside off stump, Morgan goes for the drive, doesn't pick the variation and gets beaten. Samson fumbles the ball, it looked like Morgan dragged his back foot out of the crease for a while]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Bopara, 1 run, flighted delivery on the leg stump, Bopara flicks it into the vacant mid-wicket region, looks for two but Morgan asks him to stay as Tambe quickly got to the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Bopara, 1 run, on the leg stump, nudged to square leg and he'll keep strike. Nice over, just 5 runs off it]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket now]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, full and down the leg-side, Morgan flicks it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Eoin Morgan, no run, fired wide outside off stump, driven straight to extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Eoin Morgan, no run, Morgan makes room and swings hard, but can only toe-end it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Bopara, 1 run, driven past the bowler's dive to the right to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Bopara, 2 runs, lucky runs, flighted delivery way outside off stump, Bopara tries to paddle it fine to fine leg, the ball goes over the keeper off the top edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Deepak Hooda [1.0-0-6-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's time for the <b>time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Eoin Morgan, no run, gently defended off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Eoin Morgan, 2 runs, googly from Tambe, Morgan goes for the reverse sweep, gets an under edge, on seeing Morgan go for the fancy hit, Smith at slip moved to his left but the ball went to his right to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Bopara, 1 run, very full, Bopara drives it along the ground to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Bopara, no run, punched to the left of the bowler, who makes a good stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Bopara, no run, flighted delivery from Tambe, defended]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravi Bopara, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to N Ojha, <b>out</b> Bowled!! 'Come on,' shouts Tambe with his hands aloft and blows a kiss to the sky. That was a peach of a ball from the young man. Just the previous over, this flighted delivery pitches outside leg, Ojha stays leg-side and tries to play across the line, the ball spins past his bat and hits middle and leg. Timely wicket for the Rajasthan as this partnership was slowly turning it on for the hosts. <b>N Ojha b Tambe 25(32) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Tambe to N Ojha, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Eoin Morgan, <b>FOUR</b>, slower ball, Eoin Morgan waits and delays the cut shot, times it very well, sends it through backward point and the man at sweeper had no chance. <b>Fifty partnership</b> is up, much needed stand for HYD]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to N Ojha, 1 run, short ball, Ojha gets inside the line and pulls, but Tambe tidies up at long leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to N Ojha, 2 runs, full from Southee, Ojha drives it hard to the left of long-on for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to N Ojha, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Ojha punches, Rahane makes a diving save to his left at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to N Ojha, no run, Ojha plays a cut shot without moving his feet and the ball beats the inside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, almost a top edge, short and on the stumps, Morgan goes for the pull, but mistimes it completely, luckily for him, Karun Nair doesn't get there from mid-on after running to his left]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tim Southee [2.0-0-11-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to N Ojha, no run, shortish and outside off stump, cut straight to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to N Ojha, 2 runs, <b>that's a chance not taken by RAJ</b>. Flighted delivery outside off stump, Ojha steps out and looks to go big, slices the loft high in the air, the man at sweeper, Deepak Hooda it is, ran to his right, dived full length but could only get his fingertips to it]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to N Ojha, no run, flighted delivery spinning away outside off stump, Ojha stays back to cut, but gets beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to N Ojha, 2 runs, tossed up on the leg stump, driven uppishly past the bowler's dive to long-on, where the fielder makes a fine sliding save]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to N Ojha, no run, pitches around the same area, but this one doesn't turn that much, Ojha looks to tuck but gets hit on the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip comes in now]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to N Ojha, no run, what a ball first up! Wow! This flighted delivery pitched outside leg and turned square, beat Ojha's poke and just missed the off stump]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pravin Tambe, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Eoin Morgan, <b>FOUR</b>, too short, not high or quick enough to trouble Morgan, who rocks back and nails the pull shot through backward square leg. Strong finish to the over from Morgan]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to N Ojha, 1 run, allows the short of length delivery to come and punches it off the crowd through cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, he's mistimed this but luckily it doesn't carry to long-off. Full and outside off stump, Morgan looks to go over the on-side, gets it on the outside half of the bat and it goes to the right of long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Eoin Morgan, no run, slower ball on the off stump, Morgan defends off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to N Ojha, 1 run, good length and just outside off stump, Ojha drives it along the ground to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, advances and drives the fuller length delivery to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to N Ojha, <b>FOUR</b>, poor bowling from Faulkner. Short and down the leg-side, easy pickings for Ojha, who gently tickles it away fine to the fine leg boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, on the leg stump, Morgan nudges it through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Eoin Morgan, no run, short and outside off stump, Morgan sways out of the line]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Eoin Morgan, no run, short of length delivery from Faulkner, Morgan gets hit on the pad, the ball rolls to square leg, Ojha wants a run but he's sent back, Smith has a shy at the bowler's end but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Eoin Morgan, <b>SIX</b>, and it's smashed. Slower ball bumper outside off stump, Morgan waits and muscles the pull shot over the deep mid-wicket boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Free-hit</b> coming up]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to N Ojha, <b>no ball</b>, top edge and the keeper does well to quickly move to his left and take the catch. Oh no! Looks like Faulkner has overstepped. Or has he? The third umpire is having a long look. That's really tough. Has the foot landed on the line? The zoomer comes in. Still taking a long time to make the call. Chettithody Shamshuddin is the third umpire. Lucky escape for Ojha. My word! We could have had some 9-10 balls bowled. The decision took so long. Short of a length delivery on the stumps, Ojha goes for the pull, gets a top edge, the ball lobs off the thigh pad and keeper takes the catch]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to N Ojha, no run, short of length delivery angling away from the right-hander, Ojha goes for the cut and gets beaten as the ball bounces extra]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Eoin Morgan, 2 runs, the slower bouncer from Binny, Morgan waits on it and pulls it behind square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Eoin Morgan, no run, Binny keeps it full as Morgan gave the charge, he gets a toe-end on the drive and the ball rolls towards short extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to N Ojha, 1 run, too straight from Binny, worked past mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to N Ojha, no run, that's a cracker from Binny, shortens his length and gets it to seam away after hitting the deck, Ojha is opened up completely as he looked to defend and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, short of a length and on Morgan's pads, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Eoin Morgan, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, left alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Stuart Binny, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to N Ojha, no run, the slower leg-cutter from Faulkner, the back of the hand delivery, Ojha was cramped for room as he looked to dab it towards third man, gets an inside edge onto the thigh pad, the ball rolled close to the leg-stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, back of a length and on Morgan's hips, tucked past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to N Ojha, 1 run, back of a length and on the stumps, Ojha nudges it in front of mid-on for a quick single. Morris has a shy at the bowler's end but Ojha was well in]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to N Ojha, <b>wide</b>, the bouncer from Faulkner, but this is way too high, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to N Ojha, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Faulkner, short and on Ojha's pads, he waits on it and flicks it fine. Tamble runs across to his right at fine leg, puts in the dive, but the ball beats him to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, short of a length and angling into the left-hander, worked past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Eoin Morgan, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Morgan stays behind the line and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to N Ojha, no run, Kulkarni shortens his length outside off, defended with soft hands and towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to N Ojha, no run, back of a length and in that channel outside off, defended off the back foot and towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to N Ojha, <b>wide</b>, the slower bouncer from Kulkarni, but it's a tad too short and too high, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to N Ojha, no run, that's nicely bowled by Kulkarni, slips this one full and gets it to nip back into Ojha, the batsman was caught in his crease and is lucky that the inside edge thudded onto his pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, too straight from Kulkarni, ends up drifting onto Morgan's pads, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to N Ojha, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, Ojha stands tall and pushes it past Rahane at point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to N Ojha, no run, on a good length and just outside off, blocked back towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to N Ojha, 1 run, back of a length and on Ojha's pads, tucked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to N Ojha, no run, confusion between the two batsmen, but Eoin Morgan gets back in time. Ojha flicked a full ball towards mid-wicket, Morgan set off for a quick single before being sent back. The fielder has a shy and misses but Morgan was just about in]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to N Ojha, <b>FOUR</b>, that's exquisitely played! Fraction too full and just outside off, Ojha leans forward, meets the ball on top of the bounce and creams it through extra cover, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to N Ojha, no run, back of a length and in that channel just outside off, Ojha hops across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to N Ojha, no run, beaten! This was short and just outside off, too close to attempt the cut, Ojha flashes at that and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to N Ojha, no run, short of a length and angling back into Ojha, he shuffles across and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Morris [1.0-0-12-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Eoin Morgan, no run, <b>wicket-maiden from Kulkarni</b>, on a good length and shaping away from the left-hander, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Eoin Morgan, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Morgan swivels across on the pull, doesn't get hold of the shot and mistimes it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Eoin Morgan, no run, nicely bowled by Kulkarni, he went up in an appeal for a catch at the wicket, but there was no one supporting him. Morgan shimmied down the track to one that left him, beaten on the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Eoin Morgan, no run, short of a length and just outside off, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Eoin Morgan, no run, muted appeal for LBW, but there was a big inside edge there. Morgan was caught in his crease as he poked at one that shaped away, gets an inside edge onto the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hat-trick ball</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Eoin Morgan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Rahul, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Now Rahul falls! HYD are in huge trouble! This is as plumb as it gets. This was pitched up and nipped back in a fraction, Rahul was shuffling across on the clip and missed, gets struck low on his pads. The impact was around middle and leg, the ball would have crashed into the leg-stump. Kulkarni is on a hat-trick now. <b>Rahul lbw b D Kulkarni 2(5)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[D Kulkarni to Rahul, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Naman Ojha, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Rahul, <b>out</b> Warner Run Out!! Lazy running from Warner. He wasn't too happy with his partner as well. Rahul was looking to nudge one that nipped back at him towards the leg-side, misses and is struck high on the pads. He immediately called for a quick single as the ball rolled to the left of backward point. Warner was late in responding, Rahane moved across quickly and makes a direct hit at the striker's end. Warner was miles short of his crease. <b>Warner run out (Rahane) 21(14) [4s-3 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Southee to Rahul, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Appeal for a run-out. Warner has given himself OUT. He is walking. He's OUT by a long way]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Rahul, 2 runs, short of a length and just outside off, Rahul plays an awkward looking chop, gets it past cover and comes back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[A silly mid-on in place, Smith has placed himself there]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Rahul, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Rahul presses forward and drives it towards short extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Rahul, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, Rahul shuffles across and defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Warner, 1 run, on a good length and well outside off, Warner stays back and nudges it square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Warner, <b>wide</b>, Warner will feel he missed out there, full toss and just outside leg, Warner was looking to flick and missed, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Warner, <b>SIX</b>, that's smashed! Southee banged one short as Warner made room outside leg, Warner gets on top of the bounce and upper-cuts it over point, the ball sails over the ropes for a maximum]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tim Southee [1.0-0-1-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Lokesh Rahul, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Dhawan, <b>out</b> Caught by Samson!! That's an excellent comeback from Kulkarni! He shortened his length as Dhawan was moving across his crease, the angle took it away from off-stump, Dhawan pokes at that, the edge is found and Samson moves across to his left to complete the catch. First wicket down for the Hyderabad. <b>Dhawan c Samson b D Kulkarni 10(12) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[D Kulkarni to Dhawan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, much better from Dhawan, excellent use of the feet, gets to the pitch of the ball and drills it over extra cover for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Warner, 1 run, another slower ball from Kulkarni, Warner works it to the left of point and sets off for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Warner, no run, Kulkarni slips in the slower off-cutter, Warner was way too early on the slash and missed. The ball goes to the keeper on the bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Warner, no run, short of a length and going away with the angle, Warner was looking to heave it out of the ground and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;D Kulkarni to Dhawan, 1 run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, driven to the right of Faulkner at mid-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhawal Kulkarni, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Warner, no run, pushed through flatter and on the off-stump line, Warner backs away and mistimes the cut, the ball rolls back towards the bowler, off his pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[The slip moves across to extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Dhawan, 1 run, slower and just outside off, Dhawan is beaten in the flight as he came down the track, gets an inside edge for a single towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Dhawan, <b>wide</b>, Hooda pushes one well down leg-side, given as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Dhawan, no run, Dhawan backed away even before the bowler released the ball, Hooda fires one flat and on the stumps, cracked straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a nice way to get going, Dhawan jumps down the track, takes the ball on the full and flicks it past mid-wicket for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Dhawan, no run, flighted delivery and on the off-stump line, Dhawan goes back and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Deepak Hooda to Dhawan, no run, Hooda starts with an arm-ball, Dhawan makes room and cuts it straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Deepak Hooda, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Warner, no run, Morris shortens his length outside off, Warner was looking to crash it through point, goes hard on the shot and mistimes it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Warner, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Warner stays besides the line and pushes it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, fraction overpitched and just outside off, Warner gets forward and caresses it to the right of cover-point, beats the man in the deep as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Warner, no run, Morris slips in the slower ball, Warner watches it all along and blocks it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Morris, width on offer, Warner gets on top of the bounce and cracks it square past cover-point, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, loosener from Morris, short and just outside off, Warner swivels across and pulls it over mid-on, the fielder gets a fingertip on the leap, but the ball scurries away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Morris, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Dhawan, no run, Dhawan gets lucky! Shimmies down the track to one that shaped away, he was looking to flick, closed the face of the bat and gets a thick edge, the ball went to the left of Smith at wide slip, he dived across and took it on the second attempt, but the ball had bounced in front of him. Smith's grab wasn't clean as well, the ball looked like it bounced off the deck when he attempted that take]]></line><line><![CDATA[Has the ball carried through to Smith at wide slip? He isn't sure, motions towards the umpires and they decide to have another check with the third umpire, the umpire suggests that it didn't carry. Looks like it's bounced in front of the fielder. NOT OUT should be the call.]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Dhawan, no run, nicely bowled by Southee, keeps it very full and gets it to nip back into Dhawan, he fell over on the flick, gets a bottom edge onto the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Dhawan, no run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, looking to tempt Dhawan into the drive, he can't resist, goes chasing after that and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Dhawan, no run, tad fuller and a hint of shape back into Dhawan, he was looking to drive and gets an inside edge towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Warner, 1 run, full and swinging onto Warner's pads, that's easy pickings for the left-hander as he flicks it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Warner, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Warner was way too early on the pull, ends up getting a toe-end towards cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Warner and Dhawan are at the crease. Warner is on strike. Southee will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Right, the players are out in the middle. Warner got a fifty against BLR and he will take first strike. Southee has the new ball and has a slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hyderabad</b> (Playing XI): Shikhar Dhawan, David Warner(c), Lokesh Rahul, Naman Ojha(w), Eoin Morgan, Ravi Bopara, Ashish Reddy, Karn Sharma, Praveen Kumar, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Trent Boult]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajasthan</b> (Playing XI): Ajinkya Rahane, Sanju Samson(w), Steven Smith(c), Karun Nair, Deepak Hooda, Stuart Binny, James Faulkner, Chris Morris, Tim Southee, Dhawal Kulkarni, Pravin Tambe]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajasthan have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[No Shane Watson today as well. <b>Smith</b>: "You just need to have the gears to be able to go up and down (when asked about his current form). The atmosphere is good within the team. The pitch looks pretty good, bit of grass on it. Hopefully it will stay even for 40 overs. We are going to bowl. We think we have been chasing pretty well. Every day is a new day, you've got to treat it like that. Same XI for us."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Warner</b>: "It was a fantastic response by our bowlers (in the last game), especially after the first game. Looks a nice wicket, it's going to stay the same throughout the 40 overs. You just have to keep playing your game and back your strengths. The toss is irrelevant I think. We've got Kane (<b>Williamson</b>) out, (Eoin) <b>Morgan</b> in."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Toss time</b> folks!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather Report:</b>  It has been a sunny day at Vizag. No clouds around, that removes chances of any rain. The humidity is expected to be around 84%. A cool breeze is expected to blow across the ground.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-Head record:</b> The two teams have met each other 5 times since the change of management in the Hyderabad franchise. Rajasthan enjoy a 3-2 winning advantage.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Boasting of a powerful bowling line-up, the Hyderabad have had the luxury of dropping a world class bowler in Dale Steyn. Skipper, <b>David Warner</b> has made his preference clear and believes that Boult deserves to play ahead of Steyn - on current form. "Trent is bowling just ahead of Dale now. We will definitely use Dale in the tournament. At the moment Trent is going fantastic, so Dale just misses out," he said, ahead of today's match.]]></line><line><![CDATA[After a below par performance against CHN, Hyderabad were a completely different outfit against BLR. The bowlers responded to the skipper's call, restricting the powerful batting line-up of the Challengers to 166. Trent Boult took 3 wickets in an over and Ravi Bopara chipped in with a couple of crucial strikes. 167 was a tricky target to chase - but David Warner took the wind out of BLR's sails, smashing a 27-ball 57. He was well supported by Shikhar Dhawan and HYD romped home by 8 wickets and with 16 deliveries to spare.]]></line><line><![CDATA[While the batting has been sublime, the bowlers have more or less kept things under the lid. Tim Southee has been expensive at times, but the rest of the bowling unit have made up for his rather lacklustre show. While Chris Morris has been the pick of the pacers, 43-year old Pravin Tambe continues to belie expectations. Can they rock the Hyderabad boat? On form, they should.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Motivated by Rahul Dravid and led superbly by stand-in captain Steven Smith, Rajasthan have become the team to beat in the early stages of the tournament. Such has been their dominance that the absence of regular captain, Shane Watson, has largely gone unnoticed. Ajinkya Rahane has settled on his anchor role, Sanju Samson has improved leaps and bounds, particularly in the keeping department while Smith himself has been a revelation and has continued to pile on the runs. Deepak Hooda has announced himself to the world in sensational fashion.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Match 11 of the Indian Premier League and it pits the unbeaten Rajasthan against the Hyderabad. The Rajasthan have had a wonderful run so far in the tournament, blitzing aside their opponents and are well placed with six points from three matches. On the other hand, Hyderabad started with a stutter, losing badly to Chennai. But they rebounded in spectacular fashion, going past Bangalore, in their second match.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/>Hyderabad will have little time to dwell on their comfortable eight-wicket win against Bangalore since they will be hosting Rajasthan, who are on a three-match winning streak. David Warner and his men would be engulfed by a stiffer challenge when the two teams meet in Match 11 of the Pepsi Indian Premier League at Visakhapatnam on Thursday.<br/><br/>The outcome will not be an easy one to predict but Rajasthan seem to have the edge solely due to the fact that they've been unbeaten and that two of their three wins have been convincing.<br/><br/>Hyderabad haven't been shoddy. After being at the receiving end of Brendon McCullum's assault in their first game, they did well to bounce back against Bangalore on their home turf. They bowled out a batting-heavy BLR unit for 166 and gunned the target down with 16 deliveries left. David Warner has a half-century in both matches while Shikhar Dhawan announced his arrival with a fifty of his own. Not often does one find Dale Steyn warming the bench, an indication that Trent Boult has grabbed the brass ring as the fast bowling spearhead.<br/><br/>When an unchanged team takes the field in three matches in-a-row, it means everything is boding well. Rajasthan' upbeat spirit is an evidence of their clinical display on the field. After brushing aside Punjab by 26 runs in their opening game, Rajasthan emerged victorious over Delhi in a humdinger. Their most recent win - a breezy seven-wicket victory over Mumbai - has made them the team to reckon with. With their top order contributing and skipper Steve Smith leading from the front, Rajasthan don't seem to put a foot wrong in IPL 2015.<br/><br/><b>Venue:</b> Dr. Y.S. Rajasekhara Reddy ACA-VHYDA Cricket Stadium<br/><br/><b>Date:</b> April 16, 2015 <br/><br/><b>Time:</b> 2000 IST<br/><br/><b>Weather:</b> Clear sky with a maximum of 35 degree Celsuis<br/><br/><b>Teams:</b><br/><br/><b>Hyderabad</b><br/><br/>"Never alter a winning combination", they say. After the debacle against Chennai, Hyderabad got their team composition right. Swapping Ishant Sharma with Praveen Kumar proved to be sensible. Expect the Uttar Pradesh seamer to retain his place. Ashish Reddy and Parvez Rasool may be fighting for a spot but both players did not make the most of the opportunities they got. However, if HYD opt for the J&K allrounder, Rasool will need to bat higher.<br/><br/>Probable XI: 1 David Warner (captain), 2 Shikhar Dhawan, 3 Kane Williamson, 4 KL Rahul, 5 Naman Ojha (wicket-keeper), 6 Ravi Bopara, 7 Ashish Reddy/Parvez Rasool, 8 Karn Sharma, 9 Praveen Kumar, 10 Bhuvneshwar Kumar, 11 Trent Boult.<br/><br/><b>Rajasthan</b><br/><br/>Since Shane Watson's recovery from injury doesn't seem complete, Rajasthan do not need to change their winning team. Sanju Samson's struggle at the top may be a concern. The management might be tempted to push Karun Nair up the order and play Samson in the middle-order.<br/><br/>Probable XI: 1 Ajinkya Rahane, 2 Karun Nair, 3 Steven Smith (captain), 4 Sanju Samson (wicket-keeper), 5 Deepak Hooda, 6 Stuart Binny, 7 James Faulkner, 8 Chris Morris, 9 Tim Southee, 10 Dhawal Kulkarni, 11 Pravin Tambe.<br/><br/><b>Quotes:</b><br/><br/>Trent Boult has been in fantastic form. He was the best bowler in the World Cup, behind Mitchell Starc. The conditions suited him here and in the last game. Trent is bowling just ahead of Dale [Steyn] now. We will definitely use Dale in the tournament, but at the moment Trent is going fantastic - David Warner on preferring Trent Boult over Dale Steyn in the Playing XI.<br/><br/>Not 100 percent sure yet, but he's recovering fast. Hopefully we'll see him on the field soon - Steven Smith on Shane Watson's fitness.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajasthan</b> (From): Ajinkya Rahane, Sanju Samson(w), Steven Smith(c), Karun Nair, Deepak Hooda, Stuart Binny, James Faulkner, Chris Morris, Tim Southee, Dhawal Kulkarni, Pravin Tambe, Rajat Bhatia, Abhishek Nayar, Ben Cutting, Dishant Yagnik, Vikramjeet Malik, Ankit Sharma, Rahul Tewatia, Dinesh Salunkhe, RustyTheron, Pardeep Sahu, Brainder Sran, Sagar Trivedi]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hyderabad</b> (From): Shikhar Dhawan, David Warner(c), Kane Williamson, Lokesh Rahul, Naman Ojha(w), Ravi Bopara, Ashish Reddy, Karn Sharma, Praveen Kumar, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Trent Boult, Dale Steyn, Ishant Sharma, Moises Henriques, Parvez Rasool, Ricky Bhui, Chama Milind, Kevin Pietersen, Eoin Morgan, Laxmi Shukla, Hanuma Vihari, Prasanth Padmanabhan, Siddarth Kaul]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>127</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>5</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Hyderabad">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1739</playerid>
					<name>David Warner</name>
					<batsman-name>Warner</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Warner</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>21</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ajinkya Rahane</fielder>
						<fielderId>1447</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1446</playerid>
					<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhawan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhawan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>10</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>D Kulkarni</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1451</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sanju Samson</fielder>
						<fielderId>8271</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8733</playerid>
					<name>Lokesh Rahul</name>
					<batsman-name>Rahul</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rahul</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>D Kulkarni</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1451</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1599</playerid>
					<name>Naman Ojha</name>
					<batsman-name>N Ojha</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>N Ojha</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>25</runs>
					<balls>32</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Tambe</bowler>
					<bowlerId>9237</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>624</playerid>
					<name>Eoin Morgan</name>
					<batsman-name>E Morgan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Eoin Morgan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>27</runs>
					<balls>30</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Tambe</bowler>
					<bowlerId>9237</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>571</playerid>
					<name>Ravi Bopara</name>
					<batsman-name>R Bopara</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bopara</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>23</runs>
					<balls>19</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6301</playerid>
					<name>Ashish Reddy</name>
					<batsman-name>Ashish Reddy</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ashish Reddy</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>13</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1844</playerid>
					<name>Karn Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Karn Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Karn Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>592</playerid>
					<name>Praveen Kumar</name>
					<batsman-name>P Kumar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>P Kumar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1726</playerid>
					<name>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</name>
					<batsman-name>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8117</playerid>
					<name>Trent Boult</name>
					<batsman-name>T Boult</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Boult</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1446</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>25</runs>
				<overs>3.6</overs>
				<batsman>Shikhar Dhawan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dhawan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1739</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>35</runs>
				<overs>5</overs>
				<batsman>David Warner</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Warner</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8733</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>35</runs>
				<overs>5.1</overs>
				<batsman>Lokesh Rahul</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rahul</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1599</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>87</runs>
				<overs>14.1</overs>
				<batsman>Naman Ojha</batsman>
				<batsman-name>N Ojha</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>624</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>96</runs>
				<overs>16.3</overs>
				<batsman>Eoin Morgan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>E Morgan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>1</byes>
			<wides>4</wides>
			<noballs>1</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>6</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Rajasthan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1057</playerid>
					<name>Tim Southee</name>
					<bowler-name>Southee</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Southee</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>30</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8333</playerid>
					<name>Chris Morris</name>
					<bowler-name>C Morris</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>C Morris</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>23</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9427</playerid>
					<name>Deepak Hooda</name>
					<bowler-name>Deepak Hooda</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Deepak Hooda</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>11</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1451</playerid>
					<name>Dhawal Kulkarni</name>
					<bowler-name>D Kulkarni</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>D Kulkarni</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>9</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7789</playerid>
					<name>James Faulkner</name>
					<bowler-name>Faulkner</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Faulkner</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>20</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1530</playerid>
					<name>Stuart Binny</name>
					<bowler-name>Binny</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Binny</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>12</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9237</playerid>
					<name>Pravin Tambe</name>
					<bowler-name>Tambe</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Tambe</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>21</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1447</playerid>
					<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
					<bowler-name>A Rahane</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rahane</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8271</playerid>
					<name>Sanju Samson</name>
					<bowler-name>Samson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Samson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2250</playerid>
					<name>Steven Smith</name>
					<bowler-name>S Smith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Smith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8257</playerid>
					<name>Karun Nair</name>
					<bowler-name>Nair</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nair</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>131</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>4</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Rajasthan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1447</playerid>
					<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
					<batsman-name>A Rahane</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rahane</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>62</runs>
					<balls>56</balls>
					<fours>9</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>T Boult</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8117</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8271</playerid>
					<name>Sanju Samson</name>
					<batsman-name>Samson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Samson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>26</runs>
					<balls>30</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>R Bopara</bowler>
					<bowlerId>571</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Naman Ojha</fielder>
						<fielderId>1599</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2250</playerid>
					<name>Steven Smith</name>
					<batsman-name>S Smith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Smith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>13</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Karn Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1844</bowlerId>
						<fielder>David Warner</fielder>
						<fielderId>1739</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8257</playerid>
					<name>Karun Nair</name>
					<batsman-name>Nair</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nair</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>R Bopara</bowler>
					<bowlerId>571</bowlerId>
						<fielder>R Bopara</fielder>
						<fielderId>571</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1530</playerid>
					<name>Stuart Binny</name>
					<batsman-name>Binny</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Binny</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>16</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7789</playerid>
					<name>James Faulkner</name>
					<batsman-name>Faulkner</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Faulkner</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9427</playerid>
					<name>Deepak Hooda</name>
					<batsman-name>Deepak Hooda</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Deepak Hooda</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8333</playerid>
					<name>Chris Morris</name>
					<batsman-name>C Morris</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>C Morris</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1057</playerid>
					<name>Tim Southee</name>
					<batsman-name>Southee</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Southee</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1451</playerid>
					<name>Dhawal Kulkarni</name>
					<batsman-name>D Kulkarni</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>D Kulkarni</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9237</playerid>
					<name>Pravin Tambe</name>
					<batsman-name>Tambe</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Tambe</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8271</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>64</runs>
				<overs>10.2</overs>
				<batsman>Sanju Samson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Samson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>2250</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>84</runs>
				<overs>13.2</overs>
				<batsman>Steven Smith</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Smith</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8257</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>91</runs>
				<overs>14.4</overs>
				<batsman>Karun Nair</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Nair</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1447</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>118</runs>
				<overs>18.4</overs>
				<batsman>Ajinkya Rahane</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Rahane</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>1</byes>
			<wides>4</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Hyderabad">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1726</playerid>
					<name>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</name>
					<bowler-name>Bhuvneshwar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bhuvneshwar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8117</playerid>
					<name>Trent Boult</name>
					<bowler-name>T Boult</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Boult</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>31</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>592</playerid>
					<name>Praveen Kumar</name>
					<bowler-name>P Kumar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>P Kumar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>30</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1844</playerid>
					<name>Karn Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Karn Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Karn Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>19</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>571</playerid>
					<name>Ravi Bopara</name>
					<bowler-name>R Bopara</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bopara</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>18</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6301</playerid>
					<name>Ashish Reddy</name>
					<bowler-name>Ashish Reddy</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ashish Reddy</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>5</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1446</playerid>
					<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhawan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhawan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1739</playerid>
					<name>David Warner</name>
					<bowler-name>Warner</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Warner</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8733</playerid>
					<name>Lokesh Rahul</name>
					<bowler-name>Rahul</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rahul</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1599</playerid>
					<name>Naman Ojha</name>
					<bowler-name>N Ojha</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>N Ojha</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>624</playerid>
					<name>Eoin Morgan</name>
					<bowler-name>E Morgan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Eoin Morgan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



