<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14648" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>55th Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Bangalore</home>
		<away>Delhi</away>
		<teamsabbr>BLR vs DEL</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>BLR</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>DEL</awayabbr>
		<homeId>59</homeId>
		<awayId>61</awayId>
		<venue>M.Chinnaswamy Stadium, Bengaluru</venue>
		<startdate>17 05 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>17 05 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Bangalore</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>No result</status>
		<result type="no result">
			<winningteam></winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Kumar Dharmasena</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Krishnamachari Srinivasan</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Pashchim Pathak</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Ranjan Madugalle</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>10:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150517141207</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>BLR</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>DEL</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>2</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>0</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>1.1</batteamovers>
		<status>No result</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>1413</playerid>
			<name>Virat Kohli</name>
			<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Kohli</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>1</runs>
			<balls-faced>2</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>247</playerid>
			<name>Chris Gayle</name>
			<batsman-name>Gayle</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Gayle</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>1</runs>
			<balls-faced>5</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>71</playerid>
			<name>Zaheer Khan</name>
			<bowler-name>Zaheer</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Zaheer</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>0.1</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>0</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>8182</playerid>
			<name>Jayant Yadav</name>
			<bowler-name>Jayant Yadav</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Jayant Yadav</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>1</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>2</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>188</target>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>0</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>0</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[. 1 . . . 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/BLR_DEL_MAY17/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[<b>19:39 Local Time, 14:09 GMT:</b> Unfortunately, unrelenting rain has forced the game to be <b>called off</b>. <b>BLR qualify for the playoffs</b> and in all likelihood, they will play Rajasthan in the first eliminator. With no rain on the radar in Hyderabad, the winner of the game between HYD and MUM will qualify as the second ranked team, meaning they will get an extra opportunity to reach the finals. The loser though will bow out of the tournament and hence, both teams will give it their all to try and win it. Switch tabs to follow the action from that game.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>19:20 Local Time, 13:50 GMT:</b> The cut-off time for a 5-over game is <b>20:07</b> local time.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:58 Local Time, 13:28 GMT:</b> Just about when we were getting ready for the resumption, the drizzle is back. The covers are back on and we will definitely start losing overs now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:47 Local Time, 13:17 GMT, 18:47 IST:</b> Russell Arnold has tweeted that there might be a <b>7 PM start</b> if there is no more rain. No overs will be lost either. We have a confirmation that the game will resume at <b>19:00</b> local time.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:35 Local Time, 13:05 GMT:</b> The covers are coming off, but the outfield is still wet. The groundstaff will definitely take some time to get it all ready. There will be an official inspection at <b>18:45 local time</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:24 Local Time, 12:54 GMT:</b> Good news folks! It has stopped raining at the Chinnaswamy. Meanwhile, the official IPL twitter account has tweeted this: The pitch inspection, which is likely to be at about 19:00, will involve some very muddy boots! #BLRvsDEL #IPL]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:21 Local Time, 12:51 GMT:</b> The super soppers are currently working hard at the ground. Right now, it's just a light drizzle.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:10 Local Time, 12:40 GMT:</b> Our man, Mani is at the ground. He tells us that the rain eased off for a little while, but now it has once again become heavy.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>17:59 Local Time, 12:29 GMT:</b> Rain has stopped play. There was a drizzle in the air, but suddenly it turned into a heavy downpour. The groundstaff have covered the pitch and currently working to cover the square as well. The <b>par score for BLR after 5 overs is 39 if they don't lose a wicket</b>. Remember, Duckworth-Lewis can only be taken into consideration after 5 overs have been bowled in this innings.]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Gayle, no run, bowls a low full toss that was tailing in towards the pads, Gayle was looking to play it into the on-side, but the ball rolls away to mid-off off the outside half of the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[A slip in place for Zaheer]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Zaheer Khan, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Gayle, 1 run, flatter and drifting in on middle stump line, Gayle pushes it into the mid-wicket region and gets off strike with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Gayle, no run, pushed through on middle and leg, Gayle turns it towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Gayle, no run, darted on the pads, Gayle kneels down and looks to sweep, he misses and the ball hits him on the pad, there was half an appeal from the keeper and the bowler, but it was definitely going down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Gayle, no run, touch quicker and on off, Gayle defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[Comes from round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[Long-on and deep mid-wicket are the two fielders out for Gayle. A slip has been put in place too.]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Kohli, 1 run, drifting in on middle and leg, Kohli clips it towards square leg, where Yuvraj dives to his left and stops the ball, can't prevent the single though]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Kohli, no run, flatter and just outside off, Kohli goes on the back foot and nudges it into the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kohli and Gayle are at the crease. Kohli is on strike. Jayant Yadav will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ohh, wait a minute! Looks like the rain is not going to play spoilsport for now. Even though it's raining near the ground, there's nothing major going on at the stadium. Kohli and Gayle walk out to the centre. Jayant Yadav will open the bowling. No slips in place for now. Here we go then...]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>17:52 Local Time, 12:22 GMT, 17:52 IST:</b> The rain has become heavier at the moment and we might well have a delay here.]]></line><line><![CDATA[There is a slight drizzle at the Chinnaswamy. Nothing strong but the groundstaff have kept the covers near the pitch as a precautionary measure. They will cover the pitch if the rain becomes heavier.]]></line><line><![CDATA[BLR would back themselves to chase down the target on a flat deck and climb to second spot in the points table.  There is a threat of rain playing spoilsport as well. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Quinton de Kock and JP Duminy's  sterling knocks took DEL to a good score. It was de Kock and Duminy who strung together an enterprising stand to keep the scorecard moving. However, in the nick of time, Harshal Patel and Yuzvendra Chahal chipped in with crucial wickets to put the brakes on the scoring rate. Mitchell Starc also made his presence felt by bowling economically up front. It was Duminy then, who played fine shots in the slog overs to up the ante. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to S Tiwary, 1 run, low full toss down leg and following the backing away Tiwary, driven to long-on. They are content with just a single as the fielder is AB]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Duminy, 1 run, very well bowled. Yorker on middle, Duminy jams it out near short mid-wicket, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Duminy, 2 runs, low full toss, hit straight down the ground, AB covers a lot of ground and slides to prevent the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Duminy, <b>FOUR</b>, short on the stumps and Duminy pulls for four. Backs away and gets it to deep square leg, one bounce over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Duminy, 2 runs, full and outside off, Duminy makes room and slices it over the infield, Sarfraz runs back to keep it to two]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to S Tiwary, 1 run, full and angling in, Tiwary heaves and gets a thick inside edge to fine leg, wants two but Duminy sends him back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to S Tiwary, 1 run, very full and on the stumps, Tiwary drives to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to S Tiwary, <b>SIX</b>, now Tiwary gets six. These slower balls are sitting up for the batsmen, Tiwary stays in his crease and then biffs it flat over the sightscreen. The Delhi camp are happy. Much needed blows these]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Duminy, leg byes, 1 run, Harshal Patel follows Duminy who was going for the big hit once again, Duminy swings and misses, they take a leg bye as the ball goes down the track]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Duminy, <b>FOUR</b>, again over cover. No-one there as Harshal Patel bowls full and on the stumps, Duminy backs away and crashes the lofted drive into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Duminy, <b>FOUR</b>, Kohli not happy with Harshal Patel, it was another short delivery, Duminy pulls behind square and beats Starc to his left at deep backward square leg, one bounce over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Duminy, no run, that was close. The slower delivery from Harshal Patel, from round the wicket, Duminy swings and misses, not far from the off stump]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel [3.0-0-15-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Duminy, 1 run, short on the stumps, Duminy controls the hook and sends it to deep backward square leg. Gets to <b>fifty</b> in the process]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Duminy, <b>FOUR</b>, no-one in the deep on the off-side and that's the price Starc pays for bowling a foot short of yorker length, Duminy makes room and drives wide of cover and that will do nicely]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Duminy, 2 runs, low full toss on the stumps, flicked to deep mid-wicket, AB runs around and keeps it to two]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to S Tiwary, 1 run, full outside off, flat-batted drive but straight to the fielder at long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[It has gotten dark and the groundstaff are moving around]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Duminy, 1 run, yorker length on middle and leg, dug out to square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Duminy, no run, very full and on the stumps, angling down, Duminy flicks and gets an inside edge onto the pads]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc [2.0-0-15-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Duminy, 1 run, short and wide outside off, mistimed cut square of the wicket, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to S Tiwary, 1 run, high full toss outside off, Tiwary just pats it down to long-off, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Duminy, 1 run, full outside off, driven to extra cover, Dinda dives to field that inside the circle]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to S Tiwary, 1 run, short of length on the stumps, whipped to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Duminy, 1 run, on the pads, nudged through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Duminy, 2 runs, slower delivery outside off, Duminy gets forward and drives to deep backward point, Chahal slides to his right from sweeper and keeps it to a couple]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese [3.0-0-32-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to S Tiwary, no run, Tiwary comes down the track and drives along the ground, finds cover though]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Duminy, 1 run, googly, turns away, cut square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to S Tiwary, 1 run, full on the stumps, clipped through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Duminy, 1 run, turning in, Duminy shuffles across and nudges to backward square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Saurabh Tiwary, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Duminy, <b>out</b> Mathews Run Out!! Unfortunate for Mathews but that's a way of getting out in this game. Drilled hard and low to Chahal's right who deflected it onto the stumps. Mathews' bat was in the air when the ball hit the stumps. Third umpire confirms the decision. <b>Mathews run out (Chahal) 1(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chahal to Duminy, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Has Chahal got Mathews out? Appeal for a run-out. Third umpire called for. Looks like Mathews' bat is in the air. Definitely Chahal touched it. Mathews could be gone. Yes Mathews' bat is in the air]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Duminy, no run, low full toss outside off, Duminy gets forward and cracks the drive but straight to the fielder at cover at the edge of the circle]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Timeout</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Duminy, leg byes, 1 run, angling in and full on the stumps, Duminy misses the flick, takes a leg bye, would've gone down]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Mathews, 1 run, full toss on the stumps, Mathews wrists it to long-on, to get off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Mathews, no run, the slower short ball outside off, Mathews drops his wrists and lets it go. Called one short ball for the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Mathews, no run, very full outside off, jammed out to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Angelo Mathews, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to K Jadhav, <b>out</b> Caught by D Karthik!! Kedar Jadhav falls for a golden duck. Second short and wide delivery outside off that has got a wicket today. Jadhav gets a cue-ender on the cut. Walks without even looking back at the umpire. <b>K Jadhav c D Karthik b Harshal Patel 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Harshal Patel to K Jadhav, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[It is currently bright and sunny]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Duminy, 1 run, short of length on middle and leg, clipped to deep square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel [2.0-0-13-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Duminy, 1 run, the googly from Chahal, Duminy gets forward and wrists it to long-on, for a single. 20 off the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kedar Jadhav, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Yuvraj, <b>out</b> Caught by Starc at long-off!! Yuvraj goes trying for consecutive sixes. Bowled slower outside off, Yuvraj swung but mistimed it, Starc settles under the skier inches from the rope and takes it well. <b>Yuvraj c Starc b Chahal 11(7) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chahal to Yuvraj, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Yuvraj, <b>SIX</b>, that is simply superb from Yuvraj. A little shimmy down the track and just a flick of the wrists, nothing more but what power packed into those wrists. Sails into the crowd at deep mid-wicket. Third six of the over and effortless from Yuvraj]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Duminy, 1 run, Chahal pulls his length back, short outside off, cut to backward point, stopped with a dive]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Duminy, <b>SIX</b>, make that two in a row. Not well-timed as the previous one, took it from outside off and went for the slog-sweep, gets enough bat to clear AB at deep mid-wicket, even mishits carry all the way here]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Duminy, <b>SIX</b>, magnificent sweep from Duminy. The wrong 'un, down leg, Duminy was onto it in a flash, down on his knees and sweeping it into the crowd at deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Duminy, 1 run, another slower delivery on off stump, Duminy shuffles across and flicks through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Duminy, no run, slower delivery outside off, driven straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Yuvraj, 1 run, full outside off, Yuvraj leans into a flowing drive to deep extra cover, Mandeep keeps it to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Duminy, 1 run, short on the stumps, pulled hard to deep mid-wicket, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Yuvraj, 1 run, short of length outside off, punched to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[Karthik is up to the stumps now]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Yuvraj, 2 runs, Yuvraj skips out and then punches the slower delivery to deep extra cover, for a couple]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese [2.0-0-26-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Yuvraj, 1 run, another short delivery, another toe-end on the pull, wide of mid-wicket. Yuvraj has a look at his bat after playing that. Is off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Yuvraj, no run, no flight from Chahal, outside off, Yuvraj defends off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Duminy, 1 run, flat and on the stumps, Duminy gets back to work it through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Duminy, no run, Duminy advances and looks to work it away, takes it on the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuvraj Singh, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to de Kock, <b>out</b> Caught by Kohli!! de Kock goes. May have been the wrong 'un from Chahal, tossed it up and gets it to turn away, de Kock skews the lofted hit over cover and Kohli running back takes a well-judged catch over his shoulder. <b>de Kock c Kohli b Chahal 69(39) [4s-9 6s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chahal to de Kock, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Duminy, 1 run, that kept low and Duminy's pull finds the toe-end, doesn't carry to deep mid-wicket. If Duminy had got it off the middle, it may have carried to the man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuzvendra Chahal, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to de Kock, <b>SIX</b>, de Kock is smashing them now. Full and on the stumps, allows de Kock to get under that and heave it over deep mid-wicket. Got the elevation required to go all the way. Dinda has given 18 off that over]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to de Kock, no run, de Kock looks for a repeat and gets a thick inside edge that bounces over the stumps, refuses the quick single as the ball goes to DK]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to de Kock, <b>SIX</b>, fabulous strike. de Kock picks the slower delivery from Dinda and gets forward to lift it way over long-on, came right out off the middle of the bat. Dinda proving to be expensive]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to de Kock, <b>FOUR</b>, that is unlucky for Dinda, low full toss outside off, de Kock gets a thick outside edge past the keeper, runs away beating third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to Duminy, 1 run, full outside off, Duminy heaves and gets a thick inside edge onto the pads, runs away towards the keeper, quick single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to de Kock, 1 run, low full toss outside off, slapped square of the wicket, but straight to the fielder]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashok Dinda [2.0-0-21-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Duminy, 2 runs, very full outside off, jammed out square of the wicket, Chahal fumbles on the slide and that allows the second to be taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Duminy, no run, just inside the tramline as Duminy lets it go outside off, looks at Dharma for a wide, the umpire shakes his head and tells him it was a legal delivery]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to de Kock, 1 run, very full outside off, jammed out to sweeper cover, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Duminy, 1 run, Gayle slows it up and on the stumps, worked to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Duminy, <b>SIX</b>, Duminy stands and delivers over long-on. Sees the full delivery outside off and then tonks it over long-on. Went all the way. Clean hit]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Duminy, <b>wide</b>, very flat down leg, left alone, called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to de Kock, leg byes, 1 run, fired in full and outside off, from round the wicket, de Kock reverse sweeps and misses, takes a leg bye]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to de Kock, 1 run, full outside off, de Kock drags the slog to deep backward square leg, went too hard at it and mistimed it. Still 18 off the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to de Kock, <b>FOUR</b>, de Kock is all smiles as he gets to <b>fifty</b>. Full on leg stump, de Kock heaves and clears the man at mid-wicket on the edge of the circle, once he beat the man it was always a boundary. Duminy comes up to him to congratulate]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to de Kock, <b>FOUR</b>, Wiese did well to get his shins out of that shot. de Kock picks the slower delivery and comes down the track to slap it flat past the legs of the bowler. No chance for long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to de Kock, <b>SIX</b>, just over deep mid-wicket's head. It was Starc and he is a tall man but de Kock gets it over. Starc was leaning back and stretching out but it just eluded him. de Kock stood tall and heaved it flat over mid-wicket. de Kock upping the ante now]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Duminy, 1 run, short of length outside off, dabbed with an open face to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Duminy, 2 runs, shortish on the hips, swatted away to deep backward square leg, for a couple]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese [1.0-0-8-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Duminy, 1 run, tucked off the pads to deep square leg, Mandeep runs forward and prevents the batsmen from taking two. Again good work from BLR in the field]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to de Kock, 1 run, hurrying onto de Kock who pulls to deep mid-wicket, didn't time that at all]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to Duminy, 1 run, full toss, Duminy takes a step out and hits it straight down the ground, AB quickly slides to his right at long-off and keeps it to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to de Kock, 1 run, Gayle follows de Kock who was making room, slapped straight to the fielder at long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to de Kock, no run, de Kock comes down the track and looks to work it away, off the pads as he misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gayle to de Kock, no run, chance for a run-out but the throw came late to the bowler, Duminy gets back safely, de Kock flicked and missed, would've gone down and Duminy tried to steal a leg bye to short third]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Gayle, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to de Kock, 1 run, de Kock was shaping initally for the reverse paddle then shimmied back into his crease, drives it past the diving cover, but AB is there to keep it to a single at long-off. Excellent fielding]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to de Kock, no run, slower ball bouncer, may have stopped on de Kock who mistimes the pull to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to de Kock, no run, back of a length outside off, cut to Gayle at point, but on the bounce this time]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Duminy, 1 run, angling in from round the wicket, tucked through backward square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jean-Paul Duminy, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Shreyas Iyer, <b>out</b> Caught by Gayle!! Straight to point. Short outside off, Shreyas Iyer cuts and doesn't keep it down, finds Gayle who reverse cups close to his face. First one down for Delhi. End of Shreyas Iyer's impressive season. <b>Shreyas Iyer c Gayle b Harshal Patel 20(18) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Harshal Patel to Shreyas Iyer, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Kohli had some words to say to his team during the timeout]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to de Kock, 1 run, slower delivery on off, de Kock drops it beside the crease and sets off, Shreyas Iyer responds and it's an easy single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel [1.0-0-10-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out.</b> Dharmasena doesn't like Starc's verbals at Shreyas Iyer. Dharma has a word with the smiling Starc]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Shreyas Iyer, no run, full on the stumps, Shreyas Iyer makes room and swings, mistimed to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to de Kock, 1 run, very full on the stumps, de Kock jams it out past the diving point, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to de Kock, <b>FOUR</b>, that is de Kock's area. Angling in on a fuller length into the legs of de Kock who clears his front leg and then heaves it flat over mid-wicket, one bounce over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, a thick leading edge to Sarfraz at cover-point, went to ground and they take a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Shreyas Iyer, <b>SIX</b>, first six of the innings. Shreyas Iyer this time makes room and then slices the full delivery over point. Went all the way, just about but that will do]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Shreyas Iyer, no run, beautiful delivery. Angles in on a fuller length and then moves away after landing, beating Shreyas Iyer's flat-footed drive, very close to the edge and not far from the off-stump]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc [1.0-0-3-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to de Kock, <b>FOUR</b>, too many slower deliveries from Wiese and de Kock puts him away. On a length outside off and allowed de Kock to free his arms, lofted over mid-off. Spoils the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, Wiese cramps Shreyas Iyer for room with a back of a length delivery outside off, mistimed cut in front of cover, quick single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to de Kock, 1 run, de Kock is shuffling across in his crease, makes room and then cuts the slower delivery to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, slower delivery outside off, dabbed with an open face to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Shreyas Iyer, no run, full outside off, Shreyas Iyer closes the face of the bat early on the flick, gets a thick leading edge that doesn't carry to Starc at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to de Kock, 1 run, length on middle and leg, turned with supple wrists to square leg, for an easy single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, poor from Dinda. Bowls a very full delivery outside off, giving Shreyas Iyer the width who crashes the drive beating AB's chase from cover. 16 off that over]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to Shreyas Iyer, 2 runs, length on the stumps, tucked through mid-wicket, takes on Starc and makes it with ease for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to de Kock, 1 run, dug in short outside off, de Kock fetches the pull from there and gets it to deep square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to de Kock, <b>FOUR</b>, this is good batting. de Kock makes room and advances down the track, takes the slower delivery on and creams the drive through cover. Consecutive boundaries]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to de Kock, <b>FOUR</b>, fine cut shot. It was short and wide outside off, but it rose on de Kock who flashed a cut beating point to his right. No chance for third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, length delivery on the stumps, Shreyas Iyer defends to mid-on and sets off. Easy single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, slower ball on off and middle, nudged through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Shreyas Iyer, no run, angling in, on a short of length, on middle and leg, Shreyas Iyer clips and misses, takes it on the thigh]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to de Kock, 1 run, off-speed delivery, bowled short outside off, cut to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dinesh Karthik is now up to the stumps, with a helmet on]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to de Kock, <b>FOUR</b>, de Kock charges Harshal Patel and hits the length delivery on the rise and splits point and cover-point. Was in the air but in the gap too]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now Harshal Patel round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to de Kock, no run, de Kock shuffles across well outside off and Harshal Patel changes the pace, bowls a slower delivery, de Kock looks to guide and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to de Kock, <b>FOUR</b>, superbly hit. Overpitched from Harshal Patel, outside off, smashed past mid-off and Shreyas Iyer did well to get out of that as it was heading straight at his legs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to Shreyas Iyer, no run, swing and a miss from Shreyas Iyer, shortish and moving away, rising too, Shreyas Iyer flashes hard and doesn't connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to de Kock, 1 run, slower delivery from Dinda, de Kock charges and swipes across the line, gets a thick edge that drops well in front of Starc at third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to de Kock, no run, big appeal for lbw by Dinda but de Kock was struck well outside off as he shuffled across on the pull and missed. Easy decision for the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, shortish outside off, cut away to third man, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to de Kock, 1 run, short of length on the stumps, tucked wide of backward square leg, Sarfraz runs around and dives to keep it to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[It is getting dark at the Chinnaswamy]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, short of length on off stump, Shreyas Iyer drops it in front of point and sets off, de Kock responds too, quick single taken]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dinda to Shreyas Iyer, <b>wide</b>, swing for Dinda, but starts well outside off and moves further away, called a wide after Shreyas Iyer leaves]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashok Dinda, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc starts off with a tight over]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to de Kock, no run, short of length outside off, de Kock defends to backward point and says 'no' for the quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to de Kock, <b>wide</b>, sliding down leg, called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to de Kock, no run, short of length on off stump, de Kock defends from the crease to point. Tight line from Starc]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to de Kock, no run, big inside edge onto the pads as de Kock tried to pull and then realised the short ball was getting big on him, he then tried to defend and got an big edge on the thigh]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, swing for Starc but starts on leg stump, Shreyas Iyer flicks and misses, no real appeal as the ball would've gone down leg, given as runs, not sure whether Iyer got an inside edge onto the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Shreyas Iyer, no run, pitched up outside off, Shreyas Iyer gets forward and opens the face of the bat on the square drive, but finds point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to de Kock, 1 run, short of length on off stump, softly nudged in front of square leg for an easy single. de Kock is off the mark]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>de Kock and Shreyas Iyer are at the crease. de Kock is on strike. Starc will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[de Kock and Iyer the openers. One slip and four men in on the off-side. Here we go...]]></line><line><![CDATA[The BLR team are in a huddle. Plenty of smiles in that camp. Out walk the umpires and the players. Once again worth a reminder - the BLR are in their green jerseys - part of their Go Green initiative. Starc will start off proceedings.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Delhi</b> (Playing XI): Quinton de Kock(w), Shreyas Iyer, Jean-Paul Duminy(c), Yuvraj Singh, Kedar Jadhav, Angelo Mathews, Saurabh Tiwary, Jayant Yadav, Shahbaz Nadeem, Zaheer Khan, Gurinder Sandhu]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore</b> (Playing XI): Chris Gayle, Virat Kohli(c), AB de Villiers, Mandeep Singh, Dinesh Karthik(w), Sarfaraz Khan, David Wiese, Harshal Patel, Mitchell Starc, Yuzvendra Chahal, Ashok Dinda]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Duminy:</b> 'We would have bowled first as well. Looks like a dry surface, we want to end the season on a high. We know we had a below par season. Unfortunately <b>Albie Morkel</b> pulled up sick this morning, he has been replaced by <b>Angelo Mathews</b>.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kohli:</b> 'We will bowl first. Might rain later on in the day. The ball will come better onto the bat later on in the night, here at the Chinnaswamy stadium. The pitch looks a bit dry. It's important to win this match, we will get an extra chance to qualify for the final, if we finish in the top two. These two points are very important. No team changes for us.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-Head record:</b>  BLR hold a 8-5 winning advantage over DEL but more importantly, they haven't lost to them in the last 5 matches. Can they keep the unbeaten record intact?]]></line><line><![CDATA[On the other hand, Delhi have nothing but pride to play for. They have had a mixed season. Uncapped opener, Shreyas Iyer, has been the bright spark while star Indian batsman, Yuvraj Singh, has been a major disappointment. Zaheer Khan's return has added solidity to the bowling unit. They will look to sign off the season on a high even as they look forward to the next IPL with renewed hopes.]]></line><line><![CDATA[We have spoken a lot about the weather and qualification scenarios. It's time to talk about the teams. Hosts BLR have hit a purple patch and seriously look like a team on the move. The top-3 have fired in unison, with each of them in the top-10 of the highest scorers list. Mitchell Starc has spruced up the bowling unit and the rest have been contributing handily. BLR always had a strong team on paper, but this time around, it has actually translated into on-field performances.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Today is the green match for BLR. An environmental conscious franchise, BLR play their final evening match of every season's IPL wearing their green outfit. For all weather enthusiasts, here's some good news. It is bright and sunny at the moment. The rain gods seems to have taken a breather. But you can never predict Bangalore's weather. As of now, we will be getting a full game.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Before going any further, here are the <b>qualification scenarios</b>. BLR have one foot in the playoffs. A win today and they are guaranteed second place behind CHN. A loss by a small margin will push them down to fourth and that will mean a place in the eliminator match, probably against Rajasthan. Can BLR crash out today? Well, it's a possibility but for that to happen, they need to be trounced by a massive margin. Considering their recent form, one can safely rule out this scenario. The other team watching this match with close interest will be Kolkata. For them to qualify, BLR must lose by a massive margin or the next game, between Hyderabad and Mumbai must end in a washout.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>14:50 Local Time, 09:20 GMT</b>: It's the last day of the league phase of IPL 2015 and there are still two spots up for grabs. Chennai and Rajasthan have assured themselves of a slot in the playoffs and the fight is now between four teams for the final two places. Hello and a warm welcome to one and all to Match 55. It's Bangalore hosting Delhi in the first match of the day.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/>Following Virat Kohli's final over exploits in Hyderabad, Bangalore head into their final league fixture against Delhi in a position of relative comfort. A win at home against Delhi, a team they've done well against in the recent past, will assure the Bangalore a top-two finish because of a vastly superior run-rate.<br/><br/>Delhi, with nothing to lose, can throw a wet blanket on BLR's aspirations and end the season on a high. Despite a seventh place finish, finishing with 12 points will be a step up from their performances in the last couple of seasons.<br/><br/>Playing matches in quick succession in the IPL can be a double-edged sword. While relentless travel can take its toll on player fatigue, teams on a roll speak highly about momentum sustenance and nothing can be more counterproductive than having to wait a while to play the next game. This however, will be BLR's fourth game of the week, having played at Mumbai, Mohali and Hyderabad in 5 days, and the team management will have workload management and player recovery at the top of their agenda as the IPL moves in to its critical phase.<br/><br/><b>Venue:</b> M Chinnaswamy Stadium, Bengaluru<br/><br/><b>Date:</b> May 17, 2015<br/><br/><b>Time:</b> 16:00 IST<br/><br/><b>Weather:</b> Partly cloudy with a 60% chance of rain<br/><br/><b>Team News:</b><br/><br/><b>Bangalore</b><br/><br/>Daniel Vettori and Co. have allowed Chris Gayle the liberty to sit out a couple of games this season in order to manage his chronic back problems. The brains trust of BLR are unlikely to offer the Jamaican a respite considering the magnitude of the game. Should Sreenath Aravind not recover in time from his finger injury, Ashoke Dinda or Varun Aaron might take the Indian pacer's slot.<br/><br/>Probable XI: Chris Gayle, Virat Kohli (c), AB de Villiers, Mandeep Singh, Dinesh Karthik (wk), Sarfaraz Khan, David Wiese, Harshal Patel, Mitchell Starc, Yuzuvendra Chahal, Ashoke Dinda/Varun Aaron.<br/><br/><b>Delhi</b><br/><br/>Albie Morkel excelled in his role as the fast-bowling all-rounder against Chennai in Raipur, a performance that should keep Angelo Mathews out for another game. While the performances of Zaheer Khan and the medium-pacers have been good, JP Duminy may want to bring back one of his leading spinners, Imran Tahir or Amit Mishra, considering the quality of batsmen in the opposition rank.<br/><br/>Probable XI: Quinton de Kock (wk), Shreyas Iyer, JP Duminy, Yuvraj Singh, Albie Morkel, Kedar Jadhav, Saurabh Tiwary, Jayant Yadav, Shahbaz Nadeem/Amit Mishra, Gurinder Sandhu/Nathan Coulter-Nile, Zaheer Khan<br/><br/><b>Stats and Trivia:</b><br/><br/>- BLR's big three- Virat Kohli (480), AB de Villiers (446) and Chris Gayle (422) - feature in the Top-10 run-getters chart for IPL 2015<br/><br/>- BLR have won just once in four games played with the green jersey (worn for the last home game of the season)<br/><br/><b>Quotes:</b><br/><br/>"Virat's batting form and his leadership has gone a long way for us to win pressure games in the tournament"<br/><br/>- Head coach Daniel Vettori spoke about Virat Kohli's influence in the team.<br/><br/>"I have told him on his face that he will be playing for India in the next two-three years"<br/><br/>- Delhi skipper JP Duminy was all praise for Shreyas Iyer, who he claims is an exciting prospect.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Delhi</b> (From): Quinton de Kock(w), Shreyas Iyer, Jean-Paul Duminy(c), Yuvraj Singh, Kedar Jadhav, Albie Morkel, Saurabh Tiwary, Nathan Coulter-Nile, Jayant Yadav, Amit Mishra, Zaheer Khan, Gurinder Sandhu, Imran Tahir, Shahbaz Nadeem, Manoj Tiwary, Mayank Agarwal, Angelo Mathews, Jaydev Unadkat, Chidhambaram Gautam, Travis Head, Srikar Bharat, Marcus Stoinis, Domnic Joseph, KK Jiyas]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore</b> (From): Virat Kohli(c), Chris Gayle, AB de Villiers, Mandeep Singh, Dinesh Karthik(w), Sarfaraz Khan, David Wiese, Harshal Patel, Mitchell Starc, Sreenath Aravind, Yuzvendra Chahal, Nic Maddinson, Varun Aaron, Ashok Dinda, Vijay Zol, Abu Nechim, Sandeep Warrier, Yogesh Takawale, Rilee Rossouw, Iqbal Abdulla, Manvinder Bisla, S Badrinath, Darren Sammy, Sean Abbott, Jalaj Saxena, Shishir Bhavane]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>187</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>5</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Delhi">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8520</playerid>
					<name>Quinton de Kock</name>
					<batsman-name>de Kock</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>de Kock</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>69</runs>
					<balls>39</balls>
					<fours>9</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Chahal</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7910</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Virat Kohli</fielder>
						<fielderId>1413</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9428</playerid>
					<name>Shreyas Iyer</name>
					<batsman-name>S Iyer</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shreyas Iyer</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>20</runs>
					<balls>18</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Harshal Patel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8175</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Chris Gayle</fielder>
						<fielderId>247</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>211</playerid>
					<name>Jean-Paul Duminy</name>
					<batsman-name>Duminy</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Duminy</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>67</runs>
					<balls>43</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>69</playerid>
					<name>Yuvraj Singh</name>
					<batsman-name>Yuvraj</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Yuvraj</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>11</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Chahal</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7910</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mitchell Starc</fielder>
						<fielderId>7710</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1851</playerid>
					<name>Kedar Jadhav</name>
					<batsman-name>K Jadhav</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>K Jadhav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Harshal Patel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8175</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dinesh Karthik</fielder>
						<fielderId>145</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1629</playerid>
					<name>Angelo Mathews</name>
					<batsman-name>Mathews</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mathews</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Yuzvendra Chahal</fielder>
						<fielderId>7910</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1601</playerid>
					<name>Saurabh Tiwary</name>
					<batsman-name>S Tiwary</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Tiwary</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>13</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8182</playerid>
					<name>Jayant Yadav</name>
					<batsman-name>Jayant Yadav</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Jayant Yadav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8501</playerid>
					<name>Gurinder Sandhu</name>
					<batsman-name>Gurinder Sandhu</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Gurinder Sandhu</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>71</playerid>
					<name>Zaheer Khan</name>
					<batsman-name>Zaheer</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Zaheer</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7906</playerid>
					<name>Shahbaz Nadeem</name>
					<batsman-name>S Nadeem</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Nadeem</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9428</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>55</runs>
				<overs>6.2</overs>
				<batsman>Shreyas Iyer</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Iyer</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8520</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>110</runs>
				<overs>11.2</overs>
				<batsman>Quinton de Kock</batsman>
				<batsman-name>de Kock</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>69</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>137</runs>
				<overs>13.5</overs>
				<batsman>Yuvraj Singh</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Yuvraj</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1851</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>139</runs>
				<overs>14.2</overs>
				<batsman>Kedar Jadhav</batsman>
				<batsman-name>K Jadhav</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1629</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>141</runs>
				<overs>15.2</overs>
				<batsman>Angelo Mathews</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mathews</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>3</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>6</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Bangalore">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7710</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
					<bowler-name>M Starc</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Starc</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1467</playerid>
					<name>Ashok Dinda</name>
					<bowler-name>Dinda</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dinda</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>39</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8175</playerid>
					<name>Harshal Patel</name>
					<bowler-name>Harshal Patel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Harshal Patel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>30</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8589</playerid>
					<name>David Wiese</name>
					<bowler-name>D Wiese</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Wiese</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>39</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>247</playerid>
					<name>Chris Gayle</name>
					<bowler-name>Gayle</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Gayle</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>15</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7910</playerid>
					<name>Yuzvendra Chahal</name>
					<bowler-name>Chahal</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chahal</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>26</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<bowler-name>Kohli</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Kohli</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>370</playerid>
					<name>AB de Villiers</name>
					<bowler-name>de Villiers</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>de Villiers</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6319</playerid>
					<name>Mandeep Singh</name>
					<bowler-name>Mandeep</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mandeep</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>145</playerid>
					<name>Dinesh Karthik</name>
					<bowler-name>D Karthik</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>D Karthik</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9429</playerid>
					<name>Sarfaraz Khan</name>
					<bowler-name>Sarfaraz Khan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sarfaraz Khan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>2</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>0</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>1.1</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Bangalore">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Kohli</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>247</playerid>
					<name>Chris Gayle</name>
					<batsman-name>Gayle</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Gayle</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>370</playerid>
					<name>AB de Villiers</name>
					<batsman-name>de Villiers</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>de Villiers</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6319</playerid>
					<name>Mandeep Singh</name>
					<batsman-name>Mandeep</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mandeep</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>145</playerid>
					<name>Dinesh Karthik</name>
					<batsman-name>D Karthik</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>D Karthik</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9429</playerid>
					<name>Sarfaraz Khan</name>
					<batsman-name>Sarfaraz Khan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sarfaraz Khan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8589</playerid>
					<name>David Wiese</name>
					<batsman-name>D Wiese</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Wiese</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7710</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
					<batsman-name>M Starc</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Starc</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8175</playerid>
					<name>Harshal Patel</name>
					<batsman-name>Harshal Patel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Harshal Patel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7910</playerid>
					<name>Yuzvendra Chahal</name>
					<batsman-name>Chahal</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chahal</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1467</playerid>
					<name>Ashok Dinda</name>
					<batsman-name>Dinda</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dinda</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>0</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>0</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Delhi">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8182</playerid>
					<name>Jayant Yadav</name>
					<bowler-name>Jayant Yadav</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Jayant Yadav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>2</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>71</playerid>
					<name>Zaheer Khan</name>
					<bowler-name>Zaheer</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Zaheer</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0.1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8520</playerid>
					<name>Quinton de Kock</name>
					<bowler-name>de Kock</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>de Kock</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9428</playerid>
					<name>Shreyas Iyer</name>
					<bowler-name>S Iyer</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shreyas Iyer</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>211</playerid>
					<name>Jean-Paul Duminy</name>
					<bowler-name>Duminy</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Duminy</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>69</playerid>
					<name>Yuvraj Singh</name>
					<bowler-name>Yuvraj</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Yuvraj</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1629</playerid>
					<name>Angelo Mathews</name>
					<bowler-name>Mathews</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mathews</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1851</playerid>
					<name>Kedar Jadhav</name>
					<bowler-name>K Jadhav</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>K Jadhav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1601</playerid>
					<name>Saurabh Tiwary</name>
					<bowler-name>S Tiwary</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Tiwary</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8501</playerid>
					<name>Gurinder Sandhu</name>
					<bowler-name>Gurinder Sandhu</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Gurinder Sandhu</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7906</playerid>
					<name>Shahbaz Nadeem</name>
					<bowler-name>S Nadeem</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Nadeem</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



