<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14624" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>28th Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Chennai</home>
		<away>Kolkata</away>
		<teamsabbr>CHN vs KOL</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>CHN</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>KOL</awayabbr>
		<homeId>58</homeId>
		<awayId>63</awayId>
		<venue>MA Chidambaram Stadium, Chennai</venue>
		<startdate>28 04 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>28 04 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Kolkata</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Chennai won by 2 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Chennai</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>2</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Vineet Kulkarni</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Rajesh Deshpande</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Richard Illingworth</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Javagal Srinath</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>14:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150428180954</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>KOL</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>CHN</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>132</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>9</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>20</batteamovers>
		<status>Chennai won by 2 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>140</playerid>
			<name>Brad Hogg*</name>
			<batsman-name>B Hogg</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>B Hogg</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>2</runs>
			<balls-faced>1</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>640</playerid>
			<name>Ryan ten Doeschate</name>
			<batsman-name>ten Doeschate</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>ten Doeschate</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>38</runs>
			<balls-faced>28</balls-faced>
			<fours>3</fours>
			<sixes>2</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>269</playerid>
			<name>Ashish Nehra*</name>
			<bowler-name>Nehra</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Nehra</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>38</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>242</playerid>
			<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
			<bowler-name>DJ Bravo</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>3</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>22</runs>
			<wickets>3</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>135</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>1858</playerid>
<name>Umesh Yadav</name>
<player-runs>0</player-runs>
<player-balls>1</player-balls>
<runs>116</runs>
<wicket-nbr>9</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>269</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Nehra</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>5</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[1 1 1 1 W1 L1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>W 2 L1 . W 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. 4 6 1 W 2 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. . . 6 4 4 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/CHN_KOL_APR28/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[Alrighty folks. That's it from this game. But the action continues tomorrow. It is Bangalore taking on Rajasthan at the Chinnaswamy. We can expect an exciting game as BLR are on a two match winning streak and RAJ are second on the points table. Will catch you all for that game. Until then, take care and Cya!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Let's take a look at some of the best tweets from this game.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Harsha Bhogle:</b> Just too many people to call on for MSD. Today spin from Ashwin, Jadeja, Raina. Bravo at the end. #CHN. #KOL slept a bit in the middle overs]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shahrukh Khan:</b> CHN played like the champs they are. Extremely deserving victors. We need to believe/play harder. Insha Allah. Nikal gayi  Chennai Express…]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ayaz Memon:</b>  Sterling effort by Ryan ten Doeschate, but more important is how Chennai defended a small total. Whistlepodu!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sanjay Manjrekar:</b>  KOL lost but happy for Ryan Tendoeschate.This should do his confidence a world of good. He has so much to offer to the #ipl2015.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Anurag Rekhi:</b>  #CHN gave the game to #KOL on platter but I guess &#KOL was fasting today #CHNvKOL #PepsiIPL]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bravo:</b> "I think it is a great team effort. I failed with the bat with 7 overs left and wanted to do something special. Well done to Mahi (Dhoni), he led the team very well and won us the game. That catch was really special one, it reminded me 4-5 years ago when I started playing international cricket. I still have it in me. I prepare myself to defend 14 off the last over and if anything is over 14, it is a bonus. This is the kind of situations I practise, bowling to McCullum and Pollard back home. We always play as a team."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his bowling figures of <b>3-0-22-3</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhoni:</b> "It's a fantastic victory. We didn't know what a good score is on this wicket. If you bat well, you could have got 160. Robin (Uthappa) got them off to a good start, but the bowlers did well to pull things back. Raina has done well for us and he bowls with a flatter trajectory. He rose to the occasion and bowled very well. I thought the bowlers did really well. We did drop two catches today, but we did field well. Russell's run-out was important for us. Brendon McCullum is lightning in the field, but we also have Raina, Faf and Jadeja. We just want to take one game at a time, keep doing well and moving. We need to keep winning and reach the quarter-finals and then take it from there."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Gambhir:</b> "Containing CHN to 134 was a commendable job. We should have chased it down, but the batsmen got stuck in the middle overs. With the start we got, we should have finished the game. It is a difficult pill to swallow. We can't afford to have those many runs at that stage of the innings, but Tendo tried hard. The bowlers have done a fantastic job to contain the opposition. One of the top 3 has to be there till the 15th over. We need batsmen getting 50s and 60s. We played too many dot balls and that is where we lost the match. We play them again in a couple of days and hope to turn it around."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier in the day, KOL's bowlers led by Hogg restricted the strong CHN batting line-up to a mere 134. The Australian bowled at the start and at the end, he kept it tight. For CHN, McCullum, Smith, Raina all got starts, but a handy innings from Faf saw them reach the total they got. These two sides meet again in a couple of days time and it will be KOL's home then.]]></line><line><![CDATA[As everyone expected CHN and Dhoni on that type of wicket is a formidable combination. Gambhir went off the second ball of the innings, but Uthappa came into his own and was looking good before he tried to take on Ashwin straightaway. After that, it was the spinners that spun a web around Suryakumar and Pathan. Raina rolled his arm and kept things quiet. When they need to up the ante, Bravo came on and varied it nicely. He also bowled the last over, where he had to defend 17 runs and he did the job for his side.]]></line><line><![CDATA[CHN players congratulate each other before heading towards the dugout. The KOL players come out and shake hands. It has been a superb match for CHN. With the win, they move on top of the points table, overtaking Rajasthan, while KOL remain in third position.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to ten Doeschate, <b>FOUR</b>, KOL fall short by 2 runs. <b>CHN register their 9th successive win at home.</b> Tendo fought hard, but he had just too much to do. Another full delivery outside off, ten Doeschate shimmies down the and drills it to the deep extra cover fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to ten Doeschate, <b>FOUR</b>, ten Doeschate is doing it fabulously for KOL. It was a full delivery outside off, Tendo charges down, gives himself some room and drives it square of the wicket, there was no one in the deep and he keeps KOL in the game]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to ten Doeschate, <b>SIX</b>, massive! Is there still life in the game? KOL need two more of those to win it. ten Doeschate was expecting the slower ball, waits and waits before tonking it over cow corner, the ball sails over the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to ten Doeschate, no run, Bravo has been simply brilliant, another off-cutter just outside off, ten Doeschate advances down the wicket and fails to make contact with the big shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhoni has removed his pads. That will make him move quicker.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to ten Doeschate, no run, second dot ball for Bravo, this is excellent bowling, again the change of pace deceives the batsman, ten Doeschate is way too early into the shot, misses it by a mile]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to ten Doeschate, no run, slower delivery which is short in length, ten Doeschate cracks the cut to sweeper cover, he doesn't take the single. He knows that he is the one who has to do it for KOL]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>17 runs required off the last over</b>. Can Tendo do it for KOL? Bravo to bowl the last over.]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to B Hogg, 2 runs, fullish and just outside off, Hogg moves away and drives it past the diving extra cover fielder, Jaddu mops up in the deep and the batsmen take two in the meantime]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Brad Hogg, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to U Yadav, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Knocked over! Umesh thought he wanted to go for the jugular. A length delivery in the slot, Umesh goes towards the leg-side and has a slog at that, he missed it completely and the ball hits the top of middle-stump. That was a mindless shot from Umesh, who had Tendo at the other end, he just had to rotate the strike. <b>U Yadav b Nehra 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nehra to U Yadav, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to ten Doeschate, 1 run, Nehra comes round the wicket, bowls the low full toss, ten Doeschate toe-ends the drive down the wicket, Nehra bends down and parries it to long-on, Tendo wanted two but Umesh was not interested, the throw comes to Dhoni and goes over the head, the duo think about the second then, but the back up was quite good. Dhoni was not too pleased with the throw]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to ten Doeschate, <b>SIX</b>, smashed! Tendo is not giving up yet. A length delivery right in the slot, ten Doeschate gets his front leg out of the way and hammers it over deep mid-wicket for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to ten Doeschate, <b>FOUR</b>, a nice juicy full toss and ten Doeschate cashes in. It was at a good height as well, ten Doeschate heaves it towards deep square leg, it almost went the distance. The TV umpire checked and confirmed that the ball bounced before the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to ten Doeschate, no run, top ball from Nehra, ten Doeschate was moving away to the leg-side, Nehra follows him with a yorker, Tendo can't get away from it, the ball hits his back leg and rolls away. The batsmen can't take the run as ten Doeschate was not playing a shot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to ten Doeschate, 1 run, the 6th slower delivery of the over, ten Doeschate goes for the hoick towards cow corner, the inside-edge rolls to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Chawla, <b>out</b> Caught by Dhoni!! Second of the over. CHN inch closer towards victory. Chawla goes without troubling the scorers. Once more it is the slower one that outfoxes the batsman, Chawla advances and goes for the loft, skies it straight up, Dhoni calls for it and takes it right next to the stumps. Bravo embraces him in a bear hug. Chawla's bottom hand comes off the bat as he played that. <b>Chawla c Dhoni b Dwayne Bravo 0(2)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dwayne Bravo to Chawla, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Chawla, no run, another off-cutter just outside off, Chawla was totally deceived for pace, is early into the shot and fails to make contact]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to ten Doeschate, leg byes, 1 run, 108.5kph slower delivery, ten Doeschate fails to connect with the nudge to the on-side, Chawla calls for the run, Bravo moves forward, picks the ball and fires it straight into ten Doeschate, who was running in a straight line]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to ten Doeschate, 2 runs, off-cutter around off, ten Doeschate nurdles it to square leg, Bravo goes chasing after the ball but can't prevent the batsmen taking two. The commitment of these CHN players is unbelievable]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Piyush Chawla, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to P Cummins, <b>out</b> Caught by Ravindra Jadeja!! Another one bites the dust. CHN running away with the game. Bravo has his second of the game. It was the off-speed delivery, Cummins clears his front leg and goes for the mighty heave, picks out Jadeja perfectly at deep mid-wicket. <b>P Cummins c Ravindra Jadeja b Dwayne Bravo 0(2)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Dwayne Bravo to P Cummins, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to P Cummins, leg byes, 1 run, loud shout for lbw, but the umpire just moves away. Nehra was pleading with the umpire, good length ball on the stumps, Cummins misses the flick, is struck just above the kneeroll, the ball rolls to third man. The only thing that would have saved him is the height]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pat Cummins, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to ten Doeschate, <b>out</b> A Russell Run Out!! 1 run completed. KOL are falling apart here. CHN have applied the choke superbly. It was banged in halfway down the wicket, ten Doeschate mistimes the pull to deep square leg, Jaddu runs to his left, picks it one-handed and throws it to Dhoni, who does the rest. It was Tendo's call as he was the one who called for two. Russell is not a happy man, he hits the bat on the ground as he walks off. <b>A Russell run out (Ravindra Jadeja/Dhoni) 4(4)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nehra to ten Doeschate, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire called in for a run-out check. Russell thinks he is out. So do the CHN players as they are all hugging Jadeja. He is OUT!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to A Russell, 1 run, shortish and just outside off, Russell slaps it to extra cover, Faf shies at the stumps, but Russell had made it]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to ten Doeschate, 1 run, pitched up just outside off, ten Doeschate walks across and lofts it to long-off, the bat turned in his hands and hence didn't get the timing right]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to A Russell, 1 run, full and on the sticks, Russell eases it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ashwin still in the dugout, doesn't seem like he is going to come on.]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to ten Doeschate, 1 run, straight on middle, ten Doeschate shuffles across and works it wide of mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashish Nehra [2.0-0-20-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The equation reads <b>40 off 4 overs</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to ten Doeschate, 1 run, short and just outside off, ten Doeschate makes room and cuts square of the wicket, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to A Russell, 1 run, rolls his fingers across the ball, Russell presses forward and dabs it to backward point, Tendo calls for a quick single and gets it easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to ten Doeschate, 1 run, ten Doeschate backs away and Bravo follows him, nurdled away to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to A Russell, 1 run, full delivery angling in on middle and leg, Russell drives it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Y Pathan, <b>out</b> Bowled!! The strangle is on. Pathan looks at the stumps in disbelief. Bravo is overjoyed as he does another one of his jigs. An off-cutter which is short in length, keeps a tad low as well, Pathan goes for the pull and under-edges it onto the stumps. CHN all over KOL at the moment. <b>Y Pathan b Dwayne Bravo 13(18)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dwayne Bravo to Y Pathan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to ten Doeschate, 1 run, starts with a slower one, ten Doeschate tickles it fine, MS moves across to his left and stops the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ashwin is seen coming out of the dressing room. He is sitting in the dugout right now. Had a ball in his hand and was giving it a rip with his injured finger. Looked fine from here.]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Y Pathan, 2 runs, short and width on offer, Pathan cracks the cut square of the wicket, Aparajith on as a substitute tides up in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to ten Doeschate, 1 run, back-of-the-hand slower delivery, ten Doeschate drops it in front of cover and picks up a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to ten Doeschate, no run, good length ball on the stumps, ten Doeschate goes back in the crease and defends to the right of Mohit, he collects it and Pathan was hurrying back to the crease as he was backing up]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Y Pathan, 1 run, slower delivery on the stumps, Pathan nurdles it to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to ten Doeschate, 1 run, for the nth time in this game it is Baz with the effort. Shortish and outside off, ten Doeschate cuts it towards backward point and takes off, Pathan rightly sends him back as Baz hits the sticks at the striker's end, ten Doeschate was diving in to make his ground. He put in the full length dive]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire called to check a run-out chance. Tendo is the man in question. He seems to be alright, Not Out shows the giant screen]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Y Pathan, 1 run, back of a length close to off, Pathan manages to run it down to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Y Pathan, 1 run, slower through the air, Pathan eases it to long-on and retains strike. There have been no boundaries hit for the last <b>43 balls</b>, that is a very long time in a T20 game]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Y Pathan, <b>wide</b>, darted down the leg-side, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to ten Doeschate, 1 run, bunted wide of cover, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to ten Doeschate, no run, <b>dropped!</b> It was a tough chance though, but for McCullum's class you expect him to take it. Floated up on the stumps, ten Doeschate comes down the track and whips it to short mid-wicket, Baz dives to his left and is not able to hang on. That ball was travelling]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to ten Doeschate, no run, worked to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to ten Doeschate, no run, stifled appeal for lbw, tossed up on middle, ten Doeschate plonks his foot forward and misses the nudge through the on-side, the ball was sliding down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Y Pathan, 1 run, fired outside off, Pathan goes hard on the drive, mistimes it to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to ten Doeschate, no run, Baz once again at it. He saved a couple there, shortish and outside off, ten Doeschate cuts it towards backward point, McCullum flies to his left and stops the ball from going any further]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Y Pathan, 1 run, again, the length is short and outside off, Pathan punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to ten Doeschate, 1 run, back of a length on off, ten Doeschate bunts it towards cover, wanted the single, but Pathan is not too keen, Raina runs across to his left and misfields, that allowed the duo to take the run]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Y Pathan, 1 run, too straight, on middle and leg, Pathan nurdles it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Y Pathan, <b>wide</b>, bouncer which is well over Pathan's head, square leg umpire calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ryan ten Doeschate, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Suryakumar Yadav, <b>out</b> Caught by Dwayne Bravo!! That's a stunner. Bravo enjoyed it and so did the crowd. The West Indian runs off in celebration. A wicket at the right time for CHN. Short delivery from Mohit, Yadav was hurried on the pull, he spoons it towards mid-on, Bravo runs all the way from long-on, dives forward and snaffles it with both hands. He made sure he had control on the ball when he hit the ground. The best part was even Faf was coming from mid-off, but he was not put off by that. Replays show that, he went with both hands but the ball got stuck in his left hand. <b>Suryakumar Yadav c Dwayne Bravo b Mohit Sharma 16(26) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mohit Sharma to Suryakumar Yadav, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Suryakumar Yadav, no run, back of a length around off, Yadav goes for the pull and misses, the ball sneaks under his bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma [1.0-0-14-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, too full and on the stumps, Yadav eases it to long-on and retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Suryakumar Yadav, no run, tossed up around off, Yadav works it towards mid-wicket, Baz keeps the batsmen at their respective ends]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Y Pathan, 1 run, Pathan goes back and steers it to short third man, Yadav sees that Nehra is the fielder and calls his partner through for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Y Pathan, no run, turns it gently to short mid-wicket, no chance for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, flighted outside off, driven away to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ashwin is going off the field. He injured his bowling finger and it started bleeding immediately. Hopefully, it is not serious as CHN need him today and for the rest of the tournament]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Suryakumar Yadav, 2 runs, <b>dropped!</b> Ashwin puts down the catch. Flatter and just outside off, Yadav goes back and punches it in the air towards cover, Ash dives to his right and spills it. He has hurt his finger in the process.]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[A slight hold up as Pathan has a drink. Don't understand why as the time-out was taken couple of overs ago.]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, floated up on off, Yadav kneels down and sweeps it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Suryakumar Yadav, no run, quicker and on the stumps, Yadav defends off the inner part of the bat to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Suryakumar Yadav, no run, flighted around off, Yadav defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Suryakumar Yadav, no run, goes for the drive and gets a thickish edge towards cover, Baz once more prevents the single being taken, he has been brilliant so far]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Suryakumar Yadav, no run, CHN's fielding has been top class. Yadav pushes it to the right of the bowler, Jadeja moves across quickly and makes a half stop, enough to stop the run]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Suryakumar Yadav, no run, tossed up around off, Yadav knocks it to the left of cover, he wanted the run but Pathan was not interested]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, this one is given more air, driven down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Y Pathan, 1 run, flighted delivery and well outside off, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Y Pathan, no run, dangerous from Pathan, pushed through flatter and just outside off, Pathan waits on it and looks to dab it very fine, almost edged it to Dhoni]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, flighted delivery and just outside off, punched past Baz at short mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Suryakumar Yadav, no run, full toss from Raina, Yadav was a tad over eager as he went hard on the drive and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Suryakumar Yadav, no run, tossed up and a hint of spin back into Yadav, dabbed towards short third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, this one is given more more air, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Y Pathan, 1 run, fraction short and just outside off, Pathan makes room and cuts it square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Y Pathan, no run, this one drifts back with the angle, Pathan prods forward and gets an inside edge towards silly mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Y Pathan, no run, Jadeja fires one onto Pathan's pads, turned towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, pushed through by Jadeja, worked away wristily behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Suryakumar Yadav, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Yadav presses forward and defends it in front of cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Y Pathan, 2 runs, pushed through by Ashwin, Pathan loses one hand off the handle as he went for the sweep, gets a top-edge that rolls away behind square on the on-side. Pathan is off the mark with a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Y Pathan, no run, tossed up and just outside off, Pathan presses forward defensively]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Y Pathan, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Pathan dabs it to the right of first slip, Faf gets across quickly and stops a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, Ashwin shortens his length and gets this one to break back into the batsman, he makes room and punches it uppishly through cover-point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Suryakumar Yadav, no run, flighted and just outside off, Yadav prods across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Yusuf Pathan, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to M Pandey, <b>out</b> Caught by Dwayne Bravo!! Poor cricket from Manish! Second wicket for Ashwin, this was tossed up slower and just outside off, Manish went for the big slog sweep, is done in by the turn and gets a thick top-edge. The ball goes high and towards deep mid-wicket where Bravo's waiting, he doesn't drop it and KOL have lost another set batsman. <b>M Pandey c Dwayne Bravo b Ashwin 15(20) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Ashwin to M Pandey, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Suryakumar Yadav, no run, tossed up by Jadeja, Suryakumar Yadav watches it all along and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Suryakumar Yadav, <b>FOUR</b>, nicely played by Suryakumar Yadav, pushed through flatter and just outside off, Yadav waited on it, opens the face of the bat at the last moment and guides it past first slip, Ashwin gives chase but it's one in vain]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Suryakumar Yadav, no run, pushed through by Jadeja, Yadav goes back and turns it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to M Pandey, 1 run, tossed up and on the stumps, eased down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, pushed through and just outside off, Suryakumar Yadav makes room and cuts it square past cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to M Pandey, 1 run, slower and just outside off, looked like it stopped on Manish, he was early into the push and nearly lobs it back at the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to M Pandey, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, punched down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to M Pandey, no run, fraction shorter and on Manish's pads, tucked towards leg slip where Raina makes a smart stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to M Pandey, no run, tossed up and breaking back into Manish, he was making room for the drive, looked ungainly as he got an inside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to M Pandey, no run, shout for LBW, but Manish was struck well outside off, he was pressing forward on the defensive push, this one was slower and spun back in, clips him on the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Yadav rolls his wrists and nudges it past leg-slip for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and a leg-slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Suryakumar Yadav, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Uthappa, <b>out</b> Caught by Brendon McCullum!! Sharp catch at short mid-wicket and Ashwin has struck first ball! This was tossed up and wider outside off, Uthappa went for the slog sweep, doesn't get hold of the shot and ends up hitting it straight to Baz, he doesn't drop those, a much needed break for CHN. Can they press further and cause panic in KOL's ranks? <b>Uthappa c Brendon McCullum b Ashwin 39(17) [4s-6 6s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Ashwin to Uthappa, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to M Pandey, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four</b>, split the gap between MS and Ashwin at first slip, both were ball watching, this was full and slanting across the right-hander, drew Manish into the lazy drive, the edge is found and it flies through the gap. Ashwin was at wide slip, if at all it was a chance, it should have been Dhoni's]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Uthappa, 1 run, pitched up and just outside off, Uthappa gets forward and dabs it in front of cover-point, calls for a quick single and gets it with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, overpitched and well outside off, Uthappa leans forward, presents the full face of the bat and lofts it over mid-off, almost went all the way, just one bounce and over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to M Pandey, 1 run, on a length and just outside off, Manish shuffles across and gets a bottom edge on the pull, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to M Pandey, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Manish makes room and punches it towards McCullum at cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to M Pandey, no run, short of a length and angling across the right-hander, sliced straight to RJ at backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashish Nehra [1.0-0-10-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to M Pandey, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, eased in front of mid-on for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to M Pandey, no run, width on offer from Mohit, Manish cracks it to the left of cover-point where McCullum makes a tumbling stop, saves four runs for his team, Manish wanted a run and has to rush back]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Uthappa, 1 run, much better from Mohit, more intent on this short ball, Uthappa looks to pull and it goes high off the bat, just a single back over the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, Mohit isn't learning here, he has only one man in the deep on the on-side, yet he bowls short and just outside off, Uthappa swivels across and helps it behind square on the on-side, a third successive boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, too short from Mohit, can't bowl with his pace, Uthappa was lunging forward, swivels across and pulls it over square leg for another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>drilled</b>, length ball on off, no pace either from Mohit, Uthappa picks up the length early and heaves it wide of mid-on for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to M Pandey, no run, the loopy bouncer from Pandey, Manish was way too early with his attempted cut, misses by a long way]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Uthappa, 1 run, very full and just outside off, Uthappa squeezes it to the right of mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pandey loses his run-up and aborts mid-way]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Uthappa, <b>wide</b>, Pandey strays in line and slips this one well down leg-side, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, this is turning out to be an expensive over, full and on the stumps, Uthappa uses the bottom hand to good effect and flicks it over mid-wicket for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Uthappa, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Uthappa closes the face of the bat and drives it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Uthappa, <b>SIX</b>, Uthappa is looking in excellent touch, length ball and on his pads, Uthappa gets forward, uses his wrists and flicks it handsomely over the mid-wicket fence, first six of the innings]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhoni is up to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to M Pandey, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, Manish swivels across and pulls it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Uthappa, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Uthappa plays with an angled bat and defends it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, fraction short and just outside off, Uthappa swivels across and pulls it high and over mid-wicket, a couple of bounces and over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to M Pandey, 1 run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, slashed away towards third man. Bravo fumbles but the batsmen decide against a second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Uthappa, 3 runs, outstanding from McCullum, on a good length and just outside off, Uthappa leans into the shot and punches it square through cover. Any other fielder and this would have been a boundary, McCullum hares after that and pulls it back in, saves a run for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Uthappa, 2 runs, tad fuller and just outside off, Uthappa leans forward and punches it past cover-point. Faf chases from mid-off and keeps them down to a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Uthappa, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Uthappa closes the face of the bat and drives it towards mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[A slip and a gully in place for Nehra]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashish Nehra, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to M Pandey, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Pandey shuffles across and nudges it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to M Pandey, no run, Pandey shortens his length and gets this one to shape away from outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to M Pandey, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, width on offer from Pandey, Manish leans into the drive and cracks it in front of square on the off-side, doesn't need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to M Pandey, no run, fuller length delivery and a hint of shape away from outside off, Pandey covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Manish Pandey, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Gambhir, <b>out</b> Caught by Dhoni!! Pandey has struck! That's a poor waft from the KOL skipper. This was short and shaping away from outside off, there were two slips in place, yet Gambhir went for the cute little dab, gets a thin edge, straight into Dhoni's gloves. Just the start CHN were after. First duck of the season for Gambhir. <b>Gambhir c Dhoni b I Pandey 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[I Pandey to Gambhir, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Uthappa, 1 run, that's excellent work from McCullum, palmed the ball onto the stumps at the striker's end, but Gambhir was well in. Uthappa set off after dabbing softly in front of point, looked like an easy single until McCullum came into the picture]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Uthappa and Gambhir are at the crease. Uthappa is on strike. I Pandey will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. Two slips in place as Ishwar Pandey opens the attack..]]></line><line><![CDATA[The pitch looks like a slow one and the ball is not coming onto the bat. A lot will depend on Ashwin and Jadeja as to how they bowl. If Nehra can continue his good form and strike early, then it will be the perfect set-up for the spin-twins. It is not going to be easy as Dhoni relishes these type of conditions. Can the CHN bowlers make a match of it? Join us in a short while to find out....]]></line><line><![CDATA[KOL bowlers justified their captain's decision to bowl first. McCullum and Smith came out all guns as usual. However, the former fell to a leg-spinner for the third time this season. Raina got off the mark with a six, but didn't get going after that. They lost a heap of wickets in the middle part of the innings. Russell and Chawla were excellent in that period. However, it was Hogg who applied the brakes just after the mandatory powerplay. The experienced campaigner finished with 1/18 in his 4 overs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Ashwin, 1 run, shortish and just outside off, Ashwin makes room and slaps it to extra cover, no timing on that as he didn't get it off the middle]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Ashwin, <b>FOUR</b>, poor delivery. Full toss and down leg, Ashwin just needed to get some bat on that, he gets enough to glance it fine and pick up his second boundary. These are handy runs for CHN]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Ashwin, <b>FOUR</b>, too straight from Umesh, Ashwin walks across his stumps and flicks it to square leg, Pandey misfields and allows the ball to go through, Russell runs across from deep mid-wicket, slides and hauls it in. But, he was in contact with the ad cushions]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to du Plessis, 1 run, Faf advances down the wicket, makes room as well, Umesh bowls it well wide of him, du Plessis toe-ends it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to du Plessis, no run, off-cutter on middle and leg, du Plessis shuffles across and misses the scoop. Good start to the final over]]></line><line><![CDATA[Faf went away and didn't even bother about the single. He seems to be fine now and will carry on.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to du Plessis, no run, short delivery at the batsman, du Plessis was early into the shot and is hit on the chest. He goes down immediately. In fact, it was the slower ball bouncer]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav [3.0-0-26-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Ashwin, no run, Ashwin had no clue about that. The wrong 'un that turns away, Ashwin gets his bat inside the line and lets it go. He then has a look at the wicket. A great spell from Hogg comes to an end, his figures: <b>4-0-18-1</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Ravindra Jadeja, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Sensational from the experienced Hogg. He has been rewarded for some brilliant bowling. Jadeja gave the charge, Hogg saw that and pushed it through, the batsman was beaten by the pace on that and the ball goes onto crash into middle-stump. CHN not getting the momentum in the final overs. <b>Ravindra Jadeja b B Hogg 15(20)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[B Hogg to Ravindra Jadeja, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to du Plessis, 1 run, floated up on middle and leg, du Plessis comes down the track and lofts it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to du Plessis, no run, excellent stuff from the veteran. He knows that the batsmen are trying to get after him, he slips in the googly, du Plessis goes for a slog across the line, misses it by a mile]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, touch quicker and around off, Jadeja cuts it to backward point, for only a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to du Plessis, 1 run, du Plessis backs away to the leg-side, wanted to go inside out, Hogg drops it short, mistimed cut to extra cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to du Plessis, 1 run, another off-speed delivery, bowled at 118.2kph, du Plessis swipes it across the line without much timing, the long-on fielder keeps it to a single. Another bowler who was tidy for KOL, Cummins' spell: <b>4-0-25-0.</b> He bowled <b>13 dot balls</b> in his 4 overs]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to du Plessis, <b>wide</b>, slower ball bouncer, Faf watches it sail over him, umpire calls it a wide for height]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to du Plessis, no run, off-cutter which is short in length, du Plessis is early into the pull, the ball sneaks through under his bat and goes on the bounce to Robin]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to du Plessis, <b>wide</b>, fires the full delivery outside off, outside the guideline, easy call for the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, pushed well wide of off, Jadeja reaches out and toe-ends it to third man. That would have been a wide had he let it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to du Plessis, 1 run, slower short ball, du Plessis has to wait for it and pulls it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, slanted across Jadeja, who backs away and slashes it to sweeper cover. Good that they didn't go for the second as the throw from Russell was right next to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, starts with a slower delivery, Jadeja cuts and finds Gambhir at backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pat Cummins [3.0-0-19-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, quicker and around off, Jadeja is late on the pull, mistimes it to the left of the bowler and picks a single to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to du Plessis, 1 run, flighted on middle and leg, swept along the ground to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, pushed through on the stumps, Jadeja pulls it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to du Plessis, 1 run, touch short and just outside off, du Plessis cuts it square of the wicket, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, brilliant shot! It was tossed up well wide of off, du Plessis kneels down and fetches it from outside off and sweeps it between deep mid-wicket and long-on. He split the two fielders in the deep to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, half tracker, Jadeja rocks back and pulls it straight to Russell at deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brad Hogg [2.0-0-6-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, full and just outside off, Jadeja lofts it on the bounce to long-on. Russell too ends his spell, he has identical figures to Chawla]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, takes the pace off the ball, Jadeja inside edges the flick onto the pads, the ball rolls to the off-side, he wanted the run but Faf sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Ravindra Jadeja, 2 runs, another short delivery, Jadeja looks to swat it across the line, the top-edge flies down to third man, Yusuf once more saves a couple, he dived full length and hauled the ball in]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, <b>Jadeja is struck on the helmet</b>. It was a sharp bouncer from Russell, Jadeja goes for the pull and misses it completely, is struck low on the helmet. He was very close to the stumps as well, did well to not fall over]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to du Plessis, 1 run, change of pace from Russell, du Plessis is early on the pull, drags it onto the right hip and the ball dribbles to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to du Plessis, <b>wide</b>, slower delivery outside off, du Plessis leaves it alone, umpire calls it a wide even though it was inside the tramline]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to du Plessis, 2 runs, short of length on the hips, flicked away to deep backward square leg, Yusuf had to run a long way from fine leg, he does well to keep it to a couple]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell [3.0-0-19-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, extra bounce on that occasion for Chawla, Jadeja picks it off the turf and dabs it to short third man. Chawla finishes his spell, his figures read: <b>4-0-26-2</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Ravindra Jadeja, 2 runs, these two are quick between the wickets, Jadeja works it in front of mid-wicket, calls for two and Faf makes it with ease at the non-striker's end]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to du Plessis, 1 run, short and just outside off, du Plessis rocks back and pulls it on the bounce to long-on, he was early into the shot and had to wait for it]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to du Plessis, 2 runs, again, Chawla drops it short for Faf, he goes back and cuts it in front of square on the off-side, Russell tidies up in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, wrong 'un on middle, Jadeja nurdles it to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to du Plessis, 1 run, fraction short and just outside off, du Plessis cuts it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, fullish and on the fourth stump line, Jadeja defends it straight to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to du Plessis, 1 run, short of length just outside off, du Plessis stands tall and punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, on a length just outside off, Jadeja pushes it to long-off and calls for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, back of a length close to off, Jadeja goes for the cut, but doesn't make contact. That was too close to the stumps for Jaddu to play the cut]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Ravindra Jadeja, 2 runs, short of length around off, Jadeja pulls it through mid-wicket, Hogg runs quickly to his right, slides and keeps it to two]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, angled across the left-hander, Jadeja lets it go. A rare sight in a T20 game]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pat Cummins [2.0-0-15-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Dwayne Bravo, <b>out</b> Caught by Suryakumar Yadav!! Chawla has his second of the night. It was a poor shot from Bravo. CHN have lost half their side and are in trouble. Floated up just outside off, Bravo goes for the inside out loft, gets it straighter than he wanted, offers a simple catch to long-off. <b>Dwayne Bravo c Suryakumar Yadav b Chawla 5(7) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chawla to Dwayne Bravo, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Dwayne Bravo, no run, tossed up around off, Bravo blocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Dwayne Bravo, no run, googly outside off, Bravo goes for the big hit, fails to make the connection. Uthappa thought there was a nick, but nothing from Chawla]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to du Plessis, 1 run, pushed through close to off, du Plessis bunts it wide of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Dwayne Bravo, 1 run, sharp single taken. But, Faf had made it in comfortably. Flighted just outside off, Bravo defends in front of cover and calls for a quick single, Pandey runs forward, picks the ball and under-arms it to the striker's end]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to du Plessis, 1 run, drifted onto the pads, nurdled away behind square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dwayne Bravo, <b>FOUR</b>, enough sighters says Bravo, pitched up delivery just outside off, Bravo doesn't move his feet much, drives it in the air over mid-off, that ball rocketed away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dwayne Bravo, no run, back of a length around off, Bravo moves across and defends it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dwayne Bravo, no run, Russell greets his fellow countryman with a bumper, Bravo half ducks and lets it go over his left shoulder]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, <b>out</b> Caught by Uthappa!! KOL on top! Russell has got the big wicket of Dhoni. He runs across and pumps his fists. The rest of his mates catch up with him. Banged in halfway down the wicket, Dhoni goes for the pull, the ball kisses the glove on the way to Uthappa. It was a sharp delivery from the West Indian. <b>Dhoni c Uthappa b A Russell 3(6)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A Russell to Dhoni, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to du Plessis, 1 run, short and down leg, du Plessis helps it down to fine leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, 1 run, back of a length on off, Dhoni shuffles across slightly and nurdles it to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Dhoni, 1 run, slower through around off, Dhoni knocks it in front of backward point, Faf calls for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to du Plessis, 1 run, quicker and on off, du Plessis pulls it to long-on, he was hurried onto the shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to du Plessis, no run, googly on off, du Plessis gets right behind the line and defends down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Dhoni, 1 run, shortens the length just outside off, Dhoni fetches it from there and turns it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to du Plessis, 1 run, again, a bit too straight, du Plessis works it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to du Plessis, 2 runs, flighted on middle and leg, du Plessis takes a couple of steps down the wicket and nudges it to deep mid-wicket, Tendo fumbles and the duo take the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Piyush Chawla [1.0-0-10-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Dhoni prods across and defends it with soft hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, <b>3 wides</b>, this is poor bowling from Russell, fires this one miles down leg-side. Uthappa dives and gets a hand onto it, Dhoni runs hard and wants the second run, a direct hit might have found him <b>short of his ground</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to du Plessis, 1 run, on a length and on du Plessis' pads, tucked away past Gambhir at mid-wicket, Faf wanted a second run but is sent back by MS]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to du Plessis, <b>wide</b>, short and angling well down leg-side, du Plessis gets inside the line and lets it go, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhoni, leg byes, 1 run, short of a length and angling into Dhoni, he shuffles across and looks to tuck it fine, misses and the ball rolls past Uthappa off the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>MS Dhoni, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Raina, <b>out</b> Caught by Uthappa!! Edged and caught! KOL are chipping away at the wickets. This was short of a length and went away with the angle, Raina was expecting the short ball again, he was deep inside the crease, ends up sparring at the ball, gets a thick edge and Uthappa does the rest. CHN are in some trouble now. <b>Raina c Uthappa b A Russell 17(21) [4s-2 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A Russell to Raina, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Raina, <b>wide</b>, the bouncer from Russell, but it's too short and too high, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Raina, no run, short of a length and angling across the left-hander, he swivels across and finds mid-wicket with the pull]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to du Plessis, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, dabbed away towards third man for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to du Plessis, 1 run, this one is given more air, du Plessis works it in front of long-on for a single, another excellent over from Hogg, just 4 runs from it]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to du Plessis, no run, nicely bowled by Hogg, flighted delivery and just outside off, du Plessis shuffles across and defends it back at the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Faf du Plessis, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Raina, <b>out</b> Dwayne Smith Run Out!! That's a smart piece of work from Yusuf at short third man. Excellent delivery first-up by Hogg, the leg-break, ripping across Raina, he was down the track and stranded, luckily, the ball hit his arm and rolled away towards short third man. He called for a quick single, Dwayne Smith responded early but fails to beat the direct hit from Pathan. CHN have lost both openers now. <b>Dwayne Smith run out (Y Pathan) 25(19) [4s-3 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[B Hogg to Raina, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Appeal for a <b>run-out</b>. A direct hit and Smith is <b>well short</b>. He is <b>OUT</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, Hogg drifts one on Smith's pads, clipped away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Raina, 1 run, more luck, this time for Raina, this was tossed up and spun away slightly, Raina was looking to drive it through extra cover, ends up slicing it through cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Smith shuffles across and works it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, overpitched and in the zone outside off, Raina leans forward, presents the full face of the bat and chips it over extra cover, no chance for the fielder getting across from long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Raina, no run, Russell keeps it short and just outside off, Raina made room and was looking to play the upper-cut, is beaten by the extra bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Raina, no run, short of a length and going away with the angle, Raina was looking to dab it towards third man and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Raina, no run, short of a length and just outside off, chopped straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, eased down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Raina, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Raina drives it towards short extra cover and calls for a quick single. Dwayne Smith was late to start off, Gambhir rushes in and misses the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Raina, 1 run, flighted delivery and on off, Raina nudges it behind square on the on-side for a single, just two singles from Hogg's first over on his return to IPL]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Raina, no run, pushed through flatter and quicker, Raina had no room to work it towards mid-wicket, hits it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Raina, no run, this one is given more air, pushed back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Raina, no run, Hogg drifts one onto Raina's pads, turned towards short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Raina, no run, the leg-break from Hogg, Raina presses forward, opens the face of the bat and runs it towards short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Smith prods across and works it in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brad Hogg, left-arm chinaman, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Hogg has been introduced into the attack, at 44y and 81d, he is the oldest player to feature in the IPL]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Raina, no run, Yadav keeps it full and just outside off, Raina was looking to work it away towards the on-side, closes the face of the bat early and gets a soft leading edge, the ball rolls back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Raina, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Raina presses across and defends it with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, this is poor bowling from Yadav, bangs it short and well outside off, Raina gets on top of the bounce and cracks it over backward point, away from Russell at third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Raina, no run, on a good length and angling away from off, Raina plays with an open face and dabs it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Raina, no run, short of a length and on the stumps, Raina was shuffling across on the flick, misses and the ball hits him high on the thigh-pad, almost rolls back onto the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, Smith gets lucky again, this was banged in short and on the stumps, Smith was looking to pull and miscues it towards square leg, no one's there and he gets away with a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Raina, <b>SIX</b>, that ruins the over for Chawla, tossed up and well outside leg, Raina gets down on his knees and sweeps it high and over backward square leg, sails into the crowd, not a bad way to begin your innings]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Raina, no run, Raina comes down the track to a well flighted delivery and defends it towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Brendon McCullum, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Chawla has struck for KOL! This was a well disguised googly, pitched around off and spun back in, McCullum plonked his foot forward as he shaped for the push, didn't read the delivery one bit and was struck low on his pads and in front of off-stump. The ball was going on to crash into middle, McCullum wasn't happy with the call, but there was no edge on that and it looked pretty adjacent. <b>Brendon McCullum lbw b Chawla 19(14) [4s-3 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chawla to Brendon McCullum, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Brendon McCullum, no run, that's a good comeback from Chawla, the slider, pushed through quicker and well outside off, McCullum was rooted inside the crease as he aimed a big drive and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, aggressive batting from McCullum, shimmies down the track, Chawla goes wider outside off, McCullum reaches out and slaps it back over the bowler's head, a couple of bounces and over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Brendon McCullum, no run, tossed up and on the off-stump line, driven towards mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Piyush Chawla, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four</b>, no luck for Yadav, this was full and in that channel outside off, lured Smith into the drive, finds the outside edge. The ball dropped in between the keeper and Manish at first slip and races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Yadav, bowled at <b>146kmph</b> but drifts it onto Smith's pads, he gets the fine glance going and it races away past Uthappa and into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dwayne Smith, <b>SIX</b>, <b>top-edge and six</b>, T20 is not a game for the bowlers, this was banged in short and just outside off, Smith was shaping for the pull, the ball didn't rise as much as he expected, gets a top edge that loops over the keeper and clears the ropes on the full]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dwayne Smith, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Smith was playing from his crease, ends up pushing in front of the body and gets a bottom edge towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dwayne Smith, no run, appeal for LBW, but once again the angle was taking it down leg, Yadav gets this one to shape back into Smith, caught him in the crease as he looked to flick, the impact was on leg-stump and would have been sliding down]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dwayne Smith, no run, Yadav shortens his length and gets this one to shape back into Smith, beats him for pace and hits him high on the thigh pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dwayne Smith, <b>wide</b>, wayward ball from Yadav, short and well down leg-side, Uthappa dives across and keeps it to just one wide]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, Cummins goes for the leg-stump yorker, ends up offering a low full-toss on McCullum's pads, McCullum flicked it behind square on the on-side. Hogg gets across from deep square leg, puts in the dive but the ball beats him to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, nudged in front of mid-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Brendon McCullum, leg byes, 1 run, full and on McCullum's pads, he looks to flick and misses, the ball rolls away towards square leg for a leg-bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Brendon McCullum, <b>SIX</b>, McCullum was itching to get going, runs down the track, makes room as he did so and slams Cummins, back over his head and into the sightscreen, that's the first six of the innings]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Brendon McCullum, no run, Cummins shortens his length and angles it across McCullum, cramps the right-hander on the cut, he goes hard on the shot and gets a bottom edge, the ball rolls away back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Brendon McCullum, no run, tad fuller and shaping back into McCullum, he presents the full face of the bat and drives it towards mid-on, that was clocked at <b>145kmph</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, McCullum prods forward and drives it to the right of mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Brendon McCullum, no run, Yadav keeps it full and follows McCullum as he charged down the track, the batsman is cramped for space, ends up swishing and the ball beats him to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, short of a length and angling into Smith, he swivels across on the pull and gets an inside edge past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Brendon McCullum, leg byes, 1 run, fraction too short and on McCullum's pads, he looks to flick and gets struck on the pads, rolls away past the keeper for a leg-bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Brendon McCullum, no run, on a good length and just outside off, McCullum prods half-forward and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, that could have been close, but Pathan was late to move across at third man, this was short and just outside off, McCullum rides with the bounce and runs it towards third man, Yusuf has to put in the slide in the end, the ball bounces in front of him and goes past him for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[One slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Dwayne Smith, no run, appeal for LBW, but it looked like the angle was taking it down leg, this one shaped back in off a length, Smith was shuffling across on the whip and missed, the impact was in front of leg-stump, must have been sliding down, <b>excellent first over from Cummins though</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Dwayne Smith, no run, Cummins is getting some extra bounce, on a good length and just outside off, rears from a length, Smith goes back and defends it with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Dwayne Smith, no run, that's a cracker from Cummins, pitched in that corridor outside off, seams off the deck and shapes away, Smith was in no position as he sparred and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four</b>, lucky runs for Smith, width on offer from Cummins, Smith threw his bat at that, gets a thick edge that flies over the lone slip and races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Dwayne Smith, no run, nicely bowled by Cummins, tad fuller and on the off-stump channel, gets some extra bounce, Smith plays with soft hands and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[Just one slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Cummins to Dwayne Smith, no run, short of a length and holding its line outside off, Smith covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go. Uthappa drops the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Smith and Brendon McCullum are at the crease. Dwayne Smith is on strike. P Cummins will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The two openers are out in the middle.. Pat Cummins has the new ball. Can he emulate Morne Morkel and strike early for KOL?]]></line><line><![CDATA[We are ready for action. Brad Hogg is back in IPL action and he's playing for a different franchise this time around. Waiting for him to come onto bowl. KOL are in the midst of the team huddle and it's Hogg who's doing all the talking.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kolkata</b> (Playing XI): Gautam Gambhir(c), Robin Uthappa(w), Manish Pandey, Suryakumar Yadav, Ryan ten Doeschate, Yusuf Pathan, Andre Russell, Piyush Chawla, Pat Cummins, Brad Hogg, Umesh Yadav]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai</b> (Playing XI): Brendon McCullum, Dwayne Smith, Suresh Raina, Faf du Plessis, MS Dhoni(w/c), Ravindra Jadeja, Dwayne Bravo, Ravichandran Ashwin, Mohit Sharma, Ashish Nehra, Ishwar Pandey]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>MS Dhoni:</b> 'We would have batted first. It's a fresh wicket, will like to put runs on the board and put them under pressure. Our wins have been big, that reflects in the net run-rate, the batting and bowling looks fine. It's looking pretty good. Same playing XI for us.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Gambhir:</b> 'We will bowl. Looks like a good wicket, we will look to chase down the target. We are looking in good shape, but we need to get some points, can't rely on the last few matches, don't want to put pressure on ourselves. Three changes for us. <b>Pat Cummins</b> replaces <b>Morne Morkel</b>, <b>Brad Hogg</b> replaces <b>Sunil Narine</b> and <b>Ryan ten Doeschate</b> replaces <b>Johan Botha</b>'.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kolkata have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Narine</b> will not be playing tonight. It's toss time]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather Report:</b> It was a clear and sunny morning and the temperature is around 31 degrees at the moment. Humidity is a factor in Chennai though and at 70%, it feels like 38 degrees in the centre.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-Head record</b>: When it comes to competition between the two teams, CHN hold the advantage, with a 9-5 winning record. However, if we are to consider the last 5 meetings between the two teams, it's a lot closer, with CHN edging it by a 3-2 margin.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The batting has flattered to deceive more often than not this season. Robin Uthappa hasn't converted starts into bigger knocks while Manish Pandey and Suryakumar Yadav have been patchy at best. That has meant more responsibility on the likes of Gautam Gambhir and Yusuf Pathan and the duo have risen to the occasion. Add the big hitting Andre Russell, the batting has more often than not delivered, but not before keeping their fans on a knife edge.]]></line><line><![CDATA[On the other hand, KOL come into the match with some concerns. The washout against Rajasthan gave them a point and left them just ahead of a bunch of teams (BLR, HYD and DEL) - who have 6 points each. Narine has completed yet another round of testing on his bowling action at the Sri Ramachandra University in Chennai and could well feature today. While his form hasn't been great, Narine's presence always adds intrigue and quality to any bowling unit. Morne Morkel is in splendid form and the rest of the bowling unit has been effective.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The all-Indian bowling unit has hardly been tested and the return to form of lead spinners Ravichandran Ashwin and Ravindra Jadeja augurs well for MS Dhoni's men - especially with wickets expected to offer more help to the spinners as the tournament progresses. It's a settled outfit which has hardly forced MS Dhoni to ring in changes. Will CHN experiment tonight on a ground where they have reeled off 8 wins in a row? Knowing MS, he might just be tempted to play the same combination once again.]]></line><line><![CDATA[On form, both teams have looked very solid. Hosts CHN are on a roll and the loss to Rajasthan has been the only blip to an otherwise flawless season. With five wins out of six matches, they are nicely placed with 10 points, just one point below Rajasthan, who have played two extra matches. Much of their strengths lie with their top-order. Dwayne Smith and Brendon McCullum have provided electrifying starts and that has allowed the middle order to consolidate during the middle overs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:40 Local Time, 13:10 GMT, 18:40 IST:</b> Many neutral experts believe that the two teams playing today will eventually meet once again in the final of this season's Indian Premier League. The other six franchises may differ with their views, but for now Chennai and Kolkata are up against each other in what should be a mouthwatering contest. This is the first match of the double-header between these two teams. Chennai travel to Kolkata for the return match in a couple of days time.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview</b><br/><br/>It has been a mixed season so far for defending champions Kolkata whereas Chennai have lived up to their reputation of pre-tournament favourites. CHN have won five out of their six games in IPL 2015, while KOL have won three. MS Dhoni's men are placed second while Gambhir and Co. are right behind at third spot. There's not a lot to choose from between the two teams but CHN's consistent record at home will give them a slight edge. For KOL, it is a chance to regain some momentum. Their previous two outings have been a washout and a loss.<br/><br/>The game is an opportunity for CHN to climb ahead of Rajasthan in the points table. RAJ have played two games more with the same number of wins. Clearly, CHN have been more consistent and they will be looking to extend their good form. That and the home advantage puts them slightly ahead.<br/><br/><b>Venue:</b> MA Chidambaram Stadium, Chennai<br/><br/><b>Date:</b> April 28, 2015<br/><br/><b>Time:</b> 2000 IST<br/><br/><b>Team news:</b><br/><br/><b>Chennai</b><br/><br/>The most settled looking team of the IPL has it as one of their biggest advantages. The team is packed with match-winners and in-form players that has made MS Dhoni's job a little easier. The return to form of Ravindra Jadeja with the ball solves that last bit of the jigsaw puzzle for them. Dwayne Smith and Brendon McCullum's contributions at the top have given CHN invaluable platforms to cash in. The duo are fourth and fifth in the list of leading run-getters this season while Ashish Nehra's vital strikes with the ball has come as a welcome surprise for the team. More than their batting might, it is the consistent showing with the ball that has lent the side a striking balance. Expect no changes for tomorrow's game unless there is an injury concern.<br/><br/><b>Probable XI:</b> Brendon McCullum, Dwayne Smith, Suresh Raina, Faf du Plessis, MS Dhoni (c & wk), Dwayne Bravo, Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Mohit Sharma, Ishwar Pandey, Ashish Nehra<br/><br/><b>Kolkata:</b><br/><br/>W, L, W, W, L, NR - That has been KOL's journey this season. Quite evidently it has been a see-saw tournament. The washout in the previous game did not help their cause of gathering momentum. The defending champions have been oddly hampered by things out of their control. With their previous two games being affected by rain, KOL will desperately need a good game under their belt to restart their defence of the title. The suspicion over their premier spinner Sunil Narine's action has only added to their woes. Will Narine be treated with caution now? Can KOL afford to sit him out as a precaution? Narine has been sent to the Chennai testing center but can play for now until the test results come out. Will KOL risk him though? Those are the toughest questions that the team management will have to answer. In case Narine doesn't play, Johan Botha could get another game.<br/><br/>They also need that one comprehensive performance with both batting and bowling clicking in unison. Gambhir, Robin Uthappa, Suryakumar Yadav, Manish Pandey and Andre Russell have all had their moments this year but it is important for all of them to come together at the right time. If they do produce such a performance against the mighty CHN then that is exactly the kind of rejuvenation that will breathe fresh air to their campaign.<br/><br/><b>Probable XI:</b> Robin Uthappa (wk), Gautam Gambhir (c), Manish Pandey, Suryakumar Yadav, Yusuf Pathan, Andre Russell, Johan Botha, Piyush Chawla, Brad Hogg, Morne Morkel, Umesh Yadav<br/><br/><b>Stats:</b><br/><br/>CHN and KOL have played each other 15 times with CHN having a clear lead with nine wins.<br/><br/>CHN have also won four out of the six meetings in Chepauk.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kolkata</b> (From): Gautam Gambhir(c), Robin Uthappa(w), Manish Pandey, Suryakumar Yadav, Yusuf Pathan, Andre Russell, Johan Botha, Piyush Chawla, Kuldeep Yadav, Morne Morkel, Umesh Yadav, Sunil Narine, Pat Cummins, Ryan ten Doeschate, Veer Pratap Singh, Azhar Mahmood, Brad Hogg, Sumit Narwal, Sheldon Jackson, Aditya Garhwal, Kishan Cariappa, Vaibhav Rawal]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai</b> (From): Brendon McCullum, Dwayne Smith, Suresh Raina, Faf du Plessis, MS Dhoni(c/w), Ravindra Jadeja, Dwayne Bravo, Ravichandran Ashwin, Mohit Sharma, Ashish Nehra, Ishwar Pandey, Baba Aparajith, Matt Henry, Mithun Manhas, Pawan Negi, Samuel Badree, Ronit More, Michael Hussey, Rahul Sharma, Kyle Abbott, Ankush Bains, Irfan Pathan, Pratyush Singh, Andrew Tye, Eklavya Dwivedi]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>134</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>6</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Chennai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Smith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>25</runs>
					<balls>19</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Yusuf Pathan</fielder>
						<fielderId>790</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Brendon McCullum</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>19</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Chawla</bowler>
					<bowlerId>466</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Raina</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>17</runs>
					<balls>21</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>A Russell</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7736</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Robin Uthappa</fielder>
						<fielderId>527</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7825</playerid>
					<name>Faf du Plessis</name>
					<batsman-name>du Plessis</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>du Plessis</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>29</runs>
					<balls>29</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhoni</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>A Russell</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7736</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Robin Uthappa</fielder>
						<fielderId>527</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>242</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
					<batsman-name>DJ Bravo</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>5</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Chawla</bowler>
					<bowlerId>466</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Suryakumar Yadav</fielder>
						<fielderId>7915</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<batsman-name>R Jadeja</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>15</runs>
					<balls>20</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>B Hogg</bowler>
					<bowlerId>140</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<batsman-name>Ashwin</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ashwin</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Mohit Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mohit Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>269</playerid>
					<name>Ashish Nehra</name>
					<batsman-name>Nehra</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nehra</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8665</playerid>
					<name>Ishwar Pandey</name>
					<batsman-name>I Pandey</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>I Pandey</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>201</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>42</runs>
				<overs>4.4</overs>
				<batsman>Brendon McCullum</batsman>
				<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>255</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>64</runs>
				<overs>8.4</overs>
				<batsman>Dwayne Smith</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>413</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>67</runs>
				<overs>9.3</overs>
				<batsman>Suresh Raina</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>265</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>81</runs>
				<overs>11.3</overs>
				<batsman>MS Dhoni</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>242</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>88</runs>
				<overs>12.6</overs>
				<batsman>Dwayne Bravo</batsman>
				<batsman-name>DJ Bravo</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>587</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>124</runs>
				<overs>18.5</overs>
				<batsman>Ravindra Jadeja</batsman>
				<batsman-name>R Jadeja</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>9</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>3</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>12</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Kolkata">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8095</playerid>
					<name>Pat Cummins</name>
					<bowler-name>Pat Cummins</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>P Cummins</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1858</playerid>
					<name>Umesh Yadav</name>
					<bowler-name>Umesh</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>U Yadav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>466</playerid>
					<name>Piyush Chawla</name>
					<bowler-name>Chawla</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chawla</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>26</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>140</playerid>
					<name>Brad Hogg</name>
					<bowler-name>B Hogg</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>B Hogg</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>18</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7736</playerid>
					<name>Andre Russell</name>
					<bowler-name>A Russell</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>A Russell</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>26</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>6</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>308</playerid>
					<name>Gautam Gambhir</name>
					<bowler-name>Gambhir</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Gambhir</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>527</playerid>
					<name>Robin Uthappa</name>
					<bowler-name>Uthappa</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Uthappa</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1836</playerid>
					<name>Manish Pandey</name>
					<bowler-name>M Pandey</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M Pandey</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7915</playerid>
					<name>Suryakumar Yadav</name>
					<bowler-name>Suryakumar Yadav</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Suryakumar Yadav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>640</playerid>
					<name>Ryan ten Doeschate</name>
					<bowler-name>ten Doeschate</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>ten Doeschate</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>790</playerid>
					<name>Yusuf Pathan</name>
					<bowler-name>Y Pathan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Y Pathan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>132</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>9</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Kolkata">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>527</playerid>
					<name>Robin Uthappa</name>
					<batsman-name>Uthappa</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Uthappa</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>39</runs>
					<balls>17</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Ashwin</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1593</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Brendon McCullum</fielder>
						<fielderId>201</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>308</playerid>
					<name>Gautam Gambhir</name>
					<batsman-name>Gambhir</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Gambhir</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>I Pandey</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8665</bowlerId>
						<fielder>MS Dhoni</fielder>
						<fielderId>265</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1836</playerid>
					<name>Manish Pandey</name>
					<batsman-name>M Pandey</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M Pandey</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>15</runs>
					<balls>20</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Ashwin</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1593</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dwayne Bravo</fielder>
						<fielderId>242</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7915</playerid>
					<name>Suryakumar Yadav</name>
					<batsman-name>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>16</runs>
					<balls>26</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mohit Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8181</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dwayne Bravo</fielder>
						<fielderId>242</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>790</playerid>
					<name>Yusuf Pathan</name>
					<batsman-name>Y Pathan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Y Pathan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>13</runs>
					<balls>18</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>DJ Bravo</bowler>
					<bowlerId>242</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>640</playerid>
					<name>Ryan ten Doeschate</name>
					<batsman-name>ten Doeschate</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>ten Doeschate</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>38</runs>
					<balls>28</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7736</playerid>
					<name>Andre Russell</name>
					<batsman-name>A Russell</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>A Russell</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ravindra Jadeja</fielder>
						<fielderId>587</fielderId>
						<fielder2>MS Dhoni</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>265</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8095</playerid>
					<name>Pat Cummins</name>
					<batsman-name>Pat Cummins</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>P Cummins</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>DJ Bravo</bowler>
					<bowlerId>242</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ravindra Jadeja</fielder>
						<fielderId>587</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>466</playerid>
					<name>Piyush Chawla</name>
					<batsman-name>Chawla</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chawla</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>DJ Bravo</bowler>
					<bowlerId>242</bowlerId>
						<fielder>MS Dhoni</fielder>
						<fielderId>265</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1858</playerid>
					<name>Umesh Yadav</name>
					<batsman-name>Umesh</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>U Yadav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Nehra</bowler>
					<bowlerId>269</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>140</playerid>
					<name>Brad Hogg</name>
					<batsman-name>B Hogg</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>B Hogg</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>308</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>1</runs>
				<overs>0.2</overs>
				<batsman>Gautam Gambhir</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Gambhir</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>527</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>52</runs>
				<overs>5.1</overs>
				<batsman>Robin Uthappa</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Uthappa</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1836</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>61</runs>
				<overs>7.1</overs>
				<batsman>Manish Pandey</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Pandey</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7915</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>76</runs>
				<overs>12.2</overs>
				<batsman>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>790</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>91</runs>
				<overs>15.2</overs>
				<batsman>Yusuf Pathan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Y Pathan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7736</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>100</runs>
				<overs>16.5</overs>
				<batsman>Andre Russell</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Russell</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8095</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>101</runs>
				<overs>17.1</overs>
				<batsman>Pat Cummins</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Pat Cummins</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>466</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>104</runs>
				<overs>17.5</overs>
				<batsman>Piyush Chawla</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Chawla</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1858</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>116</runs>
				<overs>18.5</overs>
				<batsman>Umesh Yadav</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Umesh</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>5</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Chennai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8665</playerid>
					<name>Ishwar Pandey</name>
					<bowler-name>I Pandey</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>I Pandey</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>18</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>269</playerid>
					<name>Ashish Nehra</name>
					<bowler-name>Nehra</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nehra</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>38</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Mohit Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mohit Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>24</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<bowler-name>Ashwin</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ashwin</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>5</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<bowler-name>R Jadeja</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>11</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<bowler-name>Raina</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Raina</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>12</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>242</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
					<bowler-name>DJ Bravo</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>22</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<bowler-name>B McCullum</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Brendon McCullum</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<bowler-name>Dwayne Smith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Smith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7825</playerid>
					<name>Faf du Plessis</name>
					<bowler-name>du Plessis</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>du Plessis</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhoni</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhoni</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



