<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14639" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>46th Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Mumbai</home>
		<away>Bangalore</away>
		<teamsabbr>MUM vs BLR</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>MUM</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>BLR</awayabbr>
		<homeId>62</homeId>
		<awayId>59</awayId>
		<venue>Wankhede Stadium, Mumbai</venue>
		<startdate>10 05 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>10 05 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Bangalore</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Bangalore won by 39 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Bangalore</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>39</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Chettithody Shamsuddin</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Johanes Cloete</Name>
			<Country>RSA</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Krishnaraj Srinath</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Javagal Srinath</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>10:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150510140314</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>MUM</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>BLR</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>196</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>7</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>20</batteamovers>
		<status>Bangalore won by 39 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>599</playerid>
			<name>Lendl Simmons*</name>
			<batsman-name>L Simmons</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Simmons</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>68</runs>
			<balls-faced>53</balls-faced>
			<fours>5</fours>
			<sixes>3</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>7624</playerid>
			<name>Mitchell McClenaghan</name>
			<batsman-name>McClenaghan</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>McClenaghan</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>12</runs>
			<balls-faced>4</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>2</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>7710</playerid>
			<name>Mitchell Starc*</name>
			<bowler-name>M Starc</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Starc</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>41</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>7910</playerid>
			<name>Yuzvendra Chahal</name>
			<bowler-name>Chahal</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Chahal</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>51</runs>
			<wickets>2</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>236</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>10357</playerid>
<name>Jagadeesha Suchith</name>
<player-runs>4</player-runs>
<player-balls>4</player-balls>
<runs>184</runs>
<wicket-nbr>7</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>7910</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Chahal</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>4</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[4 6 . . 4 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 Wd 6 W . 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>2 W 1 1 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>2 W . 6 . 6 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/MUM_BLR_MAY10/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[That's it from us! Hop tabs to get all the action from the game between CHN and RAJ. Goodbye!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>de Villiers</b>: "Things just went my way today. I didn't start well, but Virat Kohli calmed me down. The basics stay same for all formats. It is just that the rhythm changes. I never decide on a specific game plan before I go in to bat. I always want to keep it simple, watch the ball, keep the head still. Want to wish all Mothers a Happy Mother's Day. Especially to my Mom and my Mother-in-Law and of course my wife who's a Mom to be."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>AB de Villiers</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his 59-ball 133.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kohli</b>: "We couldn't have asked for anything more from the team. I didn't expect 235 to be honest, I was thinking about 175 after 6 overs, but I was pretty wrong (smiles). It was a memorable day for me watching AB bat at the other end. Beating Mumbai in Mumbai is never easy. They have beaten us here. We want to play consistent cricket."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, AB de Villiers' breathtaking artistry with the willow tore apart the opposition ranks. By carting 19 fours and four sixes, de Villiers  captured the hearts of the crowd. In short, de Villiers twinned grace with superhuman skills to effortlessly bisect the gaps and reached his century in just 47 balls. His knock turned out to be the highest score in this year's IPL. de Villiers also stitched an unbroken stand of 215 with Virat Kohli. It is now the highest partnership for any wicket in the history of IPL as well as T20s. With this morale-boosting win, BLR are now placed fourth in the points table.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Despite Kieron Pollard and Lendl Simmons essaying fine knocks, MUM slumped towards a defeat. In particular, Pollard landed crunching blows to give MUM a glimmer of hope of overhauling the massive target. However, once Sreenath Aravind snared Pollard's wicket, it was all but over for the hosts. Aravind, Harshal Patel, Mitchell Starc and Yuzvendra Chahal all picked up wickets.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to McClenaghan, <b>SIX</b>, shuffles in the crease and plays a lovely slog-sweep over deep square leg. <b>BLR win by 39 runs</b>. This is a comprehensive win!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to McClenaghan, no run, Karthik appeals for a catch and puts the umpire off. Flighed delivery well down the leg-side, McClenaghan sweeps and misses. That should have been a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to McClenaghan, <b>SIX</b>, good hit! Tossed up and in the slot, McClenaghan lofts it over long-on, the fielder jumps high but the ball escapes]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to McClenaghan, no run, googly from Chahal, McClenaghan gets down on one knee and tries to slog, but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Jagadeesha Suchith, <b>out</b> Caught by D Karthik!! Easy catch for the keeper. Flighted delivery just outside off stump, Suchith slogs, mistimes it completely, the ball takes a top edge and goes towards short cover. Karthik calls for the catch and takes it easily. <b>Jagadeesha Suchith c D Karthik b Chahal 4(4)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chahal to Jagadeesha Suchith, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Jagadeesha Suchith, 2 runs, Suchith dances down the track and slices the big hit, the ball goes over extra-cover and it's good enough for a couple of runs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuzvendra Chahal [3.0-0-37-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's just a formality now for BLR. MUM need 54 off 6 balls.]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Jagadeesha Suchith, 1 run, full and outside off stump, Suchith slices it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Simmons, 1 run, a good leg stump yorker, Simmons swings hard and gets an inside edge that rolls into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Jagadeesha Suchith, 1 run, short and on the off stump, Jagadeesha Suchith backs away and cuts well, but sweeper cover tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Simmons, 1 run, full and on the off stump, driven to extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jagadeesha Suchith, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Harbhajan, <b>out</b> Caught by Kohli!! No calling was needed this time as it went straight to the fielder. Harbhajan looks for a maximum but hits this full ball straight to long-on, where Kohli takes a simple catch. <b>Harbhajan c Kohli b Starc 3(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to Harbhajan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Harbhajan, 2 runs, in the airrrr and <b>put down</b>. Poor calling from Chahal and Mandeep. Full delivery on the off stump, Singh mistimes the lofted drive, Chahal runs back from extra-cover, Mandeep runs in from long-off, both fielders go for the catch, miss the ball and almost collide with each other]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc [3.0-0-35-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>60</b> needed off 12 balls. Mathematically still possible though!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Harbhajan, 1 run, low full toss, driven down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Simmons, 1 run, very full from Harshal Patel, Simmons drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Simmons, no run, full outside leg, Simmons advances and slogs, but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Harbhajan Singh, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Rayudu, <b>out</b> Caught by de Villiers!! Oh he made that look so easy did AB de Villiers. Ah! What an athlete. Full delivery just outside off stump, Rayudu steps out and looks to drive inside-out, hits it well but doesn't get the placement right. AB moves to his left, dives and takes a good low catch. Rayudu asks AB if he caught it cleanly and AB showed him the thumbs up. <b>Rayudu c de Villiers b Harshal Patel 14(4) [6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Harshal Patel to Rayudu, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Rayudu, <b>SIX</b>, slower delivery on the off stump, Rayudu gets down on one knee and slog-sweeps it, the ball lands on the rope and it's a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Rayudu, <b>wide</b>, Rayudu moves across the stumps, Harshal Patel tries to outsmart him by bowling a widish yorker, Rayudu lets it go and the umpire calls a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Simmons, 1 run, low full toss from round the wicket, Simmons mistimes the drive towards long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel [3.0-0-26-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[MUM need 70 runs off 18 balls.]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Simmons, 1 run, low full toss on the leg stump, Simmons flicks it to deep mid-wicket and keeps strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, unlucky for the bowler. Wiese bangs this slower ball short, Simmons advances and goes for the pull, gets a top edge and it flies past the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Simmons, no run, Simmons goes way too early into the slog, lack of pace on the ball meant it took the toe-end of the bat and it rolls to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Simmons, no run, fantastic yorker from Wiese, Simmons just manages to dig it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Simmons, <b>SIX</b>, shortish in length, on the leg stump, Simmons takes his front leg out of the way and smashes it flat over long-on. This is a great start to the over for MUM]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>fifty</b> for Simmons, but it's come off 43 balls. He needs to up the ante. Short of a length delivery just outside off stump, Simmons cuts and beats the fielder at backward point, who was diving to his left]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese [3.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Rayudu, <b>SIX</b>, completely mistimed, AB tries his best at long-off but he can only palm it over the rope. Flighted delivery spinning away outside off stump, Rayudu steps out and looks to go big, the bat turns in his hands and goes high towards long-off, AB jumps and tries to take it with one hand but doesn't succeed]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Rayudu, 2 runs, flighted delivery on the leg stump, Rayudu flicks it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ambati Rayudu, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>. Kohli is back on the field and a substitute gives him some medicine]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Pandya, <b>out</b> Stumped!! Well bowled! Chahal not afraid to toss the ball despite being hit for a six. Pandya comes down the track and looks for a gallery hit, the ball spins past the bat and Karthik effects an easy stumping. <b>Pandya st D Karthik b Chahal 8(4) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chahal to Pandya, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Stumped!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Pandya, <b>SIX</b>, he's continuing from where he left the other day in Chennai. No flight whatsoever on this one from Chahal, Pandya hangs back and lofts it easily over long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Simmons, 1 run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Simmons advances and drives it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Pandya, 1 run, Pandya steps out and takes it on the full, gets an inside edge that rolls to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuzvendra Chahal [2.0-0-21-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Virat Kohli is off the field, Dinesh Karthik is captaining the side. Kohli was gesturing to the physio as if he was feeling a bit of dizziness.]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Simmons, no run, slower delivery outside off stump, Simmons inside-edges the slog onto boot]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Pandya, 1 run, full and on the leg stump, Pandya flicks it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Simmons, 1 run, shortish from Aravind, Simmons mistimes the pull to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Simmons, no run, slower delivery outside off stump, Simmons jumps down the track and misses the slog]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hardik Pandya, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Pollard, <b>out</b> Caught by Starc!! Is that the match for BLR? Massive wicket for the Bangalore boys! They are all charged up. They know the importance of this wicket. Pollard was looking determined to steal the match but he's gone now. Slower delivery just outside off stump, Pollard goes for a big hit over long-on, he was deceived by the slower ball, the ball takes the outside half of the bat and flies towards sweeper cover, where Starc takes a good low catch. That was a difficult grab as it was in the air for a long time but Starc was so cool under it. <b>Pollard c Starc b Aravind 49(24) [4s-6 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Aravind to Pollard, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Pollard, <b>FOUR</b>, can't lose your length at this stage of the innings. A full ball right in the slot, Pollard lofts it to the right of long-on and begins the over in style]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sreenath Aravind [3.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[What an over from Wiese. Just 4 singles in it. MUM need 107 off 36 balls.]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Pollard, 1 run, Wiese is very lucky to get away with a slower ball low full toss, Pollard slogs but hits it straight to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Pollard, no run, Pollard advances but Wiese bowls a yorker length delivery outside off stump and beats Pollard's attempted squeeze]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Simmons, 1 run, Simmons is forced to manufacture some pace as Wiese bowls another slower ball, slogged wide of long-on. That was a mis-hit]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Simmons, no run, clever bowling from Wiese. Simmons moves leg-side very early, Wiese bowls a slower ball on a good length, Simmons lets it go thinking it was a wide but it was well inside the line]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Pollard, 1 run, a big swing of the bat, but Pollard mistimes the pull to deep mid-wicket. Had that taken the middle of the bat, it would have gone out of the park!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Simmons, 1 run, effortlessly played. Slower ball outside off stump, Simmons stays leg-side and cuts it to deep point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese [2.0-0-19-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Pollard, <b>FOUR</b>, too short, thank you very much says Pollard and gets four more. Short and angling across, not good enough to trouble the big all-rounder and he nails the pull shot to perfection over mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Simmons, 1 run, Simmons moves right across the sticks and flicks the yorker length delivery through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Pollard, 1 run, slower delivery just outside off stump, Pollard taps it to point with one hand]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Pollard, no run, Starc bowls the yorker outside off stump, Pollard tries to run it down to third man with an open face but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Pollard, <b>FOUR</b>, where is long-off, Virat Kohli? This is ridiculous! Pollard loves to play with a straight bat and he takes full toll of the field. Good length delivery outside off stump, Pollard doesn't try to do anything fancy, just lofts it over mid-off and it rockets for four]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Pollard, 2 runs, full and on the leg stump, Pollard flicks it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc [2.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Okay, that onslaught has forced Kohli to bring back his best bowler, Mitchell Starc. Oh it's Starc v Pollard again! What do we have in store?]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mumbai have scored 47 runs off the last 3 overs. They need 123 more from 8 overs. Can they do it? They certainly can if these bat for 5-6 overs!]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Simmons, <b>SIX</b>, clean hit! He didn't go hard at it at all. Just came down the track, got to the pitch of the ball, got under it and lofted it easily straight back over the bowler's head]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Pollard, 1 run, Pollard races down the track, this time gets too close to the pitch of the ball, hence gets the inside half of the bat and it rolls to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Simmons, 1 run, this is sensible from Simmons, just knocks it to mid-wicket and gets Pollard back on strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Pollard, 1 run, shortish and on the leg stump, punched to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Pollard, <b>SIX</b>, in the airrrr, does it have enough legs to go all the way? Yes it has! Pollard is turning it on and the crowd get right behind Pollard. Flighted delivery just outside off stump, Pollard steps out and lofts high into the sky, clears the sightscreen by a distance. This is interesting, Chris Gayle goes to Virat Kohli and has a tip for him. He knows Pollard well!]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Simmons, 1 run, hangs on the back foot and drives it through cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuzvendra Chahal [1.0-0-5-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Pollard, <b>SIX</b>, oh <b>that's gone into orbit</b>. Mumbai aren't out of this until this man is at the crease. Too short from Harshal Patel, Pollard muscles the pull way back over deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Simmons, 1 run, short ball, the slower delivery again, Simmons backs away early, doesn't get into a great position, toe-ends the pull to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Pollard, 1 run, whipped uppishly but deep backward square leg tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Pollard, <b>FOUR</b>, freebie! Takes pace off the ball, but it was too short, although Pollard was beaten by the lack of pace just a touch, he swivelled and pulled it fine past short fine leg, Aravind runs to his right in the deep but the ball wins the race]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Simmons, 1 run, Simmons goes deep in the crease as he rocks back, pulls this short ball wide of long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Pollard, leg byes, 1 run, slower delivery down the leg-side, Pollard fails to tickle it, the ball rolls behind square on the on-side, Pollard is disappointed that he didn't get bat on ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, that's an excellent shot, nothing wrong with the ball, full and perhaps just a little bit of width, Simmons opens the face of the bat and runs it past short third man for a boundary, <b>17 came from the over</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Simmons, 2 runs, the slower ball from Aravind, Simmons works it in front of square on the on-side, runs hard and gets back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Pollard, 1 run, that's a fine yorker from Aravind, Pollard jams his bat down in the nick of time and gets an outside edge towards short third man. Mandeep fumbles, but the batsmen decide against a second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Pollard, <b>FOUR</b>, another meaty blow from Pollard, on a good length and just outside off, mid-off was inside the ring and Pollard goes over that fielder, turning out to be an expensive over]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Pollard, <b>FOUR</b>, that's nicely played by Pollard, back of a length and on his thighs, he uses the pace of the ball and runs it past short fine for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Pollard, 2 runs, short of a length and angling into Pollard's pads, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a brace]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sreenath Aravind [2.0-0-6-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Aravind comes from round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Simmons, no run, Harshal shortened the length as Simmons came down the track, he swivels across and gets an inside edge on the pull, straight to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Pollard, 1 run, Harshal bangs one short and on the stumps as Pollard came down the track, he's hurried onto the pull, gets a bottom edge towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Pollard, no run, short of a length and just outside off, punched back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Simmons, 1 run, fuller length delivery and on Simmons' pads, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Pollard, 1 run, short of a length and angling into Pollard, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kieron Pollard, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Rohit, <b>out</b> Caught by Mandeep!! Massive blow for MUM, they lose their skipper. Excellent piece of bowling from Harshal, he held this one back slightly as Rohit made room for the lofted shot. It's the off-cutter, there was no pace on the ball, Rohit had to reach out for the shot, he loses control over it and ends up lobbing it down the throat of long-on. <b>Rohit c Mandeep b Harshal Patel 15(13) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Harshal Patel to Rohit, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel [1.0-0-10-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Simmons, 2 runs, this one is given more air by Chahal, Simmons works it with the spin and in front of mid-wicket. Rohit wants the second run and the two batsmen complete it with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Rohit, 1 run, Rohit shimmies down the track to a well flighted delivery and drives it to the left of the bowler. He dives and palms it towards cover, can't stop the single though]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Rohit, no run, tossed up slower and on the off-stump line, dabbed in front of short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Simmons, 1 run, Chahal drifts one on the leg-stump line and gets it to turn across Simmons, nudged in front of mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Simmons, no run, pushed through flatter and just outside off, Simmons makes room and cuts it straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Rohit, 1 run, tossed up and on the stumps, Rohit pushes forward and gets an inside edge past square leg, just a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuzvendra Chahal, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Rohit, 1 run, fuller length delivery and outside off, driven straight to Kohli at cover. Simmons was backing up and Kohli has a shy at his end, he misses and concedes an overthrow]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Rohit, <b>SIX</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, the slower ball goes wrong for Wiese, drops it halfway down the pitch, Rohit swivels across and pulls it high and over mid-wicket for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Rohit, no run, slower short ball from Wiese, Rohit looks to cut and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[Karthik is up to the stumps for Rohit]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Simmons, 1 run, Simmons shimmies down the track to a short of a length delivery and slaps it towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Karthik goes back to his original position]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, clever batting from Simmons, this was full and just outside off, he was looking for the yorker, Simmons waits on it, opens the face of the bat at the last moment and runs it past the keeper for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Rohit, 1 run, on a good length and on the stumps, eased to the left of Gayle at mid-wicket. He runs across and keeps them down to a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Rohit, 1 run, Harshal keeps it full and on Rohit's pads, tucked away in front of square on the on-side, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Simmons, 1 run, full toss on the stumps, whipped away towards deep mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Simmons, 2 runs, the bouncer from Harshal, Simmons charges down the track and pulls it wide of mid-on, the ball slows down near the ropes, just a couple of runs for Simmons]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Simmons, <b>SIX</b>, Simmons breaks free! This was pitched up and in the zone for Simmons, he steps down the track, hits it with the angle and clears mid-wicket with ease, first maximum of the innings]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Simmons, no run, nicely bowled by Patel, followed Simmons as he backed away, the length was very full. Simmons can only squeeze it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Simmons, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Simmons heaves and gets a thick inside edge towards mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, if AB can do it, so can I, says Rohit, goes down on his knees to a full ball and sweeps it behind square on the on-side, no one in the deep and the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Rohit, no run, pitched up and just outside off, Rohit presses forward and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[The keeper is up to the stumps now]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Rohit, no run, Wiese keeps it on a good length and just outside off, Rohit runs down the track and gets an inside edge on the hoick]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Rohit, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Rohit is early into the drive and gets an inside edge towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Rohit, <b>wide</b>, Wiese goes wider outside off and gets it to shape away, left alone by Rohit, called as a wide though]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Simmons, 1 run, Wiese slips in the slower ball, Simmons comes down the track and mistimes the drive towards mid-on, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Simmons, no run, short of a length and just outside off, dabbed away straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit Sharma, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Simmons, <b>out</b> Parthiv Patel Run Out!! Unlucky for Parthiv Patel, the bat got jammed in front of the return crease and he wasn't able to ground it properly. Excellent work though by Kohli and Karthik. This was short and just outside off, Simmons hopped across and punched it in front of cover-point, calls for a quick single. Parthiv was quick to respond, but the accurate throw finds him short of his ground. <b>Parthiv Patel run out (Kohli/D Karthik) 19(11) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Aravind to Simmons, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[The third umpire has been called for a run-out chance. Parthiv Patel is the man in question. He is <b>OUT</b>. Or is he? He's definitely short, but did Karthik remove the bails before the ball slipped out of his grasp. The third umpire decides in favour of the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Simmons, no run, this is good bowling from Aravind, short of a length and just outside off, no room for Simmons, he backs away and dabs it straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Parthiv Patel, 1 run, Aravind slips in the slower ball, Parthiv was way too early on the heave, gets an inside edge behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Simmons, 1 run, <b>just short of Wiese at mid-on</b>, short of a length and on the stumps, Simmons backs away and muscles the pull towards mid-on, drops in front of the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Parthiv Patel, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, dabbed in front of backward point for a quick single. The fielder shies at the striker's end and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Simmons, 1 run, short of a length and on Simmons' pads, tucked away behind square on the on-side. Chahal makes a tumbling stop and keeps them down to a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Parthiv Patel, <b>FOUR</b>, this is excellent cricket from Parthiv, comes down the track, takes the ball on the full and drills it past cover, third boundary of the over. MUM are off and running]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Parthiv Patel, no run, yorker length delivery and just outside off, Parthiv jams it out towards point. AB rushes in and prevents the chance of a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Parthiv Patel, <b>FOUR</b>, that's nicely played by Parthiv, fraction too straight from Starc, Parthiv gets inside the line, delays the flick and gets it fine past short fine, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Parthiv Patel, no run, Starc keeps it full and gets it to nip back into Parthiv, he was shuffling across on the flick and gets an inside edge onto the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Parthiv Patel, <b>FOUR</b>, that's much better from Parthiv, tad fuller and shaping back in, Parthiv presses forward, presents the full face of the bat and punches it back past the bowler for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Parthiv Patel, 2 runs, short and climbing onto Parthiv, he wasn't in complete control over the pull, just manages enough to clear Wiese at mid-wicket, comes back for the second run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Simmons, no run, tad fuller and in that zone outside off, Simmons goes hard on the drive and mistimes it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Simmons, no run, nicely bowled by Aravind, saw Simmons coming down the track and shortened his length, pushed towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Parthiv Patel, 1 run, short of a length and angling into Parthiv's pads, flicked away past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Simmons, 1 run, Aravind slips in the slower ball, Simmons leans forward and pushes it in front of mid-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Simmons, no run, the off-cutter from Aravind, Simmons reaches out and pushes it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aravind to Simmons, no run, short of a length and on Simmons' pads, he looks to flick and misses, the ball brushed his thigh on the way to the keeper]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sreenath Aravind, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Simmons, 1 run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Simmons looks to drive and gets a thick inside edge towards square leg. Chahal fumbles and allows a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Simmons, no run, yorker length delivery and just outside off, Simmons plays with an open face and squeezes it straight to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, half-volley on Simmons' pads, he gets inside the line and clips it effortlessly past mid-on, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Parthiv Patel, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, pushed in front of mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Simmons, 1 run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, Simmons pushes forward and gets an inside edge behind square, off the mark with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Parthiv Patel, 1 run, full and on the stumps, flicked away behind square for a single to long leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Parthiv Patel, <b>wide</b>, short of a length and slipping down leg-side, Parthiv looks to flick and misses, called as a wide]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Parthiv Patel and Simmons are at the crease. Parthiv Patel is on strike. Starc will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. It was carnage in the first innings. Can MUM do something similar? They will have to get past Mitchell Starc first.. A slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[At the end of the innings, AB was congratulated by Bhajji and then he walked off to a standing ovation. Gayle and the entire Bangalore team were on their feet to welcome AB in]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>AB de Villiers:</b> "I started with five dots, a little bit nervous at the beginning. One of the best players in the world, if not the best supported me and it was my day. A couple of lucky bounces and it went my way. That's alright - can't play for those kind of things (when mentioned he didn't get enough strike in the last over to have a crack at the Orange Cap). It is a small ground and it is a good wicket. Little bit on the slower side and Virat communicated really with me. I hit a couple early on in my innings and it was my day."]]></line><line><![CDATA[At the other end of the spectrum, Kohli played with composure to score a fifty. It has to be said that the hosts didn't help their cause by dropping catches. Gayle's drop catch didn't cost them much. However, they would rue the fact that Kohli was given a reprieve when he was on six. McClenaghan was the unlucky bowler on both occasions.  For MUM, the only bowler, who bowled with good control was Malinga.]]></line><line><![CDATA[AB de Villiers' sparkling spread of run-scoring powered BLR to a mammoth total. After Chris Gayle was dismissed early on in the innings, de Villiers and Virat Kohli strung together a marvellous stand. It was in the eighth over when de Villiers opened up his shoulders to cart Harbhajan Singh for a four and a six. He gave a glimpse of his ability to play shots all over the ground by sweeping MUM's spearhead Lasith Malinga for a four. de Villiers then reached his ton off just 47 balls in style by thwacking Bumrah for a six. Once de Villiers reached his hundred, he took his game to dizzying heights by walloping Pandya for 14 runs in the 18th over. de Villiers' knock turned out to be the highest score in this year's IPL. The stunning partnership of 215 between Kohli and de Villiers is now the highest stand for any wicket in the history of the IPL.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Kohli, no run, finally Pandya gets the yorker out. Off the final delivery, dug out back to the bowler. A dot to end the innings]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Kohli, <b>SIX</b>, the gifts continue. Ridiculous tactics from Mumbai. They seem to have given up. Another full toss on the stumps, heaved over wide long-on. Hit a long way back into the stands, six more to the total. Rohit grimaces]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, another full toss, would you believe that? So easy for Kohli as he simply lofts it inside out over cover, one bounce over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, full toss on the pads, whipped stylishly over mid-wicket, the fielder went to his left but couldn't get there. This is bad bowling and gifts for the BLR batsmen]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Kohli, 2 runs, has Rohit been hit on the mouth? Or on the chin? Yes he has been. He is down for sometime but gets up and is ok to continue. Worried faces in the crowd. Rohit charged in from mid-wicket to take the catch, it bounced in front of him and hit him on the chin. He didn't get up for 20-25 seconds but then rises. In the meantime the batsmen take two as the throw comes in to the striker's end. Kohli made it back with a dive]]></line><line><![CDATA[de Villiers went up to Kohli to have a word]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to de Villiers, 1 run, de Villiers comes down the track and gets too close to the pitch of the ball, squeezes it out to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to de Villiers, 1 run, skips out and reaches out to toe-end a drive to cover, they scamper a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, everyone in on the off-side and de Villiers eyed that area. Great shot too. Malinga did nothing wrong there, followed the backing away de Villiers, but de Villiers was too good. It was full and outside leg, but de Villiers lofted it over cover after shifting his weight well back. Genius stuff!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to de Villiers, 2 runs, de Villiers comes down the track and takes it on the full, lofted straight down the ground, for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Kohli, 1 run, low full toss on the stumps, wristed to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to de Villiers, 1 run, very full on the stumps, de Villiers clears his front leg and smashes it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to de Villiers, <b>wide</b>, de Villiers gets the better of Malinga. Allan Donald and Varun Aaron are all smiles in the dugout. de Villiers outsmarted Malinga there, went outside leg then came back in line, Malinga fired that well outside leg and rightly called wide. Malinga has a word with the umpire but to no avail]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, a one-handed sweep for four. One-bounce four. Malinga just goes "oooo". de Villiers kneels down and knows that Malinga will target the stumps with a full toss or an yorker, swept behind square]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga [3.0-1-13-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Kohli, no run, yorker length outside off, Kohli fails to dig it out. Some sanity at last. Pandya got it right off the final delivery of the over. Needed to hit those lengths earlier]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, another full toss on the stumps, Kohli heaves it wide of Pollard at long-on, to the big man's right and he had no chance of stopping that. This is cutting Mumbai into pieces]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to de Villiers, 1 run, very full on the stumps, clipped to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, more power from de Villiers, more runs. Muscled straight down the ground, Pollard ran around from long-on and dived but could just get a fingertip on it, ran past him and into the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to de Villiers, <b>SIX</b>, Gayle with just a towel draped across his shoulders, asks the ball to come and hit him with a smile on his face. Low full toss and de Villiers lofted it over long-off. The ball almost went into the BLR dugout]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, Pandya's cutters isn't going to pose any problems to de Villiers. Full on the stumps, de Villiers clears his front leg and blasts it straight down the ground, nearly cleaned the umpire up there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Hardik Pandya [1.0-0-15-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Kohli, <b>SIX</b>, these full tosses aren't helping Mumbai one bit. Low full toss and Kohli lofted it over wide long-on, easily done. <b>25 off that over</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to de Villiers, <b>no ball</b>, 1 run, high full toss and called a no-ball, over the waist and de Villiers awkwardly helps it away to the fine leg region]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to de Villiers, no run, tries to be a little too cute and misses out, it was a low full toss down leg, de Villiers tries to reverse paddle and misses out, may have got a feather on that, not sure, goes to the keeper on the bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to de Villiers, <b>SIX</b>, <b>100 for de Villiers.</b> Kohli has de Villiers in a bear hug. That legend - Sammy is on his feet clapping. de Villiers does a jig celebrating, pointing at someone. Maybe at Sammy or Gayle. Not sure. He got to his 100 with a powerful slog across the line, picked the slower delivery from outside off and sent it way back into the deep mid-wicket stands. This has been an outstanding knock. <b>Second IPL hundred for de Villiers and first for BLR</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to de Villiers, <b>SIX</b>, Allan Donald applauds that from the dugout. Gets outside off and on one knee, low full toss on the stumps, de Villiers sweeps it into the stands at fine leg, that went a long way, got plenty of elevation to deposit that]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Kohli, 1 run, low full toss on the stumps, Kohli takes a step out and wrists it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, Kohli gets into the act. Full outside off, driven powerfully along the ground through cover and long-off running to his left can't get there, that scorched across the turf]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jasprit Bumrah [3.0-0-27-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, short outside off, and de Villiers doesn't pull, but flat-bats it over mid-off, inside the ring. How on earth does he have the field mapped out in his brain? Only he will know. Moved slightly outside off and hit it. Into the nineties now]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Kohli, 1 run, tucks the length ball on the stumps through mid-wicket and gets to his <b>fifty</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to de Villiers, 1 run, short from McClenaghan again, de Villiers murdered the pull but Rayudu was quick to get across from deep mid-wicket to keep it to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, has it hit the ad-cushions on the full? No. Bounced just before. So four. Short on the stumps, pulled over mid-wicket, into the gap and de Villiers gets to 87]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to de Villiers, 2 runs, short of length on the stumps, de Villiers pulls it hard and Rayudu does well to run and then slide from deep mid-wicket to keep it to two]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Kohli, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Kohli gets forward and pushes it to extra cover, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [3.0-0-27-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Kohli, 1 run, looked like the cutter stopped on Kohli as he skipped out, one hand comes off the bat handle and he chips it uppishly to long-on, well in front of the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to de Villiers, 1 run, good delivery, yorker on the stumps, dug out to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, and what does de Villiers do. Go over mid-off. Pandya helped de Villiers there with a full toss, lifted over the fielder. Hat-trick of boundaries and Kohli goes up to de Villiers to pat him on the back]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mid-off up]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, look at that now. de Villiers goes well outside off and deep in his crease, it was bowled wide outside off, still somehow de Villiers gets elevation to clear cover, once he did that it was four all the way]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, de Villiers is just toying with the bowling now. Full and wide outside off, de Villiers got it wide of cover and sweeper couldn't get there]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Kohli, 1 run, an off-cutter to start off with from Pandya, Kohli pushes it to long-off. Tells de Villiers that Pandya is bowling cutters]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Hardik Pandya, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two of the best batsmen in the world at the crease for Bangalore. But it is de Villiers who is batting on a different planet. He is making it look so simple and easy. Kohli on the other hand isn't quite up to de Villiers' level. That's the difference between the two who would like to compare the two of them. Kohli still some way off reaching de Villiers' level. May get there some day but not currently. Undoubtedly de Villiers is the best batsman in the world at the present moment in all formats. Today he is just showing everyone why he is the world's best.]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to de Villiers, 2 runs, even Polly is fumbling now, but no extra damage done, low full toss on the stumps, swung wide of long-on, Polly tried to pick it up with one hand and missed, Rayudu mops up from deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to de Villiers, 2 runs, yorker on middle and leg, dug out in front of mid-on, easy two by the time long-on comes around to field]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, Rayudu did all the hard work but gives away four. Slower on the stumps, de Villiers swipes it with fabulous timing and it raced across the turf, Rayudu went to his left at deep mid-wicket, slid and pushed it back but the ball slipped over the ad-cushions]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Kohli, 1 run, Bumrah follows Kohli as the batsman advanced down the track, clipped to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to de Villiers, 1 run, full on the stumps, heaved to deep mid-wicket, Kohli sends de Villiers back as the fielder came in quickly. Also Kohli was running to the danger end there]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Kohli, 1 run, short of length outside off, a flat-batted slap to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jasprit Bumrah [2.0-0-16-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to de Villiers, no run, magnificent from Rohit at cover. Saved a certain boundary. Full and outside off, de Villiers smashed the drive alongh the ground, it was speeding until Rohit dived full length to his right and came out with the ball in his hand. Sensational stuff]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, de Villiers knows the field inside out. Kneels down and then sweeps Malinga for four. Full toss on the stumps, de Villiers gets it over mid-wicket, no-one in the deep there and another four to de Villiers]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Kohli, 1 run, yorker length outside off, dug out to cover, quick single taken this time]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Kohli, no run, yorker length outside off, squeezed out to backward point, de Villiers sends Kohli back]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to de Villiers, 1 run, full toss and de Villiers thumps it straight down the ground, Polly keeps it down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Tense faces in the Mumbai camp. Unless they get de Villiers out quickly here, the game is slipping away from their grasp. Rohit recognises that and has gone for Malinga]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Kohli, 1 run, low full toss on off, Kohli swings and gets a thick inside edge to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga [2.0-1-6-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, poor delivery from McClenaghan and de Villiers doesn't need any special invitation right now. Slower off-cutter outside off, sat up to be hit and de Villiers rocked back to cut hard, gives sweeper no chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, de Villiers still gets four. Wide of Pollard at long-on. <b>Fifty</b> for de Villiers too. His mates stand up and applaud from the dugout. Raced down and then smashed the full ball along the ground, Polly had little distance to cover but the ball sped away across the turf]]></line><line><![CDATA[McClenaghan is bowling from round the wicket to both batsmen to cut the angle and cramp them for room]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Kohli, 1 run, Kohli comes down the track and then pushes the full ball to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to de Villiers, 1 run, well bowled by McClenaghan, followed de Villiers with a short delivery, it was rearing onto him, he was trying to ramp that away, but it cramped him for room and he manages to awkwardly deflect it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Kohli, 1 run, short of length outside off, dabbed with an open face to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Kohli, 2 runs, Kohli closes the face of the bat and turns it to the left of short fine, Malinga is the fielder who is a bit slow and the batsmen recognise that, hare back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [2.0-0-14-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Kohli, 1 run, on middle and leg, whipped off the back foot to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to de Villiers, 1 run, fraction short outside off, cut to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, fabulous from de Villiers. Backs away, then comes back to his original position, takes it on the full and sweeps powerfully to the deep backward square leg fence, no chance for the fielder at deep square leg, de Villiers manipulated Suchith brilliantly there]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Kohli, 1 run, Jagadeesha Suchith pulls the length back, seeing Kohli advance, punched to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Kohli, <b>SIX</b>, when he hit it, I thought he had holed out, but it goes all the way over long-on. The bat turned as he came down the track to loft it, still had enough to clear Rayudu]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Kohli, no run, Jagadeesha Suchith follows the advancing Kohli, Kohli flicks and gets an inside edge onto the pads]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Kohli, 1 run, Harbhajan fires this one outside off, Kohli just calmly pushes it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Kohli, <b>SIX</b>, Kohli goes over mid-wicket and gets six. Skips out and hoicks the offie way back into the stands. Timed superbly to get the elevation. Got to the pitch and hit it for a biggie]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to de Villiers, 1 run, flat outside off, de Villiers went for a hard cut but mistimed it to long-off, that cramped him for room]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to de Villiers, <b>3 wides</b>, Harbhajan loses it and bowls it well down leg, the keeper can't stop it and they take two extra runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Kohli, 1 run, short and spinning down leg, pulled to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Kohli, 2 runs, two to mid-wicket. de Villiers was the one who pushed Kohli, turned to the right of Rohit and hit softly to get two. Great running]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to de Villiers, 1 run, Harbhajan from round the wicket now, tossed up and de Villiers takes a step to push straight down the ground]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to de Villiers, 1 run, fired in on the pads, flicked to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, that fumble brings de Villiers back on strike and he gets four more. What a brilliant shot that is again from de Villiers, it wasn't all that short but de Villiers went back and lofted it over cover, de Lange this time was a mere spectator]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to de Villiers, 2 runs, more sloppiness from Mumbai in the field. It is the sub - de Lange now, cut to him at sweeper and he fumbles to give an extra run. Rohit is unhappy]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, de Villiers is timing the ball so well. Not good signs for Mumbai. Another flick along the ground and to the left of short fine, Simmons was the fielder, he put in the dive but didn't get there]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Kohli, 1 run, flat on the stumps, Kohli gets back and wrists it through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Kohli, no run, tossed up outside off, driven straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jagadeesha Suchith [1.0-0-10-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to de Villiers, <b>SIX</b>, de Villiers is attacking Harbhajan and gets six. Down the track in a jiffy and then flicks the off-break over mid-wicket, it has the legs to go all the way, kept the fielder interested for a while but it sailed over him]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, what timing from de Villiers. It was just a push again, off the front foot, beats Bumrah at cover and gave sweeper no chance. How did that go for four? I'm stunned as would millions of people watching]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Kohli, 1 run, now Kohli comes down the track and wrists a bottom-handed drive to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to de Villiers, 1 run, tossed up and de Villiers comes down the track to flick to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to de Villiers, 2 runs, tossed up outside off, de Villiers pulls out the reverse sweep to deep backward point, McClenaghan runs around to prevent the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Kohli, 1 run, offie, turning in, nudged to backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harbhajan Singh, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Kohli, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Kohli closes the face of the bat and pushes it past the diving short mid-wicket, a single after it slips past the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to de Villiers, 1 run, de Villiers skips out and goes outside off, to punch that down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to de Villiers, 2 runs, full outside off, de Villiers lofts over cover, Hardik Pandya at sweeper moves to his right quickly but can't prevent the two]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to de Villiers, no run, short of length outside off, driven on the rise but straight to the fielder at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Kohli, 1 run, full outside off, Kohli drives and gets a thick edge along the ground to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Kohli, 2 runs, slashed off the front foot square of the wicket, past the diving Pollard at point, Kohli wants two and makes it as the throw is wide. A better throw would've made things interesting]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to de Villiers, no run, de Villiers has missed out there, rocked back and mistimed the pull straight to the fielder at backward square leg, if he got it past that man it would've been another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, brilliant from de Villiers. Even the bowler is impressed. Jagadeesha Suchith has his tongue out. It was nothing but a push after he came down the track, Malinga at mid-on didn't dive there and once it went past him it was timed so well that it raced away. Needed the dive]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, over cover. de Villiers is looking to back away and play against Jagadeesha Suchith, this was slightly short and that allowed de Villiers to clear the infield. Fine shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to de Villiers, no run, tosses it up on the stumps, de Villiers makes room and pushes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to Kohli, 1 run, shortish, Kohli goes back and plays a short-arm pull, straight to the fielder at deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jagadeesha Suchith to de Villiers, 1 run, flat and on the stumps, de Villiers makes room and hits it wide of Jagadeesha Suchith who was diving to his left]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jagadeesha Suchith, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to de Villiers, 1 run, good length and around off, nips back in a tad, de Villiers dabs it with soft hands to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Kohli, 1 run, angling in again, Kohli shuffles across and tucks it through square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[No slip now]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, Kohli takes charge. Races down the track and then hits it on the rise, through cover, no-one moved as it raced away]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Kohli, no run, angling in on a back of a length on the stumps, Kohli closes the face of the bat a bit early and pushes it tentatively back down the track]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to de Villiers, 1 run, short of length outside off, dabbed fine to third man, Suchith does well to keep it to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Kohli, 1 run, short of length outside off, wristed through the vacant mid-wicket area, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Kohli, <b>wide</b>, sliding down leg, Kohli flicks and misses, wide called]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jasprit Bumrah, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to de Villiers, no run, full outside off, de Villiers hits it on the rise but can't beat cover. It is a packed off-side field out there]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to de Villiers, no run, pitched up outside off, driven well but finds cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to de Villiers, no run, short of length outside off, defended to the left of Malinga who leaps and fields]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to de Villiers, no run, pitched up outside off, a cracking drive from de Villiers on the rise, but mid-off runs and dives to his right to save four runs. That is a fine piece of fielding and applause from the Mumbai dugout for that effort]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to de Villiers, no run, short of length outside off, defended back to Malinga]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>AB de Villiers, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Gayle, <b>out</b> Caught by Simmons!! Simmons shows his mates how to do it. A replay of the catch he took last game. Gayle walks off with a wry smile on his face. It was the slower delivery outside off, width was there but Gayle edged the cut, it was going to the left of short third man and eluding Simmons, but he leaps to his left and gets both hands, hangs on. All the Mumbai fielders go to him. McClenaghan manages a smile as well. Simmons was airborne as he took that. Sensational stuff, not as brilliant as the one he took to dismiss Yuvraj, but still superb. <b>Gayle c Simmons b Malinga 13(12) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Malinga to Gayle, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Kohli, no run, pitched up outside off, pushed off the front foot to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Kohli, no run, <b>now dropped by Harbhajan at slip.</b> What is going on, Mumbai? McClenaghan again with a cry of anguish. This is hurting him big time, Kohli gave the charge and edged the big drive, it went comfortably to Bhajji at slip who tried to take it reverse cup and put it down, very sloppy by Mumbai. McClenaghan came round the wicket and got the edge, but he has no luck. Will these drops hurt Mumbai, come the end of the day?]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Gayle, 1 run, <b>Rohit has dropped Gayle.</b> How costly could that turn out to be? Gayle made room and skied the length ball straight up as he was cramped for room, it went way up and Rohit circled around it at mid-on, got both hands and out it went, Rohit tried to grab the rebound and failed. McClenaghan is down on his knees and almost in tears]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Kohli, 1 run, short of length outside off, dabbed to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, Malinga has given away four at fine leg. McClenaghan and Rohit aren't happy at all. It was short down leg, Kohli swivel-pulled it to the right of Malinga who overran the ball and let it slip through his hands. A single turns out to be four]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Kohli, no run, short of length outside off, dabbed with an open face to point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Gayle, <b>FOUR</b>, thick outside edge and it flies over backward point. Gayle saw the slower delivery outside off and threw his bat at it, no-one at third man and once he got it over the infield it was four]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Gayle, no run, very full and swinging back in to off stump, Gayle drives hard to cover, no timing again]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Kohli, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Kohli gets forward to drive and gets a thick inside edge that misses the stumps and goes down to fine leg. Kohli got lucky there]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Gayle, 1 run, full on leg stump, flicked to deep backward square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Gayle, no run, another cutter, shortish outside off, Gayle goes hard on the cut and mistimes it to backward point, tried to hit the leather off it and that foiled the timing]]></line><line><![CDATA[Already there is eyeballing going on between Polly and Kohli. After Polly stopped the drive, there ensued a staring match without a word being spoken. This could get very spicy today]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Gayle, no run, Malinga begins with a slower delivery outside off, Gayle pushes out tentatively and is beaten, doesn't carry to the keeper]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Kohli, no run, that's more good fielding, at point now by Pollard, pitched up outside off, Kohli gets forward and opens the face of the bat to square drive, timed it well but Polly dives and saves at least a couple, if not a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Gayle, 1 run, McClenaghan keeps it short and that's good fielding by Hardik Pandya sliding to his right at deep mid-wicket, kept it to a single as the shot was laced with power, Gayle pulled it again]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Gayle, no run, bit more oomph in that short delivery, hurries onto Gayle who tries to pull and inside-edges it onto the leg, the ball rolls to cover, McClenaghan cramped Gayle for room there]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Gayle, <b>SIX</b>, very predictable from McClenaghan and Gayle was waiting for it, short outside off, Gayle fetches the pull and hits it over mid-wicket. That was cracked by Gayle, off the mark in style]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Gayle, <b>wide</b>, bouncer, too high and called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Gayle, no run, back of a length outside off, bit of extra bounce for McClenaghan that time, again Gayle leaves, this time in an extravagant fashion turning his body around as he shouldered arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>The King of cool - Gayle is batting in shades</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Gayle, no run, short of length outside off, Gayle shoulders arms and the ball loops - tennis ball style to the keeper]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Gayle and Kohli are at the crease. Gayle is on strike. McClenaghan will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Gayle will face]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Mumbai team were in a huddle. Gayle and Kohli walk out to the middle. It will be McClenaghan who will start proceedings. Very hot day in Mumbai. Will test the players. Gayle failed against Mumbai in Bangalore. Can he make up for that today? Let's wait and watch]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mumbai</b> (Playing XI): Lendl Simmons, Parthiv Patel(w), Rohit Sharma(c), Ambati Rayudu, Kieron Pollard, Hardik Pandya, Harbhajan Singh, Jagadeesha Suchith, Mitchell McClenaghan, Jasprit Bumrah, Lasith Malinga]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore</b> (Playing XI): Chris Gayle, Virat Kohli(c), AB de Villiers, Dinesh Karthik(w), Sarfaraz Khan, Mandeep Singh, David Wiese, Harshal Patel, Mitchell Starc, Sreenath Aravind, Yuzvendra Chahal]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit</b>: "The pitch has always been good throughout the 40 overs here. We all know we have to win but we are taking this as just another game. It's important to keep doing the right things. We've got two changes, <b>Malinga is back</b> and Bumrah comes in for Vinay Kumar."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kohli</b>: "We are going to bat first. Looks like it is a really nice wicket. The boys are coping up with all the travel. They want to win, we want to win as well. Same XI for us."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Toss time</b>!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Stay tuned to find out the team changes. Toss coming up in a few minutes....]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-head:</b> The score is 9-7 in favour of Mumbai in 16 previous meetings between both teams. Although MUM have a slight advantage, the competition has been very stiff and we can expect another cracking contest, for both sides are loaded with star players.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Since the inclusion of Mitchell Starc, BLR's bowling, which has been their weaklink over the years, has been bolstered. Returning to the side after a long time, Sreenath Aravind rattled the sticks at will at the Chinnaswamy a few days ago and along with Yuzvendra Chahal and Harshal Patel he would to look forward to do well on a pitch that has something to offer for bowlers. The BLR bowlers will have to be very careful at the death because the likes of Rohit, Kieron Pollard and Ambati Rayudu can change the game in an over.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Skipper Virat Kohli has not been in great touch, despite opening the innings. He has got starts,  but has struggled to convert it into a substantial score. Kohli also has to keep an eye on his strike-rate as he has not managed to score at a brisk pace on a consistent basis. What plans do MUM have to stop AB de Villiers? He's a special player and if you are not good enough, he will hurt you badly. Young Sarfaraz Khan has been very impressive and has grabbed eyeballs with his wide array of strokes. In fact, he would be confident of his game today because he is playing at his home ground.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The last time BLR played a game of cricket, Chris Gayle went berserk. In fact, he smashed PUN's attack to shreds. However, when these two sides met earlier in the season, Gayle played an uncharacteristic innings, which many believe cost BLR the match. He struggled to pick Malinga and was eventually knocked over by Harbhajan. Now, that he is fresh from playing a scintillating knock, he would like to settle scores with MUM.]]></line><line><![CDATA[MUM captain Rohit Sharma normally is a fine T20 player, but has not managed to record a fifty in his last seven games. However, he will fancy his chances to get one today because he normally bats well at the Wankhede. The good news for MUM is that <b>Lasith Malinga will be back in action</b>. Harbhajan Singh and Mitchell McClenaghan, who have done well so far, need to be at their best against a star-studded BLR batting line-up.]]></line><line><![CDATA[35, 42, 43, 111, 84 - these are the opening partnerships between Lendl Simmons and Parthiv Patel, barring MUM's home game against Delhi. So, in the last seven matches, the duo have got MUM off to a superb start. Although MUM have a fine middle-order, with a nice blend of experience and aggression, they rely on a good start to set the platform for the middle-order to come into play. When DEL got the early wicket, Mumbai struggled in their run chase and one can be sure that Allan Donald would have taken note of this and told Virat Kohli and his bowlers the importance of bowling well up front.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>14:45 Local Time, 09:15 GMT, 14:45 IST:</b> Having won their last five matches, Mumbai are on a roll. Can they make it six in a row? Well, they certainly have a great chance to do it, considering that they are playing at their fortress Wankhede today. However, to do so, they need to be at their best because they are up against the formidable Bangalore from Bangalore. Probably the fact that they beat BLR in their own backyard will give them the extra confidence going into this game. The morale of the team should be very high, especially after a thumping win against Chennai a couple of days ago.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview</b><br/><br/>Who would have expected Mumbai to turn around their fortunes so remarkably? After registering just one win in the first six matches of the season, Mumbai have been in red hot form. They've won their previous five matches and are placed at No 4 in the rankings. Furthermore, their stellar show against Chennai must have contributed a great deal to boost the team's confidence ahead of their crucial tie against the Bangalore. A win for either team will take them close to sealing a play-off berth, whereas a loss will jeopardise their chances to a great extent. The CHN-Rajasthan encounter will guarantee one team for the knockouts, which will leave MUM, BLR, RAJ, KOL and HYD jostling for remaining three spots.<br/><br/>A major chunk of Mumbai' success goes to the fact that all their players have stepped up to the occasion and exhibited individual brilliance. After Lendl Simmons, Lasith Malinga, Harbhajan Singh and the rest, it was Hardik Pandya's turn on Friday to leave an impact. Needing 30 off the last two overs, the Baroda batsman deposited left-arm spinner Pawan Negi for three sixes in the 19th over, allowing Mumbai to hand CHN their first loss at the Chepauk Stadium since 2013.<br/><br/>BLR are coming off a three-day gap after delivering a pounding to Punjab, knocking them out of the tournament. Similar to their opponents, BLR will also have their tail-up after a clinical performance at the M Chinnaswamy stadium, where Chris Gayle returned to his destructive self and hammered his fifth IPL century. It was coupled with splendid bowling performances from Mitchell Starc and Sreenath Aravind, both of whom picked up four wickets to complete a demolition of the opposition.<br/><br/>Both BLR and Mumbai have things in common - their start to the season was abysmal, but consistency and clarity in team composition has helped them stage a terrific comeback. Also, the availability of Starc and Lendl Simmons for their respective sides has paved way for encouraging performances.<br/><br/>Venue: Wankhede Stadium, Mumbai<br/><br/>Date & Time: May 10, 1600 IST<br/><br/><b>Team News</b><br/><br/><b>Mumbai</b><br/><br/>With Lasith Malinga now available to reclaim his spot in the line-up, South African pacer Marchant de Lange, who filled in and played his first game, is expected to be benched. Hardik Pandya seems to have sealed his spot after his match-winning cameo, so it might still be a while before Unmukt Chand gets a game back.<br/><br/>Probable XI: 1 Lendl Simmons, 2 Parthiv Patel (wk), 3 Rohit Sharma (capt), 4 Kieron Pollard, 5 Ambati Rayudu, 6 Hardik Pandya, 7 Harbhajan Singh, 8 J Suchith, 9 Vinay Kumar, 10 Lasith Malinga, 11 Mitchell McClenaghan<br/><br/><b>Bangalore Bangalor</b><br/><br/>BLR have been one of the strongest sides on paper, and are beginning to display the same on the ground. Their batting looks composed and the bowling sorted. Expect no change in their team composition unless someone is out injured.<br/><br/>Playing XI: 1 Chris Gayle, 2 Virat Kohli (capt), 3 Dinesh Karthik (wk), 4 AB de Villiers, 5 Sarfaraz Khan, 6 Mandeep Singh, 7 David Wiese, 8 Mitchell Starc, 9 Harshal Patel, 10 Yuzvendra Chahal, Sreenath Aravind<br/><br/><b>Quotes</b><br/><br/>I was batting very well in the nets. It is good that they had the faith and sent me ahead of Bhajji Pa (Harbhajan Singh). The side boundaries are long and it was easier to clear the straight boundary, than the side ones - Hardik Pandya on being promoted ahead of Harbhajan Singh.<br/><br/>It's been interesting working with [Mitchell] Starc in the nets. Everyone knows he's been a superb bowler for Australia recently. I've picked up many things from him. Yorker is his biggest weapon, so I've learnt quite a bit - Sreenath Aravind says he's leart quite a bit from the Australian pacer.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore</b> (From): Virat Kohli(c), Chris Gayle, AB de Villiers, Mandeep Singh, Dinesh Karthik(w), Sarfaraz Khan, David Wiese, Harshal Patel, Mitchell Starc, Sreenath Aravind, Yuzvendra Chahal, Nic Maddinson, Varun Aaron, Ashok Dinda, Vijay Zol, Abu Nechim, Sandeep Warrier, Yogesh Takawale, Rilee Rossouw, Iqbal Abdulla, Manvinder Bisla, S Badrinath, Darren Sammy, Sean Abbott, Jalaj Saxena, Shishir Bhavane]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mumbai</b> (From): Lendl Simmons, Parthiv Patel(w), Rohit Sharma(c), Ambati Rayudu, Kieron Pollard, Hardik Pandya, Harbhajan Singh, Jagadeesha Suchith, Vinay Kumar, Mitchell McClenaghan, Lasith Malinga, Colin Munro, Aditya Tare, Jasprit Bumrah, Marchant de Lange, Pawan Suyal, Shreyas Gopal, Pragyan Ojha, Abhimanyu Mithun, Aiden Blizzard, Akshay Wakhare, Nitish Rana, Siddhesh Lad, Unmukt Chand, Ben Hilfenhaus, Corey Anderson]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>235</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>1</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Bangalore">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>247</playerid>
					<name>Chris Gayle</name>
					<batsman-name>Gayle</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Gayle</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>13</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Malinga</bowler>
					<bowlerId>111</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Lendl Simmons</fielder>
						<fielderId>599</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Kohli</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>82</runs>
					<balls>50</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>4</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>370</playerid>
					<name>AB de Villiers</name>
					<batsman-name>de Villiers</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>de Villiers</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>133</runs>
					<balls>59</balls>
					<fours>19</fours>
					<sixes>4</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>145</playerid>
					<name>Dinesh Karthik</name>
					<batsman-name>D Karthik</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>D Karthik</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9429</playerid>
					<name>Sarfaraz Khan</name>
					<batsman-name>Sarfaraz Khan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sarfaraz Khan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6319</playerid>
					<name>Mandeep Singh</name>
					<batsman-name>Mandeep</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mandeep</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8589</playerid>
					<name>David Wiese</name>
					<batsman-name>D Wiese</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Wiese</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8175</playerid>
					<name>Harshal Patel</name>
					<batsman-name>Harshal Patel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Harshal Patel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7710</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
					<batsman-name>M Starc</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Starc</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1850</playerid>
					<name>Sreenath Aravind</name>
					<batsman-name>Aravind</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Aravind</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7910</playerid>
					<name>Yuzvendra Chahal</name>
					<batsman-name>Chahal</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chahal</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>247</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>20</runs>
				<overs>3.1</overs>
				<batsman>Chris Gayle</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Gayle</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>6</wides>
			<noballs>1</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Mumbai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7624</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell McClenaghan</name>
					<bowler-name>McClenaghan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>McClenaghan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>40</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>111</playerid>
					<name>Lasith Malinga</name>
					<bowler-name>Malinga</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Malinga</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>27</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9311</playerid>
					<name>Jasprit  Bumrah</name>
					<bowler-name>Bumrah</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bumrah</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>52</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10357</playerid>
					<name>Jagadeesha Suchith</name>
					<bowler-name>Jagadeesha Suchith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Jagadeesha Suchith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>75</playerid>
					<name>Harbhajan Singh</name>
					<bowler-name>Harbhajan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Harbhajan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>30</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9647</playerid>
					<name>Hardik Pandya</name>
					<bowler-name>H Pandya</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Pandya</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>51</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>599</playerid>
					<name>Lendl Simmons</name>
					<bowler-name>L Simmons</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Simmons</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>74</playerid>
					<name>Parthiv Patel</name>
					<bowler-name>Parthiv Patel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Parthiv Patel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>576</playerid>
					<name>Rohit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Rohit</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rohit</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6311</playerid>
					<name>Ambati Rayudu</name>
					<bowler-name>Rayudu</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rayudu</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>657</playerid>
					<name>Kieron Pollard</name>
					<bowler-name>K Pollard</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Pollard</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>196</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>7</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Mumbai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>74</playerid>
					<name>Parthiv Patel</name>
					<batsman-name>Parthiv Patel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Parthiv Patel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>19</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Virat Kohli</fielder>
						<fielderId>1413</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Dinesh Karthik</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>145</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>599</playerid>
					<name>Lendl Simmons</name>
					<batsman-name>L Simmons</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Simmons</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>68</runs>
					<balls>53</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>576</playerid>
					<name>Rohit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Rohit</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rohit</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>15</runs>
					<balls>13</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Harshal Patel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8175</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mandeep Singh</fielder>
						<fielderId>6319</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>657</playerid>
					<name>Kieron Pollard</name>
					<batsman-name>K Pollard</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Pollard</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>49</runs>
					<balls>24</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Aravind</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1850</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mitchell Starc</fielder>
						<fielderId>7710</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9647</playerid>
					<name>Hardik Pandya</name>
					<batsman-name>H Pandya</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Pandya</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>8</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[stumped]]></status>
					<bowler>Chahal</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7910</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dinesh Karthik</fielder>
						<fielderId>145</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6311</playerid>
					<name>Ambati Rayudu</name>
					<batsman-name>Rayudu</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rayudu</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>14</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Harshal Patel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8175</bowlerId>
						<fielder>AB de Villiers</fielder>
						<fielderId>370</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>75</playerid>
					<name>Harbhajan Singh</name>
					<batsman-name>Harbhajan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Harbhajan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Starc</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7710</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Virat Kohli</fielder>
						<fielderId>1413</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10357</playerid>
					<name>Jagadeesha Suchith</name>
					<batsman-name>Jagadeesha Suchith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Jagadeesha Suchith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Chahal</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7910</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dinesh Karthik</fielder>
						<fielderId>145</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7624</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell McClenaghan</name>
					<batsman-name>McClenaghan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>McClenaghan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>12</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9311</playerid>
					<name>Jasprit  Bumrah</name>
					<batsman-name>Bumrah</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bumrah</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>111</playerid>
					<name>Lasith Malinga</name>
					<batsman-name>Malinga</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Malinga</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>74</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>29</runs>
				<overs>4</overs>
				<batsman>Parthiv Patel</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Parthiv Patel</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>576</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>63</runs>
				<overs>8.1</overs>
				<batsman>Rohit Sharma</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rohit</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>657</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>133</runs>
				<overs>14.2</overs>
				<batsman>Kieron Pollard</batsman>
				<batsman-name>K Pollard</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9647</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>143</runs>
				<overs>15.4</overs>
				<batsman>Hardik Pandya</batsman>
				<batsman-name>H Pandya</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6311</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>174</runs>
				<overs>17.3</overs>
				<batsman>Ambati Rayudu</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rayudu</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>75</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>178</runs>
				<overs>18.2</overs>
				<batsman>Harbhajan Singh</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Harbhajan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>10357</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>184</runs>
				<overs>19.2</overs>
				<batsman>Jagadeesha Suchith</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Jagadeesha Suchith</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>4</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Bangalore">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7710</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
					<bowler-name>M Starc</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Starc</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>41</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1850</playerid>
					<name>Sreenath Aravind</name>
					<bowler-name>Aravind</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Aravind</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>29</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8589</playerid>
					<name>David Wiese</name>
					<bowler-name>D Wiese</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Wiese</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>38</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8175</playerid>
					<name>Harshal Patel</name>
					<bowler-name>Harshal Patel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Harshal Patel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7910</playerid>
					<name>Yuzvendra Chahal</name>
					<bowler-name>Chahal</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chahal</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>51</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>247</playerid>
					<name>Chris Gayle</name>
					<bowler-name>Gayle</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Gayle</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<bowler-name>Kohli</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Kohli</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>370</playerid>
					<name>AB de Villiers</name>
					<bowler-name>de Villiers</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>de Villiers</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>145</playerid>
					<name>Dinesh Karthik</name>
					<bowler-name>D Karthik</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>D Karthik</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9429</playerid>
					<name>Sarfaraz Khan</name>
					<bowler-name>Sarfaraz Khan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sarfaraz Khan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6319</playerid>
					<name>Mandeep Singh</name>
					<bowler-name>Mandeep</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mandeep</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



