<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14653" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>Final</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Mumbai</home>
		<away>Chennai</away>
		<teamsabbr>MUM vs CHN</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>MUM</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>CHN</awayabbr>
		<homeId>62</homeId>
		<awayId>58</awayId>
		<venue>Eden Gardens, Kolkata</venue>
		<startdate>24 05 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>24 05 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Chennai</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Mumbai won by 41 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Mumbai</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>41</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Kumar Dharmasena</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Richard Illingworth</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Vineet Kulkarni</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Ranjan Madugalle</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>14:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150524181737</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>CHN</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>MUM</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>161</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>8</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>20</batteamovers>
		<status>Mumbai won by 41 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>587</playerid>
			<name>Ravindra Jadeja*</name>
			<batsman-name>R Jadeja</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>11</runs>
			<balls-faced>8</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>8181</playerid>
			<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
			<batsman-name>Mohit Sharma</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Mohit Sharma</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>21</runs>
			<balls-faced>7</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>2</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>7624</playerid>
			<name>Mitchell McClenaghan*</name>
			<bowler-name>McClenaghan</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>McClenaghan</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>25</runs>
			<wickets>3</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1449</playerid>
			<name>Vinay Kumar</name>
			<bowler-name>Vinay</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Vinay</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>39</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>203</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>1593</playerid>
<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
<player-runs>2</player-runs>
<player-balls>4</player-balls>
<runs>137</runs>
<wicket-nbr>8</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>7624</bowlerid>
<bowlername>McClenaghan</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>2</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[. W 4 1 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 Wd . W 1 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. W 1 1 1 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 2 6 2 6 4 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/MUM_CHN_MAY24/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[What a turnaround it has been for Mumbai. They were written off after losing the first four games, but they managed to stick together and bring out the best when the chips were down. Yet another IPL season comes to end. We witnessed some great knocks, great bowling spells and great fielding efforts. We enjoyed bringing it to you. Hope you've enjoyed it as well. The focus now moves to international cricket as the T20 carnival ends here. Looking forward to your company on another day. Take care, goodbye!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Below are some of the best <b>tweets</b> related to this game...]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Boria Majumdar:</b> Eden Gardens and @ImRo45 the love affair continues. Good captaincy. Credit to Ricky Ponting for the turnaround. Road too far for CHN.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Harsha Bhogle:</b> #CHN won the first over but nothing after that. It has been pretty one -sided actually. #MUMvsCHN]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kumar Sangakkara:</b> What an IPL for @mipaltan wonderful team effort. To win it from where they were at the start is true character and team belief and team work]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jigar Mehta:</b> The trend continues. Since 2011, the team that has finished 2nd in table has won the IPL. So the teams know what to do next season.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ishant Sharma:</b> Another brilliant season of IPL comes to an end. Congratulations @mipaltan. #MUMvCHN #IPLFinal]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Aakash Chopra:</b> #MUM worthy winners...Rohit Sharma's captaincy was the highlight of this season. #IPL]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sanjay Manjrekar:</b> Cricket logic prevailed. Good pitch & as expected, the better team won. Well done MUM ! Congrats Rohit & Ricky! #IPL2015]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>VVS Laxman:</b> Congratulations @mipaltan on winning the 2015 IPL. Really impressed with the way @ImRo45 lead the team. #IPLFinal]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rohit Sharma goes on the stage and gets the trophy from Jagmohan Dalmiya (BCCI President). Rohit's team-mates now go up and join their skipper to celebrate the moment. They pose for the cameras as confetti sprays in the background.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit</b>: "We played like true champions. Mumbai have shown great character. It was just a matter of putting everything on the field and I couldn't have asked for anything better. We've got guys in our team to do well. We always spoke about showing character. We won in 2013, but this is very sweet. We came from nowhere to win. Credit to all the boys for doing well. It was important that we got some momentum, it didn't happen at the start, but the turnaround was great."]]></line><line><![CDATA[The winners cheque of Rs. 15 crore goes to Rohit Sharma (Mumbai).]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhoni</b>: "I think they got too many on the board. First over was very good but the second wasn't and that was the instance when Mumbai gained momentum. The kind of momentum they built from that point, it was difficult for us. We didn't start well with the bat as well. There was some uneven bounce as the game progressed. They got some extra 10-15 runs and that can put a lot of pressure while chasing. This was more of a team effort. There are a few cricketers in our team who have not played to their potential but we have done well as a team. Losing Brendon McCullum was a big blow, he would have been perfect at the start for us today."]]></line><line><![CDATA[MS Dhoni (Chennai) gets a runners-up cheque for Rs. 10 crore]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now the match officials get their mementos.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bravo</b>: "First of all congratulations to the Mumbai for winning the final. That's the role for me in the team (to bowl at the death). They backed me to deliver in the slog overs. I just want to remind some people that I am still able to perform at the highest level. I missed cricket for two months and was very disappointed. I am happy to perform at this level."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo</b> gets the <b>Purple Cap</b> for taking 26 wickets.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>David Warner</b> wins the <b>Orange Cap</b> for scoring 562 runs in the season.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai</b> bag the <b>Fair Play award</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Iyer</b>: "I got to learn a lot from the seniors. It's a good feeling that seniors tag me as the emerging player. I just played on my instincts, backed my ability and I knew I had the potential to score the big runs."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shreyas Iyer</b> has been named the <b>Emerging Player</b> of the season.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Gayle</b> gets the <b>Maximum Sixes</b> award, for hitting <b>38 sixes.</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Best Catch</b> of the season award goes to <b>Dwayne Bravo</b>, for his breathtaking effort at long-on to dismiss Shane Watson in Chennai.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit Sharma</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his 26-ball 50.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the presentation.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sachin Tendulkar</b>: I wasn't nervous. We were just telling ourselves that it was just another match for us. It was all about going out there and executing our plans. The support staff was doing a good job. As and when my inputs were needed, I shared it with the batters. Overall, it has been a terrific turnaround after a poor start. It was a tough season for us, but we stuck together. Our batting picked up as time went by. They worked hard and got some victories, the time went by and we kept playing better cricket by the day. It's always great to be here.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jonty Rhodes:</b> We drop some, we take some. It was good to see some great ground fielding. I have sweated a great deal. I don't pull my hair out when I get stressed. The head coach is the one who takes the stress. I just do my bit with the fielding.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ponting:</b> It's been extremely satisfying. Coming to the ground today, I thought that it will be special if we win tonight. We have done it today. 6 games in the tournament and it was very stressful. The cricket we have played is first class. We probably played the best game of the tournament today. Rohit was very keen to get out early today. Unfortunately, Parthiv got out early today, he got his opportunity and he showed how good a player he is.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Harbhajan:</b> Feels great. The way we finished, we are really proud of it. I bowled well when the team wanted me to do well. We have done really well as a team. You can't really do well more than that. Doing well here, it really helped me get back into the Indian side. Hopefully, I can play like this for India as well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Malinga:</b> I have been with Mumbai every year. It's a great feeling. We didn't start well but we finished it right. Bowlers can do something different in T20 cricket, Mitchell (McClenaghan) did a great job for us. Everyone did well and that's why we are here today.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pollard:</b> No one would have believed that we will be here after the start we got. I can take the tape off. The staff and management have done well. I want to thank them as well for supporting us. The experienced players need to come to the party. Most of the experienced guys won games for us. Youngsters like Hardik too won game for us. It was a total team effort.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Bond:</b> Of course, it was not a great start for us. The boys have turned it around, they have been magnificent. The situation was not great at the start, but the character everyone has shown is great.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Anil Kumble:</b> It means a lot. Even two years ago, it was a similar kind of start. We won it against the same opposition and at the same venue. Credit to Rohit with the way he played. Obviously, when we got 200 on the board, it was going to be tough for the opposition. The support staff have done really well. Bhajji has been working really hard. He has been a great performer. McClenaghan and Malinga at the top, then Bhajji, Suchith and Vinay too bowled really well. The batters have done their job too.]]></line><line><![CDATA[There are a lot of player interviews being taken at the moment and we'll get you some of them in a short while.]]></line><line><![CDATA[While chasing down a monstrous target, CHN put up a listless show with the bat too. Dwayne Smith and Suresh Raina essayed useful knocks, but struggled to up the tempo. All of MUM's bowlers bowled with discipline to keep the opposition on their toes. The MUM camp will celebrate long and hard today. It undoubtedly has been a sterling comeback from MUM after they found themselves languishing at the bottom of the table in the league phase.]]></line><line><![CDATA[MUM's batsmen gave a superb exhibition of batting to ensure their second IPL title. The explosion of fireworks from the bat of Lendl Simmons and Rohit Sharma gave MUM a splendid start. Kieron Pollard and Ambati Rayudu then took over by constructing a crucial stand as they amassed a massive total. For the beleaguered CHN set-up, only Ashish Nehra bowled with purpose up front. However, he too was taken to the cleaners in the slog overs by Pollard.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The MUM dug-out runs out to the middle to join the celebrations. The players are ecstatic and they hug and congratulate each other. Meanwhile, the fireworks light up the night sky. MUM form a huddle near the pitch and celebrate. CHN walk out onto the field to congratulate the champions.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Mohit Sharma, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>Mumbai have won their second IPL title</b>. It was at this very venue that they thumped CHN for the crown in 2013 and two years later, they have repeated the feat. Coming back to the ball, Mohit throws the kitchen sink at this short of length delivery, gets a thick edge and it goes fine past the keeper for four. MUM become the second team to win the IPL twice after CHN and KOL]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Mohit Sharma, <b>SIX</b>, six more! Full and outside off stump, Mohit lofts it over extra-cover and it clears the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Mohit Sharma, 2 runs, full and just outside off stump, Mohit swings hard and gets a thick edge that flies over backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Mohit Sharma, <b>SIX</b>, oh he's hit that a long way up in the air and it's gone deep into the stands. Short of a length delivery outside off stump, Mohit smashes it over sweeper cover for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Mohit Sharma, 2 runs, advances and drives the full ball to extra-cover for a quick single, Rohit has a needless shy at the bowler's end and concedes an extra run]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, full toss outside off stump, driven gently to deep extra-cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Vinay Kumar [3.0-0-18-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Mohit Sharma, no run, short delivery on the leg stump, Mohit pulls and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, short ball on the leg stump, Jadeja pulls it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Mohit Sharma, 1 run, backs away, exposes all his sticks and punches it square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, full toss from round the wicket, Jadeja glances it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Ashwin, <b>out</b> Caught by Jagadeesha Suchith!! Ashwin goes across the stumps, lines himself up for a big hit over cow corner, it was full and in the slot, Ashwin swings hard, but only manages to get the toe-end of the bat, the ball goes high in the air, deep mid-wicket runs forward and takes a simple catch. <b>Ashwin c Jagadeesha Suchith b McClenaghan 2(4)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[McClenaghan to Ashwin, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Ashwin, no run, yorker length delivery outside off stump, Ashwin tries to squeeze it out but misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [3.0-0-22-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Malinga ends 4-0-25-2.]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Ashwin, 1 run, backs away to this slower delivery and taps it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, fullish and on the off stump, Jadeja looks to defend off the front foot, gets an inside edge that rolls through square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Ashwin, 1 run, slower delivery on the off stump, Ashwin taps it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Negi, <b>out</b> Caught by Pandya!! Leading edge and that's a dolly to Pandya. Slower delivery on the off stump, Negi looks to work on the on-side, is foxed by the change of pace, plays early and the edge flies straight to backward point. After taking the catch, Pandya takes his cap off, drops it down, has his hands aloft in joy and celebrates in Shahid Afridi style. In fact, looks like he was also showing off his new hairstyle. <b>Negi c Pandya b Malinga 3(5)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Malinga to Negi, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Negi, no run, edged but doesn't carry to the keeper. Negi slogs at this slower delivery and gets the toe-end of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Negi, <b>wide</b>, slower delivery way outside off stump, left alone and rightly so. It was way too wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, yorker on the leg stump, Jadeja works it through square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, low full toss, flicked to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Negi, 1 run, almost a yorker, Negi wrists it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, very full and on the leg stump, Jadeja drills it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Ravindra Jadeja, <b>FOUR</b>, easy ball and Jadeja helps himself to a boundary first ball. Full and down the leg-side, Jadeja tickles it fine to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to du Plessis, <b>out</b> Caught by Rohit!! It's all falling apart quickly for CHN. Full and outside off stump, du Plessis advances and tries to clear the infield, he drives but picks out extra-cover, who jumps and takes a good catch above his head. Rohit throws the ball up in the air in delight after completing the catch. <b>du Plessis c Rohit b Vinay 1(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Vinay to du Plessis, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to du Plessis, no run, widish length ball outside off stump, du Plessis swings and misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Vinay Kumar [2.0-0-11-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>78</b> needed off 24 balls now. Yes, it's mathematically possible, but practically thinking, this is out of CHN's reach.]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to du Plessis, 1 run, slower delivery outside off stump, du Plessis taps it to backward point and opens his account]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Faf du Plessis, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dhoni, <b>out</b> Bowled!! That should be the game for MUM. Malinga bowls a yorker, it was just slipping down the leg side, Dhoni, who was sitting deep in the crease, tried to go over long-on, missed the ball and it deflected onto the stumps off the pad. Happy faces in the MUM dug-out and why not! <b>Dhoni b Malinga 18(13) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Malinga to Dhoni, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dhoni, 2 runs, low full toss on the leg stump, Dhoni flicks it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Negi, <b>no ball</b>, 1 run, that's called a no ball as Malinga disturbed the bails with his knee while delivering the ball, slower delivery on the leg stump, Negi taps it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dhoni, 1 run, almost a yorker, drilled to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dhoni, <b>SIX</b>, Malinga just misses the yorker and Dhoni somehow manages to get under it. Dhoni takes the front leg out of the way and smashes it over long-on. The ball goes towards the CHN dressing room, where Raina comes out and takes a catch]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Negi, 1 run, yorker length delivery wide outside off stump, Negi reaches out and squeezes it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga [2.0-0-7-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[CHN need 91 runs off 30 balls. Looks like MUM have this in the bag. Can Dhoni help CHN gain a miraculous victory? Malinga has two more overs to go and it's going to be very tough.]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dhoni, no run, short and angling away from the right-hander, Dhoni tries to dab it fine but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dhoni, <b>FOUR</b>, shortish and on the leg stump, Dhoni swivels and pulls it all along the ground through backward square leg, beating fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dhoni, no run, uppish but safe, oh this could be a run-out at the non-striker's end but Negi escapes. Dhoni was shaping for the slog over the on-side, McClenaghan bowls a length ball just outside off stump, Dhoni checks his shot and it goes towards mid-off, Negi looks for a quick single but Dhoni sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pawan Negi, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dwayne Bravo, <b>out</b> Caught by Simmons!! That's sliced in the air and straight to third man. Big wicket for MUM. Short of a length delivery outside off stump, Bravo looks to go inside-out, plays with an angled bat and ends up slicing it high in the air, Simmons sees it nicely and takes an easy catch. <b>Dwayne Bravo c Simmons b McClenaghan 9(6) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[McClenaghan to Dwayne Bravo, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dwayne Bravo, no run, good length delivery angling away from the right-hander, Bravo swings and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dwayne Bravo, <b>SIX</b>, that's hit back over the bowler's head, looked like it went off the inside half of the bat, yes it did, but it had enough legs to run away. Full and in the slot, Bravo lofts it over the infield and beats long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [2.0-0-12-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dwayne Bravo, 1 run, floated up on off, Bravo comes forward and nudges it to mid-wicket, they think about the second but decide against it]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dwayne Bravo, no run, beauty! This goes straight on, Bravo presses forward and plays for the turn, he is beaten all ends up]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dwayne Bravo, 2 runs, flighted up and gets it to turn, Bravo leans forward and tickles it fine, Malinga gives chase, slides and hauls the ball in, just a couple taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Raina, <b>out</b> Stumped!! Harbhajan once again turning it on for MUM. For a second time in as many games he got rid of Raina. Harbhajan expected Raina to give the charge, fires it full and outside off, Raina tries to reach for it and squeeze it out, he misses and Parthiv does the rest behind the sticks. MUM are running away with the game. <b>Raina st Parthiv Patel b Harbhajan 28(19) [4s-3 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Harbhajan to Raina, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Stumped!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Raina, no run, flighted outside off, Raina mistimes the drive to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dhoni, 1 run, quicker and just outside off, Dhoni brings his bat down and dabs it in front of square on the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[The final <b>time-out</b> of this IPL has been taken. Raina and Smith started to shift gears, but just when they got going Bhajji struck and sent back Smith. A lot depends on these two, if CHN have to win. As of now, MUM are still in the driver's seat.]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, superb shot! That is his favorite shot. Fuller and just outside off, Raina makes a bit of room, lofts it inside out over extra cover, he hit that sweetly as McClenaghan coulnd't get there from sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Raina, 2 runs, good length ball on off, Raina goes for a mighty heave, gets a thick inside edge behind square, these two are very quick and they come back easily for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Dhoni, 1 run, back of a length around off, Dhoni punches to sweeper cover, only a single available]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Dhoni, 2 runs, good length ball just outside off, Dhoni drives it through extra cover, the sweeper cover runs to his right and hunts the ball down]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Dhoni, no run, shortens the length on off and middle, Dhoni can't connect with the glance, he wears it on the thigh pad, the ball rolls to the off-side, he looks for the single and was racing down before being sent back as Pandya moves quickly forward and under-arms the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Dhoni, no run, back of a length around off, Dhoni takes a step forward, looks to play the cut, misses as the ball nips back in]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dhoni, 1 run, low full toss outside off, Dhoni leans forward and eases it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>MS Dhoni, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dwayne Smith, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Harbhajan has struck! He has removed the dangerous looking Smith. This was the quicker delivery, Smith went down on his knee to play the sweep, he misses and is struck on the back thigh. That was pretty adjacent and umpire Illingworth had no hesitation in raising his finger. Big wicket for MUM as the partnership was gathering momentum. <b>Dwayne Smith lbw b Harbhajan 57(48) [4s-9 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Harbhajan to Dwayne Smith, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, smashed! Harbhajan drops it short, Smith was onto it in a flash, he goes back and pulls it flat, betwee deep mid-wicket and long-on. It bounced only once before reaching the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Raina, 1 run, Raina comes down the track, takes it on the full and drives it down the wicket, Harbhajan gets a hand and parries it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, marginally short, Smith pulls to deep mid-wicket, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Raina, 1 run, flighted outside off, Raina goes for the inside out loft, hits it straight to the deep extra cover fielder]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, superb shot! The CHN innings is gaining momentum. Smith gets to his <b>fifty</b> as well. Shortens the length just outside off, Smith stands tall and guides it behind point, no chance for the fielder at third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Raina, 1 run, too straight, on the pads, Raina flicks it to short fine leg, straight to Malinga, either side and that would have been four more]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Raina, no run, <b>run-out chance missed!</b> Raina had given up. Pandya appeals for a lbw, but umpire Dharma moves away. Back of a length, Raina misses the steer to third man and is rapped on the pads, the ball rolls to short third man, Bhajji had all the time in the world to hit the stumps at the striker's end as Raina was looking for the run, he misses and Raina survives. The lbw was not given as the ball pitched outside leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, Raina was expecting this, short and on the stumps, he shuffles across, gets inside the line and pulls it over short fine leg, one bounce and into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, fullish and outside off, Smith throws his bat at that, the thickish outside edge flies on the bounce to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, Pandya drags the length short, no pace to trouble Smith, who rocks back and pulls it in front of square, split the two fielders in the deep to perfection]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Raina, <b>SIX</b>, lovely shot! Great use of the feet, shimmies down the wicket to this flighted delivery, meets the pitch of the ball and lofts it handsomely over wide long-on for his first maximum. Harbhajan was livid after being hit]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Raina, <b>wide</b>, darted outside off, Raina has nothing to do with it, wide given]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, swept away to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dwayne Smith, no run, "catch it" shouted Parthiv, but it landed well in front of Vinay. Flighted on off and middle, Smith reverse sweeps it in the air, ball was in the air and drops in front of Vinay at short third man, Raina wanted the single but is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dwayne Smith, no run, slows this up considerably, Smith kneels down and can't connect with the slog sweep]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Raina, 1 run, quicker, fuller and on off, Raina squeezes the drive to long-off. That was bowled at <b>102kph</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, Smith goes deep in the crease and works it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, back of a length around off, Smith mistimes the punch to cover, collects a single and keeps strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Dwayne Smith, no run, huge shout for lbw from Pandya, umpire Dharmasena shakes his head. Another one that jags back in, Smith stay rooted to the crease, misses the clip, is struck on the kneeroll on the back pad, height might have been an issue there]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Dwayne Smith, no run, nips back in from short of length, Smith can't meet with the flick, wears it on the pad and the ball rolls to backward point, no appeal for lbw as it was sliding down]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, a long half volley and Smith has put that away. It was well wide of off, Smith stretches forward and drives, splits the fielders at extra cover and mid-off, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Dwayne Smith, no run, back of a length and angles in, Smith stays leg-side of the ball and fails to connect with the cut]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Dwayne Smith, <b>no ball</b>, another quick short delivery, Smith pulls and misses, the umpire signals a no-ball because of the height. It looked fine from the side on camera angle, harsh call]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Raina, 1 run, banged in short and at Raina, who goes for the hook and gets a fat top-edge, the ball stays in the air for sometime and drops in front Simmons who is running from deep backward square. Pandya wanted Simmons to make a better effort]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, second four of the over and it is the best over of the innings for CHN. Slower and around off, Smith gets to the pitch and whips it in the air, right between deep mid-wicket and long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Raina, 1 run, floated up outside off, Raina lofts it inside out to sweeper cover, goes on the bounce to Pollard]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Raina, 2 runs, flighted around off, Raina comes down the track and heaves it wide of long-on, Rayudu fields the ball on the bounce, the momentum was taking him over the rope, he does well to flick the ball in and keep it to a double]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Raina, no run, quicker delivery, it was fraction short, Raina plays the cut and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, tossed up around off, Smith goes for the conventional sweep, finds the fielder at deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, cheeky! Pushed through on off, Smith kneels down, reverse sweeps it past short third man, who was square and had no chance of chasing that]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harbhajan Singh, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, too straight, on off and middle, Smith nudges it to deep mid-wicket, retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Dwayne Smith, no run, slower delivery well wide of off, Smith reaches for it, but can't get there. The umpire thinks it is a fair delivery]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Dwayne Smith, no run, shortens the length around off, Smith goes for the short-arm pull, the angle beats the inside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Raina, 1 run, good length ball on the pads, Raina works it off the inside half of the bat towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, again, the length is short, Smith is hurried on the pull this time, gets an inside edge onto the pad, the ball dribbles away behind square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, good start after the break. These two might try and target the youngster. Short and on the stumps, Smith swivels and pulls it behind square, the ball races across the turf for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Hardik Pandya, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b> has been taken. CHN's run-chase is going nowhere. The required run-rate has shot up to above 12. MUM well ahead in the game and if they keep bowling the way they have till now, no reason why they shouldn't win this.]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Raina, no run, hits the seam and jags away, Raina was looking to push at that, but is beaten by the late movement. No carry on that, goes on the bounce to Parthiv]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, on a length close to off, Smith works it to the right of mid-on, picks up an easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Dwayne Smith, no run, shortish and on off, Smith swivels on the pull, can't make the required connection, is hit on the thigh pad and the ball rolls to Rayudu at slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Dwayne Smith, no run, play and miss! This was a nothing shot from Smith. Back of a length nips back in slightly, Smith stays leg-side of the ball and looks to target cow corner, misses and the ball flies past leg-stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Dwayne Smith, no run, back of a length around off, Smith knocks it to extra cover, the call is "wait" for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, streaky four! But CHN will take that. Good length ball just outside off, Smith looks to loft it through the line, the ball squirts off the outside edge and flies over point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, edged and four! Another good short ball from McClenaghan, Raina was hopping and poking, the outside edge flies between slip and gully, third man was fine and he had no chance of stopping that. Plenty of oohs and aahs]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Raina, no run, Raina is greeted with a short delivery, McClenaghan goes up for a caught behind appeal, but nothing from his mates. Bumper at the batsman, Raina ducks under it rather awkwardly, the ball climbs over his right shoulder]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Hussey, <b>out</b> Caught by Jagadeesha Suchith!! Hussey was struggling and he has to go. This might just be what CHN needed, the asking rate had jumped up over 11. Full delivery outside off, Hussey presses forward, gets under that, slices it to cover-point, the ball just about carried to Suchith, who did well to wrap his fingers underneath the ball. <b>M Hussey c Jagadeesha Suchith b McClenaghan 4(9) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[McClenaghan to M Hussey, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[MUM are claiming a catch. Did it go on the bounce? Suchith is the fielder, he is not sure. The umpires get together. They send it upstairs, the soft signal from Dharma is Not Out. No problems with the no-ball. He might have got his fingers underneath that. MUM are already celebrating. The camera has been zoomed in. This should be OUT. The third umpire wants to be absolutely sure. The finger is raised and Hussey has to depart.]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Hussey, no run, short and outside off, there was width to work with it but Hussey has missed out, he flashes a cut and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, good length ball on off, Smith knocks it to mid-off and sets off immediately]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dwayne Smith, no run, good length ball on off, Smith brings his bat down at an angle, squirts it off a thickish outer half to cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [1.0-0-7-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to M Hussey, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>just over Simmons!</b> Hussey might just feel a bit relieved now. Pitched up outside off, Hussey drives in the air, eludes the leap from Simmons at extra cover and the ball races away to the fence. In fact, he got a fingertip on that]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to M Hussey, no run, Hussey is struggling. On a length and holds its line, Hussey plays inside the line and and is beaten off the inside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to M Hussey, no run, full and outside off, it hit the seam and moved away late, Hussey goes for the drive and is beaten by the movement]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to M Hussey, <b>wide</b>, pushes this further wide of off, Hussey can't reach it with a drive, umpire Illingworth calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to M Hussey, no run, on a length and slanted across the left-hander, Hussey drives and misses, the ball sneaks under his bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[A wide slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, banged in halfway down the wicket, Smith goes for the pull and toe-ends it to long-on, he was a tad early into the shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vinay to Dwayne Smith, no run, short of length and bit more bounce, Smith rides it and taps it gently to backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Vinay Kumar, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, slower delivery down leg, Smith tickles it towards short fine leg, McClenaghan dives to his right and stops the ball. That would have been a wide had Smith let go]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dwayne Smith, no run, off-cutter on a length, Smith watches it carefully and defends back down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to M Hussey, leg byes, 1 run, shaping into the pads off a fuller length, Hussey can't meet with the flick, ball rolls behind square after thudding into the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to M Hussey, no run, full toss and Hussey has missed out. It was low and outside off, Hussey eases the drive to cover-point, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, takes the pace off the ball, drifts it onto the pads, Smith nudges it square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dwayne Smith, no run, short of length on off, Smith stays beside the line and knocks it back to Malinga]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Hussey, no run, first ball and Hussey wanted to send it into the stands. Back of a length just outside off, goes for the pull and fails to make contact. A puff of the cheeks as he missed that]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, on a length close to off, Smith drags the drive to the left of the bowler, McClenaghan gets a hand and takes the pace off the ball, Bhajji dives to his left and makes a half stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dwayne Smith, <b>SIX</b>, not where Smith wanted but he will take that. Well directed short delivery, right at the batsman, Smith goes for the pull, the top-edge flies over the keeper and the short boundaries gets Smith six]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dwayne Smith, no run, Pollard makes a fine save, short and width on offer, Smith cuts it towards backward point, the big man dives to his left and stops it from going any further]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dwayne Smith, no run, short of length on off, Smith guides it with an angled bat to backward point, Pollard dives to his left and stops the ball. Once more the bottom hand comes off the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dwayne Smith, no run, back of a length angled across the right-hander, Smith goes for the extravagant drive on-the-up, is beaten as there was no footwork]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, change of pace, right in the blockhole, Smith spots it well, digs it to the on-side and picks up an easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dwayne Smith, no run, too full and around off, Smith squeezes the drive back to Malinga, who palms it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, Smith off the mark with a boundary. Tad overpitched and outside off, Smith comes forward and drives, was not off the middle, but he found the gap wide of mid-off, the lightning fast outfield takes care of the rest]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dwayne Smith, no run, again, Malinga keeps it full and on the stumps, Smith squeezes it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dwayne Smith, no run, full and outside off, Smith was in no shape to play the drive, goes for it away from the body, the bottom hand comes off the bat and the ball whizzes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Dwayne Smith, no run, inswinging low full toss, on middle and leg, Smith gets his front foot out of the way, brings his bat down and jams it to mid-on. Right on the money is Malinga]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Smith and M Hussey are at the crease. Dwayne Smith is on strike. Malinga will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. The run-chase is about to begin. The highest target chased in an IPL final is 200 by KOL. CHN have won two IPL's when they batted first. So, the odds are against them. Can they overhaul this target? We'll find out as the players make their way out to the middle. Malinga is marking his run-up. He has a slip in place. Here we go...]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rayudu:</b> "It's a good wicket, but not as good as Wankhede or some of the other pitches. 180 is a par score on the wicket. After the start that we got, we lost a couple of wickets and we needed to rebuild. Our target was 200 after 10 overs. No, I am nervous (when asked what does he think of MUM's chances). They are a good batting side and hopefully things will go our way."]]></line><line><![CDATA[At the other end of the spectrum, CHN had a forgettable day in the field. Faf du Plessis gave them plenty to cheer by running out Parthiv Patel with a direct-hit. However, once Simmons and Rohit started to essay shots, they lost the plot. CHN, who have won the IPL twice, need to rise to the occasion with the bat to overcome their spirited opponents in the grand final. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Lendl Simmons and Rohit Sharma cracked thrill-a-minute knocks to power MUM to a mammoth total. After MS Dhoni surprisingly won the toss and elected to field on a flat deck, MUM's batsmen took advantage of some poor bowling by the opposition to check in a flurry of boundaries. Only Ashish Nehra proved his worth by keeping the lid on the scoring rate with the new ball before Pollard took him to the cleaners. Once Simmons and Rohit were dismissed, Ambati Rayudu and Kieron Pollard strung together a key partnership to put them in a position of strength. Pollard even smacked Nehra for 22 runs in a single over.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Harbhajan, no run, yorker on the stumps, Harbhajan squeezes it back to the bowler, Bravo collects it and doesn't bother to throw the ball as the batsmen were not attempting to run]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Harbhajan, leg byes, <b>FOUR</b>, lucky four for MUM and it brings up the <b>200</b>. Bravo goes round the wicket, bowls the near perfect yorker, Harbhajan was moving away to the leg-side, misses to get bat on ball, it hits the pad and goes to the right of the keeper, Dhoni was wrong-footed and had no chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Harbhajan, <b>SIX</b>, no sighters needed for Bhajji. First ball and he sends it into the crowd. A length delivery just outside off, Harbhajan uses the depth of the crease, swings it with the line and lofts it over extra cover for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Rayudu, 1 run, on a length just outside off, Rayudu drills it on the bounce to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Harbhajan Singh, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Pandya, <b>out</b> Caught by Raina!! Raina pulls off a terrific catch. He has been brilliant tonight. A full toss on the stumps, Pandya heaves it to deep mid-wicket, didn't get it off the middle, hence no distance on that, Raina comes haring forward, dives full length and takes it inches from the ground. That will go into the list of spectacular catches. <b>Pandya c Raina b Dwayne Bravo 0(2)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dwayne Bravo to Pandya, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Pandya, no run, Bravo goes wide of the crease, fires in a full delivery around leg-stump, Pandya gets his front leg out of the way, can't make the connection on the flick. The ball slipped through his legs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rayudu, no run, Rayudu lets out a cry as he misses the length ball outside off, it was in the slot and Rayudu went too hard at that, fails to make the connection]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hardik Pandya, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Pollard, <b>out</b> Caught by Raina!! A quickfire innings from Pollard comes to an end. He has done his job. Full delivery just outside off, Pollard looks to go inside out over extra cover, doesn't get it off the middle, spoons it to deep extra cover, Raina was not going to drop that. <b>Pollard c Raina b Mohit Sharma 36(18) [4s-2 6s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mohit Sharma to Pollard, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rayudu, 1 run, low full toss outside off, Rayudu walks across his stumps, was shaping to play the scoop, the line was not there, hence guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rayudu, no run, fires the yorker outside off, Rayudu can't lay bat on ball as he looks to squeeze]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rayudu, <b>SIX</b>, that shot gets even Sachin on his feet. It was a pre-meditated hit from Rayudu and he connects well. The field is set on the off-side, walks across his stumps, kneels down and helps the back of a length delivery over backward square. That was ala ABD style]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Pollard, 1 run, good start to the over, yorker on off and middle, Pollard digs it out to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma [3.0-0-30-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Pollard, 1 run, full toss on the stumps, Pollard flicks it wide of long-on and settles with one]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Rayudu, 1 run, <b>dropped!</b> This was a dolly for Smith. The off-cutter well wide of off, Rayudu reaches out for it and toe-ends the loft towards long-off, Smith runs in, settles under it and spills it. He went with hard hands, the ball hit his palm and popped out]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Rayudu, no run, gets the slower delivery to dip on the batsman, Rayudu was early into the paddle, misses it by some distance]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Rayudu, <b>SIX</b>, magnificent! The off-speed delivery from Bravo, Rayudu spotted it early, he had to take that from outside off, lofts it inside out over extra cover, the ball sails away into the stands]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Pollard, 1 run, too full and outside off, didn't allow Pollard to get under that, driven to long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Back over the wicket for Pollard]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Rayudu, 1 run, Bravo starts from round the wicket, drops the slower ball short, Rayudu reaches and cuts to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo [2.0-0-19-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Pollard, <b>SIX</b>, Pollard is dealing in sixes. This is the third six of the over. Very poor over from Nehra. Full and outside off, Pollard extends his arms and lofts it handsomely over extra cover, the ball cleared the rope with ease. 23 runs off the over and that also brings up the <b>50-run</b> stand]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Pollard, <b>SIX</b>, even mishits are carrying the distance. A low full toss, Pollard's bat turned in his hands, doesn't get it anywhere close to the middle, but had enough power to send it sailing over long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now a straightish mid-on in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Pollard, <b>FOUR</b>, what power! Full and angling in on middle and leg, Pollard gets his front leg out of the way and whips it in front of square, the fielder at deep mid-wicket was a mere spectator]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Pollard, no run, too full and almost a yorker, Pollard squeezes it to the right of the bowler, Nehra stretches his hand and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Pollard, <b>SIX</b>, that's just hammered. A length delivery right in the slot, Pollard clears his front leg and heaves it over deep mid-wicket. That was the slower ball from Nehra and Pollard picked it early, sent it a long way into the crowd]]></line><line><![CDATA[A straightish mid-off in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rayudu, 1 run, good length ball around off, Rayudu opens the bat face and guides it towards backward point, quick single taken]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashish Nehra [3.0-0-18-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rayudu, 1 run, change of pace outside off, Rayudu waits for the ball to arrive, glides it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Pollard, 1 run, takes a step out of the crease, Mohit drags the length back, another inside edge onto the pad, the ball rolls towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Pollard, no run, slower delivery around off, Pollard goes for a nudge through the on-side, ekes out an inside edge onto the pad, the ball rolls to the right of Dhoni, who dives and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Pollard, 2 runs, some confusion between the two batsmen, shortish and on middle, Pollard swivels on the pull and sends it to deep backward square, he also wanted two but Rayudu was late in taking off, Ashwin fires a wayward throw at the bowler's end and hence Rayudu made it comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Pollard, no run, full and attacking the stumps, Pollard turns it to mid-wicket, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Pollard, no run, starts with a slower ball bouncer, Pollard drops his wrists and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma [2.0-0-26-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Rayudu, 2 runs, Bravo lost it under the floodlights! This was the slower bouncer from Smith, Rayudu was early into the pull, gets a steepling top-edge over mid-wicket. Bravo ran back, had the ball covered but then lost it completely, the ball lobbed over his shoulder and bounced in front of him, another brace for Rayudu]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Rayudu, 2 runs, on a good length and well outside off, Rayudu leans forward and drives it cripsly past extra cover. Negi gets across from long-off, puts in the dive and keeps the batsmen down to a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Rayudu, <b>SIX</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, fraction fuller and well outside off, Rayudu bends down low, picks up the length early and slog swipes it high and over deep mid-wicket for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Rayudu, 2 runs, short of a length and well outside off, punched in front of square on the off-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Rayudu, no run, Smith is dragging CHN back in the contest with the ball, back of a length and just outside off, left Rayudu at the last moment, he ended up dabbling at that and is beaten on the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Rayudu, no run, wide slower ball from Smith, Rayudu threw his bat at that and is beaten]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Pollard, <b>FOUR</b>, nicely played! This is like adding insult to injury, on a good length and well outside off, Pollard waits on it, opens the face of the bat at the last moment and steers it in the gap between backward point and short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Pollard, 2 runs, Pollard gets lucky! The bouncer was short, the bouncer was high and it was well outside off, Pollard went for the pull, gets a big top-edge, he wasn't in any control over the shot. The ball drops in between two men in the deep, Bravo has his hands on his knee]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Rayudu, 1 run, another slower ball from Bravo, Rayudu waits on it and cracks it towards sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Pollard, 1 run, width on offer from Bravo, Pollard gets on top of the bounce and cracks it towards deep cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Rayudu, 1 run, the slower short ball from Bravo, Rayudu waits on it and runs it down towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Rayudu, no run, tad fuller and holding its line outside off, Rayudu prods across and pushes it back towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Rayudu, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, driven past cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Rayudu, 2 runs, tad fuller and just outside off, driven to the left of long-off for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Rayudu, no run, fuller length and just outside off, pushed back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Pollard, 1 run, on a length and angling into Pollard, worked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Rayudu, 1 run, that's a terrific stop at cover, but the fielder has given it away by conceding an overthrow. This was full and well outside off, Rayudu drove to the left of cover, the fielder tumbled and made a stunning stop. He gets up and shies at the bowler's end, Pollard was well in though and they sneak in an overthrow]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ambati Rayudu, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Simmons, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Smith is on a celebratory run after scalping Simmons. This is a cracker of a yorker, very full and nipping back into Simmons, he was late in bringing his bat down in time. The ball clips the base of off-stump. Dhoni celebrates, so does the bowler. Are CHN back in this? Looks like Dhoni's stern words has worked. <b>Simmons b Dwayne Smith 68(45) [4s-8 6s-3]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Dwayne Smith to Simmons, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kieron Pollard, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Smith, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[An agitated Dhoni leads the team huddle. He has plenty of strong words to say to his team. They decided to bowl and things haven't gone according to plan. Can CHN stage a fightback?]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Rohit, <b>out</b> Caught by Ravindra Jadeja!! Rohit has thrown his wicket away. Relief for CHN and Dhoni. This was full and in that channel outside off, the slower ball from Bravo. Rohit was looking to clear mid-wicket with the lofted shot, doesn't get hold and ends up hitting it high and straight into the palms of Jadeja at long-on. The MUM skipper is disappointed with himself as he walks away. <b>Rohit c Ravindra Jadeja b Dwayne Bravo 50(26) [4s-6 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dwayne Bravo to Rohit, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, that's smashed by Rohit, gets to his <b>fifty</b> as well, pretty full and wide outside off, Rohit plays with an open face and laces it in front of cover, no chance for the man in the deep, the dug-out applauds the effort]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Simmons, 1 run, Bravo slips in the slower ball, worked towards mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Simmons, no run, on a good length and angling back into Simmons, he is cramped for room and pushes it back at the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Rohit, 1 run, very full and on the stumps, Rohit presents the full face of the bat and punches it down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, even Bravo is going for runs, width on offer first ball, Rohit waits on it and cracks it square past point, no chance for the man getting across from third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Jadeja, he drops this one short and wide outside off, Simmons gets on top of the bounce and cracks it behind point, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rohit, 1 run, good fielding from Ashwin at short third man, Rohit slashed at a short and wide ball, gets a thick edge and to the left of Ashwin, he tumbles and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Simmons, 1 run, another low full toss from Jadeja, driven towards sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Rohit, 1 run, flighted delivery and on the stumps, Rohit goes down on one knee and sweeps it powerfully towards deep mid-wicket, straight to the fielder though. Negi makes sure that he didn't hit the ropes, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Simmons, 1 run, tossed up and well outside off, Simmons goes for the cut and gets a bottom edge past Dhoni, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, that's another gift from Jadeja, full toss and well outside leg, swung away behind square on the on-side for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja [1.0-0-14-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Simmons, 1 run, tad fuller and just outside off, Simmons plays with an open face and eases it past cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Simmons, 2 runs, short of a length and angling into Simmons, worked in front of square on the on-side for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, plenty of width on that from Mohit, Simmons gets on top of the bounce and cracks it square on the off-side, beats the man in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Simmons, 2 runs, the ball is teasing Negi tonight, he can't grab a leading edge this time around, Simmons was early on the flick, closed the face of the bat and gets a leading edge towards point. Negi gets across from backward point, goes full stretch with the dive, but ends up palming it away towards sweeper cover. Simmons gets to his <b>fifty</b> with a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rohit, 1 run, tad fuller and just outside off, Rohit plays with an open face and drives it towards Smith at long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rohit, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Rohit drives it to the right of cover where Raina makes a diving stop]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma [1.0-0-16-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Rohit, 1 run, too short from Negi, Rohit has plenty of time to go back and punch it down towards long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Simmons, 1 run, flatter and on his pads, Simmons goes back and works it in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Simmons, <b>SIX</b>, <b>massive</b>, excellent use of the feet from Simmons, comes down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and sends it sailing high and deep into the crowd at long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Simmons, no run, flighted and just outside off, Simmons lunges forward, plays with an open face and guides it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Rohit, 1 run, slower and on the off-stump line, Rohit opens up and drives it square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Simmons, 1 run, tossed up and just outside off, eased down towards long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rohit, 2 runs, a better throw might have had Rohit struggling, this was tossed up and on his pads, Rohit nudges it behind square and calls for the second run. Mohit was quick onto the ball but his throw is wayward. Dhoni has to go a long way to collect it, Rohit makes it in with a dive. The skipper of CHN isn't happy one bit with his fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rohit, <b>SIX</b>, excellent batting from Rohit, comes down the track, plays it with the turn and hoists it high and over deep mid-wicket for a maximum. Ashwin is under pressure once again]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Rohit, no run, slower and on off, Rohit presses half-forward and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, 1 run, flatter and on the pads, clipped away behind square on the on-side for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, no run, Ashwin drifts one onto Simmons' pads, he was looking to work it towards the on-side, misses and the ball lobs off his pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, no run, flighted delivery and on Simmons' pads, turned towards the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin [1.0-0-12-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Simmons, 1 run, tossed up and on the off-stump line, Simmons shuffles across and works it in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Simmons, no run, pushed through and angling onto Simmons' pads, he looks to flick and misses, appeal for LBW, but the ball was sliding down]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Negi, drops one short and wide outside off, Simmons makes room, plays it very late and chops it behind square on the off-side for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Rohit, 1 run, pushed through by Negi, Rohit comes down the track and works it towards mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Simmons, 1 run, tossed up and just outside off, eased down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Rohit, 1 run, flighted and well outside off, Rohit leans forward and drives it towards deep cover for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pawan Negi, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, this is a poor start from Jadeja, a juicy full toss now, Simmons gets forward and thumps it over mid-on, one bounce and over the ropes. MUM are flying after losing an early wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Simmons, <b>SIX</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, Jadeja bowls with a round-arm action, gives this one plenty of air, Simmons gets underneath the length and sends it high and over long-off for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Simmons, no run, pushed through and just outside off, Simmons presses forward and gets an inside edge towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Simmons, no run, fired in quicker and on off, Simmons gets half-forward and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Simmons, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Simmons prods forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, Simmons is on the attack, this was tossed up and on the stumps, he clears his left leg and plays the cross batted heave, clears mid-wicket and races away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Simmons, 1 run, tad fuller and just outside off, punched to the right of mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, this is good batting from Simmons, too short from Nehra, Simmons waits on it, uses his bottom hand to good effect and works it past short fine leg, once it beat the fielder, the ball raced away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Simmons, no run, good change of pace from Nehra, shortens the length and slips in the slower ball, Simmons was way too early on the pull and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Simmons, no run, nicely bowled by Nehra, follows Simmons as he charged down the track, he is cramped for space and is beaten on the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rohit, 1 run, short of a length and angling across the right-hander, dabbed away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Simmons, byes, 1 run, a direct hit might have had Simmons in trouble! Nehra banged one short and on the stumps as Simmons came down the track, he swung and missed. Dhoni didn't stop it cleanly, Rohit calls Simmons through for a quick single. MS does well to recover and shies at the bowler's end, <b>Simmons was struggling</b> and might have been short had there been a direct hit]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, 1 run, pushed through flatter and quicker, Simmons lunges forward and turns it towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, no run, fraction short and just outside off, Simmons makes room and cuts it straight to the fielder at cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, no run, appeal for a LBW, Simmons was lunging forward in defence, gets struck around off and the ball was spinning down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, no run, tossed up and just outside off, Simmons prods forward and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, <b>SIX</b>, poor ball for a free-hit, juicy full toss from Ashwin, Simmons makes room and goes back over the bowler's head, straight into the sightscreen]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, <b>no ball</b>, Ashwin has overstepped! This was tossed up and just outside off, Simmons prodded forward in defence, gets an inside edge and the ball rolls away to the left of the keeper. Rohit wanted a single and has to rush back as Dhoni shies and misses. The fielder at mid-off dives and saves some overthrows]]></line><line><![CDATA[Back over the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, clever from Simmons, Ashwin came from round the wicket and dropped one well outside leg, Simmons gets down on his knees and sweeps it behind square on the on-side for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Spin in the form of Ashwin, a leg slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Simmons, 1 run, another bouncer from Nehra, Simmons swivels across and pulls it behind square on the on-side, he didn't get hold of the shot, goes to the fielder in the deep on the bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rohit, 1 run, Nehra shortens his length and gets this one to angle across Rohit, steered away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, tad too full and well outside off, Rohit leans forward, presents the full face of the bat and drives it past Smith at extra cover, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>just over mid-wicket</b>, fraction short and just outside off, Rohit swivels across and pulls it in the air towards mid-wicket. Negi leaps and gets a fingertip on that, but the ball scurries away to the fence in a hurry]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rohit, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Rohit prods forward, presents the full face of the bat and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Simmons, 1 run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Simmons was caught in the crease as he looked to play the drive, gets an inside edge onto the pad, the ball rolls in front of cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, 16 runs from the over! This is the best of the lot, a poor over from Mohit, once again short and well outside off, Rohit gets on top of the bounce and cracks it square past point, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rohit, 2 runs, almost chopped on! This was a tad fuller and held its line outside off, Rohit was looking to force it away off the back foot, gets a thick inside edge and past the off-stump, gets back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rohit, <b>FOUR</b>, this is even better from Rohit, width on offer from Mohit, Rohit waits on it, opens the face of the bat at the last moment and runs it wide of Raina at wide slip, the ball races away to the fence in a hurry]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rohit, <b>SIX</b>, Rohit gets going with a six! Poor ball from Mohit, short and wide outside off, Rohit gets on top of the bounce and throws his bat at that, cuts it up and over third man for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rohit, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Rohit hops across and dabs it straight to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rohit, no run, back of a length and well outside off, Rohit stands tall and punches it towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Simmons, no run, on a good length and shaping away from outside off, Simmons is happy to let it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit Sharma, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Parthiv Patel, <b>out</b> Parthiv Patel Run Out!! Sensational fielding from Faf du Plessis, Parthiv has been run-out for a duck. This has come out of nothing for CHN, just shows the value of fielding. This was a tad fuller and just outside off, Parthiv was looking to nudge it towards the on-side, gets a thick inside edge and in front of mid-on. Faf rushed forward, he was unbalanced as he flicked at the stumps at the bowler's end, hits the bails with Parthiv struggling. That was simply unbelievable, a freak dismissal, if there was one. <b>Parthiv Patel run out (du Plessis) 0(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nehra to Parthiv Patel, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[A direct hit from Faf du Plessis. Is Parthiv runout? CHN are celebrating already. He is well short.]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Parthiv Patel, no run, back of a length and in that channel outside off, Parthiv stays behind the line and defends it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Parthiv Patel, no run, Nehra keeps it full and just outside off, Parthiv prods forward and pushes it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Simmons, 1 run, fuller length delivery and in that channel outside off, Simmons was late on the drive, gets a thick inside edge past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Simmons, no run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, he prods across and defends it towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Simmons and Parthiv Patel are at the crease. Simmons is on strike. Nehra will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nehra steams in with a slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[Right.. it's time for action. Bat first and defend is the norms of any final, but MS has decided to go the other route. This is the third time that the two teams are meeting in a final. The team batting first has won the previous two times. We had the national anthem done.. CHN fielders stride briskly onto the field, they are followed by the two MUM openers.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mumbai</b> (Playing XI): Lendl Simmons, Parthiv Patel(w), Rohit Sharma(c), Kieron Pollard, Ambati Rayudu, Hardik Pandya, Harbhajan Singh, Jagadeesha Suchith, Vinay Kumar, Lasith Malinga, Mitchell McClenaghan]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai</b> (Playing XI): Dwayne Smith, Michael Hussey, Faf du Plessis, Suresh Raina, MS Dhoni(w/c), Pawan Negi, Dwayne Bravo, Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Mohit Sharma, Ashish Nehra]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>MS Dhoni:</b> 'It was good to play at home (against BLR in qualifier 2). We want to keep playing games, we had a good recovery yesterday. We didn't practice a lot, we have played a lot of cricket for the last two months. It is just a one-off game in the final, whoever performs better will become the champions. We will bowl first. The wicket looks slightly sticky, but I don't think it will have a major impact. We have made no changes.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit Sharma:</b> 'Ready to go. We had a very good preparation, it's pretty humid and we got a couple of days to prepare. It's a good hunting ground for me, but I want to do the best for my team. We won in 2013, it gives us another opportunity today. We would have batted first anyway. It's a big game and we would like to put the runs on the board first up. We are playing the same team.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-Head record:</b> In terms of competition, there's nothing much to choose between the two teams. They have faced off 21 times with MUM holding a 11-10 winning record. This is the third time that the two teams will face each other in an IPL final. CHN won in 2010 while MUM returned the favour in 2013.]]></line><line><![CDATA[We have had 59 matches so far. So what has been the highlight of the tournament? Is it Umesh Yadav's magic over where he knocked over David Warner and Naman Ojha? Is it AB's 133* against Mumbai, the highest score in this season's IPL, is it the brilliance of Dwayne Bravo and his CHN fielders? Is it the coolness of captain Dhoni or did Kohli surprise one and all with his maturity? It has been a quality tournament. India's youngsters have come to the fore. Shreyas Iyer has become a household name, Yuzvendra Chahal continued to be the most impressive of the bowling lot while the likes of Hardik Pandya and Sarfaraz Khan took baby steps towards greatness. It was not a youngsters dominated tournament though. Veterans Ashish Nehra and Brad Hogg turned the clock back with some stellar shows.]]></line><line><![CDATA[While CHN have been the Mr. Consistent of IPL, Mumbai are fast turning out to be the ideal challengers. This will be their third shot at the title and they would love to go home with their second title. Unlike their opponents tonight, MUM took the tough route to the final. After six matches, they had a solitary win and five losses. MUM were almost down and out, not many counted them to be amongst the top four at the end of the season. The revival began with the entry of West Indian opener, Lendl Simmons, and MUM haven't looked back since then. They went on to win 8 out of their next 9 matches to become the first team to book a slot in the final. Rohit Sharma has a thing or two for Eden Gardens. He has his Test best on this ground, his 264 against Sri Lanka, the best ever score by a batsman in ODIs, came at this venue. His success in the 2013 IPL, the only time MUM has won the title - also came here. Co-incidentally, his opponents were CHN, led by MS Dhoni. Can MUM sustain their red-hot form?]]></line><line><![CDATA[Consistency is the other name for Chennai. They breezed through the league stages and deservingly earned the right to have a second shot at the final - after losing to Mumbai in the first qualifier. What has been their recipe for success as they reach their sixth final in eight editions of the tournament? Some say it's all about player loyalty, CHN is one team that has made efforts to retain their core, right from the first season. Others are not that charitable - afterall it's an all-international team - with the Indian youngsters only watching all the action from the sidelines. Skipper, MS Dhoni, was blunt in accepting the fact that his team hasn't given chances to some of the bench players, but believes that they can learn a lot from simply watching the masters in action. They haven't won this tournament since 2011, but can Mahendra Singh Dhoni and his boys change the script tonight?]]></line><line><![CDATA[Before going any further, let's have a recap of what has been an exciting tournament. It all began on April 8th with Kolkata taking on Mumbai at this very venue. There have been runs, with as many as four players (Warner, Rahane, AB and Kohli) going past the 500-run mark. It's not that the bowlers have found it tough either. Five of them (Bravo, Chahal, Nehra, Malinga and Starc) hit the 20-wicket mark. There have been some remarkable catches, some stunning ground fielding - as well as some desperately poor stuff. It has been a tournament that has satisfied the purists as well as delighted the T20 enthusiasts. All in all, it has been one memorable competition - bringing the best out of every teams.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>18:30 Local Time, 13:00 GMT</b>: 56 league matches, a qualifier between the top two teams, an eliminator between the third and the fourth team and another qualifier between the winner of Match 58 v the loser of Match 57. At the end of it all, we have the two finalists. It's Mumbai against the Chennai in the final of the 8th edition of the Indian Premier League. Kolkata's famed Eden Gardens is the venue of what should be another cracking contest between the two most consistent teams in the history of the tournament. Domestic T20 cricket can't get better than this. It's CHN's consistency up against MUM's flair. It should be a fascinating contest to draw the curtains on what has been a tremendous season.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/><br/>As the dust settles on another frenetic season of Indian Premier League (IPL), the usual suspects - Chennai (CHN) and Mumbai - remain the last teams standing. Statistically, the two most successful sides (most number of matches won) in the tournament history, CHN and MUM have pushed boundaries and unravelled newer dimensions of the T20 format with each passing encounter. The next chapter of this rivalry features a battle for the coveted IPL trophy, something these two sides have fought for twice before.<br/><br/>58 matches and 43 days after after the tournament opener, Mumbai return to the grandest stage of Indian Cricket at the Eden Gardens, hoping to complete their remarkable turnaround - a run that has seen them upset the odds and become the first team to qualify for the final despite suffering losses in each of their first four games, including the opener in Kolkata.<br/><br/>Chennai meanwhile, like only then can do, sauntered through the group stages and despite not being at their best, have found ways to win the matches that matter. Remarkably, they now find themselves in their sixth final in the tournament's eight-year history. However, since their win in 2011, they have lost two subsequent finals, including one against Mumbai in 2013, and would dearly want to put one past their arch-rivals en route their third title.<br/><br/><b>Venue:</b> Eden Gardens, Kolkata<br/><b>Date:</b> May 24, 2015<br/><b>Time:</b> 20:00 IST<br/><b>Weather:</b> Humid with a ten percent chance of rain around 9 PM.<br/><br/><b>Team News:</b><br/><br/><b>Mumbai</b><br/><br/>A bulk of MUM's success in the second half of the tournament has been due to their opening combination in both bowling and batting. Lendl Simmons, Parthiv Patel, Mitchell McClenaghan and Lasith Malinga have been at the heart of their revival and with key contributions coming in from all quarters, the team management will not want to tinker with their playing eleven. Besides, by winning their first qualifier, MUM have given themselves two extra days of rest to tend to niggles or fatigue of any kind.<br/><br/>Probable XI: Parthiv Patel (wk), Lendl Simmons, Rohit Sharma (c), Ambati Rayudu, Kieron Pollard, Hardik Pandya, Harbhajan Singh, Jagdeesha Suchith, Mitchell McClenaghan, Vinay Kumar, Lasith Malinga.<br/><br/><b>Chennai</b><br/><br/>Not known to chop and change their team composition even during the league stages, CHN are unlikely to make any 11th-hour changes despite facing a quick turnaround from their last game. MS Dhoni is comfortable playing three frontline spinners in R Ashwin, Pawan Negi and Ravindra Jadeja. However, reports suggest that the pitch to be used for the final will not be the spin haven KOL enjoy playing on, and MS Dhoni might contemplate bringing in Ishwar Pandey for one of the two left-armers. <br/><br/>Probable XI: Michael Hussey, Dwayne Smith, Suresh Raina, Faf du Plessis, MS Dhoni, Dwayne Bravo, Pawan Negi, Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Mohit Sharma, Ashish Nehra<br/><br/><b>Stats and Trivia</b><br/><br/>- CHN and MUM are tied 1-1 in IPL Finals. Mumbai edged ahead in the overall H2H 12-11 by winning the Qualifier.<br/><br/>- Suresh Raina has 346 runs in 16 matches with just two fifties - his lowest returns in any season of the IPL since inception.<br/><br/>Quotes<br/><br/><i>"There is just one more game left and I know I need to bowl well and hopefully do the job for the team yet again."</i><br/><br/>- <b>Harbhajan Singh</b>, whose performances in the IPL earned him a Test spot, knows his four overs will be crucial to MUM's chances in the final<br/><br/><i>"I am hoping it sort of works out like 2013 where we beat MUM in the first Qualifier to go straight to the final and then lost to them in the final. This time we lost to them in the qualifier and hopefully can turn the tables on them in the final."</i><br/><br/>- <b>Michael Hussey</b> sees a pattern emerging in the rivalry ahead of the big final.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mumbai</b> (From): Lendl Simmons, Parthiv Patel(w), Rohit Sharma(c), Kieron Pollard, Hardik Pandya, Ambati Rayudu, Harbhajan Singh, Jagadeesha Suchith, Vinay Kumar, Lasith Malinga, Mitchell McClenaghan, Colin Munro, Aditya Tare, Jasprit Bumrah, Marchant de Lange, Pawan Suyal, Shreyas Gopal, Pragyan Ojha, Abhimanyu Mithun, Aiden Blizzard, Akshay Wakhare, Nitish Rana, Siddhesh Lad, Unmukt Chand]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai</b> (From): Dwayne Smith, Michael Hussey, Faf du Plessis, Suresh Raina, MS Dhoni(c & w), Pawan Negi, Dwayne Bravo, Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Mohit Sharma, Ashish Nehra, Ishwar Pandey, Baba Aparajith, Mithun Manhas, Rahul Sharma, Irfan Pathan, Andrew Tye, Eklavya Dwivedi, Pratyush Singh, Ankush Bains]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>202</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>5</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Mumbai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>599</playerid>
					<name>Lendl Simmons</name>
					<batsman-name>L Simmons</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Simmons</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>68</runs>
					<balls>45</balls>
					<fours>8</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Dwayne Smith</bowler>
					<bowlerId>255</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>74</playerid>
					<name>Parthiv Patel</name>
					<batsman-name>Parthiv Patel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Parthiv Patel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Faf du Plessis</fielder>
						<fielderId>7825</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>576</playerid>
					<name>Rohit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Rohit</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rohit</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>50</runs>
					<balls>26</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>DJ Bravo</bowler>
					<bowlerId>242</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ravindra Jadeja</fielder>
						<fielderId>587</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>657</playerid>
					<name>Kieron Pollard</name>
					<batsman-name>K Pollard</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Pollard</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>36</runs>
					<balls>18</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mohit Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8181</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Suresh Raina</fielder>
						<fielderId>413</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6311</playerid>
					<name>Ambati Rayudu</name>
					<batsman-name>Rayudu</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rayudu</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>36</runs>
					<balls>24</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9647</playerid>
					<name>Hardik Pandya</name>
					<batsman-name>H Pandya</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Pandya</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>DJ Bravo</bowler>
					<bowlerId>242</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Suresh Raina</fielder>
						<fielderId>413</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>75</playerid>
					<name>Harbhajan Singh</name>
					<batsman-name>Harbhajan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Harbhajan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10357</playerid>
					<name>Jagadeesha Suchith</name>
					<batsman-name>Jagadeesha Suchith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Jagadeesha Suchith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1449</playerid>
					<name>Vinay Kumar</name>
					<batsman-name>Vinay</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Vinay</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>111</playerid>
					<name>Lasith Malinga</name>
					<batsman-name>Malinga</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Malinga</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7624</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell McClenaghan</name>
					<batsman-name>McClenaghan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>McClenaghan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>74</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>1</runs>
				<overs>0.5</overs>
				<batsman>Parthiv Patel</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Parthiv Patel</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>576</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>120</runs>
				<overs>11.6</overs>
				<batsman>Rohit Sharma</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rohit</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>599</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>120</runs>
				<overs>12.1</overs>
				<batsman>Lendl Simmons</batsman>
				<batsman-name>L Simmons</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>657</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>191</runs>
				<overs>18.5</overs>
				<batsman>Kieron Pollard</batsman>
				<batsman-name>K Pollard</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9647</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>191</runs>
				<overs>19.2</overs>
				<batsman>Hardik Pandya</batsman>
				<batsman-name>H Pandya</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>1</byes>
			<wides>0</wides>
			<noballs>1</noballs>
			<legbyes>4</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>6</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Chennai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>269</playerid>
					<name>Ashish Nehra</name>
					<bowler-name>Nehra</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nehra</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>41</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Mohit Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mohit Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>38</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<bowler-name>Ashwin</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ashwin</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>21</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<bowler-name>R Jadeja</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>26</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8281</playerid>
					<name>Pawan Negi</name>
					<bowler-name>Negi</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Negi</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>18</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>242</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
					<bowler-name>DJ Bravo</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<bowler-name>Dwayne Smith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Smith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>17</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>4772</playerid>
					<name>Michael Hussey</name>
					<bowler-name>M Hussey</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M Hussey</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7825</playerid>
					<name>Faf du Plessis</name>
					<bowler-name>du Plessis</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>du Plessis</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<bowler-name>Raina</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Raina</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhoni</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhoni</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>161</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>8</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Chennai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Smith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>57</runs>
					<balls>48</balls>
					<fours>9</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Harbhajan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>75</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>4772</playerid>
					<name>Michael Hussey</name>
					<batsman-name>M Hussey</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M Hussey</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>McClenaghan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7624</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Jagadeesha Suchith</fielder>
						<fielderId>10357</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Raina</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>28</runs>
					<balls>19</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[stumped]]></status>
					<bowler>Harbhajan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>75</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Parthiv Patel</fielder>
						<fielderId>74</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhoni</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>18</runs>
					<balls>13</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Malinga</bowler>
					<bowlerId>111</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>242</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
					<batsman-name>DJ Bravo</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>McClenaghan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7624</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Lendl Simmons</fielder>
						<fielderId>599</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8281</playerid>
					<name>Pawan Negi</name>
					<batsman-name>Negi</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Negi</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Malinga</bowler>
					<bowlerId>111</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Hardik Pandya</fielder>
						<fielderId>9647</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7825</playerid>
					<name>Faf du Plessis</name>
					<batsman-name>du Plessis</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>du Plessis</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Vinay</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1449</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Rohit Sharma</fielder>
						<fielderId>576</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<batsman-name>R Jadeja</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>11</runs>
					<balls>8</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<batsman-name>Ashwin</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ashwin</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>McClenaghan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7624</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Jagadeesha Suchith</fielder>
						<fielderId>10357</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Mohit Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mohit Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>21</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>269</playerid>
					<name>Ashish Nehra</name>
					<batsman-name>Nehra</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nehra</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>4772</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>22</runs>
				<overs>4.4</overs>
				<batsman>Michael Hussey</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Hussey</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>255</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>88</runs>
				<overs>11.5</overs>
				<batsman>Dwayne Smith</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>413</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>99</runs>
				<overs>13.3</overs>
				<batsman>Suresh Raina</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>242</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>108</runs>
				<overs>14.3</overs>
				<batsman>Dwayne Bravo</batsman>
				<batsman-name>DJ Bravo</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>265</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>124</runs>
				<overs>15.5</overs>
				<batsman>MS Dhoni</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7825</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>125</runs>
				<overs>16.2</overs>
				<batsman>Faf du Plessis</batsman>
				<batsman-name>du Plessis</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8281</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>134</runs>
				<overs>17.3</overs>
				<batsman>Pawan Negi</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Negi</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1593</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>137</runs>
				<overs>18.2</overs>
				<batsman>Ravichandran Ashwin</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Ashwin</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>2</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Mumbai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>111</playerid>
					<name>Lasith Malinga</name>
					<bowler-name>Malinga</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Malinga</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7624</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell McClenaghan</name>
					<bowler-name>McClenaghan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>McClenaghan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1449</playerid>
					<name>Vinay Kumar</name>
					<bowler-name>Vinay</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Vinay</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>39</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9647</playerid>
					<name>Hardik Pandya</name>
					<bowler-name>H Pandya</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Pandya</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>75</playerid>
					<name>Harbhajan Singh</name>
					<bowler-name>Harbhajan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Harbhajan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>34</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>599</playerid>
					<name>Lendl Simmons</name>
					<bowler-name>L Simmons</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Simmons</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>74</playerid>
					<name>Parthiv Patel</name>
					<bowler-name>Parthiv Patel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Parthiv Patel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>576</playerid>
					<name>Rohit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Rohit</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rohit</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>657</playerid>
					<name>Kieron Pollard</name>
					<bowler-name>K Pollard</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Pollard</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6311</playerid>
					<name>Ambati Rayudu</name>
					<bowler-name>Rayudu</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rayudu</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10357</playerid>
					<name>Jagadeesha Suchith</name>
					<bowler-name>Jagadeesha Suchith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Jagadeesha Suchith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



