<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14640" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>47th Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Chennai</home>
		<away>Rajasthan</away>
		<teamsabbr>CHN vs JAI</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>CHN</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>JAI</awayabbr>
		<homeId>58</homeId>
		<awayId>64</awayId>
		<venue>MA Chidambaram Stadium, Chennai</venue>
		<startdate>10 05 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>10 05 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Chennai</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Chennai won by 12 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Chennai</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>12</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Marais Erasmus</Name>
			<Country>RSA</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Nandan</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Chris Gaffaney</Name>
			<Country>NZ</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Rajendra Jadeja</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>14:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150510181505</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>JAI</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>CHN</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>145</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>9</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>20</batteamovers>
		<status>Chennai won by 12 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>8333</playerid>
			<name>Chris Morris*</name>
			<batsman-name>C Morris</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>C Morris</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>16</runs>
			<balls-faced>10</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>1</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>9237</playerid>
			<name>Pravin Tambe</name>
			<batsman-name>Tambe</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Tambe</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>1</runs>
			<balls-faced>1</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>8181</playerid>
			<name>Mohit Sharma*</name>
			<bowler-name>Mohit Sharma</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Mohit Sharma</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>25</runs>
			<wickets>3</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>242</playerid>
			<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
			<bowler-name>DJ Bravo</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>43</runs>
			<wickets>2</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>158</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>7810</playerid>
<name>Ankit Sharma</name>
<player-runs>0</player-runs>
<player-balls>1</player-balls>
<runs>143</runs>
<wicket-nbr>9</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>242</bowlerid>
<bowlername>DJ Bravo</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>2</wides>
			<noballs>2</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>6</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[. 4 1 1 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 1 6 W 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>Wd 1 N1 1 W W . 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>N6 2 2 1 W 1 1 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/CHN_JAI_MAY10/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[That's it from us. It's a single-header tomorrow and it's Hyderabad taking on Punjab in a crucial game. Looking forward to your company then. Take care! Goodbye!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Let's have a look at some of the tweets.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sanjay Manjrekar</b>: Dhoni does not like discarding out of form players he has faith in. Both Mohit & Jadeja repaying that trust tonight.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Harsha Bhogle</b>: Easily one of the catches of the tournament. In fact, you can have a spectacular #Bravo catches showreel!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohandas Menon</b>: The only other time Ashwin did not bowl in an #IPL match was vs #MUM at Cape Town in 2009. It was in his IPL debut match.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Navneet Mundhra</b>: Yet again... Chennai storm into the play-offs! Customary for them.. Remarkable consistency... Congrats.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Alt Cricket</b>: Dwayne Bravo pulls off an NBA-style RIDICUCATCH! Never seen a tournament with so many incredible, unlikely catches.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jadeja</b>: "First I would like to thank my mom. Today is Mother's day. I was enjoying my bowling out there. Brendon has been hitting well. It's good for the team. He (Dwayne Bravo) is a good fielder and an entertainer in T20 cricket."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jadeja is the Man of the Match</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhoni</b>: "I think calling it a secret is wrong. I think the secret is them (opposition captains) calling it wrong (when asked what was his secret that helps him win tosses). Also there was a sequence when I lost 29 of the 32 tosses. There is a joke in the dressing room that if Baz (Brendon McCullum) bats for 6 overs, he's cooked there. Michael Hussey will replace McCullum. Hussey has been great for us. Yes it is a big loss that Brendon will have to go back (to attend national duty). Jadeja and Negi were bowling well. I felt as if there's no point bowling Ashwin. It's not that he's not good enough, but it is just that I didn't have to use him today."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Smith</b>: "Shane (Watson) decided to hand over the captaincy to me, so that he can focus on his skills, batting and bowling, and that's how it is going to be for the rest of the tournament. I thought the bowlers did a decent job, but we lost wickets in the middle. Jadeja bowled well. It was tough to form many partnerships. We've got a 6-day break. Hopefully we can regroup and make it to the playoffs."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, it was Brendon McCullum, who shone brightly with a sterling innings. It wasn't one of those typical knocks from McCullum, as he looked to play himself in before upping the tempo. Among RAJ's bowlers, Chris Morris picked up three scalps. RAJ now will have to beat KOL to have a realistic chance to qualify for the playoffs. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ravindra Jadeja bowled a parsimonious spell to snare four wickets as CHN registered a fine victory. With this victory, the hosts have almost qualified for the playoffs. On a slow track, RAJ's batsmen just couldn't come to grips with Jadeja's bowling. Even Mohit Sharma mixed up his pace well to snaffle three wickets. Shane Watson and Ajinkya Rahane played fluent hands, but the visitors needed more from their opening duo. James Faulkner and Sanju Samson too made their presence felt, but they had too much to do. It also has to be remembered that Dwayne Bravo took a couple of excellent catches, especially he showed great judegment at long-on to pluck a catch out of thin air and send Watson back to the pavilion.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nehra takes the Purple Cap off his head and gives it to Dwayne Bravo. He pats him on the head and also points to the camera to show that he's the highest wicket-taker now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to C Morris, 1 run, shortish from Bravo, Morris pulls it wide of long-on. <b>CHN win by 12 runs</b> and this win helps them to get back on top of the points table. <b>CHN are almost through to the playoffs</b>. Disappointment for the Rajasthan, they are under a bit of pressure now with just one game to go. They are stuck on 14 points. The next match is a must-win game for them]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Tambe, 1 run, ah! <b>A big smile on Dhoni's face for the first time today</b>. He wanted to win this game badly. Slower delivery outside off stump, Tambe toe-ends the slog to the right of the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pravin Tambe, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two legitimate deliveries will take CHN home.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Ankit Sharma, <b>out</b> Caught by Nehra!! Oh Nehra jumps and takes a good catch. Second wicket for DJ. Slower delivery outside off stump, Ankit Sharma swings hard and gets an outside edge, short third man moves to his left, times his jump to perfection and takes it with both hands. <b>Ankit Sharma c Nehra b Dwayne Bravo 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dwayne Bravo to Ankit Sharma, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Need a couple of sixes and a four. 15 off 3 balls now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to C Morris, 1 run, he's hit this too hard and he can't get two this time, straight to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to C Morris, 2 runs, full from Bravo, Morris lofts it over the bowler's head, Baz rushes in but they get back for the second. Ankit Sharma responds well by quickly returning for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to C Morris, 2 runs, Dhoni is livid with the fielder, Jadeja it is, for the poor throw. He just throws the ball away in anger after collecting the return. Morris slogs it to deep mid-wicket and returns back for the second run. Jadeja throw it very wide]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[It's now down to <b>20 needed off 6</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to C Morris, <b>no ball</b>, <b>SIX</b>, this is interesting! Full toss above the waist, Morris helps it on its way over short fine leg and it goes for a flat six]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>27 needed off 6</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to C Morris, 1 run, low full toss outside off stump, Morris drives it to deep extra-cover, it was an easy two, Ankit Sharma races for the second, but because Morris wanted the strike he sent him back. Ankit Sharma was halfway down the wicket but Negi threw the ball at the wrong end]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to C Morris, no run, <b>no hat-trick</b>. Slower delivery outside off stump, Morris swings and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ankit Sharma, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to R Bhatia, <b>out</b> Caught by du Plessis!! He's taken a good catch, but he straightaway holds his right hamstring! He's in pain. Slower delivery outside off stump, Bhatia steps out and goes hard at it, slices it, backward point runs to his right and takes it. Just as he was about to catch, he stretched his legs awkwardly and probably that hurt him. <b>Mohit Sharma is on a hat-trick</b>. <b>R Bhatia c du Plessis b Mohit Sharma 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mohit Sharma to R Bhatia, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajat Bhatia, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Faulkner, <b>out</b> Caught by Dwayne Bravo!! The DJ with his dance moves again. Wow! He takes these catches so easily. Low full toss outside off stump, Faulkner reaches out and drives, hits in the air, Bravo jumps high at extra-cover and grabs it above his head with both hands before tumbling onto the ground. The key to that catch was he timed his jump to perfection. Another great catch from the Trinidadian. <b>Faulkner c Dwayne Bravo b Mohit Sharma 16(13) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mohit Sharma to Faulkner, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to C Morris, 1 run, <b>even Brendon McCullum drops a catch</b>. Is the ball too greasy? Slower delivery full and outside off stump, Morris slices the loft, Baz runs to his left from long-off, it was an easy catch and came at a good height but he spills it]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Faulkner, <b>no ball</b>, 1 run, full toss, but it's <b>above the waist</b>. <b>Called a no-ball</b>. Faulkner only manages to pull it to long leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to C Morris, 1 run, low full toss outside off stump, Morris reaches out and drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Dhoni has tucked his right glove in his pants so as to have a shy at the stumps if the batsmen try to steal a bye.]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to C Morris, <b>wide</b>, should be a wide and is a wide. Way outside off stump, Mohit Sharma lost control of the slower delivery]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma [3.0-0-19-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Rajasthan need 33 runs off 12 balls. It's difficult on this pitch, but still doable!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to C Morris, 1 run, slower delivery outside off stump, Morris flicks it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Faulkner, 1 run, low full toss, flicked to long-on, that was so kind from Faulkner. He should have muscled that one]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Morris, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Samson, <b>out</b> Caught by Dwayne Smith!! <b>Dwayne Bravo is now the leading wicket-taker of the season</b>. This is brave from Samson but he's holed out. Despite the keeper standing up to the stumps, he races down the track, Bravo bangs this slower ball short, Samson looks to slap hard but slices it, Smith runs forward from sweeper cover and completes a fine catch. Samson was batting well and was picking Bravo, but he's gone now! <b>Samson c Dwayne Smith b Dwayne Bravo 26(17) [4s-1 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dwayne Bravo to Samson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhoni is now up to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Samson, <b>SIX</b>, Samson has no problems in picking the slower ones from Dwayne Bravo. Dances down the track, manufactures a length ball and slogs it high over deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Faulkner, 1 run, yorker length delivery, Faulkner digs it out hard onto the ground, it bounces over the bowler and rolls to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Samson, 1 run, <b>comedy of errors</b>! Slower delivery on the stumps, Samson slogs hard and loses his bat, gets a top edge, Bravo runs back, he had it covered, went with both hands but it popped out. <b>Bravo has dropped a sitter</b>. Samson's bat almost flew to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Good over in the context of the game. Just 8 runs off it. 43 needed off 18.]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Samson, 1 run, fine delivery to end the over, yorker length on the leg stump, Samson drills it hard, Nehra gets his right hand to it in his followthrough and takes some pace off as it rolls to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Faulkner, 1 run, bangs the slower ball too short and gets away with it, Faulkner pulls it to the left of deep backward square leg, where Smith runs and bends down nicely to field the ball. He gets a cheer from the crowd as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Samson, 1 run, slower delivery on the off stump, pushed through cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Faulkner, 1 run, advances and takes it on the full, Faulkner swings hard, not timed properly, beats McCullum's dive to his right at extra-cover, long-off tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Faulkner, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a clever hit. Just used the pace on the ball, short of a length and on the leg stump, helped on its way past short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Faulkner, no run, low full toss, driven to extra-cover, Samson takes off for a run but Faulkner sends him back, Baz has a shy and misses. Anyway Samson would have been in as he dived full length]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashish Nehra [3.0-0-21-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's 51 off 24 balls now! Looks like we are not going to see Ashwin with the ball tonight.]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Faulkner, 1 run, slower delivery on the leg stump, Samson nudges it to mid-wicket, Samson looks for the second but Jadeja gets to the ball very quickly from the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Faulkner, <b>FOUR</b>, poor fielding from Dwayne Smith again. Short of a length delivery outside off stump, Faulkner cuts it through deep point, Smith runs to his left from sweeper but doesn't get down quickly and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Samson, 1 run, oh Samson runs at the bowler, gets close to the pitch of the slower delivery and flicks it through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Samson, <b>SIX</b>, that is a brilliant shot from Samson. He anticipated the slower ball, picked it early, down on one knee, the slog-sweep was timed so sweetly that it cleared deep mid-wicket by some distance]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Faulkner, 1 run, on the leg stump, nudged through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Samson, 1 run, slower delivery outside off stump, Samson mistimes the drive on the bounce to extra-cover, they go for the run, Baz had a lot of time to take aim but missed the sticks at the bowler's end. Samson would have been out by some distance]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Jadeja ends 4-0-11-4 - his best figures this season.]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Samson, 1 run, flighted delivery on the leg stump, Samson advances and flicks it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Samson, no run, big appeal for LBW/catch. Jadeja was running in his appeal, he can't believe that the finger hasn't gone up. Fast and full, Samson misses the sweep, too full to sweep in fact, gets hit on the pad but again it was going down. Dhoni takes the catch, they appeal for the catch as well but it missed the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Faulkner, 1 run, full and outside off stump, Faulkner drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Faulkner, no run, fired full from Jadeja, Faulkner misses the flick and gets hit on the pad, loud appeal from Jadeja but it was sliding down]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Samson, 1 run, on the leg stump, Samson works it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Deepak Hooda, <b>out</b> Caught by Raina!! Would you believe it! It's a full toss and it's a wicket for Jadeja. Wicket number for four him. What a night he's having. Hooda loses his shape as he tries to go hard at this freebie after coming down the track, mistimes it completely, goes high in the air and long-on settles under it to take a good catch. As soon as he hit the ball, Hooda swung his bat in disappointment. <b>Deepak Hooda c Raina b Ravindra Jadeja 15(14) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Ravindra Jadeja to Deepak Hooda, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja [3.0-0-8-3] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, Hooda shuffles in the crease, Bravo follows him with a slower ball, glanced to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Deepak Hooda, no run, slower delivery on the off stump, Hooda defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Samson, 1 run, flicked away into the on-side, through square leg again]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, down the leg-side, flicked straight to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Samson, 1 run, on the leg stump, nudged to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, slower delivery on the off stump, Hooda flicks it to mid-wicket, Samson wants two, but Hooda sends him back, Jadeja comes in from the deep but doesn't pick it up cleanly]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, nicely driven along the ground but straight to deep extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Samson, 1 run, on the leg stump, glanced to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Samson, <b>wide</b>, fired down the leg-side, easy call for the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Samson, <b>FOUR</b>, excellent shot! Quicker ball outside off stump, Samson waits for the ball, cuts very late and beats backward point to his left. He made use of the pace on the ball on that occasion]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Samson, no run, Samson looks to work this into the on-side, but gets a soft leading edge that rolls back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, shortish from Negi, Hooda punches it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Deepak Hooda, 2 runs, Hooda dances down the track and flicks it wide of Bravo at long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Samson, no run, tossed up on the off stump, Samson defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sanju Samson, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Nair, <b>out</b> Caught by Ashwin!! Nair attempts another sweep shot, but it's a top edge this time and Ashwin didn't have to move an inch at short fine leg. The Rajasthan need to be careful now. Can't afford to throw away wickets at will. Third wicket for Jadeja. Nair got down on one knee to sweep, but couldn't get the execution right. <b>Nair c Ashwin b Ravindra Jadeja 10(12) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ravindra Jadeja to Nair, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, flighted delivery just outside off stump, Hooda pushes it uppishly wide of long-off, Hooda looks for two, but Smith rushes in quickly and prevents the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Nair, leg byes, 1 run, big appeal for LBW, but umpire Marais Erasmus said it was too high. Nair fails to connect with the sweep, gets hit on the body]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Deepak Hooda, leg byes, 1 run, slider darted in, Hooda misses the flick, hit on the pad but no appeal as it was sliding down]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Nair, 1 run, flighted delivery on the leg stump, Nair drives it to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[The Rajasthan need 87 runs off 54 balls.]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Deepak Hooda, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely hit inside-out over extra-cover. Comes down the track and lofts this drive over the infield to end the over on a high]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Deepak Hooda, no run, Hooda comes down the track again, Negi drags his length back and forces Hooda to defend]]></line><line><![CDATA[One slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Nair, 1 run, very full and outside off stump, driven square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Nair, no run, sharp turn, Nair opens the face of the bat and dabs it to point, Deepak Hooda takes off for a run but Nair sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Deepak Hooda, 1 run, the use of the feet now to get close to the pitch of this flighted delivery, driven to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Deepak Hooda, 2 runs, on the pads, Hooda flicks it to deep mid-wicket and quickly returns for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Deepak Hooda, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Watson, <b>out</b> Caught by Dwayne Bravo!! That's a spectacular catch from Bravo at long-on! One of the best in this edition's IPL. That looked like a six the moment Watson hit it. He hadn't counted for Bravo's brilliance though. This was tossed up and on the stumps, Watson lunged forward on the shovelled loft, got a meaty connection on the willow. It looked to be sailing past Bravo, he leapt full length and takes a one-handed blinder, stretching his right hand as far as he could. He then controls himself, makes sure he didn't step onto the ropes and starts his celebratory run. Watson is stunned, the third umpire has a look, but it was a clean catch. <b>Watson c Dwayne Bravo b Ravindra Jadeja 28(30) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ravindra Jadeja to Watson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Nair, 1 run, pushed through by Jadeja, Nair makes room and drives it down towards long-off for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Watson, 1 run, Jadeja drops one short and on the stumps, pulled away towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Watson, no run, slower and just outside off, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Nair, 1 run, tossed up and just outside off, driven past extra cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Watson, 1 run, flighted delivery and on Watson's pads, worked towards deep mid-wicket for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Watson, 1 run, Negi drops one short and on the stumps, Watson rocks back and pulls it towards deep mid-wicket, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Looks like the dew is taking full effect. Some vigorous rubbing of the ball is going on]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, this was tossed up and well outside off, Watson gets a big stride forward and drills it past extra cover. Faf gets across from long-off, but he landed on the ball as he dived, ends up palming it to the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Watson, no run, fraction short and just outside off, Watson backs away and cuts it straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Nair, 1 run, flighted and just outside off, Nair goes back and works it square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Nair, <b>FOUR</b>, sloppy from Smith, this was tossed up and just outside off, Nair went down on his knees as he played the slog sweep. Smith got across quickly but was lazy to bend down, goes one-handed and helps the ball to the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Nair, no run, flighted delivery and on the stumps, Nair goes back and defends it towards the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Nair, 1 run, this one is given more air, Nair makes room, presents the full face of the bat and drives it past cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Nair, no run, tossed up and just outside off, Nair gets forward and drives it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Karun Nair, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to S Smith, <b>out</b> Bowled!! That's a big blow for RAJ. This was tossed up and on the leg-stump line, Smith went for the sweep, he got a long way across his stumps as he missed the shot, the ball clipped the outer half of the leg-stump on its way to the keeper. Jadeja was appealing for a caught behind, the sound was ball hitting the stumps though. Replays confirm it and RAJ have lost their second wicket. <b>S Smith b Ravindra Jadeja 4(6)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ravindra Jadeja to S Smith, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Has Smith been bowled? MS was confident, Jadeja was appealing for a caught behind. The third umpire has been called to look into this. Yes, Smith has been bowled. <b>OUT</b> is the call]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to S Smith, no run, flighted delivery and on the stumps, Smith goes back and punches it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Watson, 1 run, fraction short and well outside off, Watson makes room and cuts it to deep cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Watson, no run, flighted and on Watson's pads, he looks to flick and misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Watson, 1 run, tossed up and on Watson's pads, nudged to the right of mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to S Smith, 1 run, the arm-ball from Negi, Smith makes room and pushes it square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Watson, 1 run, Negi drops one short and well outside leg, pulled away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to S Smith, 1 run, Smith shimmies down the track to a well flighted delivery and eases it down towards long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to S Smith, 2 runs, this one is given more air and just outside off, driven crisply past extra cover. Baba Aparajith makes a lot of ground, slides and pulls the ball back in]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Watson, 1 run, Negi drops one short and well outside off, Watson makes room and cuts it towards deep cover for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pawan Negi, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to S Smith, no run, short of a length and angling onto Smith's pads, he shuffles across and tucks it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Watson, 1 run, on a good length and on the middle stump line, Watson closed the face of the bat a tad too early, gets a leading edge and to the right of Bravo at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Watson, 2 runs, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Watson drives it firmly and to the right of extra cover. Dwayne Smith makes a half-stop and the ball rolls away towards long-off. Smith calls for a second run and completes it with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Steven Smith, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rahane, <b>out</b> Caught by Dwayne Bravo!! Bravo does the familiar jig after taking a good running catch. It was another bouncer from Mohit, but there was a lot of effort put into it. Rahane was looking to pull, is hurried onto the shot and ends up skying it high and over square leg. Bravo runs in from the deep and takes a good catch bending forward. Rahane was looking good but has to walk back to the hut. <b>Rahane c Dwayne Bravo b Mohit Sharma 23(17) [4s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mohit Sharma to Rahane, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rahane, 2 runs, too straight from Mohit, worked away behind square on the on-side. Bravo gets across from deep square leg and keeps them down to a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Watson, 3 runs, slower ball from Mohit, Watson spots it early and lofts it over extra cover. Faf runs from mid-off, puts in the dive and pulls the ball back in, saves a run for his team]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Watson, 1 run, full and just outside off, Watson is late on the drive, gets a bottom edge that bounces off the turf. Rahane calls him through for a quick single. Nehra gets across and has a shy at the bowler's end, but Watson was too quick for him]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Watson, <b>FOUR</b>, Watson breaks the shackles! Width on offer from Nehra, Watson waits on it and cracks it square past point, no one in the deep and the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rahane, 1 run, back of a length and on Rahane's pads, nudged away awkwardly behind square for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, Rahane is looking very positive, overpitched by Nehra, Rahane gets forward and tonks it back over the bowler's head, sails over mid-on and races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Watson, 1 run, Nehra bangs one short and on the stumps, stayed a tad low as well, Watson crunches and pulls it towards deep mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Watson, no run, change of pace from Nehra, this one was slanted across Watson, he goes for the big drive and misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rahane, 2 runs, on a good length and well outside off, Rahane presses forward and lifts it over Faf at mid-off. He scrambles behind the ball, puts the slide in and drags it back into play, keeps the batsmen down to just a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rahane, no run, short of a length and just outside off, punched towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Watson, 1 run, on a good length and well outside off, Watson closes the face of the bat and drives it to the right of mid-off. Faf dives and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rahane, 1 run, the slower ball from Mohit, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, too short from Mohit, Rahane swivels across, rolls his wrists and pulls it behind square on the on-side. Bravo gets across and puts in the dive, but the ball slips beneath and rolls away to the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Watson, 1 run, Mohit bangs one short and on the stumps, pulled away in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Watson, 1 run, full and on Watson's pads, whipped away towards deep mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Watson, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Watson goes hard on the drive and mistimes it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Watson, no run, short of a length and angling across Watson, defended towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rahane, 1 run, back of a length and on Rahane's pads, nudged behind square on the on-side. Watson wanted a second run and there's a fumble by the fielder but Rahane sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[Has the ball been damaged by the previous boundary? The umpires concur and call for a replacement.]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, length ball from Nehra, Rahane moves into the shot and chips it high and over mid-on, a couple of bounces and over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rahane, no run, short of a length and slanting across the right-hander, Rahane went chasing after that and is beaten]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Watson, 2 runs, Mohit bangs one short and well outside off, Watson swivels across and pulls it in front of square on the on-side. Not well timed, Bravo gets across from deep mid-wicket and keeps them down to a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Watson, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Watson leans forward and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Watson, no run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, driven crisply but straight to Raina at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Watson, no run, width on offer from Mohit, Watson stands tall and crunches it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Watson, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Watson stays behind the line and punches it towards short extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Watson, no run, short of a length and holding its line outside off, Watson plays from the crease and gets an inside edge onto his thigh pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rahane, no run, tad fuller and a hint of shape back into Rahane, he prods across and defends it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, pitched up and wide outside off, Rahane leans forward and lifts it up and over point, no need to run for those. Nehra has a wry smile on his face]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rahane, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Rahane prods forward and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rahane, no run, nice shape from Nehra, ran his fingers across there, gets it to shape away from the right-hander, Rahane went poking at that and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rahane, no run, on a good length and shaping away from outside off, Rahane pushes at that and gets an inside edge onto his pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Rahane, no run, fuller length delivery and in that corridor outside off, Rahane covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rahane and Watson are at the crease. Rahane is on strike. Nehra will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place for Nehra]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. Strong words from MS Dhoni at the huddle. Can CHN finish off their home games with a ticket to the knock-out stage?]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Faulkner</b>: "They probably got away from us towards the end, but I am backing our batsmen to do the job. It is a slow wicket. We've got to dominate the first 6 overs and hopefully we'll get off to a good start."]]></line><line><![CDATA[RAJ would rue the fact that their spinners Ankit Sharma and Tambe struggled to make it count. Chris Morris, the seamer, bowled a decent spell up front. CHN have put the runs on the board on a track that should suit their spinners. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Brendon McCullum played with a calm head on his shoulders to steer CHN to a competitive total. With the wicket offering assistance to the spinners, McCullum mixed caution with aggression to keep the scorecard ticking. He also showed his ability to tackle the spinners by carting Pravin Tambe for a couple of sixes in the sixth over. At the other end, Faf du Plessis gave him valuable support as they stitched a century stand.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Dhoni, 1 run, wow! What a ball to finish from Morris. Pacy yorker, it was too quick for Dhoni, who manages an inside edge that rolls into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Dwayne Bravo, 1 run, full toss again, Bravo moves leg-side and loft-drives it over the bowler's head, just a single though as long-off tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Dhoni, 1 run, down the track, Morris bangs the slower ball short, Dhoni can only drag the pull from outside off stump to Rahane at long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Dhoni, no run, yorker length delivery outside off stump, Dhoni throws the kitchen sink at it but gets beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Dwayne Bravo, 1 run, hurried on the pull by this short ball, Bravo splices the pull but it doesn't carry to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Dwayne Bravo, <b>FOUR</b>, great placement from DJ to raise the 150 for CHN. The man sweeping on the off-side was more at deep cover, as this low full toss arrives, Bravo opens the face of the bat while driving and sends it through cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dhoni, <b>FOUR</b>, tries a similar delivery, but loses control and bowls a low full toss outside off stump, Dhoni reaches out and drives it over extra-cover, beats the fielder in the deep to end the over on a high]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dhoni, no run, beaten! Yorker angling away from the right-hander, Dhoni tries to squeeze it out through backward point but doesn't make contact]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dhoni, <b>SIX</b>, I think this has come off the inside half of the bat and it has gone way back over deep mid-wicket. Big six from the skipper and his counterpart can't watch it. Full and outside off stump, cruel delivery from the bowler and that too to Dhoni, who slogs it hard for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chants of "Dhoni, Dhoni, Dhoni" doing the rounds.]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dwayne Bravo, 1 run, guides it straight to short third man, but Dhoni is quickly off the blocks to get home safely]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dwayne Bravo, 2 runs, slower delivery on the leg stump, Bravo turns it to mid-wicket, calls for two and makes his ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Dwayne Bravo, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a ridiculous hit! He went one-handed at it, but it's gone for four. Short of a length delivery way outside off stump, Bravo had to reach out a long way to make contact, in the process loses the bottom hand grip, slices it over backward point with his left hand and it escapes]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner [3.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Great over from Morris, just 4 singles and 2 wickets in it.]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Dwayne Bravo, 1 run, good looking off-drive off the front foot, but all along the ground and more importantly straight to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Dhoni, 1 run, fantastic yorker, this would been very good for the hat-trick ball, but it's come one ball late. Anyway, Dhoni digs it out and it rolls into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Dwayne Bravo, 1 run, no hat-trick, not the best of deliveries I must say. Tries the yorker, but bowls a low full toss, driven down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[DJ to face the hat-trick ball.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Negi, <b>out</b> Caught by S Smith!! No heroics with the bat from Negi tonight. It's two-in-two for Morris and <b>he's on a hat-trick</b> against his former team. Full and in the slot, Negi cleared his right leg and went hard with the drive, the ball hit the toe-end of the bat and went straight to extra-cover. <b>Negi c S Smith b C Morris 2(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[C Morris to Negi, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>MS Dhoni, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mahendra Singh Dhoni walks out to a loud roar!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Brendon McCullum, <b>out</b> Caught by Ankit Sharma!! It's a top edge and it's taken very well by Ankit Sharma. He throws the ball up in the air in delight after completing the catch. End of a fine innings from McCullum. Short ball on the leg stump, McCullum goes for the pull, gets a big edge, fine leg runs forward, dives and takes a good low catch. <b>Brendon McCullum c Ankit Sharma b C Morris 81(61) [4s-7 6s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[C Morris to Brendon McCullum, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Negi, 1 run, slower ball very full and outside off stump, Negi drills it hard but straight to the man sweeping on the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Morris [2.0-0-7-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Brendon McCullum, <b>SIX</b>, full and just outside off stump, not the right length at this stage, a friendly ball in fact and McCullum gives everything at it and the ball clears the long-on boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Negi, 1 run, slower delivery on the off stump, Negi taps it to short-cover and sets off for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, now drives hard this time, but straight to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, lucky runs for Baz and CHN. McCullum steps out and slashes hard at this short of length delivery, thick outside edge and there was no one at slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pawan Negi, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Brendon McCullum, <b>out</b> du Plessis Run Out!! Sent back and Watson fires a direct-hit. Baz is so tired that he doesn't want to play straight for the big hit, he tries to use the pace on the ball and goes for the reverse-scoop. Fails to get bat on ball and it hits his right leg, as the ball rolls towards short mid-wicket, Faf tries to steal a run but Baz was in no position to take off for the run. Watson picks up the ball and hits timber. <b>du Plessis run out (Watson) 29(25) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Watson to Brendon McCullum, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Brendon McCullum, no run, gets early into a position to scoop, Watson sees him and fires it way outside off stump, McCullum tries to ramp it towards third man but fails to make contact]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Brendon McCullum, <b>wide</b>, too wide outside off stump, McCullum fails to reach out]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Watson [1.0-0-6-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Baz is struggling out there. The high humidity has taken a toll on him.]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, back and across, deep into the crease as well, lofted back over the bowler's head but completely mistimed. <b>100 partnership</b> comes up with that run]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Brendon McCullum, 2 runs, full and way outside off stump, McCullum reaches out and slices it over backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Brendon McCullum, 2 runs, this time he goes right across the stumps and cuts the angle, pulls it over square leg, Morris runs to his right from deep mid-wicket, dives and saves two]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to du Plessis, 1 run, in the airrrrr but safe! Oh this could be trouble for Baz, but he is safe. Short of a length delivery outside off stump, du Plessis checks his shot and pushes hard at it, the ball lands just before the man at point, they take a run and the fielder has a shy at the striker's end but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, this time he tries to drive over the off-side, but mistimes it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Brendon McCullum, no run, Baz, got to target cover with the angle away from you! Full and wide outside off stump, McCullum tries to slog it through mid-wicket and gets beaten]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner [2.0-0-16-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to du Plessis, no run, almost had him stumped! Ankit Sharma fired this wide outside off stump on seeing du Plessis advance, somehow Faf manages to reach out and get the toe end of the bat. Otherwise, he would have been out by a long way]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to du Plessis, no run, <b>dropped</b>, but a tough chance. It was a big deflection. Shortish and on the leg stump, du Plessis backs away and looks to punch through cover, gets a thick edge, it was too quick for Samson and it popped out]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, top placement from Faf! Short delivery on the leg stump, du Plessis rocks back and pulls it in the gap between long-on and deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, cramps Baz for room with a short ball as he comes down the track, flicked through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to Brendon McCullum, <b>5 wides</b>, poor bowling and poor keeping. That's gone right through Samson. He should have easily taken that. Bonus runs for CHN]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to du Plessis, 1 run, steps out and nudges this into the vacant mid-wicket region, looks for two but it's not there]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to du Plessis, no run, short and on the off stump, du Plessis rocks back and punches it to extra-cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ankit Sharma [3.0-0-20-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Bhatia to Brendon McCullum, 2 runs, too short and outside off stump, cuts to the right of extra-cover, long-off tidies up running to his left]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Bhatia to Brendon McCullum, <b>SIX</b>, in the air and Faulkner can only watch it sail over at deep mid-wicket. Too predictable from Bhatia, can't bowl a slower ball every ball, McCullum stays on the back foot and pulls it nicely for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Bhatia to Brendon McCullum, no run, Baz dances down the track and also makes room, but Bhatia follows him and yorks him, hit back towards the bowler, who makes a diving save to his right]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Bhatia to du Plessis, 1 run, slower delivery on the leg stump, du Plessis works it away to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Bhatia to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, short of length delivery on the off stump, punched very hard to extra-cover, excellent fielding by Smith as it was travelling, he has a shy at the striker's end but Faf made his ground before Samson whipped the bails off]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Bhatia to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, oh that bounces just inside the rope. Bhatia bowls a juicy full ball, it was the slower ball but Baz picked it early and lofted it easily over extra-cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajat Bhatia [2.0-0-9-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball. It was turning out to be a good over, but Tambe lost control and dropped it short, du Plessis rocked back and pulled it powerfully through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Baz flicks it through mid-wicket and gets to <b>fifty</b>. Very slow by his standards, took 44 balls but one can understand. The pitch isn't easy to bat on. The CHN dug out rises to applaud and the crowd joins the party as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to du Plessis, 1 run, full and on the leg stump, du Plessis flicks it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to du Plessis, 2 runs, punched off the back foot to deep extra-cover and these two are quick between the wickets]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to du Plessis, no run, beaten! Big spin, pitches on the off stump and turns away, bit of extra bounce as well, du Plessis looks to defend but the turn surprises him and he pokes at it]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, steps out and takes it on the full, driven to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pravin Tambe [2.0-0-15-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, short ball from Faulkner, pulled to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, the <b>Baz-scoop</b> this time. Faulkner goes full around the off stump, McCullum moves across, gets into a great position by bending his knees and scoops it over his left shoulder]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, finally he connects one! Baz races down the track, cuts down the angle a bit and slaps it hard past the diving Steven Smith at extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Brendon McCullum, no run, another swing and a miss. This time McCullum tries to cut with the angle, but only connects with thin air. Faulkner has a friendly word with Baz]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Brendon McCullum, no run, similar delivery, slightly fuller in length but a similar result. Faulkner beats McCullum's slog]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Brendon McCullum, no run, slower delivery angling away from the right-hander from over the wicket, McCullum slogs and misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner [1.0-0-7-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Bhatia to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, oh he bowls the conventional seam-up delivery for the first time in the over, punched to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Bhatia to du Plessis, 1 run, drops the slower delivery short, flicked to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Bhatia to du Plessis, no run, du Plessis mistimes the drive back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Bhatia to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, no pace whatsoever, tucked gently to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Bhatia to du Plessis, 1 run, slower delivery on the off stump, du Plessis flicks it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Bhatia to Brendon McCullum, leg byes, 1 run, slower delivery down the leg-side, McCullum fails to connect with the glance, the ball rolls to short fine leg off the pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajat Bhatia [1.0-0-5-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to du Plessis, no run, tossed up and spinning away from outside off, du Plessis cuts it straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, slower and flatter from Sharma, McCullum goes back and works it past mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to du Plessis, 3 runs, tossed up and well outside off, du Plessis was looking to play the lap sweep, gets a top-edge and over first slip, he runs hard and gets back for the third run]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, <b>just over mid-wicket</b>, pre-meditated charge from McCullum, comes down the track, doesn't get to the pitch of the ball and drags it just over mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, the slog sweep from McCullum, gets into an excellent position and sweeps it powerfully past square leg, no chance for the man getting across from mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to du Plessis, 1 run, fraction short and just outside off, worked square on the off-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ankit Sharma [2.0-0-10-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Brendon McCullum, no run, the wrong 'un from Tambe, McCullum didn't spot it as he prodded forward, the impact was outside off though, excellent comeback over from Tambe]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Brendon McCullum, no run, this one is drifted outside off, McCullum presses forward and defends it back at the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Brendon McCullum, no run, pushed through with a flatter trajectory, McCullum lunges forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Brendon McCullum, no run, flighted and on the middle stump line, McCullum lunges forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to du Plessis, 1 run, Tambe gives this one more air, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, tossed up and just outside off, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pravin Tambe [1.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Bhatia to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, short of a length and on the stumps, worked in front of mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Bhatia to Brendon McCullum, 2 runs, the reverse scoop from McCullum, this was another slower delivery outside off, McCullum was setting himself up for the paddle sweep, delays his shot and reverse paddles it over the keeper's head]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Bhatia to Brendon McCullum, no run, Bhatia is dealing with slower ones, this one held up on the surface after pitching, Brendon McCullum gets behind the line and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Bhatia to Brendon McCullum, no run, another slower ball from Bhatia, McCullum waits on it and dabs it straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Bhatia to du Plessis, 1 run, the slower ball from Bhatia, du Plessis waits on it and punches it down towards long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Bhatia to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, on a good length and on the stumps, nudged in front of mid-wicket for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajat Bhatia, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, short of a good length and just outside off, McCullum slaps it high and over cover, the ball bounces in front of the fielder getting across from sweeper cover, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four</b>, width on offer from Faulkner, McCullum was looking to play the late cut, gets a thick edge and flies past the keeper. A boundary is the end result]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Brendon McCullum, no run, short of a length and just outside off, punched to the right of point where Rahane makes a smart stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to du Plessis, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, dabbed away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, a hint of width on offer from Faulkner, McCullum cracks it to the right of Rahane at cover-point, takes off for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Faulkner to Brendon McCullum, no run, short of a length and angling across the right-hander, McCullum drops his wrists and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Faulkner, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, fraction shorter and wider from Tambe, punched down towards long-off for a single, <b>13 runs from the over</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Brendon McCullum, <b>SIX</b>, that's a superb riposte from McCullum, shimmies down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and goes with the swing, clears the long-on fence, <b>brings up 2000 IPL runs as well</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Brendon McCullum, no run, the slider from Tambe, flatter and quicker, McCullum just about got his bat down in time and blocks it]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Brendon McCullum, no run, slower and just outside off, McCullum leans forward defensively]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Brendon McCullum, no run, flatter and just outside off, punched back uppishly by McCullum, dropped well in front of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tambe to Brendon McCullum, <b>SIX</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, the leg-break from Tambe, McCullum spots it early, lifts it with the spin and goes over cover, has enough to send it all the way over the ropes]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pravin Tambe, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, slower and on McCullum's pads, worked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to Brendon McCullum, no run, lovely flight from Sharma, slowed down the pace, invites McCullum to have a go at that and gets the ball to spin across the face of the bat. McCullum nearly overbalanced as he missed his swipe, but his back foot remained static inside the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[Appeal for a stumping. McCullum looks to be SAFE though. NOT OUT is the call]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to Brendon McCullum, no run, pushed through by Ankit, McCullum prods across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to du Plessis, 1 run, <b>tough chance for Smith at short cover</b>, this was tossed up and just outside off, du Plessis was looking to go inside out over cover, the ball stopped on him and he spoons it in the air. Smith's leap was a fraction too late, only gets his fingertips on that, that will go down as a chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, turn for Ankit Sharma, but the length was far too short. du Plessis waits on the back foot and cracks it in the gap between cover and point, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to du Plessis, no run, flatter and well outside off, du Plessis cracks it straight to the fielder at cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to du Plessis, 1 run, edged! On a good length and in that channel outside off, draws du Plessis into the forward push, the edge is found but the ball drops well in front of Watson at 1st slip. He makes a half stop and the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to du Plessis, <b>wide</b>, Morris slips one down leg-slip, du Plessis looks to flick and misses, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to du Plessis, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, defended with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Faf du Plessis, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Raina, <b>out</b> Caught by Faulkner!! Soft dismissal for Raina! This was pitched up and in that channel outside off, Raina was looking to go over mid-off, the weight wasn't fully forward, he ended up chipping it in the air, a much simpler chance for Faulkner. CHN are in some early trouble now. <b>Raina c Faulkner b C Morris 3(6)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[C Morris to Raina, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Raina, no run, back of a length and on the stumps, Raina goes back and tucks it in front of square leg, wants a single but is sent back by Brendon McCullum]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Raina, no run, short of a length and angling away from outside off, Raina goes for a wild hoick and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Raina, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Raina prods forward and defends it with soft hands]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[A slip and a FSL in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Morris [1.0-0-5-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to Raina, 1 run, Raina runs down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and drills it to the left of long-on. Morris is quick onto the ball and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to Raina, 2 runs, full and on Raina's pads, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to Dwayne Smith, <b>out</b> Caught by Faulkner!! Another failure for Smith! This was nicely bowled by Ankit, floated this one outside off and got it to dip onto the batsman, Smith was lunging forward on the on-drive, the ball goes off the inner half of the bat. Faulkner slides forward at mid-on and completes the catch. A distraught Smith walks back to the hut. <b>Dwayne Smith c Faulkner b Ankit Sharma 6(10) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ankit Sharma to Dwayne Smith, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, Ankit drifts one onto McCullum's pads, nudged in front of square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to Brendon McCullum, no run, pushed through by Sharma, McCullum went hard on the defensive push, hits it in the air and just wide of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ankit Sharma to Brendon McCullum, no run, tossed up and on the off-stump line, driven back towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ankit Sharma, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Dwayne Smith, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Smith was late on the pull, gets an inside edge onto the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, McCullum works it to the right of Rahane at cover-point, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Brendon McCullum, no run, short of a length and angling into McCullum, cramps him for room, pushed towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Smith drives and gets a thick edge towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Dwayne Smith, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Smith prods forward and defends it back at the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Watson to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, loosener from Watson, width on offer as well, Smith leans into the shot and caresses it past cover for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shane Watson, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, McCullum is up and running first ball! Charges down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and lofts it over mid-on for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, width on offer from Morris, Smith goes hard on the cut, the ball flies towards third man, goes to Tambe on the bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Dwayne Smith, no run, Morris shortens his length outside off, Smith gets behind the line and nudges it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Dwayne Smith, no run, the bouncer from Morris, good pace and carry on that, Smith ducks under it and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Dwayne Smith, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Smith stays behind the line and punches it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;C Morris to Dwayne Smith, no run, short of a length and angling into Smith, he looks to pull and is hit on his body, was late on the shot there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Smith and Brendon McCullum are at the crease. Dwayne Smith is on strike. C Morris will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place as Morris steams in..]]></line><line><![CDATA[Smith is back with captaincy. Not a surprise considering that the Rajasthan managed only 6 points from 8 games after the captaincy was given to Watson. Will it change RAJ's fortunes? One thing for sure, we will have our first qualification spot sealed at the end of this match.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shane Watson is playing but Steve Smith is captaining the side.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai</b> (Playing XI): Dwayne Smith, Brendon McCullum, Suresh Raina, Faf du Plessis, MS Dhoni(w/c), Pawan Negi, Dwayne Bravo, Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Mohit Sharma, Ashish Nehra]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajasthan</b> (Playing XI): Ajinkya Rahane, Shane Watson, Sanju Samson(w), Steven Smith(c), Karun Nair, Deepak Hooda, James Faulkner, Rajat Bhatia, Chris Morris, Ankit Sharma, Pravin Tambe]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Smith</b>: "I would have batted as well. Hopefully we can restrict Chennai and chase it down later on. Ankit Sharma and Rajat Bhatia in, Stuart Binny and Dhawal Kulkarni are out."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhoni</b>: "We are looking to bat first. It is the same wicket that was used in the previous game. There are chances that it may slow down later on. It's important to build partnerships and the fielding is crucial as well. A wicket at the right time can make a big impact. We are playing the same team."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's going to be a battle of spin folks! We will bring you the toss and teams in a little while. Stay tuned!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather Update:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's been quite unChennai weather in a place which is often considered as one of the hottest cities in India. A few passing showers are predicted with temperature hovering around a high of 30 degree celsius during the course of game.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-head:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[In 16 previous occasions, CHN have won 10 games while RAJ sealed the remaining six. One of those six victories against CHN came in this season and RAJ would be keen to repeat the same.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Team news:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[CHN included Ashwin in place of Ishwar Pandey in their last game. If the latter has to feature in this game, one among Pawan Negi and Mohit Sharma might have to sit out. There won't be too many changes for sure.]]></line><line><![CDATA[RAJ replaced Tim Southee and Rajat Bhatia with Chris Morris and Pravin Tambe. They might bring in an extra spinner at the cost of a batsman or Dhawal Kulkarni.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhoni has a habit of throwing players into tough situations and he expects them to deliver their best. A prime example of it was offering the ball to Joginder Sharma in the final of the 2007 T20 World Cup. There is a lot about Dhoni's captaincy and no wonder why he has been the most successful skipper in this format of the game. Despite leaking 25 runs in the penultimate over of the last game, Pawan Negi was well backed by his skipper. MSD said, "It is a good exposure for the youngster and he will learn with time." CHN will largely rely on their spinners and the top 3 batters to play a key role in this game. Mohit Sharma and Ashish Nehra have been scratchy in the last few games, which has been their only major concern.]]></line><line><![CDATA[RAJ have won only one game in their previous seven encounters and are desperate to register a win from this game. They will be aware of last year's misfortunes where they failed to make it to the playoffs despite having a great start to the tournament. Skipper Shane Watson, holds a very good batting record against CHN, having scored 452 runs in 11 innings. Ajinkya Rahane made vital contributions and has been the lynchpin to team's success. One among Sanju Samson, Stuart Binny and Steven Smith will have to play a big role to overcome their opponents. Pravin Tambe, who bowled with some conviction in the initial few games hasn't been effective. Spin bowling will be their only weak link.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>19:00 Local Time, 13:30 GMT, 19:00 IST:</b> It's going to be a clash of heavyweights and the winner of this game will seal the top spot in the points table. Both teams are tied on 14 points and are coming into this match after facing a last over defeat in their previous games. This is the penultimate game for RAJ while CHN have two more games in hand. Who will clinch the much needed win? Will it be the Men in blue or will it be the Men in yellow? All that will be answered by the end of today as Rajasthan take on Chennai at the M A Chidambaram stadium in Chennai.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview</b><br/><br/>The 2015 edition of the IPL is proving to be an open tournament. After 43 league games, no team has sealed their spot in the play-offs. Four places, six teams in the fray. Chennai and Rajasthan are currently in the first and second position of the table but they are in a vulnerable position.<br/><br/>Both teams are tied on 14 points, with Rajasthan having played one game more. However, the gap between them and teams like Kolkata, Mumbai, Hyderabad and Bangalore has reduced. Both will be aware that another slip-up and alarm bells might just start to ring.<br/><br/>Both Chennai and Rajasthan are coming off a loss in their previous game. The Chepauk fortress was breached by Mumbai while Rajasthan lost a high-scoring match against Hyderabad. Heading into the contest, both teams are aware of the benefits of victory and the consequences of defeat.<br/><br/>Venue: MA Chidambaram Stadium, Chennai<br/><br/>Date: May 10, 2015<br/><br/>Time: 20:00 IST<br/><br/>Weather: Clear skies with temperature of 28 degrees<br/><br/><b>Team news</b>:<br/><br/><b>Chennai</b><br/><br/>The team would have suffered a jolt after losing their first match at home in this edition. However, they would be pleased by the performance of R Ashwin, who came back after suffering a finger injury and finished with figures of 4-0-17-2. Pawan Negi, who leaked 25 runs in the penultimate over against Mumbai, could sit out and Ishwar Pandey could feature in this clash.<br/><br/>Probable XI<br/><br/>1 Dwayne Smith, 2 Brendon McCullum, 3 Suresh Raina, 4 Faf du Plessis, 5 MS Dhoni (c and wk), 6 Dwayne Bravo, 7 Ravindra Jadeja, 8 R Ashwin, 9 Pawan Negi/Ishwar Pandey, 10 Mohit Sharma, 11 Ashish Nehra<br/><br/><b>Rajasthan</b><br/><br/>Like previous editions, Rajasthan are suffering a big dip towards the business end of the tournament after a bright start. In the game against Hyderabad, the team struggled with their bowling and leaked 201 runs. With the pitch in Chennai probably assisting spin, they might pack their bowling line-up with spin.<br/><br/>Probable XI<br/><br/>1 Ajinkya Rahane, 2 Shane Watson (c), 3 Steven Smith, 4 Karun Nair, 5 Sanju Samson (wk), 6 James Faulkner, 7 Stuart Binny, 8 Deepak Hooda, 9 Chris Morris/Tim Southee, 10 Dhawal Kulkarni/Ankit Sharma, 11 Pravin Tambe<br/><br/><b>Stats</b><br/><br/>Chennai hold a 4-1 advantage over Rajasthan in Chepauk<br/>Ajinkya Rahane needs 55 runs to become the second Rajasthan batsman to go past 2000 IPL runs after Shane Watson.<br/>Watson has scored 452 runs in 11 games at an average of 45.20 against Chennai, the most by a Rajasthan batsman while Suresh Raina has scored 468 runs in 16 games against them, which is the most by any batsman.<br/><br/><b>Quotes</b><br/><br/>"We gave too many loose balls to some very good players and they hurt us early on. Our fielding is a little bit of concern as well." - Steven Smith acknowledges that Rajasthan have problems in several departments<br/><br/>"It was a tactical error in the end. The fast bowlers need to step up. Yes, we have the purple cap, but we still need to improve." - Chennai skipper MS Dhoni admits that the team has to improve their bowling.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rajasthan</b> (From): Shane Watson(c), Ajinkya Rahane, Steven Smith, Karun Nair, Sanju Samson(w), Deepak Hooda, Stuart Binny, James Faulkner, Chris Morris, Dhawal Kulkarni, Pravin Tambe, Rajat Bhatia, Tim Southee, Abhishek Nayar, Ben Cutting, Dishant Yagnik, Vikramjeet Malik, Ankit Sharma, Rahul Tewatia, Dinesh Salunkhe, Rusty Theron, Pardeep Sahu, Brainder Sran, Sagar Trivedi]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai</b> (From): Dwayne Smith, Brendon McCullum, Suresh Raina, Faf du Plessis, MS Dhoni(c/w), Ravindra Jadeja, Pawan Negi, Dwayne Bravo, Ravichandran Ashwin, Ashish Nehra, Mohit Sharma, Baba Aparajith, Ishwar Pandey, Matt Henry, Mithun Manhas, Samuel Badree, Ronit More, Michael Hussey, Rahul Sharma, Kyle Abbott, Ankush Bains, Irfan Pathan, Pratyush Singh, Andrew Tye, Eklavya Dwivedi]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>157</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>5</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Chennai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Smith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Ankit Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7810</bowlerId>
						<fielder>James Faulkner</fielder>
						<fielderId>7789</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Brendon McCullum</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>81</runs>
					<balls>61</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>4</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>C Morris</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8333</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ankit Sharma</fielder>
						<fielderId>7810</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Raina</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>C Morris</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8333</bowlerId>
						<fielder>James Faulkner</fielder>
						<fielderId>7789</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7825</playerid>
					<name>Faf du Plessis</name>
					<batsman-name>du Plessis</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>du Plessis</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>29</runs>
					<balls>25</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Shane Watson</fielder>
						<fielderId>158</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8281</playerid>
					<name>Pawan Negi</name>
					<batsman-name>Negi</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Negi</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>C Morris</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8333</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Steven Smith</fielder>
						<fielderId>2250</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhoni</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>13</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>242</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
					<batsman-name>DJ Bravo</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>15</runs>
					<balls>8</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<batsman-name>R Jadeja</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<batsman-name>Ashwin</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ashwin</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Mohit Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mohit Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>269</playerid>
					<name>Ashish Nehra</name>
					<batsman-name>Nehra</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nehra</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>255</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>12</runs>
				<overs>2.4</overs>
				<batsman>Dwayne Smith</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>413</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>15</runs>
				<overs>3.4</overs>
				<batsman>Suresh Raina</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7825</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>116</runs>
				<overs>16.2</overs>
				<batsman>Faf du Plessis</batsman>
				<batsman-name>du Plessis</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>201</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>129</runs>
				<overs>17.2</overs>
				<batsman>Brendon McCullum</batsman>
				<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8281</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>129</runs>
				<overs>17.3</overs>
				<batsman>Pawan Negi</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Negi</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>7</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>8</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Rajasthan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8333</playerid>
					<name>Chris Morris</name>
					<bowler-name>C Morris</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>C Morris</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>19</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>158</playerid>
					<name>Shane Watson</name>
					<bowler-name>Watson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Watson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>19</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7810</playerid>
					<name>Ankit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Ankit Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ankit Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>31</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>5</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9237</playerid>
					<name>Pravin Tambe</name>
					<bowler-name>Tambe</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Tambe</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>24</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7789</playerid>
					<name>James Faulkner</name>
					<bowler-name>Faulkner</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Faulkner</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>40</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1468</playerid>
					<name>Rajat Bhatia</name>
					<bowler-name>R Bhatia</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>R Bhatia</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>23</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1447</playerid>
					<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
					<bowler-name>A Rahane</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rahane</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8271</playerid>
					<name>Sanju Samson</name>
					<bowler-name>Samson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Samson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2250</playerid>
					<name>Steven Smith</name>
					<bowler-name>S Smith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Smith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8257</playerid>
					<name>Karun Nair</name>
					<bowler-name>Nair</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nair</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9427</playerid>
					<name>Deepak Hooda</name>
					<bowler-name>Deepak Hooda</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Deepak Hooda</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>145</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>9</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Rajasthan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1447</playerid>
					<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
					<batsman-name>A Rahane</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rahane</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>23</runs>
					<balls>17</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mohit Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8181</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dwayne Bravo</fielder>
						<fielderId>242</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>158</playerid>
					<name>Shane Watson</name>
					<batsman-name>Watson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Watson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>28</runs>
					<balls>30</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>R Jadeja</bowler>
					<bowlerId>587</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dwayne Bravo</fielder>
						<fielderId>242</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2250</playerid>
					<name>Steven Smith</name>
					<batsman-name>S Smith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Smith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>R Jadeja</bowler>
					<bowlerId>587</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8257</playerid>
					<name>Karun Nair</name>
					<batsman-name>Nair</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nair</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>10</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>R Jadeja</bowler>
					<bowlerId>587</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ravichandran Ashwin</fielder>
						<fielderId>1593</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9427</playerid>
					<name>Deepak Hooda</name>
					<batsman-name>Deepak Hooda</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Deepak Hooda</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>15</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>R Jadeja</bowler>
					<bowlerId>587</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Suresh Raina</fielder>
						<fielderId>413</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8271</playerid>
					<name>Sanju Samson</name>
					<batsman-name>Samson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Samson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>26</runs>
					<balls>17</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>DJ Bravo</bowler>
					<bowlerId>242</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dwayne Smith</fielder>
						<fielderId>255</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7789</playerid>
					<name>James Faulkner</name>
					<batsman-name>Faulkner</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Faulkner</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>16</runs>
					<balls>13</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mohit Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8181</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dwayne Bravo</fielder>
						<fielderId>242</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8333</playerid>
					<name>Chris Morris</name>
					<batsman-name>C Morris</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>C Morris</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>16</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1468</playerid>
					<name>Rajat Bhatia</name>
					<batsman-name>R Bhatia</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>R Bhatia</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mohit Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8181</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Faf du Plessis</fielder>
						<fielderId>7825</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7810</playerid>
					<name>Ankit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Ankit Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ankit Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>DJ Bravo</bowler>
					<bowlerId>242</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ashish Nehra</fielder>
						<fielderId>269</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9237</playerid>
					<name>Pravin Tambe</name>
					<batsman-name>Tambe</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Tambe</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1447</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>37</runs>
				<overs>5.3</overs>
				<batsman>Ajinkya Rahane</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Rahane</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>2250</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>48</runs>
				<overs>7.4</overs>
				<batsman>Steven Smith</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Smith</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>158</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>63</runs>
				<overs>9.6</overs>
				<batsman>Shane Watson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Watson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8257</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>75</runs>
				<overs>11.5</overs>
				<batsman>Karun Nair</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Nair</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9427</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>90</runs>
				<overs>14.1</overs>
				<batsman>Deepak Hooda</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Deepak Hooda</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8271</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>123</runs>
				<overs>17.4</overs>
				<batsman>Sanju Samson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Samson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7789</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>130</runs>
				<overs>18.3</overs>
				<batsman>James Faulkner</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Faulkner</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1468</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>130</runs>
				<overs>18.4</overs>
				<batsman>Rajat Bhatia</batsman>
				<batsman-name>R Bhatia</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7810</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>143</runs>
				<overs>19.4</overs>
				<batsman>Ankit Sharma</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Ankit Sharma</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>2</wides>
			<noballs>2</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>6</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Chennai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>269</playerid>
					<name>Ashish Nehra</name>
					<bowler-name>Nehra</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nehra</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>29</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Mohit Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mohit Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8281</playerid>
					<name>Pawan Negi</name>
					<bowler-name>Negi</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Negi</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<bowler-name>R Jadeja</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>11</runsoff>
					<wickets>4</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>242</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
					<bowler-name>DJ Bravo</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>43</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<bowler-name>Dwayne Smith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Smith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<bowler-name>B McCullum</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Brendon McCullum</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<bowler-name>Raina</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Raina</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7825</playerid>
					<name>Faf du Plessis</name>
					<bowler-name>du Plessis</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>du Plessis</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhoni</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhoni</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<bowler-name>Ashwin</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ashwin</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



