<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14642" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>49th Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Delhi</home>
		<away>Chennai</away>
		<teamsabbr>DEL vs CHN</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>DEL</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>CHN</awayabbr>
		<homeId>61</homeId>
		<awayId>58</awayId>
		<venue>Shaheed Veer Narayan Singh International Stadium, Raipur</venue>
		<startdate>12 05 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>12 05 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Chennai</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Delhi won by 6 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Delhi</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>6</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Richard Illingworth</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Vineet Kulkarni</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>S Ravi</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Ranjan Madugalle</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>14:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150512172826</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>DEL</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>CHN</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>120</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>4</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>16.4</batteamovers>
		<status>Delhi won by 6 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>1851</playerid>
			<name>Kedar Jadhav*</name>
			<batsman-name>K Jadhav</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>K Jadhav</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>1</runs>
			<balls-faced>1</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>9428</playerid>
			<name>Shreyas Iyer</name>
			<batsman-name>S Iyer</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Shreyas Iyer</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>70</runs>
			<balls-faced>49</balls-faced>
			<fours>10</fours>
			<sixes>1</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>587</playerid>
			<name>Ravindra Jadeja*</name>
			<bowler-name>R Jadeja</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>2.4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>16</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>8281</playerid>
			<name>Pawan Negi</name>
			<bowler-name>Negi</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Negi</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>3</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>28</runs>
			<wickets>2</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>120</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>484</playerid>
<name>Albie Morkel</name>
<player-runs>8</player-runs>
<player-balls>8</player-balls>
<runs>114</runs>
<wicket-nbr>4</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>8281</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Negi</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>0</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>0</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[1 W . 1 1 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. 1 1 . . . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 4 2 1 6 W <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 4 . 1 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/DEL_CHN_MAY12/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[On behalf of <b>Krishna, Raju, Bharath</b> and my co-commentators, <b>Akshay Maanay, Ramakrishnan</b> and <b>Pradeep</b>, this is <b>Sidhant Maheshwari</b>, signing off. Take care guys!]]></line><line><![CDATA[That brings us to the end of our coverage of this game. Tomorrow, <b>Punjab</b> will lock horns with <b>Bangalore</b>. Don't forget to join us then for all the action.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Let's take a look at some of the <b>tweets</b> from this game:]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohandas Menon:</b> After 49 #IPL games this season we still do not know who will be in the final four...]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Freddie Wilde:</b> Nice win from #DEL. Iyer represents a brighter future for the team. Strangely tepid from #CHN.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sarang Bhalerao:</b> #DEL wallop table-toppers #CHN. A clinical win for Delhi who got their combination right albeit a little late.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Saurabh Malhotra:</b> Sehwag, Gambhir, Dhawan and now Dhoni. @ImZaheer ensuring he's one up on all his former team mates. Next up, Kohli.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Cricketwallah:</b> Young Shreyas Iyer cutting CHN down to size with bravado, class...and some luck.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Zaheer:</b> 'The experience always helps. I always try to use it to my advantage. The wicket was on the slower side and I used my variations accordingly. It's good to be involved in the game. If I spot something about the particular batsman, I always try to help the others out with what to bowl and what field placements to set. It will be good to finish on a winning note. We've had some close games that didn't go in our favour, but we need to keep trying harder and keep pushing forward for more wins.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Zaheer Khan</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his brilliant spell of <b>4-1-9-2</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Duminy:</b> 'It feels good. The five games we have won, we have played very good cricket and we have been very convincing. With one game to go, we would look to perform better and hopefully, come back well next year. That was the best powerplay bowling performance that I have seen. Being a spinner and bowling like that is great, all credit to Shahbaz Nadeem for that spell. We contained them really well and that powerplay overs set us up. He (Shreyas Iyer) is an exciting prospect for India and I have told him on his face that in 2-3 years, he will be playing for India.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhoni:</b> 'We got off to a horrible start. It was a difficult wicket, but in the first six, we only got under 20 runs and it is always very difficult from there. We started off with two wickets, but that dropped catch cost us. The boundaries they got because of the width we gave dented our hopes. It was not easy to play big shots but they did well. We never had enough runs on the board. We didn't have a practice session here but they were fortunate to play a game here before and they knew what length to bowl, we didn't hit the right length today. We have done well as a team, we need to move on and we need to qualify for the playoffs as the first or second team. We'll have to see how the wicket is and what's needed. We will see if we can give Hussey a chance before the playoffs. We will look to finish first or second on the table, so that we can get an extra opportunity.']]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, Zaheer Khan bowled with unremitting control and was rewarded with two wickets. In fact, he went for just over two runs per over. Shahbaz Nadeem too bowled an economical spell. MS Dhoni and Faf du Plessis played useful hands, but couldn't convert it into a big score.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shreyas Iyer played with composure to compose a fifty as DEL registered a consolation win. He showed his class while facing up to both Mohit Sharma and Ishwar Pandey and essayed a flurry of fine shots. Yuvraj Singh also made his presence felt with eye-catching strokes. The way he came down the track with twinkle-toed footwork to check in a fabulous shot off Ashwin for a six, encapsulated his precise metre of timing. Ishwar picked up a couple of wickets for CHN.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, <b>DEL win by 6 wickets</b>, <b>all thanks to a brilliant knock by Iyer</b>. It was tossed up on the stumps, Iyer eases it down to long-on for a single. This is the <b>first time the Delhi have beaten the Chennai in 8 games</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shreyas Iyer, no run, <b>stumping chance missed!</b> It was tossed up outside off and turns away as Iyer looks to push it down the ground, the ball goes past the outside edge and Iyer falls over. Dhoni though didn't collect it properly and Iyer stays]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, flighted delivery outside off, Iyer hacks it wide of long-on and gets four for that]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to K Jadhav, 1 run, floated up on off, Jadhav leans forward and works it away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kedar Jadhav, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja [2.0-0-10-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic timeout</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to A Morkel, <b>out</b> Caught by I Pandey!! Morkel bites the dust as he went for another maximum to finish off the match. It was a flighted delivery outside off, Morkel once again gives the charge, but this time he doesn't get to the pitch of the ball, he goes for another loft but doesn't quite get under it. Long-off runs to his left and takes a simple catch. <b>A Morkel c I Pandey b Negi 8(8) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Negi to A Morkel, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to A Morkel, <b>SIX</b>, that's a great shot from Morkel. He comes down the track and reaches to the pitch of the ball outside off, lofts it in style and gets it way over the long-on fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Iyer hangs back and turns it past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Shreyas Iyer, 2 runs, works this one behind square on the on-side, good running between these two ensures that they take the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, in the air but safe! It was another flatter one from Negi, Iyer pulls it past a leaping mid-wicket and the ball beats the fielder from long-on, who was running to his right. Back-to-back boundaries for Iyer]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, shortish delivery on the stumps, Iyer stays back and pulls it to the right of the diving mid-wicket fielder, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to A Morkel, no run, slider on off, Morkel looks to cut but ends up chopping it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to A Morkel, no run, a shout for lbw, but the umpire says not out. The impact was pad first but probably it was going down leg, This was pushed through on middle and leg, Morkel looks to defend with his bat close to the pad, the ball strikes the pad first and then the bat. The umpire though was not amused]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to A Morkel, no run, bowls this one flatter and quicker outside off, Morkel chops it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, turns this one through square leg from inside the crease, mid-wicket gives chase and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to A Morkel, 1 run, slows this one and gets it to turn away, Morkel hangs back and punches it towards the cover-point region for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to A Morkel, no run, pushed through on middle and leg, Morkel defends it to the right of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Shreyas Iyer, no run, Negi bowls this one slightly quicker as Iyer backs away, he cuts but picks out backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to A Morkel, 1 run, turning in on middle stump line, Morkel works it behind square on the on-side off the inside half of the bat, gets off the mark with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, low full toss from Negi, Iyer helps it down to long-on and gets off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Shreyas Iyer, no run, this one bounces a little extra as Iyer tries to force it through the off-side, goes a little uppishly to the right of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Albie Morkel, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Yuvraj, <b>out</b> Caught by Mohit Sharma!! Yuvraj perishes trying to go big once again. It was not a wicket-taking delivery but CHN won't mind it one bit. It was turning in towards Yuvraj, who kneels down and goes for the slog sweep, doesn't get the connection off the middle of the bat and offers a simple catch to Mohit at deep mid-wicket. Is there a twist in the tale? DEL would be hoping otherwise. <b>Yuvraj c Mohit Sharma b Negi 32(28) [4s-4 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Negi to Yuvraj, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, flighted delivery just outside off, Iyer opens the face of the bat and drives it square of the wicket for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, drags his length back this time, Iyer rocks back and pulls it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shreyas Iyer, 2 runs, <b>4th IPL fifty for Iyer and all have come this season</b>, it was pushed through on middle and leg, Iyer tucks it away through square leg, good running ensures that the batsmen come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shreyas Iyer, no run, bowls this one slower and gets this one to turn back in on middle, Iyer punches it to left of cover, who quickly moves across and fires the throw at the striker's end. Iyer had to rush back in and does so in time]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Yuvraj, 1 run, darted on middle and leg, Yuvraj works it through square leg and the batsmen cross over]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Yuvraj, <b>SIX</b>, <b>hammered!</b> It was floated up on middle stump line, Yuvraj comes down the track and lofts it through the line, clears the long-on fence without any fuss. He's looking in superb touch today]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Yuvraj, no run, tossed up outside off, Yuvraj leans forward and drives hard, picks out short extra cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin [2.0-0-12-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Shreyas Iyer, no run, touch slower this time from Negi, Iyer defends it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Yuvraj, 1 run, opens the face of the bat and guides it square of the wicket, gets to the other end with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Yuvraj, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a good shot from Yuvi, this was bowled flatter and outside off, Yuvraj waits for it, opens the face of the bat late and cuts it to the left of backward point, the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, drifting on middle and leg, Iyer hangs back and flicks it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Yuvraj, 1 run, drags his length back this time, Yuvraj swivels and pulls it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, floated up around off, Iyer looks to drive it through the off-side, drags it to long-on off the inside half of the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Negi comes round the wicket. Just a slip in place for him]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pawan Negi, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, <b>50 of the partnership</b> comes up. It was turning in on off, Iyer works it away through mid-wicket after going across a touch, gets a single and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Yuvraj, 1 run, drifting on the pads this time, Yuvraj works it away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, opens the face of the bat and guides it towards short third man, the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, Iyer pre-meditates as he shuffles across to this delivery down the leg-side, laps it over the fielder at leg slip and collects four for that]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Shreyas Iyer, no run, flatter and on the stumps, Iyer punches it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Yuvraj, 1 run, drifting on middle, Yuvraj eases it to the left of the bowler and gets a single down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Raina comes round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Yuvraj, 1 run, quicker and around off, Yuvraj leans forward and punches to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Yuvraj, no run, pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Yuvraj, no run, turns it off the back foot to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[Raina comes in from short fine to leg slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Yuvraj, no run, glances the flatter delivery to short fine leg, finds the fielder there]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Yuvraj, <b>FOUR</b>, tossed up on middle, turns away towards leg-stump, Yuvraj takes a step out, kneels down and goes for the sweep, the ball takes the glove and runs away fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, flighted around off, Iyer eases it to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Apologies for the commentary not getting updated. There is some technical issue and we are working on it.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, slower and outside off, Iyer leans forward, opens the bat face and guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, not all that short, Iyer uses the depth of the crease, goes right back and cuts it behind square on the off-side, beats the fielder at short third as well as the man in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shreyas Iyer, 2 runs, <b>dropped!</b> Mohit has spilled a steepler. Floated up around off, Iyer comes down the track, doesn't get to the pitch of the ball, but still goes through with the shot, he gets a lot of elevation, Mohit runs to his left from deep mid-wicket, dives and grasses it. He had plenty of time to get there, but he was not quick enough]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Yuvraj, 1 run, kneels down and sweeps to long leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Yuvraj, no run, flighted around off, Yuvraj defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Yuvraj, no run, peach! Ashwin comes round the wicket, tosses it up on middle and turns away, Yuvraj lunges forward to defend, the spin beats the outside edge. Not much Yuvi could there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin [1.0-0-4-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shreyas Iyer, no run, slower and on off, Iyer taps it softly to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Yuvraj, 1 run, pushed through on middle, Yuvraj punches to the left of the bowler, Jaddu moves across and makes a half stop, not enough to stop the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Yuvraj, no run, flatter and on off, Yuvraj turns it to mid-wicket, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, fired quicker and on the stumps, Iyer nudges it behind square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Yuvraj, 1 run, nurdled away with the turn past the leg slip fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[A leg slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, goes straight on, Iyer presses forward to defend, the ball takes the inside edge and rolls to backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Yuvraj, <b>FOUR</b>, an expensive over from Ishwar to finish his spell. The slower ball outside off, Yuvraj spotted it early and lofted it through the line, one bounce and into the fence at long-off. Ishwar ends with figures: <b>4-1-27-2</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, back of a length just outside off, Iyer steers it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, follows it up with another super shot. Too straight, on middle and leg, Iyer leans forward and flicks it elegantly through mid-wicket, the timing and placement was precise from Iyer]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Shreyas Iyer, <b>SIX</b>, fantastic shot! Ishwar shakes his head as he walks back to the mark. Fullish and outside off, Iyer stays leg-side of the ball and lofts it over extra cover, that came right off the meat as it cleared the fence with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Yuvraj, 1 run, good length ball around off, Yuvraj goes for the drive without any feet movement, the ball squirts off the inside edge to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Yuvraj, <b>FOUR</b>, Yuvraj pre-meditates, makes a bit of room for himself, Ishwar bowls a back of a length delivery on off, Yuvraj has the room to free his arms, cracks it in front of square right between cover and point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shreyas Iyer, no run, flatter on middle and leg, Iyer nudges it straight to Bravo at backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shreyas Iyer, no run, pushed through close to off, Iyer drives it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shreyas Iyer, no run, nicely tossed up delivery, breaks back in, Iyer presses forward and gets an inside edge onto the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shreyas Iyer, no run, works it with the turn to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shreyas Iyer, no run, slower and around off, Iyer defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, quicker delivery on the pads, Iyer whips it past the diving leg slip fielder, it bounced in front of Raina and raced away to the fence. Bravo gave chase in vain]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Yuvraj, no run, <b>wicket-maiden</b> for Ishwar. Short of a length on off, bit of extra bounce as well, Yuvraj goes on his feet, plays it with soft hands and drops it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Yuvraj, no run, nips back in from a length, Yuvraj moves across, brings his bat down in time to jam it to the on-side. So easily would have dragged it back like JPD]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Yuvraj, no run, back of a length outside off, Yuvraj shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Yuvraj, no run, good length ball outside off, Yuvraj comes forward, lifts his bat and lets it go. Dhoni doesn't collect it cleanly, but Smith at first slip holds onto the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Yuvraj, no run, late inswing on this short of a length delivery almost foxes Yuvi, who just about manages to tuck it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuvraj Singh, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Duminy, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Chopped on! This is a huge wicket for CHN. Ishwar has picked up his second of the night. It was on a length around off, Duminy went for the steer down to third man, drags it back onto the stumps. Just the start CHN would have hoped for. <b>Duminy b I Pandey 6(7) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[I Pandey to Duminy, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shreyas Iyer, no run, full and attacking the stumps, Iyer drives and picks out mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Duminy, 1 run, short of length close to off, steered away to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, good length ball on off, Iyer nudges it to the right of mid-on, Ashwin runs across and keeps it to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Duminy, 1 run, slanted across the off-stump, Duminy uses the angle and runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Duminy, <b>FOUR</b>, super shot! Duminy gets off the mark in style. Back of a length outside off, Duminy stands tall and creams it through cover-point. He didn't try to overhit the ball, just relied on timing]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, on a length just outside off, Iyer glides it down to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Duminy, no run, keeps it tight around off, Duminy gets right behind the line and defends back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Duminy, no run, loose from JPD, back of a length outside off, Duminy has a waft at that and the ball zips past the outside edge. He went at it half-heartedly without any footwork]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Duminy, no run, short of length just outside off, Duminy covers the line and shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jean-Paul Duminy, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Kock, <b>out</b> Caught by Ashwin!! Ishwar draws first blood for CHN. It was not a wicket taking delivery, but he will take that. Short and on the stumps, de Kock shuffles across and pulls, finds the only man in the deep on the leg-side, Ashwin at long leg, didn't have to move an inch to take it. <b>de Kock c Ashwin b I Pandey 3(7)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[I Pandey to de Kock, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, short and wide outside off, Iyer throws his bat at that, the thickish outside edge flies on the bounce to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Kock, 1 run, angled across the left-hander, de Kock moves a long way across his stumps and steers it to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! Iyer has got going. Pitched up outside off, Iyer takes a step forward and drives it past the diving cover fielder, the timing takes care of the rest]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shreyas Iyer, no run, better from Mohit, on a length in the channel around off, Iyer goes hard on the drive, plays away from the body and is beaten all ends up]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shreyas Iyer, no run, back of a length on off, Iyer knocks it in front of cover-point, wants the run but QdK sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, Iyer is very strong there. Mohit offers width outside off, Iyer comes half-forward and slashes it behind square on the off-side, the timing was so good that it beat the chase from Ishwar]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mohit too has only one slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to de Kock, 1 run, good length ball on the stumps, de Kock tucks it to the left of mid-on, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to de Kock, no run, short of length on off, de Kock knocks it down near his feet]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Shreyas Iyer, no run, bouncer on off, Iyer sways away from the line of the delivery]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, cracking shot! Ishwar provides width outside off, the length is short as well, Iyer gets on top of the bounce and cuts it behind point, the ball races away and Ashwin dives after it reaches the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Shreyas Iyer, no run, short of length on off, Iyer gets behind the line and turns it towards mid-wicket, Negi is quickly onto the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Kock, 1 run, not all that short, the line is just outside off, de Kock shuffles across and goes for the pull, drags it off the inside half to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Kock, no run, back of a length on off, de Kock hangs back and knocks it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[Just one slip in place...]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Kock, no run, fuller and around off, de Kock drives it gently to mid-on, no real timing on that as the ball rolls slowly to the fielder]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>de Kock and Shreyas Iyer are at the crease. de Kock is on strike. I Pandey will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. The total looks below par, but we know that CHN have a habit of defending low totals. They also hold the record of defending the lowest total in IPL history - 116 in 2009. So, can they come up trumps once again? Or will DEL break their 7-match winless streak against CHN? We'll find out soon as Ishwar steams in..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Zaheer</b>: "The wicket is on the slower side. I tried my variations today and tried different field placements as well. It was one of those day where it worked for me. Even if we are out of the tournament, the plan was to put out our best show. The pitch in the last game was better, the ball was stopping even more today. I am just happy to be out there on the field, just enjoying my time out there. Running between the wickets is key here as it is a big outfield."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Faf du Plessis showed measured judgment and rotated the strike  as he looked to steady the innings. MS Dhoni too landed some crunching blows. The track is offering the pacers a bit of movement off the seam and is also stopping on the batsman. CHN are known for defending small targets as well. But DEL should back themselves to chase down the target.   ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Zaheer Khan and Shahbaz Nadeem bowled exemplary spells with the new ball to restrict CHN to a below par total. The DEL think-tank surprised the opposition ranks by opening the bowling with the slow left-arm orthodox, Nadeem. Nadeem, on his part, tied down both Brendon McCullum and Dwayne Smith and ended up with creditable figures. At the other end of the spectrum, Zaheer tempted and teased McCullum to plot his downfall. Albie Morkel also snared a couple of wickets.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Zaheer Khan is a happy man. He has been mentoring the DEL bowlers and he congratulates everyone for their good show.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Negi, 1 run, very full and outside off stump, Negi tries to squeeze it, gets an outside edge and it rolls to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, slower short ball, Jadeja pulled straight to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Ravindra Jadeja, no run, oh that almost knocked him over. Good length delivery angling into the left-hander, Jadeja looks to defend, is completely taken by surprise as it zips through and goes over the leg stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Negi, 1 run, short and outside off stump, Negi looks to slap hard, can't time it well and it goes to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, low full toss outside off stump, Jadeja squeezes it out through cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Negi, 1 run, round the wicket, short of length delivery on the leg stump, Negi backs away and dabs it to backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[What a spell from Zaheer. He ends 4-1-9-2, with 19 dot balls. This is the most economical spell for Zak in IPL history.]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Negi, leg byes, 1 run, low full toss down the leg-side, Negi misses the flick, the ball rolls into the on-side off the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Negi, no run, bumper on the off stump, Negi goes for the pull but fails to make contact]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Negi, no run, Negi steps out, Zaheer bowls a widish yorker, Negi tries to squeeze it out but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Negi, 2 runs, knee-high full toss, Negi mistimes the ball and it rolls towards mid-on, before the fielder in the deep got to the ball, Jadeja scampered back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, slower delivery outside off stump, Jadeja dabs it to backward point and gets off tha mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Dhoni, <b>out</b> Caught by S Nadeem!! In the airrrrrr and Nadeem takes a good and very important catch. This could make a difference of 10-15 runs to the final total for CHN. Well disguised slower ball, looked like the off-cutter, Dhoni steps out and goes early into the loft, it goes high up in the air, deep extra-cover runs in and takes a good catch. <b>Zaheer is on a hat-trick</b>. <b>Dhoni c S Nadeem b Zaheer 27(24) [4s-3 6s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Zaheer to Dhoni, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Zaheer Khan [3.0-1-6-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Negi, no run, short of length delivery on the stumps, Negi defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Dhoni, 1 run, slower delivery from Sandhu, Dhoni mistimes it to long-on after coming down the track]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Dhoni, <b>FOUR</b>, too short and Dhoni is a good player of the pull/hook shot. Bumper on the leg stump, Dhoni swivels and pulls it hard over backward square leg for a one-bounce four]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pawan Negi, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Dwayne Bravo, <b>out</b> Caught by Duminy!! That's a dolly for Duminy, who takes his third catch of the night. Short of a length delivery just outside off stump, it hurries onto Bravo, who was looking to pull, the ball hits him high on the bat and balloons to mid-off, who didn't have to move a muscle. <b>Dwayne Bravo c Duminy b Gurinder Sandhu 8(8) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Gurinder Sandhu to Dwayne Bravo, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Dwayne Bravo, no run, that was a wild slog from Bravo, had he connected that, it would have gone way back into the stands. Slower delivery outside off stump, Bravo only connects with thin air]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Dwayne Bravo, <b>SIX</b>, it's a friendly full toss, Bravo swings hard, doesn't get the timing right, the ball goes off the inside half of the bat, the bat turns on impact with the ball but it has enough legs to clear the fielder at long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Gurinder Sandhu [2.0-0-17-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Long-on and deep square leg in place. Mid-wicket is inside the ring]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>13</b> runs off that over, the best over for CHN so far today.]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to Dhoni, 2 runs, this time down the track to nudge this into the vacant mid-wicket region, Bravo races back for the second and makes his ground before the throw arrived at his end]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to Dhoni, <b>FOUR</b>, again gives the intention that he wants to come down the track but stays in the crease, Yuvraj fires it flat and outside off stump, Dhoni uses the pace on the ball and cuts it late to the right of short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to Dhoni, no run, Dhoni looks to advance again but Yuvraj fires it wide outside off stump, Dhoni lets it go but it was well inside the line]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to Dhoni, <b>SIX</b>, good hit from MS Dhoni! Flighted delivery on the stumps, Dhoni steps out, gets closer to the pitch of the ball and muscles it back over the bowler's head and hits it over the sightscreen]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to Dwayne Bravo, leg byes, 1 run, down the leg-side, Bravo misses the flick, the ball rolls off the pad towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to Dwayne Bravo, no run, Bravo tries to use the pace on the ball and guide it fine, but the slider goes past the outside edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Dwayne Bravo, 1 run, Bravo goes for the off-drive, hit straight to mid-off, should have been a dot ball, but Zak fumbles]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Dwayne Bravo, no run, driven off the back foot but straight to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Dhoni, 1 run, Dhoni races down the track and has a big swing at that, mistimes the short of length delivery completely and it lands safely back over the bowler's head]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Dwayne Bravo, 1 run, hops across the sticks and punches the short of length delivery past the fielder at extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to du Plessis, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Dragged on! Faf doesn't want to leave, sits down on his knees. Nothing but a short of length delivery just outside off stump, du Plessis looks to guide it towards third man, the ball keeps a bit low and foxes him, takes the inside edge and crashes into the stumps. <b>du Plessis b A Morkel 29(23) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A Morkel to du Plessis, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to du Plessis, no run, that was in the slot, but Faf misses the ball. 129kph good length delivery just outside off stump, du Plessis opens up and slogs, the ball sneaks past the under edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Albie Morkel [2.0-0-18-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to du Plessis, 1 run, tossed up outside off stump, du Plessis lofts the drive inside-out, but there is a man at deep extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball! Short and down the leg-side, it was pushed through quicker as well, du Plessis stays on the back foot and helps it away fine to the left of short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to du Plessis, no run, punched uppishly to extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to Dhoni, leg byes, 1 run, down the leg-side, Dhoni misses the glance, the ball rolls to short fine off the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to Dhoni, no run, Dhoni looks to advance but Yuvraj fires it flat, bit of extra bounce, hits Dhoni high on the bat and then rolls back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to du Plessis, 1 run, shortish and cramping du Plessis for room, the batsman flicks it through mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to du Plessis, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off stump, du Plessis steers it to third man and keeps strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to du Plessis, 2 runs, again shortish and rising steeply, this time Faf mistimes the pull uppishly, wide of the fielder at mid-wicket and they get two]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to du Plessis, 2 runs, these two are very quick between the wickets. Good length delivery outside off stump, du Plessis dabs it towards third man, Dhoni jogs for the first run but Faf always wanted two and Dhoni races to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Dhoni, 1 run, pulled, not timed well though as he was off balance while playing the shot, probably this shortish ball hurried onto him and Dhoni mis-hit it over the infield through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Dhoni, leg byes, <b>FOUR</b>, fullish and angling down the leg-side, Dhoni tries to tickle it fine but fails to get bat on ball, the ball rolls off the thigh pad and runs away to the fine leg boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to du Plessis, 1 run, on the leg stump, glanced to fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Gurinder Sandhu [1.0-0-10-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>. During the break, Faf was telling Stephen Fleming that it is a two-paced wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to du Plessis, 1 run, on the off stump, du Plessis works it to mid-wicket and keeps strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to Dhoni, 1 run, Dhoni advances and gets too close to the pitch of the ball, hence not able to connect well and the mistimed drive rolls to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to du Plessis, 1 run, use of the feet to get to the pitch of the ball, nudged to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to du Plessis, no run, pushed through, on the off stump, du Plessis cuts it off the back foot to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to Dhoni, 1 run, short and spinning away outside off stump, punched to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yuvraj to du Plessis, 1 run, very full and on the leg stump, du Plessis drills it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuvraj Singh, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Yuvraj Singh v MS Dhoni, this is going to be interesting]]></line><line><![CDATA[Yuvraj Singh to bowl now]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Dhoni, no run, well bowled Jayant Yadav. On seeing Dhoni advance again, Yadav drags his length back, gets a bit of turn as well and forces Dhoni to fend at it]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Dhoni, <b>FOUR</b>, not from the middle of the bat, but Dhoni will take it. Flighted delivery from Jayant Yadav, Dhoni puts the dancing shoes on and goes for the slog, the ball takes the inside half of the bat and bisects deep mid-wicket and long-on to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Dhoni, no run, Dhoni stays in the crease and defends this offie with an angled bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to du Plessis, 1 run, oh this keeps low, du Plessis does well to keep it out though. du Plessis was camping on the back foot as the length was short, but it didn't rise at all, du Plessis manages to work it through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Dhoni, 1 run, Dhoni dances down the track but hits this flighted delivery all along the ground to long-on, hit well but straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to du Plessis, 1 run, shortish and quicker just outside off stump, punched down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to du Plessis, 1 run, on the off stump, du Plessis defends with soft hands towards point, says 'yes, yes' and Dhoni responds well]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Dhoni, 1 run, just a step forward to convert this into a length ball, worked away through square leg to get off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Dhoni, no run, this is interesting! A big swing from Dhoni but he misses. Short of a length delivery outside off stump, Dhoni steps out and tries to go big, but only connects with thin air]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to du Plessis, 1 run, short of length delivery on the off stump, du Plessis tucks it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, in the airrrr and just past the diving fielder at mid-off. Length delivery just outside off stump, du Plessis steps out and doesn't go through fully with the off-drive, it was in the air for a while but dropped in front of mid-off, Duminy dives to his right and gets a finger to it]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to du Plessis, no run, fullish and outside off stump, du Plessis defends off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Dhoni, no run, pushed through and on Dhoni's pads, he looks to work it towards the on-side and misses, the ball lobs off the pads and rolls away towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Dhoni, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Dhoni, no run, that nearly cleaned up Dhoni! This was tossed up and spun back into Dhoni, he was cramped for room and gets an inside edge onto the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Dhoni, no run, tossed up and spinning into Dhoni, nudged behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>MS Dhoni, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Raina, <b>out</b> Caught by Duminy!! That's as soft a dismissal one gets! Raina shakes his head as he walks back. This was tossed up and just outside off, Raina jumps down the track and drives it towards short extra cover, he didn't keep the ball down and offers a simple catch to Duminy. CHN are in some trouble now, they have lost their top-order. <b>Raina c Duminy b Jayant Yadav 11(8) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Jayant Yadav to Raina, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Jayant Yadav changes to round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to du Plessis, 1 run, tossed up and just outside off, du Plessis dabs it in front of point for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jayant Yadav, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, that's easy pickings for Raina, short and on his hips, he gets inside the line and pulls it behind square on the on-side, bisects the two men in the deep and the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Raina, 2 runs, Morkel drops one short as Raina came down the track, slapped over backward point. Raina is quick and gets back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Raina, no run, lovely bowling from Morkel, pitched up and shaping away from outside off, draws Raina half-forward and zips past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to du Plessis, 1 run, too straight from Morkel, worked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, that's sloppy from Saurabh Tiwary! This was pitched up and on the stumps, du Plessis presented the full face of the bat and punched it to the left of mid-on. Tiwary was lazy in bending his back and the ball slips through his fingers]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Faf du Plessis, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Dwayne Smith, <b>out</b> Lbw!! That looked plumb on first sight and Smith's misery is over! This was pitched up and nipped back in a fraction, Smith went nowhere, he got stuck in his crease and looked to get his bat in front of the pads, once he missed the ball, it was all over. The ball thudded into the back-pad, the impact was in front of middle and it would have crashed into the stumps. Vineet Kulkarni had a simple decision to make. <b>Dwayne Smith lbw b A Morkel 18(24) [4s-2 6s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[A Morkel to Dwayne Smith, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Albie Morkel, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, the slower bouncer from Sandhu, Smith swivels across and pulls it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Raina, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, nudged in front of mid-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ah! Raina twisted his left ankle as he took off for the first run, he seems OK though and is ready to face the next ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Raina, 2 runs, short of a length and on the stumps, Raina shuffles across and plays a half-arm jab in front of mid-wicket, gets back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, back of a length and on Smith's pads, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Sandhu, short and on Smith's hips, he swivels across and helps it past the keeper for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurinder Sandhu to Raina, 1 run, a <b>direct hit would have had Raina there</b>, this was a short of a length delivery outside off, Raina dabbed it behind square on the off-side. He wanted the second run, Dwayne Smith slipped as he tried to return for the second, Raina has to run back. Yuvraj has a shy at the bowler's end and misses, Raina was struggling]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place for Sandhu]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Gurinder Sandhu, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Dwayne Smith, no run, the slider from Nadeem, came back with the angle, bowled at 100kmph, Smith was looking to work it towards the on-side and missed. That ends a fine spell from Nadeem, he finishes with <b>excellent figures of 4-1-18-0</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Dwayne Smith, no run, flighted and just outside off, Smith goes back and defends it with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Dwayne Smith, <b>SIX</b>, Smith breaks the shackles! This was floated outside off, Smith uses his reach to good effect, gets underneath the length and hoists it high and over long-on for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Raina, 1 run, tossed up and on Raina's pads, nudged in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, flatter and just outside off, punched square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Dwayne Smith, no run, pushed through and just outside off, Smith gets back and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Brendon McCullum, <b>out</b> Caught by Duminy!! The pressure gets to McCullum. This is excellent bowling from Zaheer, he kept it very full and just outside off, McCullum was deep inside the crease and shuffled across as he looked to go over mid-off. He doesn't get the height needed, straight to Duminy at the edge of the circle. <b>A wicket-maiden from Zaheer.</b> CHN have scored only 16 runs in the powerplay. <b>Brendon McCullum c Duminy b Zaheer 11(21) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Zaheer to Brendon McCullum, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Brendon McCullum, no run, full and wide from Zaheer, that was there to be smacked, McCullum drills it hard and straight to Nadeem at point, McCullum is visibly frustrated]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Brendon McCullum, no run, short of a good length and just outside off, McCullum goes hard on the cut but can't get it past the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Brendon McCullum, no run, nicely bowled by Zaheer, keeps it full and outside off, McCullum charges down the track and misses his swing]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Brendon McCullum, no run, this is excellent bowling from Zaheer, he goes full and wider outside off as McCullum shaped up for the lap shot, he changes his mind, opens the face of the bat and looks to run it past the keeper, misses it completely]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Brendon McCullum, no run, short of a length and just outside off, McCullum stays behind the line and dabs it towards backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, pushed through flatter by Nadeem, McCullum comes down the track and hacks it towards long-on for a single, <b>brings up 6000 T20 runs</b>, only the third to do so.]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Brendon McCullum, no run, the sweep from McCullum, almost slipped on the shot, doesn't get hold and the ball rolls away towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Brendon McCullum, no run, flatter and on the stumps, McCullum backs away and guides it straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Brendon McCullum, 2 runs, tossed up by Nadeem, McCullum went for the big slog sweep, doesn't get hold of the shot. The man at long-on gets across and keeps them down to a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, flighted delivery and on Smith's pads, worked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, McCullum had exposed all his three stumps, Nadeem follows him, lifted over the bowler but with no timing at all. Duminy gets across and keeps them down to a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Dwayne Smith, no run, this is the off-cutter from Zaheer, pitched just outside off and angled away from the right-hander, Smith pokes at that and is beaten on the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Dwayne Smith, no run, much better from Zaheer, goes full and gets it to nip back into the batsman, Smith was caught in his crease, just about manages an inside edge onto the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, Smith is off the mark, too short from Zaheer, Smith swivels across and pulls it behind square on the on-side, the man in the deep is very square and the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[A fly-slip and a gully is in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Dwayne Smith, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Smith stays behind the line and punches it towards extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Dwayne Smith, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Smith prods across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, McCullum gives the charge to a short of a length delivery, doesn't get hold of the shot, gets it right off the toe-end of the bat, the mid-off is very straight and this goes to where the usual position is, there's a man in the deep and it's just a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, pushed through by Nadeem, nudged in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Brendon McCullum, no run, another arm-ball from Nadeem, angles back into the batsman, McCullum is cramped for room, just about manages to get his bat down in time and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Brendon McCullum, no run, flighted and just outside off, punched straight to the fielder at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, that's the first boundary of the innings, fraction too short from Nadeem, McCullum is quick to rock back and pulls it in front of square on the on-side, beats the man at deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Brendon McCullum, no run, Nadeem drops one short and just outside off as McCullum gave the charge, cut straight to the fielder at cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Brendon McCullum, no run, tossed up and just outside off, McCullum was looking to work it towards the on-side and gets an inside edge onto the pads]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Dwayne Smith, no run, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, Smith gets behind the line and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Dwayne Smith, no run, <b>almost cleaned up</b>! Wonderful line from Zaheer, on a good length and a hint of nip back into Smith, he was late as he prodded forward, gets an inside edge onto the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Dwayne Smith, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Smith prods forward and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, a direct hit from Iyer would have had Dwayne Smith short, <b>he had given up</b>, this was pitched up and just outside off, McCullum pushed forward and got an outside edge to the left of short third man. Iyer dives across, stops the ball and throws it at the striker's end - all in one action. Dwayne Smith was nowhere in the frame, perhaps Iyer had more time than he thought]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Brendon McCullum, no run, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Brendon McCullum, no run, Zaheer starts with a slower off-cutter, McCullum watches it all along and pushes it towards the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Zaheer Khan, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Dwayne Smith, no run, Nadeem starts with a <b>maiden over</b>, pushed through and on Smith's thigh pad, he goes back and gets an inside edge onto the flick, the ball rolls away towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Dwayne Smith, no run, tossed up and a hint of spin away from middle, Smith is slightly opened up as he defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Dwayne Smith, no run, another arm-ball from Nadeem, bowled with a seam-up action, drifts back into Smith, he makes room and cuts it straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Dwayne Smith, no run, the arm ball from Nadeem, it came back with the angle, Smith was caught in his crease and is struck high on the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Dwayne Smith, no run, pushed through and just outside off, Smith leans forward and drives it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Dwayne Smith, no run, flighted and just outside off, Smith prods forward and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Smith and Brendon McCullum are at the crease. Dwayne Smith is on strike. S Nadeem will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place..]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's time for action. Can CHN become the first team to make it through to the playoffs? The Delhi are in the middle of a team huddle. The two openers are out as well. Nadeem will open the bowling on a green pitch.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai</b> (Playing XI): Dwayne Smith, Brendon McCullum, Suresh Raina, Faf du Plessis, MS Dhoni(w/c), Dwayne Bravo, Pawan Negi, Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Mohit Sharma, Ishwar Pandey]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Delhi</b> (Playing XI): Quinton de Kock(w), Shreyas Iyer, Jean-Paul Duminy(c), Yuvraj Singh, Kedar Jadhav, Saurabh Tiwary, Albie Morkel, Jayant Yadav, Shahbaz Nadeem, Zaheer Khan, Gurinder Sandhu]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Duminy:</b> 'We would have batted first as well. We came a few runs short in the last game, but if we bat well, we can definitely chase the total down. We need to be professional, we want to end this tournament with a bit of pride. We have made two changes, <b>Shahbaz Nadeem</b> comes in place of Amit Mishra and <b>Gurinder Sandhu</b> replaces Nathan Coulter-Nile']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhoni:</b> 'We are looking to bat first. It was a wicket that was stopping in the last game. There is some grass on the pitch and it should assist the pacers, but it might be two paced. The longer boundaries give the spinners a chance to flight the ball more. We have made one change, <b>Ashish Nehra</b> is not fit, he has got flu and <b>Ishwar Pandey</b> comes in his place.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Toss time!</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Toss and teams are not far away from now. Stay tuned.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather Report:</b> It is going to be a clear evening in Raipur, with temperatures expected to hover around the mid thirties (degree Celsius). We will get a full game in.]]></line><line><![CDATA[There are question marks over Brendon McCullum's availability, since the Kiwi captain has to join the national team as they gear up for their Test series against England.. McCullum's unavailability will be a big blow for CHN as he has been their highest run-getter this season, amassing 419 runs at an average of 38.09. His absence though would mean that Michael Hussey will get to open the innings in his place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chennai are coming here on the back of a win against Rajasthan, a team that has lost the plot after winning their first 5 games. Ravindra Jadeja, who was struggling to make a substantial contribution with either the bat or the ball, finally rose to the occasion as he produced a Man of the Match performance. He finished his spell with figures of 4/11 and helped CHN go top of the points table with a 12-run win.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Delhi assistant coach Pravin Amre defended Yuvraj's lack of form, while CEO Hemant Dua told PTI that the player could not be blamed for commanding such a high price since the IPL player auction had been "market determined". The comments come a few weeks after the struggling Yuvraj himself said he "did not ask" for 16 crores.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Quinton de Kock, who scored a 31-ball fifty in his first game of the season against HYD, will be looking to continue his good form. However, Yuvraj Singh's form has been a major concern for the Delhi.  He has managed only 205 runs at an average of 18.63 from 12 games. With questions being raised about the justification of his price tag of 16 crores, the Delhi' team management have come out in support of Yuvi.]]></line><line><![CDATA[As we move closer to the playoffs, the fight for the first four spots is heading towards a close finish. Chennai, who are currently sitting at the top of the pile, can cement their place in the top four with a win over Delhi. On the other hand, the Delhi are currently seventh on the points table and have no chance of making it to the next stage. They will be looking to regain some pride against their formidable counterparts today.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview</b><br/><br/>No 1 versus No 7. Form team against flop team. Title contenders facing no-hopers. Game 49 of IPL 2015 in Raipur on Tuesday pits Chennai against Delhi, but there is little to suggest that the match will be much of a contest. The Shaheed Veer Narayan Singh International Stadium is Delhi' adopted home ground, but how much at home they feel remains to be seen because they just aren't getting too much correct. Some close defeats, yes, but for how long can the players and management staff keep offering that as solace to the franchise's supporters?<br/><br/>With 16 points, CHN have all but confirmed their place in the IPL 2015 playoffs. Delhi are out of the running.<br/><br/>Venue: Shaheed Veer Narayan Singh International Stadium, Raipur<br/><br/>Date: May 12, 2015<br/><br/>Time: 20:00 IST<br/><br/>Weather: A pleasant evening predicted with temperatures hovering in the mid-20s.<br/><br/>Team news:<br/><br/><b>Delhi</b><br/><br/>The way this team has chopped and changed and still not locked in a winning combination, it's anyone's guess as to what the management will put forward on Tuesday. For safety sake, they should stick to the XI from the last game.<br/><br/>Probable XI: 1 Quinton de Kock (wk), 2 Shreyas Iyer, 3 JP Duminy (capt), 4 Yuvraj Singh, 5 Kedar Jadhav, 6 Saurabh Tiwary, 7 Albie Morkel, 8 Jayant Yadav, 9 Nathan Coulter-Nile, 10 Amit Mishra, 11 Zaheer Khan<br/><br/><b>Chennai</b><br/><br/>There's uncertainty over Brendon McCullum's availability since he has to leave and join his national team on their tour to England. In that case, as MS Dhoni pointed out, Michael Hussey will reprise his role as an opener for the first time this season. Other than that, don't expect CHN to make any changes because they have all but qualified for the playoffs. <br/><br/>Probable XI: 1 Dwayne Smith, 2 Brendon McCullum/Michael Hussey, 3 Suresh Raina, 4 Faf du Plessis, 5 Pawan Negi, 6 MS Dhoni (capt/wk), 7 Dwayne Bravo, 8 Ravindra Jadeja, 9 R Ashwin, 10 Mohit Sharma, 11 Ashish Nehra<br/><br/><b>Stats and Trivia</b>:<br/><br/>The two best individual bowling performances of the season are from CHN - Ashish Nehra's 4 for 10 and Ravindra Jadeja's 4 for 11.<br/><br/><b>Quotes</b>:<br/><br/>"We threw our wickets away. Maybe I did." - Quinton de Kock after a half-century in his first game of this season.<br/><br/>"There is a joke in the dressing room that if Baz (Brendon McCullum) bats for 6 overs, he's cooked there." - MS Dhoni on his big-hitting opener.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai</b> (From): Michael Hussey, Dwayne Smith, Suresh Raina, Faf du Plessis, MS Dhoni(c/w), Ravindra Jadeja, Pawan Negi, Dwayne Bravo, Ravichandran Ashwin, Mohit Sharma, Ashish Nehra, Brendon McCullum, Baba Aparajith, Ishwar Pandey, Matt Henry, Mithun Manhas, Samuel Badree, Ronit More, Rahul Sharma, Kyle Abbott, Ankush Bains, Irfan Pathan, Pratyush Singh, Andrew Tye, Eklavya Dwivedi]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Delhi</b> (From): Quinton de Kock(w), Shreyas Iyer, Jean-Paul Duminy(c), Kedar Jadhav, Yuvraj Singh, Saurabh Tiwary, Albie Morkel, Nathan Coulter-Nile, Jayant Yadav, Amit Mishra, Zaheer Khan, Manoj Tiwary, Mayank Agarwal, Shahbaz Nadeem, Imran Tahir, Angelo Mathews, Jaydev Unadkat, Gurinder Sandhu, Chidhambaram Gautam, Travis Head, Srikar Bharat, Marcus Stoinis, Domnic Joseph, KK Jiyas]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>119</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>6</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Chennai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Smith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>18</runs>
					<balls>24</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>A Morkel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>484</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Brendon McCullum</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>11</runs>
					<balls>21</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Zaheer</bowler>
					<bowlerId>71</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Jean-Paul Duminy</fielder>
						<fielderId>211</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Raina</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>11</runs>
					<balls>8</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Jayant Yadav</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8182</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Jean-Paul Duminy</fielder>
						<fielderId>211</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7825</playerid>
					<name>Faf du Plessis</name>
					<batsman-name>du Plessis</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>du Plessis</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>29</runs>
					<balls>23</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>A Morkel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>484</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhoni</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>27</runs>
					<balls>24</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Zaheer</bowler>
					<bowlerId>71</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Shahbaz Nadeem</fielder>
						<fielderId>7906</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>242</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
					<batsman-name>DJ Bravo</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>8</runs>
					<balls>8</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Gurinder Sandhu</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8501</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Jean-Paul Duminy</fielder>
						<fielderId>211</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8281</playerid>
					<name>Pawan Negi</name>
					<batsman-name>Negi</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Negi</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>5</runs>
					<balls>8</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<batsman-name>R Jadeja</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<batsman-name>Ashwin</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ashwin</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Mohit Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mohit Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8665</playerid>
					<name>Ishwar Pandey</name>
					<batsman-name>I Pandey</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>I Pandey</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>201</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>16</runs>
				<overs>5.6</overs>
				<batsman>Brendon McCullum</batsman>
				<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>255</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>34</runs>
				<overs>8.1</overs>
				<batsman>Dwayne Smith</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>413</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>46</runs>
				<overs>9.2</overs>
				<batsman>Suresh Raina</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7825</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>83</runs>
				<overs>15.2</overs>
				<batsman>Faf du Plessis</batsman>
				<batsman-name>du Plessis</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>242</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>105</runs>
				<overs>17.3</overs>
				<batsman>Dwayne Bravo</batsman>
				<batsman-name>DJ Bravo</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>265</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>110</runs>
				<overs>18.1</overs>
				<batsman>MS Dhoni</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>0</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>7</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Delhi">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7906</playerid>
					<name>Shahbaz Nadeem</name>
					<bowler-name>S Nadeem</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Nadeem</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>18</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>71</playerid>
					<name>Zaheer Khan</name>
					<bowler-name>Zaheer</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Zaheer</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>9</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8501</playerid>
					<name>Gurinder Sandhu</name>
					<bowler-name>Gurinder Sandhu</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Gurinder Sandhu</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>33</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>484</playerid>
					<name>Albie Morkel</name>
					<bowler-name>A Morkel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>A Morkel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>21</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8182</playerid>
					<name>Jayant Yadav</name>
					<bowler-name>Jayant Yadav</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Jayant Yadav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>8</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>69</playerid>
					<name>Yuvraj Singh</name>
					<bowler-name>Yuvraj</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Yuvraj</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>23</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8520</playerid>
					<name>Quinton de Kock</name>
					<bowler-name>de Kock</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>de Kock</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9428</playerid>
					<name>Shreyas Iyer</name>
					<bowler-name>S Iyer</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shreyas Iyer</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>211</playerid>
					<name>Jean-Paul Duminy</name>
					<bowler-name>Duminy</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Duminy</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1851</playerid>
					<name>Kedar Jadhav</name>
					<bowler-name>K Jadhav</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>K Jadhav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1601</playerid>
					<name>Saurabh Tiwary</name>
					<bowler-name>S Tiwary</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Tiwary</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>120</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>4</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>16.4</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Delhi">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8520</playerid>
					<name>Quinton de Kock</name>
					<batsman-name>de Kock</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>de Kock</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>I Pandey</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8665</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ravichandran Ashwin</fielder>
						<fielderId>1593</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9428</playerid>
					<name>Shreyas Iyer</name>
					<batsman-name>S Iyer</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shreyas Iyer</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>70</runs>
					<balls>49</balls>
					<fours>10</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>211</playerid>
					<name>Jean-Paul Duminy</name>
					<batsman-name>Duminy</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Duminy</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>I Pandey</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8665</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>69</playerid>
					<name>Yuvraj Singh</name>
					<batsman-name>Yuvraj</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Yuvraj</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>32</runs>
					<balls>28</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Negi</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8281</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mohit Sharma</fielder>
						<fielderId>8181</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>484</playerid>
					<name>Albie Morkel</name>
					<batsman-name>A Morkel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>A Morkel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>8</runs>
					<balls>8</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Negi</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8281</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ishwar Pandey</fielder>
						<fielderId>8665</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1851</playerid>
					<name>Kedar Jadhav</name>
					<batsman-name>K Jadhav</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>K Jadhav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1601</playerid>
					<name>Saurabh Tiwary</name>
					<batsman-name>S Tiwary</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Tiwary</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8182</playerid>
					<name>Jayant Yadav</name>
					<batsman-name>Jayant Yadav</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Jayant Yadav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7906</playerid>
					<name>Shahbaz Nadeem</name>
					<batsman-name>S Nadeem</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Nadeem</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>71</playerid>
					<name>Zaheer Khan</name>
					<batsman-name>Zaheer</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Zaheer</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8501</playerid>
					<name>Gurinder Sandhu</name>
					<batsman-name>Gurinder Sandhu</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Gurinder Sandhu</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8520</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>16</runs>
				<overs>2.3</overs>
				<batsman>Quinton de Kock</batsman>
				<batsman-name>de Kock</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>211</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>24</runs>
				<overs>4.1</overs>
				<batsman>Jean-Paul Duminy</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Duminy</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>69</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>93</runs>
				<overs>13.2</overs>
				<batsman>Yuvraj Singh</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Yuvraj</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>484</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>114</runs>
				<overs>15.6</overs>
				<batsman>Albie Morkel</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Morkel</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>0</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>0</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Chennai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8665</playerid>
					<name>Ishwar Pandey</name>
					<bowler-name>I Pandey</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>I Pandey</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>27</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Mohit Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mohit Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>17</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<bowler-name>Ashwin</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ashwin</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>24</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<bowler-name>R Jadeja</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2.4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>16</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<bowler-name>Raina</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Raina</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>8</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8281</playerid>
					<name>Pawan Negi</name>
					<bowler-name>Negi</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Negi</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>28</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<bowler-name>Dwayne Smith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Smith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<bowler-name>B McCullum</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Brendon McCullum</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7825</playerid>
					<name>Faf du Plessis</name>
					<bowler-name>du Plessis</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>du Plessis</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhoni</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhoni</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>242</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
					<bowler-name>DJ Bravo</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



