<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14615" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>21st Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Delhi</home>
		<away>Mumbai</away>
		<teamsabbr>DEL vs MUM</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>DEL</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>MUM</awayabbr>
		<homeId>61</homeId>
		<awayId>62</awayId>
		<venue>Feroz Shah Kotla, Delhi</venue>
		<startdate>23 04 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>23 04 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Mumbai</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Delhi won by 37 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Delhi</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>37</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Simon Fry</Name>
			<Country>Aus</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Nandan</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Chris Gaffaney</Name>
			<Country>NZ</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Graeme Labrooy</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>14:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150423175742</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>MUM</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>DEL</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>153</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>9</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>20</batteamovers>
		<status>Delhi won by 37 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>9311</playerid>
			<name>Jasprit  Bumrah*</name>
			<batsman-name>Bumrah</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Bumrah</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>0</runs>
			<balls-faced>0</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>111</playerid>
			<name>Lasith Malinga</name>
			<batsman-name>Malinga</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Malinga</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>6</runs>
			<balls-faced>10</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>6667</playerid>
			<name>Imran Tahir*</name>
			<bowler-name>Tahir</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Tahir</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>22</runs>
			<wickets>3</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1629</playerid>
			<name>Angelo Mathews</name>
			<bowler-name>Mathews</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Mathews</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>2</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>15</runs>
			<wickets>2</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>191</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>75</playerid>
<name>Harbhajan Singh</name>
<player-runs>9</player-runs>
<player-balls>10</player-balls>
<runs>153</runs>
<wicket-nbr>9</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>1629</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Mathews</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>9</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>11</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[W 4 W W . . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. 1 L1 6 . 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. Wd 1 . . Wd 1 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 1 . W . . ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/DEL_MUM_APR23/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[This is <b>Sidhant Maheshwari</b>, signing off on behalf of <b>Krishna, Raju, Sriram, Bharath</b> and my co-commentators, <b>Ramakrishnan</b> and <b>Pradeep</b>. See you tomorrow!]]></line><line><![CDATA[That's all we have for you from this game. Tomorrow, <b>Rajasthan</b> will be up against the <b>Bangalore</b>. Don't forget to join us then to catch all the action.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Let's take a look at some of the best <b>tweets</b> pertaining to this game:]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@forwardshortleg:</b> Very tough fight for the Wooden Spoon this year between #BLR and #MUM. Both teams look hopeless right now. #IPL]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@sanjaymanjrekar:</b> Some real below average players amongst some class ones. That's Mumbai playing XI for you. #DELvMUM #IPL2015]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@cricketwallah:</b> Batting unable to deliver, true, but Mumbai's weak bowling showing up again,  again and again this season...]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>@cricketaakash:</b> #MUM must win 6 out of their remaining 8 games to have an outside chance of making it to the playoffs...7 to be sure. #TOUGH #IPL]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shreyas Iyer:</b> 'Actually I don't have any pressure on me. The seniors back the juniors and we all gel well together. I take some time to knock a few balls and then I start attacking the bowlers. The opening slot is suiting me. We broke the jinx of losing the home games. Certainly, it's a great feeling if you're recognized as a star.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shreyas Iyer</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his <b>56-ball 83</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Duminy:</b> 'It's quite a small ground but I will take 6 of those sixes (on being asked how many times he has hit 6 sixes in an innings). It was a nice wicket to bat on. We got to 190 but it was important for the bowlers to bowl well. Hopefully, we can make it better. He (Tahir) gives his 100 percent no matter what cap he puts on. We always knew that if we get over the 2-win mark, we can do better in the tournament. If we can win more games at home, it will be great.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Tahir:</b> 'We played well as a team. We are playing a great league, all the teams are so competitive and good. It's an honour to wear this cap. I made a promise to my wife that I will wear the Purple Cap once again after the end of today's game. Thanks to everyone for their support.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit:</b> 'I think they played really well right from the start. To come out and post a total like that on that wicket was just great. We shouldn't have let them post that total, but we need to give them credit. They have a superb batting line-up and they batted to their strengths today. They bowled great line and lengths too. The same batting line-up scored more than 200 in the last game (talking about MUM's batting order). We wanted to have the same batting line-up, but we couldn't do well today. Initially, Simmons and Parthiv got off to a good start, but we failed to capitalize on that. We have to look forward and we need to forget these losses. We need to go to Mumbai and prepare for the Hyderabad.']]></line><line><![CDATA[If Domnic Joseph bowled well up front, Tahir proved his worth by keeping it tight in the slog overs and was rewarded with three scalps in a single over. Earlier, Shreyas Iyer and Duminy played crunching knocks, as the hosts piled up a massive total.  Both the batsmen plundered the opposition ranks at will and essayed quick-fire half-centuries. Only Lasith Malinga was able to stem the run flow for the visitors. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[DEL put up a professional show to win their third game of this season. All their key bowlers bowled with good control and they were backed up in the field by some brilliant fielding. In particular, JP Duminy and Imran Tahir took stunning catches in the deep to keep the lid on the scoring rate. It was Rohit Sharma, who looked to up the tempo with a wide array of shots, but once he perished, MUM slipped towards yet another defeat. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Malinga, no run, <b>Delhi break their 9-match losing streak at the Kotla</b>, they win by <b>37 runs</b>. They have won a game here after <b>2 years and 2 days</b>. Coming back to the ball, it was full and outside off, Malinga goes for a drive but fails to lay bat on that]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Malinga, no run, slower ball outside off, Malinga swings hard and misses the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jasprit Bumrah, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Harbhajan, <b>out</b> Caught by (sub)Jayant Yadav!! That's a great catch from the substitute fielder. It was banged in halfway down the wicket, Harbhajan went for the pull but the ball hurried onto him. He got it high on the bat and Jayant from deep mid-wicket runs forward, dives and takes a superb catch. He had to cover a lot of ground there <b>Harbhajan c (sub)Jayant Yadav b Mathews 9(10) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mathews to Harbhajan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Harbhajan, no run, full outside off this time, Harbhajan goes for the drive but the ball beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Malinga, 1 run, fuller and on the stumps, Malinga whips the drive towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Malinga, <b>FOUR</b>, banged in short and at the batsman, Malinga swats the pull over a diving mid-wicket and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Angelo Mathews [1.0-0-10-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Harbhajan, no run, Harbhajan tries to play the slog sweep this time and Tahir bowls the googly, Harbhajan can't connect and the ball wasn't far away from the leg stump. Tahir can't believe that he didn't get a wicket there]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Malinga, 1 run, goes deep in the crease after making room, he was looking to pull that hard but drags it behind square on the leg-side off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Malinga, <b>wide</b>, bowls this one way wide outside off, Malinga can't lay bat on it and it is called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Malinga, no run, Malinga gives the charge and misses the quicker one from Tahir, the ball bounces extra and hits Jadhav on the shoulder. So, a <b>stumping chance</b> goes begging]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Malinga, no run, Malinga goes for a slog and Tahir bowls this slower and outside off, the ball turned away as Malinga went through with the shot, can't connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Harbhajan, 1 run, bowls a low full toss trying to target the blockhole, Harbhajan whips it towards deep mid-wicket to get off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Harbhajan, <b>wide</b>, way wide outside off, Harbhajan reached out but fails to connect, called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Harbhajan, no run, quicker one on off, the ball keeps a tad low as well, Harbhajan punches it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Harbhajan, 1 run, slower short ball outside off, Harbhajan waits for it and cuts it in the air square of the wicket, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Harbhajan, no run, Harbhajan makes room and Coulter-Nile bowls a full toss on his pads, Harbhajan fails to clip it through the on-side and the ball rolls away into the off-side off the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Harbhajan, <b>SIX</b>, one too many short balls from Coulter-Nile, Harbhajan knew that it was coming and he pulls it magnificently over the deep mid-wicket fence. That made a cracking sound as he connected with it]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Malinga, leg byes, 1 run, Malinga backs away and Coulter-Nile follows him with a short delivery, Malinga has a wild swat at it and fails to connect, the ball goes over the keeper and to his right off Malinga's body, the umpire gives it as leg byes]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Harbhajan, 1 run, back of a length delivery slightly wide outside off, Harbhajan cuts it in the air to the right of point, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Harbhajan, no run, short delivery outside off, Harbhajan looks to pull it over the on-side, but fails to connect]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>56 needed from 18 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Malinga, no run, googly from Tahir, what a beautiful delivery. Malinga goes for the big slog, but he fails to make contact and the ball misses the off stump by a whisker. An unbelievable over comes to end, <b>3 wickets came off it</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Malinga, no run, quicker one just outside off, Malinga leans forward and pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hat-trick ball coming up</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to McClenaghan, <b>out</b> Caught by K Jadhav!! Tahir is on a hat-trick. He goes on the run once more. McClenaghan goes for the reverse sweep off this flighted delivery around off, he gets an under-edge, the ball then goes off the glove and hits the pad, the ball then lobs up and catches the back of the bat. The keeper takes the simplest of catches. <b>McClenaghan c K Jadhav b Tahir 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Tahir to McClenaghan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Rayudu, <b>out</b> Caught by Coulter-Nile!! Tahir picks his second wicket now. He's pumped and Rayudu is the man gone now. 2 in 3 balls for Tahir, 3 wickets in 4 balls for DEL. It was floated slightly wide outside off, Rayudu chases it as he goes for the loft, hits it straight down the throat of long-off, who didn't have to move an inch to take that. <b>Rayudu c Coulter-Nile b Tahir 30(22) [4s-3 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Tahir to Rayudu, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Rayudu, <b>FOUR</b>, bowls this one slightly wide outside off, Rayudu goes chasing after it and slices it over backward point, Nadeem from sweeper cover runs to his left, puts in the dive but the ball beats him to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Harbhajan Singh, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Pandya, <b>out</b> Caught by Coulter-Nile!! Tahir is on the run as he picks his first wicket of the night. It's 2 in 2 for DEL now. It was tossed up on the stumps, Pandya wanted to go downtown with the loft, but fails to get under it properly. Coulter-Nile from long-off runs in to his right and dives to take another good catch. <b>Pandya c Coulter-Nile b Tahir 0(1)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Tahir to Pandya, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hardik Pandya, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out for the batting team</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Rohit, <b>out</b> Caught by S Nadeem!! Finally, Coulter-Nile gets his man. Rohit is gone and MUM's chances also take a dive with this wicket. It was a short slower delivery from Coulter-Nile, Rohit was cramped for the room there as he went for the pull, he got a top-edge that goes high in the air. There were two fielders converging in from deep square leg and deep mid-wicket there, there could well have been a collision, but Nadeem manages to take it easily in the end. Also, one of Rohit's hands came off the bat as he played that shot, probably the reason why he couldn't get power behind it. <b>Rohit c S Nadeem b Coulter-Nile 30(24) [6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Coulter-Nile to Rohit, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Rohit, 2 runs, Rohit backs away this time and Coulter-Nile follows him with a length ball, Rohit lofts it over mid-off, Duminy back-pedals and puts in the dive to his left at the long-off boundary, but <b>the ball falls out of his reach</b>. The batsmen take two in the meantime]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Rayudu, 1 run, Rayudu tries to smack this slower short ball outside off through the on-side, but gets the toe-end of the bat on it, the ball rolls away towards extra cover and the batsmen can only take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Rayudu, no run, fuller in length and just outside off, Rayudu looks to drive but the ball goes past the inside edge there, it bounces short of the keeper too]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Rayudu, <b>FOUR</b>, banged in short this time, Rayudu rocks back and pulls it over mid-wicket, who dives full length to his right but can't get a hand on it. The ball runs away to the deep mid-wicket fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Rayudu, <b>FOUR</b>, Rayudu has timed that so well. It was slightly shortish and outside off, Rayudu goes leg-side and makes room for himself, he cracks it square of the wicket and the sweeper had no chance of stopping that even though he ran to his left]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Nathan Coulter-Nile [2.0-0-17-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Rayudu, 1 run, comes down the track and flicks this quicker one through the short leg region for another single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Rayudu, 2 runs, eases this delivery on the stumps down to long-on, Mayank Agarwal from long-on gives the charge and tries to pick the ball quickly as the batsmen were threatening to take the second. He can't quite pick it properly and that allows the batsmen to come back comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Rayudu, no run, quicker one outside off, Rayudu opens the face of the bat and sets off for the single, he can't go through it as the ball went straight towards the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Rayudu, no run, gives this one more air on the stumps, Rayudu was trying to work it through the on-side and misses, the ball hits him on the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Rohit, 1 run, another one that's full and on leg, Rohit drives it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Rayudu, 1 run, full delivery on middle and leg, Rayudu drives it down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Imran Tahir [1.0-0-9-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>76 needed from 36 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Rayudu, 1 run, eases this one on the stumps down to long-on, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Rayudu, <b>SIX</b>, <b>hammered!</b> Rayudu joins the party now as he comes racing down the track and tonks this delivery on middle and leg over the cow corner fence, that went quite the distance]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Rohit, 1 run, advances this time and lofts this flighted delivery wide of long-off, only a single on that occasion]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Rohit, no run, drives this quicker delivery outside off towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Rohit, <b>SIX</b>, Rohit gives the charge this time and swings hard, he played that beautifully as the ball hits the sight screen on the full, another maximum for the MUM captain]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Rayudu, 1 run, full and outside off, Rayudu puts his front foot forward and drives it down to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Rohit, no run, drives this flighted delivery outside off straight to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Rohit, <b>SIX</b>, floated up around off, Sharma lofts it over the long-off fence with ease, that was an effortless six]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Rohit, 2 runs, flicks this delivery on the pads over mid-wicket and comes back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Rayudu, leg byes, 1 run, <b>stumping chance missed!</b> Rayudu comes down the track and fails to lay bat on this flighted delivery outside off, the ball rolls back to the right of the keeper off his pad and Rayudu had no clue where the ball was, Jadhav tries to inflict a stumping by dragging the ball onto the stumps with his right glove, but the ball misses the stumps and the batsmen then go through for a leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Rayudu, 2 runs, takes another step forward and Mishra bowls it on middle and leg, Rayudu flicks it over a leaping short mid-wicket fielder, the batsmen take a couple before the ball is hunted down in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Rayudu, no run, goes for a big heave but mistimes it to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Rohit, 2 runs, quicker and on the pads once again, Rohit nudges it through mid-wicket, the batsmen take two before the fielder at deep square leg runs to his left and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Rayudu, 1 run, takes a step forward and Nadeem drifts this one on the pads, Rayudu eases it down to long-on to get off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Rayudu, no run, gives the charge once again and knocks this flatter delivery back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Rayudu, no run, Rayudu gives the charge and Nadeem drags his length back, Rayudu can only defend it towards point in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Rohit, 1 run, quicker and on middle stump line, Rohit punches it to deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Rayudu, 1 run, floated up outside off, Rayudu leans forward and drives it past a diving cover, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shahbaz Nadeem [1.0-0-5-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Rohit, no run, pushes this back towards the bowler, Rayudu has to dive back in his crease to make his ground as Mishra threatened to flick it back on the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Rohit, no run, slower through the air and on middle stump line, Sharma tries to work it through the on-side and fails to connect. The ball hits him high on the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Rayudu, 1 run, bowled a little quicker and on the stumps, Rayudu clips it wide of long-on, only a single on this occasion]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Rohit, 1 run, knocks this flighted delivery towards cover and the batsmen take a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ambati Rayudu, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Pollard, <b>out</b> Caught by S Nadeem!! That's a huge wicket for the Delhi. The dangerman Pollard is gone. He walks back dejected. It was flatter and outside off, Pollard went for the loft, but ends up slicing it high in the air as the ball turned away. Nadeem from extra cover runs to his left and takes a well judged catch. <b>Pollard c S Nadeem b Mishra 10(8) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mishra to Pollard, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Rohit, 1 run, googly on middle and leg, Rohit waits for it and clips it through mid-wicket, he was looking for the second there but it's not available]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Pollard, no run, shortish on the stumps, punched back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Pollard, <b>SIX</b>, mighty hit. Flighted delivery on the stumps, Pollard lofts it easily over wide long-on for a 91-metre hit]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Rohit, 1 run, tossed up outside off stump, pushed away to deep cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Pollard, 1 run, googly on the leg stump, punched to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Pollard, no run, tossed up on the off stump, Pollard defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Tahir to Rohit, 1 run, full toss, but Rohit is kind enough to drive it along the ground to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Imran Tahir, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Pollard, 2 runs, on the leg stump, Pollard flicks it through backward square leg for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Pollard, no run, big shout for LBW, not given. Was it sliding down leg? Yes, good call and that was missing leg stump. Interestingly, Pollard shook his head as Mishra and Co. were appealing. Googly from Mishra, Pollard leans forward and pads it, the impact is in line with middle and leg but it was spinning too much]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Rohit, 1 run, driven to deep extra-cover along the ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Pollard, 1 run, tossed up outside off stump, Pollard looks to drive and gets a thickish outside edge that rolls through cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kieron Pollard, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Chand, <b>out</b> Stumped!! This was on the cards. Chand was bound to come down the track to go for a big hit. Mishra bowled this slower through the air, Chand missed it completely and the keeper made no mistake. Chand was a long way out of the crease. That was a good stumping by the keeper as it kept a bit low. <b>Chand st K Jadhav b Mishra 14(11) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mishra to Chand, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Stumped!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Chand, <b>FOUR</b>, that's cheeky from Chand. Googly on the off stump, he waited for the ball to come and just took in front of the off stump, Yuvraj gives chase from short third man, flicks the ball but it rolls back to hit the boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Rohit, no run, on the off stump, Rohit defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Chand, 1 run, quicker through the air, punched down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Chand, <b>wide</b>, again down the leg-side, easy call for the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Chand, <b>wide</b>, fired down the leg-side, the keeper fails to grab it cleanly. He thought it brushed the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Chand, no run, on the off stump, Chand defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Rohit, 1 run, taps this to cover and sets off for a sharp run]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Rohit, no run, slider outside off stump, Rohit drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nadeem is operating from round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Nadeem to Chand, 1 run, on the leg stump, worked away to backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shahbaz Nadeem, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Chand, 1 run, short and spinning away outside off stump, Chand waits and taps it to long-off. He was surprised by the turn and the slowness of that ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Rohit, 1 run, flatter ball, punched to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Chand, <b>2 wides</b>, googly down the leg-side, Chand misses the tickle, the keeper kicks the ball with his left foot and saves a few. Something that MS Dhoni would do]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Chand, <b>FOUR</b>, that's given as runs. I thought it missed everything. Flighted delivery down the leg-side, Chand slips while playing the sweep and the keeper didn't collect]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Rohit, 1 run, googly on the leg stump, flicked to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Chand, 1 run, very full, dug out to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Rohit, 1 run, flighted delivery just outside off stump, Rohit drives it to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[One slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Amit Mishra, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit Sharma, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Parthiv Patel, <b>out</b> Caught by Tahir!! That's another great catch from DEL in the outfield. Slower ball on a short of a length, Patel goes for the pull, gets a lot of height but not the distance. Imran Tahir runs to his right from deep square leg, again it looked like the fielder lost it for a while, but he dived to his right and took it with both hands. MUM need to be careful now. They've lost two wickets in a space of 11 balls. <b>Parthiv Patel c Tahir b Mathews 28(19) [4s-4 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mathews to Parthiv Patel, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Parthiv Patel, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Patel swings and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Parthiv Patel, <b>SIX</b>, slower delivery and he's picked it easily. Patel waits and hits it straight into the sightscreen. That was a handsome hit]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Parthiv Patel, <b>FOUR</b>, that's not connected well, but Patel will take it. Short of a length delivery on the leg stump, Patel tries to slog, gets it on outside half of the bat, the ball goes past the bowler, mid-on runs to his right and gets a hand onto it, but the ball escapes]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Parthiv Patel, no run, slower delivery outside off stump, Patel swings and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Parthiv Patel, no run, Patel steps out and tries to carve it hard, but picks out cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Angelo Mathews, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Joseph to Chand, no run, on the off stump, Chand defends well from the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Joseph to Chand, no run, good length on the off stump, Chand defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Joseph to Chand, 2 runs, short of length delivery on the off stump, Chand gets across the stumps and pulls it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[One slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Joseph to Parthiv Patel, 1 run, good length delivery outside off stump, Patel pushes it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Unmukt Chand, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Joseph to Simmons, <b>out</b> Caught by Duminy!! Oh that's gone high up in the airrrrr and that's a very good catch by the skipper. Big blow for Mumbai. Full and in the slot, Simmons would have normally muscled that out of the ground. He went for the loft over mid-on but he hit it straight up in the air, Duminy runs back to his right from mid-on, looked like he misjudged it for a while, but he stopped, then moved to his right, stretched his hands to take the catch and then tumbled onto the ground. <b>Simmons c Duminy b Joseph 15(14) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Joseph to Simmons, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Joseph to Simmons, no run, good length delivery on the stumps, Simmons defends off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Domnic Joseph [1.0-0-4-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Simmons, 1 run, low full toss but Simmons has driven it straight to mid-off. He tried to hit it to the left of the fielder there but couldn't find the gap. <b>14 came off that Duminy over</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, in the slot and that's easily driven through cover. With the ball spinning back in, it was always easy for Simmons to play Duminy and he's hit that for four]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Parthiv Patel, 1 run, that's a fine looking whip, but straight to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Parthiv Patel, no run, gets down on one knee and tries to sweep but misses and gets hit on the pad. The impact was well outside off though]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Parthiv Patel, <b>FOUR</b>, in the air but in the gap. A risky hit from Patel. Short and spinning away outside off stump, Patel cuts it between short cover and cover-point. Back-to-back boundaries for MUM]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now the slip has vanished]]></line><line><![CDATA[Oh dear! The physio is attending to Duminy. He was in some pain after diving to save a boundary earlier and he's now stretching his right leg. Probably he's done some damage to his calf muscle. He's fine to continue though. Maybe just cramps!]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Parthiv Patel, <b>FOUR</b>, flighted delivery just outside off stump, Patel backs away and slices the drive over cover-point, cleared the infield and got full value for the shot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[One slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jean-Paul Duminy, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Simmons, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Simmons defends it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, easy ball, especially after opening himself up expecting the length to be short, Simmons pulls it through mid-wicket and it raced away for four]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Simmons, no run, oh this one's took off. Bumper on the off stump, steeply rising as well, Simmons hops and looks to fend, luckily for him, it misses both bat and glove]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Simmons, no run, once again stays leg-side of the ball and tries to cut, but this one beats the inside-edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, now that is a top shot. Short of a length delivery just outside off stump, Simmons went deep in the crease and also made room, he cut it nicely past backward point and third man had no chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Simmons, no run, good length delivery outside off stump, defended towards point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Simmons, <b>wide</b>, this is an easy call for the umpire. Short of a length delivery down the leg-side, Simmons lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Simmons, <b>wide</b>, Coulter-Nile follows Simmons with a bumper, Simmons lets it go, but that's a harsh call as it went above Simmons' left shoulder]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Joseph to Simmons, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Simmons pushes it towards backward point, Mayank Agarwal makes a diving stop and saves a few]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Joseph to Parthiv Patel, 3 runs, shimmies down the track and toe-ends the slog, Duminy gives chase from mid-on and flicks it back with a dive. Oh he looks in some pain. Did he land badly on his knees? He is in some discomfort, but is ready to carry on]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Joseph to Parthiv Patel, no run, good length delivery outside off stump, Patel drives it straight to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Joseph to Parthiv Patel, no run, this one nips back in off the deck, but Patel manages to defend the good length delivery off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Joseph to Parthiv Patel, no run, short of length delivery on the leg stump, Patel steps out, heaves but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Joseph to Parthiv Patel, no run, Patel looks for a tap-and-run single, but this short of length delivery goes quickly towards backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Domnic Joseph, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Parthiv Patel, 1 run, width on offer outside off stump, Patel guides it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Parthiv Patel, <b>wide</b>, full and down the leg-side, Patel tries to tickle it away but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Parthiv Patel, <b>FOUR</b>, oh that's an excellent front foot punch from Patel. Good length delivery just outside off stump, Patel hits it to the left of mid-off, who dives in vain]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Parthiv Patel, no run, this is a nice inswinger on a good length delivery, Patel has managed to keep it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Simmons, 1 run, Coulter-Nile goes wide of the crease to deliver this short of length delivery, there was a hint of extra-bounce, but Simmons handled it well and guided it towards gully. First runs on the board]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Simmons, no run, short of length delivery and just a hint of away swing on this one, pushed to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Simmons, no run, did that hit a crack? Gee! What a ball first up. Good length delivery pitching just outside off stump, the ball nips away and also shapes away from the right-hander, luckily it was well wide of Simmons]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Simmons and Parthiv Patel are at the crease. Simmons is on strike. Coulter-Nile will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back. The openers are striding out. Two slips in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shreyas Iyer</b>: "I am really enjoying the opening role. I was made to play one down in the practice games. I enjoy playing the new ball. The wicket is two-paced. I think it's not easy to play the spinners on this wicket."]]></line><line><![CDATA[It was eventually Lasith  Malinga, who clattered Iyer's leg-stump to end what was a quality knock. However, other than Malinga, rest of MUM's bowlers were well below par. On a flat pitch and with short boundaries coming into play, MUM still have a chance to overcome the hosts. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shreyas Iyer's explosion of fireworks took DEL to a mammoth total. It was in the 11th over when Iyer clouted Jasprit Bumrah for two fours and a six to reach his fifty and lift the scoring rate. He also carted Harbhajan Singh for two sixes in the 14th over. JP Duminy too made an impact by checking in meaty blows off Kieron Pollard in the 12th over and essayed a half-century. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Duminy, 1 run, Duminy gets down on one knee and tries to sweep it fine, but gets an inside edge onto pad and it rolls towards backward square leg. Good comeback from Bumrah after conceding a six first ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to K Jadhav, 1 run, low full toss on the stumps, Jadhav gets across the stumps and sweeps it to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Duminy, 1 run, yorker outside off stump, Duminy digs it out to extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kedar Jadhav, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Yuvraj, <b>out</b> Caught by Pollard!! He didn't go through with the shot, but hit it too well and Pollard didn't have to move an inch. Very full, Yuvraj just dug that out, he hit it very hard and it went flat to long-on. Had he had a full swing at that, he could have easily cleared the boundary. <b>Yuvraj c Pollard b Bumrah 2(4)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bumrah to Yuvraj, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Duminy, 1 run, fine yorker just outside off stump, Duminy squeezes it out to backward point. This is the highest score for DEL this season]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Duminy, <b>SIX</b>, Bumrah has scored a <b>fifty off just 19 balls</b>, but not with the bat. Poor start to the over. Low full toss on the off stump, Duminy muscles it over long-on for a maximum]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jasprit Bumrah [3.0-0-45-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Duminy, 1 run, a fine yorker, Duminy could only dig it out towards long-off. Excellent over in the context of the game, just 6 runs off it]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Yuvraj, 1 run, low full toss, Yuvraj slogs, but gets the bottom of the bat and it rolls to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Duminy, 1 run, full and outside off stump, Duminy drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Yuvraj, <b>no ball</b>, 1 run, oh dear! Malinga has flicked the bails while delivering this yorker, Yuvraj digs it out to cover. It won't be a free-hit as it was not a front foot no-ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>STAT</b>: <b>Shreyas Iyer</b> has hit <b>14 sixes</b> - the most by a batsman in this season.]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Yuvraj, no run, yorker outside off stump, Yuvraj fails to dig it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[Big roar from the crowd as Yuvraj gets ready to face.]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Duminy, 1 run, low full toss, flicked away to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Duminy, no run, very full, not quite a yorker, Duminy tries to send it through mid-wicket, gets an inside-edge onto pad, they think about the run, but decide against it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuvraj Singh, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Mathews, <b>out</b> Caught by Parthiv Patel!! Again no room for Mathews to work with. As the length was on the shorter side, Mathews tries to pull but gets the toe-end of the bat, Parthiv dives forward and takes an easy catch. End of a fine cameo from Mathews. <b>Mathews c Parthiv Patel b McClenaghan 17(8) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[McClenaghan to Mathews, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Mathews, <b>FOUR</b>, oh this is a top shot from Mathews. Short and following Mathews as he makes room, he was cramped for room there, but Mathews has done exceptionally well to get on top of the bounce and guide it to the right of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Mathews, 2 runs, why is fine leg so square? Full and on the leg stump, a poor ball with that field, Mathews flicks it away nicely, deep backward square leg runs to his right, dives and saves two]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Mathews, no run, short of length delivery from McClenaghan, Mathews gives the charge and swings but toe-ends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Mathews, <b>wide</b>, full and down the leg-side, Mathews leaves it for the keeper and the umpire calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Mathews, 2 runs, McClenaghan follows Mathews this time, this length ball is nudged to the vacant mid-wicket region, Duminy returns for the second and they easily complete the run]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Mathews, <b>FOUR</b>, this is clever batting from Mathews. Short and just outside off stump, Mathews made room for himself by moving to leg-side, just opened the face of the bat at the last moment and guided it between backward point and short third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [3.0-0-25-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Mathews, 1 run, very full again from Malinga, not quite a yorker, Mathews drills it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Mathews, <b>FOUR</b>, easily done! Full and outside off stump, Mathews goes leg-side and drives it along the ground to the left of mid-off. Off the mark in style]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Angelo Mathews, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Shreyas Iyer, <b>out</b> Bowled!! He tried to be too cheeky there! Moving around in the crease is fine, but he's gone a long way across his sticks. Exposed all three stumps, can't do that to bloke called Malinga, who almost fires a pin-point yorker and takes the leg stump out. This is a sad end to a magnificent innings from the youngster. <b>In fact, the leg stump is broken</b>. <b>Shreyas Iyer b Malinga 83(56) [4s-7 6s-5]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Malinga to Shreyas Iyer, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Duminy, leg byes, 1 run, full and just missing leg, Duminy misses the flick, the ball rolls off the pad towards short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, again shuffles in the crease, a yorker on the off stump, squeezed out to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Shreyas Iyer, 2 runs, shuffles in the crease, Malinga bowls a full ball outside off stump, driven to mid-off off the toe end, McClenaghan has a shy at the bowler's end and misses. A direct-hit would have been very interesting as Iyer almost ran into Malinga there. There is no one backing up the throw and it's an extra run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga [2.0-0-9-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Duminy, <b>SIX</b>, slower ball alright, but it's right in the slot, Duminy delays his slog and nails it to perfection. Clears the deep mid-wicket by a long way. <b>15 came off the over</b>. <b>This is now the highest stand for any wicket this season</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Duminy, <b>FOUR</b>, friendly full toss, that's a cruel ball from Bumrah. Duminy doesn't try to overhit the ball, just lofts the drive over cover and picks up four more]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, another mistimed pull from Iyer and it rolls towards backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Duminy, 1 run, missed the yorker by an inch, Duminy drills it hard past the bowler, long-on runs to his right and slides to push the ball towards Pollard, who was running in from long-off. Excellent work by Unmukt Chand and Pollard at the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, slower delivery outside off stump, mistimed pull rolls to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Shreyas Iyer, 2 runs, slower delivery short and outside off stump, Iyer cuts it to deep extra-cover, Simmons runs to his right, slides and stops the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jasprit Bumrah [2.0-0-30-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Duminy, <b>FOUR</b>, full and on the leg stump, Duminy flicks it nicely through mid-wicket and there is no one in the deep to stop the ball. That spoils a good over]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, short of length delivery from Pandya, Iyer looks to pull, the ball hits him high on the bat and it goes towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Shreyas Iyer, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Iyer backs away and swings, misses, he lifted his back foot for a while, Parthiv Patel whipped the bails off in a flash, but Iyer got his foot down in time]]></line><line><![CDATA[Stumping check sent upstairs and I think that's brilliant work from Parthiv. Iyer has just got his back foot down in time. NOT OUT]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Shreyas Iyer, no run, slower delivery just outside off stump, Iyer swings hard and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Duminy, 1 run, slower ball, but it's too short, pulled to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Iyer slices it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Hardik Pandya [1.0-0-7-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[DEL have doubled their 10 overs score now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Duminy, 2 runs, tossed up, Duminy goes for the slog-sweep, gets a top edge, but it lands safely at mid-on, the fielder from the deep couldn't get there in time. <b>Fifty</b> for the skipper as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Duminy, 2 runs, shortish and just outside off stump, Duminy rocks back and cuts it to deep point for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, low full toss, driven back, that should have been stopped by Harbhajan. A lazy attempt from him, just put his right hand out and deflected the ball towards long-on. He should have gone with both hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Shreyas Iyer, <b>SIX</b>, this time it's a slog-sweep and it's six more. A little slower through the air, Iyer was down on one knee, he had to reach out for it a bit in the end, but he did very well to connect and cleared deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Shreyas Iyer, <b>SIX</b>, that's in the slot and easy pickings for Iyer. For some reason, Harbhajan is not bowling the offies to the right-hander, he's firing the sliders in, Iyer is picking them easily and he's slogged this over deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Duminy, 1 run, flighted delivery just outside off stump, Duminy looks to drive, gets an inside edge and it rolls to short fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harbhajan Singh [3.0-0-16-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>. This is a great partnership for the Delhi. The last three overs have yielded 47 runs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, edged and four. This is frustrating for the bowler. Short and outside off stump, Iyer goes for the pull again, gets a thickish edge and it goes fine past the keeper. This is <b>Iyer's highest score in IPL</b> as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Shreyas Iyer, <b>SIX</b>, top edge and it's gone for six. Short and angling into the right-hander, Iyer was cramped for room as he tried to pull the short ball, the bat turned in his hands as well, but it had enough wood on it to clear the long leg boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Shreyas Iyer, no run, and again. This time a big appeal from the bowler and the keeper but the umpire shakes his head. Similar ball and a similar shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Shreyas Iyer, no run, short of length delivery on the off stump, Iyer makes a bit of room and tries to cut but misses. McClenaghan came from round the wicket on that occasion]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Duminy, 1 run, McClenaghan follows Duminy as he steps out, it was a short ball, he plays the pull and manages to send it to deep mid-wicket. That brings up the <b>100 partnership</b> as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Duminy, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, bit of extra bounce on it too, Duminy tries to run it down to third man but misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [2.0-0-14-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Delhi have scored 36 runs off the last two overs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to Duminy, 1 run, short of length delivery on the leg stump, should have been put away, Duminy helps it on its way, Malinga dives to his right at 45 and gets a hand to it and deflects it towards deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to Duminy, <b>SIX</b>, another full toss, another mishit, this one went off the outside half of the bat but it doesn't matter. It cleared the deep mid-wicket boundary by some distance. Duminy slogs it over the infield and gets a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to Duminy, <b>SIX</b>, that's gone a long way up in the air and it's got a lot of distance on it as well. Pollard opts for another slower ball, but he bowls this very full, Duminy waits and flicks it away over square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, very full, driven down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to Duminy, 1 run, slower delivery outside off stump, Duminy drives it along the ground to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to Duminy, <b>FOUR</b>, full toss and long-on was too wide. He ran to his right and tried to stop the ball, but it was too quick for him. Duminy swings it back over the bowler's head, he actually mishit that, but it's gone for four. Duminy is disappointed with himself that he didn't make proper contact]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to Duminy, <b>wide</b>, slower ball way outside off stump, Duminy shoulders arms]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Shreyas Iyer, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Iyer cuts it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a yorker, but he's squeezed it out fine and it's gone for four. Simmons at short third man had no chance. This is Iyer's <b>second IPL fifty</b> and he continues to impress]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, full toss and he's crashed that through cover. This is poor bowling from Bumrah. Can't offer freebies to a batsman who is well set]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Shreyas Iyer, <b>SIX</b>, that's a handsome hit from Iyer. Length ball on the stumps, Iyer waits for the ball and lofts it high over long-on and hits the sightscreen]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Duminy, 1 run, good stop from Simmons at short fine, slower ball from Bumrah, ends up drifting onto Duminy's pads, nudged away fine but Simmons gets across quickly from short fine, puts in the dive and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, Iyer attempts a crude slog and gets an inside edge onto his thigh pad, this one angled in from off, the ball drops in front of short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jasprit Bumrah [1.0-0-14-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, Pollard bowled this one from well behind the umpire, Iyer has to generate all the pace by himself, pulls it in the air and to the left of deep mid-wicket, the fielder gets across quickly and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to Duminy, 1 run, full and on Duminy's pads, whipped away past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, another slower ball from Pollard, Iyer stays back and works it past mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to Shreyas Iyer, no run, short and wide from Pollard, Iyer reaches out and slaps it towards extra cover, bounces in front of the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to Duminy, 1 run, another slower ball from Pollard, sliced away square past point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pollard to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, slower ball from Pollard, Iyer goes through with the lofted on-drive, almost holes out to deep mid-wicket, bounces just in front of Simmons]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kieron Pollard, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, Harbhajan drops one short and well outside off, Iyer stays back and cracks it square past point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Shreyas Iyer, no run, Iyer comes down the track to a well flighted delivery and pushes it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Duminy, 1 run, flighted delivery and well outside off, Duminy presses forward and drives it towards long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, tossed up and well outside off, Shreyas Iyer cracks it square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Duminy, 1 run, lovely drift from Harbhajan, slows down the pace on this off-break, Duminy was early into the drive, gets a thick inside edge and the ball loops through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Duminy, no run, pushed through by Harbhajan, Duminy doesn't get to the pitch as he ran down the track, takes it on his pads]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Duminy, 1 run, short of a length and on Duminy's pads, tucked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, on a good length and on off, pushed off the inner half of the bat, calls for a quick single and was struggling, but Rohit can't gather the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Shreyas Iyer, no run, short of a length and just outside off, hurried onto Iyer, he mistimes the drive and the ball rolls back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, width on offer from Pandya, Iyer waits on it, uses the pace of the bowler and steers it behind square on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Shreyas Iyer, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Iyer was looking to force it away towards mid-wicket, gets it high on the bat and mistimes it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Pandya to Duminy, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, dabbed away towards third man for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Hardik Pandya, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Shreyas Iyer, no run, pushed through and just outside off, punched back at the bowler, almost carried back to Harbhajan on the full]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Duminy, 1 run, Harbhajan floats one onto Duminy's pads, clipped away towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, the doosra from Harbhajan, but he drifts it down leg, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Duminy, 1 run, Harbhajan gives this one plenty of air and well outside off, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Duminy, no run, Harbhajan drifts one back into Duminy, he was looking to chop it towards the off-side, gets an inside edge onto the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, tossed up and just outside off, Iyer gets a thickish outside edge towards long-off, just a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Duminy, no run, Malinga keeps it full and slants onto Duminy's pads, he looks to flick and misses, Malinga turns around in an appeal, but that was always going down]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Duminy, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Duminy goes hard on the drive and gets an inside edge towards shortish mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, <b>direct hit might have had Iyer short</b>, this was the slower ball from Malinga, Iyer dropped it in front of short mid-wicket and called for a quick single. He almost ran into Malinga, would have been short had there been a direct hit]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Shreyas Iyer, no run, low full toss from Malinga, Iyer gets forward and drives it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Shreyas Iyer, no run, the slower ball from Malinga, Iyer watches it all along and drives it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Duminy, 1 run, yorker length delivery and on the off-stump line, Duminy jams it out in front of point, Shreyas Iyer calls for a quick single and beats Pollard to the crease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga [1.0-0-7-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Duminy, 1 run, flighted delivery and on the off-stump line, worked in front of square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, slower and on off, eased down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four</b>, this was tossed up and held its line outside off, Iyer was looking to drive, gets a thick edge that races away through the vacant slip cordon]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Duminy, 1 run, Duminy comes down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and drives it to the left of mid-on. McClenaghan does well to keep them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip moves in, Rohit is the man]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, slower and on off, worked to the right of the bowler, Harbhajan can't stop it and the ball rolls to the left of mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harbhajan to Shreyas Iyer, no run, Iyer gets lucky! This was pushed through by Harbhajan, Iyer was looking to work it towards mid-wicket, gets a thick edge and the ball drops in front of short third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harbhajan Singh, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Duminy, no run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, driven sweetly but straight to the fielder at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Duminy, no run, on a good length and on the stumps, Duminy presents the full face of the bat and drives it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Duminy, <b>SIX</b>, this is poor bowling from Bumrah, once again short and on the stumps, Duminy swivels across and pulls it over backward square leg, second successive maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Duminy, <b>SIX</b>, <b>massive</b>, easy pickings for Duminy, short and on his hips, he shuffles inside the line and helps it high and over backward square, goes deep into the stands]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Duminy, no run, short of a length and just outside off, defended towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bumrah to Duminy, 2 runs, poor fielding from Rayudu at mid-wicket, length ball and on Duminy's pads, tucked away in front of square. Rayudu goes one-handed and misses it completely, allows another run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jasprit Bumrah, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Shreyas Iyer, no run, on a good length and well outside off, Iyer looks to drive, one hand comes off the handle and he ends up slicing it to Pollard at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Shreyas Iyer, <b>SIX</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, width on offer from McClenaghan, too short and too wide, Iyer makes room and cracks it high and over backward point, went sailing over the ropes for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, one too many slower delivery from McClenaghan, Iyer spots it early, waits on it and lofts it over mid-on, juts one bounce and over the ropes for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Shreyas Iyer, no run, the bouncer now, Shreyas Iyer dropped his wrists and sways away from the line]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Shreyas Iyer, no run, the slower ball from McClenaghan, driven back towards the bowler. McClenaghan threatens to throw the ball back at the stumps, Iyer moves away from his stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Shreyas Iyer, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Iyer was looking for the pull, the ball hurried onto him and he ends up dragging it back towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Duminy, no run, <b>just short of mid-on</b>, this was pitched up on middle, Duminy was looking to drive, seemed to have checked his shot at the last moment, the ball goes in the air and drops just in front of the man at mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, length ball on the pads, Iyer prods across and tucks it in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Shreyas Iyer, <b>wide</b>, the bouncer from Malinga, Iyer drops his wrists and lets it go, it's too high though, given as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Shreyas Iyer, no run, another slower ball from Malinga, he rolled his fingers across it, Iyer was early into the push, scoops it in the air and the ball drops in front of mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Shreyas Iyer, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Iyer presses forward and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Shreyas Iyer, <b>wide</b>, Malinga slips in the slower yorker, but loses his line and drifts this one down leg, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Shreyas Iyer, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, on a good length and a hint of shape away from off, Iyer covers for the movement and whips it past mid-wicket, doesn't need to run for those, that's the first boundary of the innings]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Malinga to Shreyas Iyer, no run, on a good length and a hint of away swing for Malinga, he stays behind the line and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Lasith Malinga, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Duminy, no run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, Duminy covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Duminy, <b>wide</b>, McClenaghan sprays this one short and miles outside off, Duminy went chasing after that and missed. Parthiv Patel dives in front of 1st slip and holds on, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Duminy, <b>wide</b>, the bouncer from McClenaghan, but it's too short and well down leg-side, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Duminy, no run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, Duminy pushes forward and gets an inside edge onto the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Duminy, no run, loud shout for a <b>catch at the wicket</b>, this was short and on Duminy's thigh pad, he was looking to nudge it towards the on-side, there was a deflection. Parthiv Patel moved across to his right and collected the ball. Was there some glove on that? Anyway, the umpire says NO]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jean-Paul Duminy, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Agarwal, <b>out</b> Caught by Rayudu!! Yet another failure for Agarwal, he's been dismissed for 1 for the third consective time. This was banged in short and around the off-stump line Agarwal swivelled across on the pull, struck it pretty well but hits it straight to mid-wicket. Rayudu juggled with the ball, but holds onto the rebound. <b>M Agarwal c Rayudu b McClenaghan 1(2)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[McClenaghan to M Agarwal, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Agarwal is <b>OUT</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Shreyas Iyer, 1 run, width on offer from McClenaghan, slapped away behind square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Agarwal, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, Agarwal dabs it in front of cover and sets off for a quick single, he was lazy in grounding his bat, <b>might have been short had there been a direct hit</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>M Agarwal and Shreyas Iyer are at the crease. M Agarwal is on strike. McClenaghan will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players are out in the middle. We are set for the start of Match 21. McClenaghan has the new ball. One slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Delhi</b> (Playing XI): Mayank Agarwal, Shreyas Iyer, Jean-Paul Duminy(c), Yuvraj Singh, Angelo Mathews, Kedar Jadhav(w), Nathan Coulter-Nile, Amit Mishra, Shahbaz Nadeem, Imran Tahir, Domnic Joseph]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mumbai</b> (Playing XI): Lendl Simmons, Parthiv Patel(w), Unmukt Chand, Rohit Sharma(c), Kieron Pollard, Ambati Rayudu, Harbhajan Singh, Hardik Pandya, Jasprit Bumrah, Mitchell McClenaghan, Lasith Malinga]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rohit</b>: "We are bowling first as we are not sure how the wicket will play. We don't know what's a good score. We need to improve our fielding. We have dropped a few catches. The batsmen have been doing well. We are keen to do well tonight."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Duminy</b>: "We haven't had the results going our way. We've got one change, Shahbaz Nadeem is in for Manoj Tiwary. We just wanted more spinning options."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mumbai have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The toss isn't too far away folks. Stay tuned...]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-head</b>: In their last 14 meetings in the history of IPL, both Delhi and Mumbai have won seven matches each.]]></line><line><![CDATA[MUM would be happy with how Lendl Simmons and Unmukt Chand batted in the last game. They would hope that the top-order sets a nice platform for the likes of Rohit Sharma and Kieron Pollard to go berserk at the end. Bowling still remains a worry for the Mumbai camp. Apart from Harbhajan Singh, none of the bowlers have managed to give crucial breakthroughs. Even Lasith Malinga has gone for runs. MUM certainly need to tighten their bowling if they are to do well this season.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Well, when you are playing at home, normally you have the advantage, but unfortunately the Delhi haven't had a great time at the Kotla, losing their last 9 games in a row. JP Duminy and his boys would want to end the losing streak tonight. Nothing really went their way in their last game against the Kolkata as they were completely outplayed by the Men in Purple. One positive for them though was the bowling of Domnic Joseph, who bowled three economical overs and picked up two key wickets. Overall, DEL would want to put up a good show and get back to winning ways tonight.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Having lost four games out of four, the pressure was mounting on Mumbai, but they managed to beat Bangalore in a high-scorer and finally opened their account. Is this the opening Rohit Sharma & Co. wanted to turn things around? Can they register back-to-back wins and improve their position? We'll find out in a few hours from now. Hello and welcome to game 21 of the 2015 Indian Premier League. It's Delhi hosting Mumbai at the Feroz Shah Kotla.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/>Delhi and Mumbai are two teams that are experiencing an upswing in their fortunes after a poor start in IPL 2015. Delhi snapped their 11-match losing streak by winning against Punjab in Pune and they sustained it by taking a close match against Hyderabad by four runs in Visakhapatnam. However, they came back down to earth with a defeat against Kolkata and they will be desperate to get some consistency.<br/><br/>Mumbai started off their campaign with four consecutive losses but bounced back with a win against Bangalore. With both teams aiming to make up for lost time, this encounter at the Feroz Shah Kotla on Thursday is crucial for momentum. Delhi' loss will deflate their confidence slightly and they will be aware that Mumbai have the capability to sustain a winning habit after a poor start.<br/><br/><b>Venue:</b> Feroz Shah Kotla<br/><br/><b>Date:</b> April 23, 2015<br/><br/><b>Time:</b> 20:00 IST<br/><br/><b>Weather:</b> Clear conditions with a low of 22 degrees<br/><br/><b>Team news:</b><br/><br/><b>Delhi</b><br/><br/>The franchise has been served well by the youngsters in the team. Mayank Agarwal's attacking fifty, in partnership with Yuvraj Singh, set up their first win of the season over Punjab while Shreyas Iyer's big-hitting against Hyderabad was a pleasure to watch. In the bowling front, Delhi look stable with Nathan Coulter-Nile and Imran Tahir delivering the goods while skipper JP Duminy has led from the front with both and ball. Inconsistency in the batting and bowling was once again seen in the game against KOL and this is a problem which Delhi will be aiming to fix quickly.<br/><br/>Probable XI:<br/><br/>1 Mayank Agarwal, 2 Shreyas Iyer, 3 JP Duminy (capt), 4 Manoj Tiwary, 5 Yuvraj Singh, 6 Angelo Mathews, 7 Kedar Jadhav (wk), 8 Nathan Coulter-Nile, 9 Amit Mishra, 10 Dominic Joseph Muthuswamy, 11 Imran Tahir<br/><br/><b>Mumbai</b><br/><br/>The batting finally clicked in their game against BLR , when the likes of Lendl Simmons, Unmukt Chand and Rohit Sharma helped the team amass a huge total. The contribution of the other batsmen would have come as a huge sigh of relief for Rohit, who was under pressure with his own form. Heading into this crucial game, Mumbai will be hoping that Corey Anderson is fit for this game while J Suchith's left-arm orthodox could come in handy. Vinay Kumar, who was excluded in the previous match, might also come back.<br/><br/>Probable XI:<br/><br/>1 Lendl Simmons, 2 Parthiv Patel (wk), 3 Unmukt Chand, 4 Rohit Sharma (capt), 5 Corey Anderson, 6 Kieron Pollard, 7 Ambati Rayudu, 8 Harbhajan Singh, 9 R Vinay Kumar, 10 Jagadeesha Suchith/Jaspreet Bumrah, 11 Lasith Malinga<br/><br/><b>Stats</b><br/><br/>- Harbhajan Singh is the fourth player after Suresh Raina, MS Dhoni and Virat Kohli to play 100 matches for a single franchise.<br/><br/>- Delhi have lost nine consecutive matches at home. It is a sequence stretching back to the 2013 IPL.<br/><br/><b>Quotes</b><br/><br/>"I have this bad habit of not capitalising when in. I hope I am able to curb it." - Delhi batsman Mayank Agarwal wants to convert a start into a big score.<br/><br/>"100th game is something I'm happy about, having played all 100 games for one franchise." - An ecstatic Harbhajan Singh after his 100th IPL game for Mumbai.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mumbai</b> (From): Lendl Simmons, Parthiv Patel(w), Unmukt Chand, Rohit Sharma(c), Kieron Pollard, Ambati Rayudu, Hardik Pandya, Harbhajan Singh, Lasith Malinga, Mitchell McClenaghan, Jasprit Bumrah, Corey Anderson, Aditya Tare, Marchant de Lange, Pawan Suyal, Shreyas Gopal, Pragyan Ojha, Abhimanyu Mithun, Aiden Blizzard, Akshay Wakhare, Nitish Rana, Siddhesh Lad, Jagadeesha Suchith, Vinay Kumar]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Delhi</b> (From): Mayank Agarwal, Shreyas Iyer, Jean-Paul Duminy(c), Yuvraj Singh, Angelo Mathews, Kedar Jadhav(w), Manoj Tiwary, Nathan Coulter-Nile, Amit Mishra, Imran Tahir, Domnic Joseph, Quinton de Kock, Shahbaz Nadeem, Saurabh Tiwary, Jayant Yadav, Jaydev Unadkat, Gurinder Sandhu, Chidhambaram Gautam, Travis Head, Srikar Bharat, Albie Morkel, Marcus Stoinis, Zaheer Khan, KK Jiyas]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>190</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>4</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Delhi">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>2195</playerid>
					<name>Mayank Agarwal</name>
					<batsman-name>M Agarwal</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M Agarwal</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>McClenaghan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7624</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ambati Rayudu</fielder>
						<fielderId>6311</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9428</playerid>
					<name>Shreyas Iyer</name>
					<batsman-name>S Iyer</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shreyas Iyer</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>83</runs>
					<balls>56</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>5</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Malinga</bowler>
					<bowlerId>111</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>211</playerid>
					<name>Jean-Paul Duminy</name>
					<batsman-name>Duminy</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Duminy</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>78</runs>
					<balls>50</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>6</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1629</playerid>
					<name>Angelo Mathews</name>
					<batsman-name>Mathews</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mathews</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>17</runs>
					<balls>8</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>McClenaghan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7624</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Parthiv Patel</fielder>
						<fielderId>74</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>69</playerid>
					<name>Yuvraj Singh</name>
					<batsman-name>Yuvraj</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Yuvraj</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Bumrah</bowler>
					<bowlerId>9311</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Kieron Pollard</fielder>
						<fielderId>657</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1851</playerid>
					<name>Kedar Jadhav</name>
					<batsman-name>K Jadhav</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>K Jadhav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7774</playerid>
					<name>Nathan Coulter-Nile</name>
					<batsman-name>Coulter-Nile</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Coulter-Nile</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1454</playerid>
					<name>Amit Mishra</name>
					<batsman-name>A Mishra</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mishra</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7906</playerid>
					<name>Shahbaz Nadeem</name>
					<batsman-name>S Nadeem</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Nadeem</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6667</playerid>
					<name>Imran Tahir</name>
					<batsman-name>Tahir</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Tahir</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8883</playerid>
					<name>Domnic Joseph</name>
					<batsman-name>D Joseph</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Joseph</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>2195</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>2</runs>
				<overs>0.3</overs>
				<batsman>Mayank Agarwal</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Agarwal</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9428</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>156</runs>
				<overs>16.4</overs>
				<batsman>Shreyas Iyer</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Iyer</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1629</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>174</runs>
				<overs>17.6</overs>
				<batsman>Angelo Mathews</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mathews</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>69</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>187</runs>
				<overs>19.3</overs>
				<batsman>Yuvraj Singh</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Yuvraj</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>6</wides>
			<noballs>1</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>8</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Mumbai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7624</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell McClenaghan</name>
					<bowler-name>McClenaghan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>McClenaghan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>38</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>111</playerid>
					<name>Lasith Malinga</name>
					<bowler-name>Malinga</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Malinga</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>23</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9311</playerid>
					<name>Jasprit  Bumrah</name>
					<bowler-name>Bumrah</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bumrah</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>55</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>75</playerid>
					<name>Harbhajan Singh</name>
					<bowler-name>Harbhajan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Harbhajan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>34</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9647</playerid>
					<name>Hardik Pandya</name>
					<bowler-name>H Pandya</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Pandya</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>14</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>657</playerid>
					<name>Kieron Pollard</name>
					<bowler-name>K Pollard</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Pollard</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>599</playerid>
					<name>Lendl Simmons</name>
					<bowler-name>L Simmons</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Simmons</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>74</playerid>
					<name>Parthiv Patel</name>
					<bowler-name>Parthiv Patel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Parthiv Patel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7904</playerid>
					<name>Unmukt Chand</name>
					<bowler-name>Chand</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chand</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>576</playerid>
					<name>Rohit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Rohit</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rohit</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6311</playerid>
					<name>Ambati Rayudu</name>
					<bowler-name>Rayudu</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rayudu</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>153</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>9</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Mumbai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>599</playerid>
					<name>Lendl Simmons</name>
					<batsman-name>L Simmons</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Simmons</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>15</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>D Joseph</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8883</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Jean-Paul Duminy</fielder>
						<fielderId>211</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>74</playerid>
					<name>Parthiv Patel</name>
					<batsman-name>Parthiv Patel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Parthiv Patel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>28</runs>
					<balls>19</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mathews</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1629</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Imran Tahir</fielder>
						<fielderId>6667</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7904</playerid>
					<name>Unmukt Chand</name>
					<batsman-name>Chand</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chand</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>14</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[stumped]]></status>
					<bowler>A Mishra</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1454</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Kedar Jadhav</fielder>
						<fielderId>1851</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>576</playerid>
					<name>Rohit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Rohit</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rohit</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>30</runs>
					<balls>24</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Coulter-Nile</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7774</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Shahbaz Nadeem</fielder>
						<fielderId>7906</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>657</playerid>
					<name>Kieron Pollard</name>
					<batsman-name>K Pollard</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Pollard</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>10</runs>
					<balls>8</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>A Mishra</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1454</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Shahbaz Nadeem</fielder>
						<fielderId>7906</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6311</playerid>
					<name>Ambati Rayudu</name>
					<batsman-name>Rayudu</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rayudu</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>30</runs>
					<balls>22</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Tahir</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6667</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Nathan Coulter-Nile</fielder>
						<fielderId>7774</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9647</playerid>
					<name>Hardik Pandya</name>
					<batsman-name>H Pandya</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Pandya</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Tahir</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6667</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Nathan Coulter-Nile</fielder>
						<fielderId>7774</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>75</playerid>
					<name>Harbhajan Singh</name>
					<batsman-name>Harbhajan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Harbhajan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mathews</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1629</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Jayant Yadav</fielder>
						<fielderId>8182</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7624</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell McClenaghan</name>
					<batsman-name>McClenaghan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>McClenaghan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Tahir</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6667</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Kedar Jadhav</fielder>
						<fielderId>1851</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>111</playerid>
					<name>Lasith Malinga</name>
					<batsman-name>Malinga</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Malinga</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9311</playerid>
					<name>Jasprit  Bumrah</name>
					<batsman-name>Bumrah</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bumrah</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>599</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>35</runs>
				<overs>4.2</overs>
				<batsman>Lendl Simmons</batsman>
				<batsman-name>L Simmons</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>74</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>48</runs>
				<overs>5.6</overs>
				<batsman>Parthiv Patel</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Parthiv Patel</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7904</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>68</runs>
				<overs>8.2</overs>
				<batsman>Unmukt Chand</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Chand</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>657</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>82</runs>
				<overs>10.2</overs>
				<batsman>Kieron Pollard</batsman>
				<batsman-name>K Pollard</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>576</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>131</runs>
				<overs>15.6</overs>
				<batsman>Rohit Sharma</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rohit</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9647</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>131</runs>
				<overs>16.1</overs>
				<batsman>Hardik Pandya</batsman>
				<batsman-name>H Pandya</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6311</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>135</runs>
				<overs>16.3</overs>
				<batsman>Ambati Rayudu</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rayudu</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7624</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>135</runs>
				<overs>16.4</overs>
				<batsman>Mitchell McClenaghan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>McClenaghan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>75</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>153</runs>
				<overs>19.4</overs>
				<batsman>Harbhajan Singh</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Harbhajan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>9</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>11</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Delhi">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7774</playerid>
					<name>Nathan Coulter-Nile</name>
					<bowler-name>Coulter-Nile</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Coulter-Nile</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8883</playerid>
					<name>Domnic Joseph</name>
					<bowler-name>D Joseph</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Joseph</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>7</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>211</playerid>
					<name>Jean-Paul Duminy</name>
					<bowler-name>Duminy</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Duminy</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>14</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1629</playerid>
					<name>Angelo Mathews</name>
					<bowler-name>Mathews</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mathews</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>15</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1454</playerid>
					<name>Amit Mishra</name>
					<bowler-name>A Mishra</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mishra</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>32</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7906</playerid>
					<name>Shahbaz Nadeem</name>
					<bowler-name>S Nadeem</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Nadeem</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6667</playerid>
					<name>Imran Tahir</name>
					<bowler-name>Tahir</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Tahir</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>22</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2195</playerid>
					<name>Mayank Agarwal</name>
					<bowler-name>M Agarwal</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M Agarwal</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9428</playerid>
					<name>Shreyas Iyer</name>
					<bowler-name>S Iyer</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shreyas Iyer</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>69</playerid>
					<name>Yuvraj Singh</name>
					<bowler-name>Yuvraj</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Yuvraj</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1851</playerid>
					<name>Kedar Jadhav</name>
					<bowler-name>K Jadhav</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>K Jadhav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



