<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14631" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>37th Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Chennai</home>
		<away>Bangalore</away>
		<teamsabbr>CHN vs BLR</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>CHN</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>BLR</awayabbr>
		<homeId>58</homeId>
		<awayId>59</awayId>
		<venue>MA Chidambaram Stadium, Chennai</venue>
		<startdate>04 05 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>04 05 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Chennai</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Chennai won by 24 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Chennai</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>24</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Chettithody Shamsuddin</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Krishnaraj Srinath</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Johanes Cloete</Name>
			<Country>RSA</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Javagal Srinath</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>10:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150504141230</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>BLR</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>CHN</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>124</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>10</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>19.4</batteamovers>
		<status>Chennai won by 24 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>7910</playerid>
			<name>Yuzvendra Chahal</name>
			<batsman-name>Chahal</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Chahal</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>0</runs>
			<balls-faced>0</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
			<batsman>
				<name />
				<runs />
				<balls-faced />
				<fours />
				<sixes />
			</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>242</playerid>
			<name>Dwayne Bravo*</name>
			<bowler-name>DJ Bravo</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>3.4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>17</runs>
			<wickets>2</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>8181</playerid>
			<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
			<bowler-name>Mohit Sharma</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Mohit Sharma</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>29</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>149</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>1830</playerid>
<name>Iqbal Abdulla</name>
<player-runs>0</player-runs>
<player-balls>3</player-balls>
<runs>124</runs>
<wicket-nbr>10</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>242</bowlerid>
<bowlername>DJ Bravo</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>1</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>2</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[Wd 1 . . W 1 W <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 1 . . . . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 1 1 1 . W <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>W . . W ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/CHN_BLR_MAY04/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[So, that's all we have from this game. We will update you with the post-match comments after the second game. For now, you can switch tabs to follow the game between KOL and HYD.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, Suresh Raina constructed a fine knock and MS Dhoni cracked decisive blows in the slog overs to steer the hosts to a competitive total. Mitchell Starc was again impressive with the ball in hand. With this victory, CHN have wrested back the top spot from RAJ in the points table. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[CHN's bowlers executed their plans to near perfection to overcome the visitors. Ishwar Pandey and Ashish Nehra bowled well in tandem to take five wickets between them. Dwayne Bravo also made an impact by showing remarkable reflexes off his own bowling to run-out Virat Kohli. In fact, Kohli had threatened to take the game away from the grasp of the hosts. To make it worse for the home team, Ravindra Jadeja dropped a sitter to give Kohli a let-off. In the end, it didn't prove to be costly.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to I Abdulla, <b>out</b> Caught by Negi!! <b>CHN go top of the points table with this convincing win</b>. It was a slower full ball outside off, Abdulla goes for the big booming drive, gets a thick outside edge and backward point takes an easy catch bending forward. <b>I Abdulla c Negi b Dwayne Bravo 0(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dwayne Bravo to I Abdulla, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to I Abdulla, no run, on a length and outside off, Abdulla comes down the track and looks to go big, but fails to connect with the ball once again]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to I Abdulla, no run, slower delivery angling away outside off, Abdulla backs away a touch but fails to connect with the cut, the ball goes on the bounce to Dhoni]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuzvendra Chahal, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, <b>out</b> Caught by Negi!! BLR's ship is sinking in Chennai. A slower short ball from Bravo, Wiese goes for the pull but doesn't get enough power behind it, deep backward square leg runs to his left and takes another simple catch. Bravo does a little jig after that wicket. <b>Wiese c Negi b Dwayne Bravo 17(14) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Iqbal Abdulla, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Starc, <b>out</b> Caught by Raina!! Starc is on his way back to the pavilion. Mohit takes a wicket off the last ball of his spell. It was a full delivery on middle and leg, Starc clears his front leg and swings hard, he doesn't get it off the middle of the bat. The ball goes high in the air, Raina runs forward to his left from long-on and takes a good catch. It was another slower ball from Mohit and that's why Starc couldn't time it properly. <b>Starc c Raina b Mohit Sharma 1(7)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mohit Sharma to Starc, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Starc, no run, slower ball angled across off, Starc clears his front leg and swings hard at it, but he was through his shot by the time the ball arrived. Beaten for the lack of pace there]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Wiese, 1 run, full and outside off, Wiese drives it square of the wicket, but it will only be a single as there is protection in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Starc, 1 run, full and in the blockhole this time, Starc squeezes out the drive to long-off and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Wiese, 1 run, full delivery around off, Wiese drives it straight to long-off and the batsmen cross over]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Wiese, <b>FOUR</b>, Wiese gets a boundary first ball, it was short and it was wide, Wiese hangs back and cuts it to the deep backward point fence, the ball hurries across the turf and crashes into the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma [3.0-0-22-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>32 needed from 12 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Starc, no run, <b>fourth dot ball in a row!</b> An outstanding over from Bravo, it was shortish and angling away outside off, it was slower as well. Starc goes for the cut but ends up chopping it hard back on the surface, the ball rolls away back towards the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Starc, no run, Bravo bowls another off-cutter after dragging his length back slightly, Starc looks to cut, but was way too early into the shot. Misses it by a long way]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Starc, no run, bowls another off pace delivery outside off, Starc has a wild swing at it, but the ball goes way under his bat, great bowling at the death from Bravo]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Starc, no run, another off-cutter just outside off, Starc fails to connect with the drive and the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>32 needed from 16 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, 1 run, Wiese clears his front leg and wanted to go into the leg-side, but he fails to connect that well, was fooled by the lack of pace there. He drags it to short fine leg off the inside half of the bat and sets off for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, <b>FOUR</b>, drags his length back this time, Wiese rocks back and pulls it to the deep backward square leg fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Harshal Patel, <b>out</b> Caught by Dhoni!! Harshal is extremely disappointed with that decision. I don't think that was out. It was on a yorker length and just outside off, Harshal tries to squeeze it out and the ball shapes away past the outside edge. The sound was from the bat hitting the ground, but umpire raised his finger immediately after Dhoni appealed. A lucky break for CHN and BLR slip further. <b>Harshal Patel c Dhoni b Nehra 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nehra to Harshal Patel, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Wiese, 1 run, Nehra bowls this almost on a yorker length just outside off, Wiese toe-ends the drive in front of extra cover and the batsmen hurry across for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Sarfaraz Khan, <b>out</b> Caught by Dwayne Smith!! Another one bites the dust. BLR lose their sixth wicket with nelson on the board. It was a back of a length delivery on the pads, Sarfaraz backs away and plays the pick up shot, but doesn't get the desired distance. He hits it straight to deep backward square leg, who easily takes the catch. <b>Sarfaraz Khan c Dwayne Smith b Nehra 8(8) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nehra to Sarfaraz Khan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Sarfaraz Khan, no run, full and just outside off, Sarfaraz drives it straight to extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Sarfaraz Khan, no run, Sarfaraz backs away this time and Nehra follows him with a short one, all Sarfaraz could do was drop his wrists and leave it for the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Wiese, 1 run, full delivery angled across off, Wiese drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Wiese, <b>wide</b>, that's a harsh call from the umpire. Wiese goes right across his stumps and wanted to lap it past short fine, Nehra bowls it further wide outside off, Wiese can't connect and the umpire exercises his arms]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, 1 run, <b>almost a return catch for Bravo</b>! It was a low full toss outside off, Wiese drives it to the left of the bowler, who sticks his left hand out and gets a finger on it, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Sarfaraz Khan, 1 run, slightly shortish and wide outside off, Sarfaraz cuts hard but picks out backward point, the batsmen take a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Sarfaraz Khan, 2 runs, rare misfield from McCullum, it was full outside off, Sarfaraz drives with an open face towards backward point, McCullum dives to his left at backward point but doesn't stop it cleanly, the batsmen take an extra run on the misfield]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Sarfaraz Khan, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a good shot from the youngster, it was full and slightly wide outside off, Sarfaraz reaches out and slices the drive over backward point, third man was inside the circle too and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Sarfaraz Khan, no run, off-cutter from Bravo on the stumps, Sarfaraz backs away and wants to go inside-out over cover, but checks his shot at the last moment, hits it straight to extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Wiese, 1 run, full on off and middle, Wiese drives it to the left of the bowler, the batsmen take a single before the ball dribbles away to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Wiese, 1 run, fuller in length once again and on off and middle, Wiese leans forward and drives it down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Wiese, no run, gives this one more width outside off, Wiese cracks it straight to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Sarfaraz Khan, 1 run, what sort of shot is that? Sarfaraz goes down on his knee and looks to scoop it over the keeper's head after going across. He gets an outside edge and instead of going over Dhoni's head, the ball goes to the right of Dhoni, third man moves to his left and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Wiese, 1 run, to long on, angling in on middle and leg, Wiese pushes it down to long-on and gets off the mark with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Wiese, no run, fuller in length and just outside off, Wiese opens the face of the bat and picks out backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to D Karthik, <b>out</b> Caught by Dwayne Smith!! Ohh dear! BLR are losing the plot here. 2 wickets off consecutive balls for CHN. It was banged in short this time, Karthik went for the pull and he connected well too, but he hits it straight down the throat of deep square leg, who didn't have to move an inch to take that catch. <b>D Karthik c Dwayne Smith b Nehra 23(20) [4s-4]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Nehra to D Karthik, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashish Nehra [2.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sarfaraz Khan, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Kohli, <b>out</b> Kohli Run Out!! Kohli is gone, a big wicket for CHN. Brilliant work from Bravo. It was a yorker length delivery on off, Kohli squeezes it out to the right of the bowler, who leaps across to his right and fires a quick throw at the striker's end. Kohli was out of his crease and was surprised as the throw came in like a tracer bullet. He tried to get back in with a dive, but falls short of the crease. A great throw from Bravo, another good effort from a CHN player in the fielding department. <b>Kohli run out (Dwayne Bravo) 48(44) [4s-2 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dwayne Bravo to Kohli, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire called in for a run-out check. Kohli is the man in question and he is <b>OUT</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Kohli, 2 runs, Kohli once again takes a step forward and mistimes the drive off the inside half of the bat, the ball goes uppishly towards the mid-wicket region, where Mohit Sharma had been taken out of that position after the last ball, the batsmen take two before the ball is hunted down in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Kohli, no run, Kohli gives the charge to this fuller delivery on the stumps, drags it off the inside half of the bat to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to D Karthik, leg byes, 1 run, angling in on leg stump line, Karthik fails to work it away into the on-side, there was an lbw appeal as he was hit on the pad, but it was always going down leg. The batsmen sneak in a leg bye as the ball rolls away into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to D Karthik, no run, slower delivery on a fuller length this time around, Karthik squeezes out the drive to extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to Kohli, 1 run, slower ball on a length just outside off, Kohli drops it in front of cover and sets off, the fielder runs to his left and fires the throw at the non-striker's end, his bat got stuck and he would have been <b>OUT</b> had that been a direct-hit]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kohli, 1 run, Kohli goes across this time and eases this delivery angling in from outside off towards long-on, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kohli, 2 runs, slower full ball outside off, Kohli reads it well and drives it past cover, who dives to his left but fails to stop the ball, the batsmen take two before the fielder from sweeper cover runs to his right and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kohli, 2 runs, shortish and wide outside off, Kohli cuts it past backward point, good running ensures that the batsmen come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[Fine leg comes inside the circle and mid-off goes out]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kohli, no run, short of length delivery just outside off, Kohli looks to steer it down to third man after opening the face of the bat, but fails to connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhoni is up to the stumps for Kohli]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to D Karthik, 1 run, length delivery outside off, Karthik stays on the back foot and drives it to sweeper cover for another run]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kohli, 1 run, low full toss outside off, Kohli drives it to the right of cover, where McCullum dives and takes the pace off the ball, the ball rolls away to mid-off and the batsmen take a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma [2.0-0-15-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Kohli, 1 run, floated up on middle, Kohli drives it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Kohli, 2 runs, <b>50 of the partnership</b> comes up with this couple, it was on the stumps, Kohli pushes it through the covers with soft hands, the fielder in the deep runs to his right and stops the ball, he fires the throw at the non-striker's end, Karthik had to put in the dive to make his ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Kohli, 2 runs, that's a remarkable effort from du Plessis. It was tossed up outside off, Kohli goes for the loft but doesn't connect that well, du Plessis runs to his right from long-off, puts in the dive and manages to stop the ball with his right hand outstretched. The ball fell right in front of him and he did well there to save two runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Kohli, no run, on middle and leg line, Kohli flicks it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Kohli, 2 runs, low full toss on middle and leg, Kohli clips it through mid-wicket, the batsmen hurry back for the second and makes it in time as Bravo had to run to his right to field the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Kohli, <b>SIX</b>, floated up on off, Kohli gets under it and tonks it over the long-on fence. He didn't connect that well but he had enough on the ball to get it over Bravo in the deep]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, 1 run, driven to sweeper cover off the front foot, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, no run, <b>dropped!</b> Jadeja drops a sitter! It was tossed up on the stumps, Kohli comes forward and drives it uppishly off the inside half of the bat back towards the bowler, Jadeja moves across to his right, tries to take it with both hands but shells it down]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, no run, flatter and just outside off, Kohli goes for the cut, but there was not enough width on offer, he fails to connect and Dhoni collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, no run, tossed up on off, Kohli drives it towards cover, who dives to his left and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, no run, quicker on the stumps, Kohli bunts it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to D Karthik, 1 run, flighted delivery just outside off, Karthik leans forward, opens the face of the bat and pushes it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to D Karthik, 1 run, short and on the stumps, Karthik goes back and inside edges the pull onto the pad, the ball rolls square of the wicket, Dhoni runs across and keeps it to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to D Karthik, no run, flatter and just outside off, Karthik punches and picks out cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to D Karthik, <b>FOUR</b>, drifted onto leg-stump, Karthik goes down on one knee and sweeps it fine, beats short fine to his left and the man in the deep was very square]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Kohli, 1 run, half tracker outside off, Kohli slaps it wide of long-off, there was two but the duo don't take on Faf's arm]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Kohli, no run, slower and on the stumps, Kohli drops it to the on-side, Negi tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Kohli, no run, shorter and on the stumps, Kohli nudges it towards mid-wicket, Mohit dives to his right and saves a run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pawan Negi, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, 1 run, pushed through just outside off, Kohli punches to long-off, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, 2 runs, flatter and around off, Kohli knocks it with soft hands in front of long-off, called for two and sprints back to get it comfortably. The throw was to his end, but he had made it home]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, fabulous shot! It was all wristwork from Kohli. Floated up outside off, Kohli gets a good stride forward and drives, he rolled his wrists on top of the ball to get the placement right, beats sweeper cover with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to D Karthik, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Karthik opens the bat and eases it square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to D Karthik, no run, slower through the air, Karthik defends to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[Karthik moves away even as Jadeja delivers the ball, he was not ready]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Kohli, 1 run, flighted on middle and leg, Kohli drives inside out to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to D Karthik, <b>FOUR</b>, Karthik keeps getting the required boundary for the over. He is done it for the third successive over. Good length just outside off, Karthik opens the bat face and guides it fine, the ball races away from the chasing fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to D Karthik, no run, what a save from Baz. Short of a length, Karthik takes a step forward and punches it towards cover, Baz moves quickly to his right, dives full length and fields the ball. All this to save a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kohli, 1 run, back of the hand slower delivery, Kohli drags the drive to long-on, got it off the inner part]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to D Karthik, 1 run, on a length just outside off, Karthik steers with an angled bat to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kohli, 1 run, short of length on off, Kohli knocks it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kohli, no run, back of a length around off, Kohli looks to force it off the back foot, ekes out an inside edge onto the pad, the ball dribbles to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to D Karthik, no run, fullish and outside off, Karthik comes well forward and drives towards cover, excellent save by Baz diving to his left]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to D Karthik, <b>FOUR</b>, short delivery and it deserved the treatment. Karthik is quick to swivel across and pull behind square leg, Smith runs to his right and dives, gets a hand as well, but the ball wins the race]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to D Karthik, no run, full and angling in, Karthik flicks towards mid-wicket, Raina dives to his right and prevents the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Kohli, 1 run, short and outside off, Kohli cracks the cut to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to D Karthik, 1 run, off-speed delivery on off, Karthik waits for the ball to arrive and nudges to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Kohli, 1 run, almost another for Ishwar! Takes the pace off the ball, it was the off-cutter, Kohli is early into the drive, gets it off the inside half of the bat, the ball lobs up and just eludes the outstretched hand of Ishwar]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to D Karthik, <b>FOUR</b>, french cut! Mohit has his hands on his head. This one nips back in from a length, Karthik goes hard on the drive, the ball squirts off the inside edge, missed the stumps by a whisker and races away to the fine leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to D Karthik, no run, back of a length on off, Karthik mistimes the pull towards mid-wicket, shouts a loud "no" for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kohli, 3 runs, too straight from Mohit, Kohli leans forward and clips it handsomely in front of square on the leg-side, Ishwar runs to his left from deep square leg, dives and flicks it in, the ball was rolling back and he dived again to push it back]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to D Karthik, 1 run, good length on off, Karthik pushes it past the non-striker, the batsmen almost collided, but complete the single easily in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dinesh Karthik, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kohli, <b>out</b> Mandeep Run Out!! Mandeep goes for a diamond duck. The match-winner from the last game, goes without even facing a ball. There was never a single and Kohli called for it. Good length ball on off, Kohli flicks it straight to mid-wicket and takes off, Mandeep had no other choice than to respond to the captain's call, Negi fires a throw to MS, who whips the bails off in a flash. Mandeep dived, but in vain. <b>Mandeep run out (Negi/Dhoni) 0(0)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mohit Sharma to Kohli, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire called in for a run-out check. CHN think they have got Mandeep. He is well short of the crease. OUT!]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mohit Sharma to Kohli, no run, on a length just outside off, Kohli steers it to the left of backward point, Jaddu moves quickly and makes a sliding stop]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mandeep Singh, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Villiers, <b>out</b> Caught by du Plessis!! Would you believe it? Another full toss and another wicket for CHN and Ishwar. The bowler is delighted as he knows he has got a lucky wicket. ABD could have hit that anywhere, but drives in the air and hits it straight towards mid-off, Faf doesn't drop those. BLR in a bit of trouble now. <b>de Villiers c du Plessis b I Pandey 21(14) [4s-5]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[I Pandey to de Villiers, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Villiers, no run, change of pace outside off, de Villiers glides it to Raina, no run available]]></line><line><![CDATA[Raina is on the edge of the ring now]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, deftly done! Good length ball around off, de Villiers shuffles across and dabs it past the diving slip fielder, third man was inside the ring and he beat him as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Villiers, no run, back of a length around off, punched off the back foot to extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, put away with ease. It was a freebie from Ishwar, full toss on middle and leg, de Villiers picked his spot and flicks it between mid-wicket and mid-on. The ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhoni is up to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Kohli, 1 run, wicket-to-wicket stuff from Ishwar, Kohli nudges it wide of mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, smashed! Nehra was ducking for cover there. Length delivery on off and middle, de Villiers comes down the track and hammers it in the air straight back at the bowler, Nehra did well to get down in time, the ball was coming right at him at the rate of knots]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to de Villiers, no run, Nehra gets away with a short delivery, he can afford a smile now, not if that had reached the fence. de Villiers rocks back and nails the pull straight to mid-wicket, either side and that would have been four]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, 1 run, full and on the stumps, Kohli walks across and flicks to the right of mid-on, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to de Villiers, 1 run, good length ball on off, de Villiers pushes it to mid-off and takes off immediately]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to de Villiers, no run, on a length close to off, de Villiers gets behind the line and defends to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, 1 run, slight hesitation between the duo, but no harm done. Back of a length around off, Kohli taps it in front of backward point, starts and stops for the run, ABD just kept running. He would have made it easily even if Jaddu had collected the ball and fired at the striker's end]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Villiers, no run, very full delivery around off, de Villiers jams it to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhoni up to the stumps now]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, ABD gets his second boundary of the over. Ishwar sees the batsman dance down the wicket, takes the pace off the ball and drops it short, de Villiers adjusts well and heaves it over mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Villiers, no run, fuller and outside off, de Villiers plants his foot forward and drives to mid-off, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, off the mark in typical AB fashion. Short and plenty of width on offer, de Villiers goes back in the crease and cuts it over backward point, couple of bounces and into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to de Villiers, no run, back of a length just outside off, the ball just stops on ABD, he wanted to slash it through the off-side, hits him high on the bat and rolls to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>AB de Villiers, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Maddinson, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Cleaned up! Maddinson was struggling to get bat on ball and now he has missed out on a freebie. It was a full toss from Ishwar, Maddinson advances down the track, fails to connect with the drive, the off-stump gets uprooted. Perfect start for CHN. <b>Maddinson b I Pandey 4(7) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[I Pandey to Maddinson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, no run, fullish and angled outside off, Kohli reaches out and drives with an open face to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, no run, on a length around off, Kohli hangs back in the crease and knocks it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, <b>FOUR</b>, cracking shot! Nehra offers a bit of width on the full delivery, Kohli gets a good stride forward and drills the drive through cover, that was hit powerfully as the ball raced away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, 2 runs, hint of shape into the right-hander, Kohli gets inside the line and tucks it between mid-wicket and mid-on, easy two for the batsman]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, no run, short of length on off, Kohli shuffles across, blocks it solidly towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Kohli, no run, back of a length around off, Kohli gets nicely behind the line and defends to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashish Nehra, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Maddinson, no run, short and on the leg-stump, Maddinson is early into the pull, the ball hits him on the thigh pad and drops down on the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Maddinson, no run, on a length close to off, Maddinson drops it in front of cover-point, wanted the run but Kohli is not interested]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Maddinson, no run, Maddinson once more gives the charge, Ishwar drags the length back and gets it to straighten, Maddinson misses the heave and the ball goes past leg-stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Maddinson, <b>FOUR</b>, Ishwar errs in line, drifts it onto Maddinson's pads, glanced away fine. He got it very fine and the fielder in the deep had no chance of stopping that]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Maddinson, no run, Maddinson shimmies down the wicket, looks to pull the back of a length delivery, fails to connect. The ball sails over the sticks]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Maddinson, no run, huge shout for lbw, but umpire Srinath moves away. Good length delivery that nips back in a touch, Maddinson takes a step forward and misses the flick, is struck in front, but he was long way down the wicket. That is the only thing that saved him]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Maddinson and Kohli are at the crease. Maddinson is on strike. I Pandey will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. A new opening combination for BLR. Kohli walks out with Nic Maddinson.. It is a slow wicket and we all know how Dhoni marshall's his troops on such wickets. They defended 135 against KOL in the last game. Can they restrict the opposition one more time? We'll find out soon as Ishwar steams in..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashwin</b>: "The finger is alright. It is just stitching up together now, not yet got the stitches off so I think it's going to take a couple more days. The wicket is a bit slow. We batted well in the middle overs. If we can get a few wickets up front, I think this will be a good score. Negi can be handy in these conditions."]]></line><line><![CDATA[For BLR, Mitchell Starc was again on the money and took three wickets. He gave a fine exhibition of swing bowling in the first over and cleaned up Dwayne Smith. Harshal Patel too bowled a fine spell. On this deck, BLR's batsmen have a task on their hands as it won't be easy to chase down the target.  ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Suresh Raina assessed the pitch and conditions well to essay a well-measured fifty, and guide CHN to a competitive total. After Brendon McCullum was dismissed by David Wiese, Raina took up the mantle of steering the hosts to a good score. Raina gave a glimpse of his ability to handle the spinners with ease by chipping down the track to cart Yuzvendra Chahal for a six in the 13th over. MS Dhoni and Pawan Negi then smacked meaty blows in the slog overs.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Nehra, <b>out</b> Mohit Sharma Run Out!! Round the wicket, reverse swinging yorker just missing the off stump as Nehra fails to dig it out. Mohit Sharma tries to steal a bye but Karthik quickly takes the glove off and fires a direct-hit. Good finish for BLR. <b>Mohit Sharma run out (D Karthik) 0(0)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to Nehra, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashish Nehra, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Negi, <b>out</b> Bowled!! This is a fantastic yorker on the stumps and it's too good for Negi. Starc is pumped up after taking the wicket. Negi backs away but the yorker was very fast for him and it crashed into the base of middle and off. <b>Negi b Starc 13(7) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to Negi, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Negi, <b>wide</b>, Starc sprays this yorker down the leg-side, Negi tries to tickle it away but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohit Sharma, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Bravo, <b>out</b> Caught by Wiese!! Low full toss outside off stump, Bravo walks across the stumps and looks to drive inside out, hits it uppishly and extra-cover takes a good catch diving forward and to his left. <b>Dwayne Bravo c Wiese b Starc 2(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to Dwayne Bravo, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Bravo, 2 runs, Bravo exposes all the sticks and forces Starc to bowl at the stumps, it's a low full toss on the off stump, bit of reverse for Starc but Bravo manages to flick it through mid-wicket for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Bravo, no run, full angling away from the right-hander, Bravo fails to reach out and squeeze]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Negi, 1 run, backs away, Starc bowls a full ball on the off stump, Negi mistimes the drive to extra-cover, takes off for a run, the fielder has a shy and misses. A direct-hit would have been curtains]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc [3.0-1-20-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Negi, 1 run, full and outside off stump, Negi drives it down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Negi, <b>FOUR</b>, this is good batting from Negi. Short delivery on the off stump, it was the slower ball and it sat up nicely, Negi nails the pull shot to perfection and sends it to the deep square leg boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Negi, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Negi backs away, slashes and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Dhoni, <b>out</b> Caught by Starc!! Straight to long-off, but looks like Starc has hurt his finger while taking the catch. Straightaway he wants the physio to come out. This was full and in the slot, Dhoni went really hard at that, he couldn't get the elevation right and picked out the fielder to perfection. <b>Dhoni c Starc b Wiese 29(18) [4s-2 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Wiese to Dhoni, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Dhoni, no run, yorker length delivery outside off stump, Dhoni fails to keep it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Dhoni, 2 runs, slower delivery outside off stump, Dhoni slogs with one hand, yet it almost beat the deep mid-wicket fielder, who had to dive to save the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese [3.0-0-22-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Great over for CHN, 15 runs came off it.]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Negi, <b>SIX</b>, the camera has lost the ball, <b>that is a humongous hit</b>. Flighted delivery on the stumps, Negi steps out, gets to the pitch of the ball and muscles it over long-on. Gee! What a hit that was from Negi]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dhoni, 1 run, short and spinning away outside off stump, Dhoni mistimes the pull to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Negi, 1 run, waits for the ball to spin back in and turns it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dhoni, 1 run, shortish and spinning away outside off stump, pushed to deep extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Dhoni, <b>SIX</b>, this is an incredible hit from the skipper. Flighted delivery spinning away outside off stump, Dhoni leans forward and plays a flicky-slog and it goes a long way back over the deep mid-wicket boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pawan Negi, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Ravindra Jadeja, <b>out</b> Caught by Kohli!! Flighted delivery from Chahal, Jadeja looks to clear his front leg and tries to slog, doesn't get the timing right, Kohli almost misjudged it at deep mid-wicket, but he jumps and takes it with both hands above his head. <b>Ravindra Jadeja c Kohli b Chahal 3(4)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Chahal to Ravindra Jadeja, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuzvendra Chahal [3.0-0-21-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dhoni, <b>FOUR</b>, full delivery on the leg stump, Dhoni swings hard, gets it on the inside half of the bat, AB runs to his right from long-on, dives and tries to flick the ball, but the ball wins the race]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dhoni, 2 runs, full toss but Starc is very lucky to get away with it, Dhoni swings hard but mistimes it, long-off runs forward but fumbles the ball and CHN get an extra run. Kohli and Starc are not happy with Sarfaraz]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, full and on the stumps, Jadeja flicks it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dhoni, 1 run, good length delivery outside off stump, Dhoni cuts it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dhoni, no run, low full toss, tapped to the right of the bowler, who stops it with his right hand]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, good length delivery outside off stump, Jadeja looks to push away from the body, gets an inside edge onto pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Starc [2.0-1-11-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Dhoni, <b>FOUR</b>, comes down the track and looks to loft over long-on, gets a thick outside edge and that flies past the keeper. The fielder at short third man had no chance. Handy over for CHN, 12 runs came off it]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Dhoni, no run, on the leg stump, nudged into the on-side, Abdulla moves to his right and stops the run]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Ravindra Jadeja, 1 run, shortish and spinning back in, flicked away through square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Dhoni, 1 run, on the leg stump, worked away off the back foot to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Dhoni, <b>SIX</b>, that's a flat six from MSD. Flighted delivery just spinning away, Dhoni steps out and gets to the pitch of the ball, lofts it hard and it clears the long-off boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Dhoni, no run, tossed up on the stumps, Dhoni defends it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Iqbal Abdulla [2.0-0-22-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, <b>out</b> Lbw!! This is a big wicket and a big over for BLR. Two set batsmen removed in one over. Slower delivery on the stumps, Raina walks across and tries to help it fine behind square on the on-side, misses and is struck in front. End of a fine innings from Raina. Harshal Patel finishes off his spell with 4-0-19-2. Excellent bowling figures. <b>Raina lbw b Harshal Patel 52(46) [4s-5 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Harshal Patel to Raina, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, 2 runs, excellent diving save by Bisla. Full toss outside off stump, Raina slices it past backward point, Bisla runs to his left from third man and saves two]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dhoni, 1 run, fullish and on the off stump, Dhoni drives it down to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dhoni, no run, fullish and outside off stump, Dhoni pushes it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Dhoni, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Dhoni cuts well, but Sarfaraz makes a diving save at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>MS Dhoni, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to du Plessis, <b>out</b> Bowled!! A well deserved wicket for Harshal Patel. He has bowled well and has been rewarded now. Nothing but a short of length delivery outside off stump, du Plessis moves across the stumps and looks to force it off the back foot through the off-side, the ball takes a big inside edge and disturbs the sticks. <b>du Plessis b Harshal Patel 24(20) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Harshal Patel to du Plessis, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel [3.0-0-16-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to du Plessis, 1 run, slower delivery on the off stump, du Plessis flicks it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, 1 run, full and outside off stump, Raina drives it wide of long-off and that's brings up Raina's <b>25th IPL fifty</b>. This is his second fifty of the season and both have come against BLR]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, cheeky hit from Raina! With fine leg inside the ring, Raina walks across the sticks and scoops the length ball over the man at 45. He loses balance and tumbles after completing the shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to du Plessis, 1 run, slower delivery outside off stump, du Plessis dabs it third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, 1 run, fullish in length and also cramping the batsman for room as he comes down the track, Raina drives it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to du Plessis, 1 run, good length delivery angling in on the leg stump, du Plessis flicks it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese [2.0-0-13-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to du Plessis, 1 run, shortish from Chahal, punched to extra-cover for a quick single, the fielder has a shy at the bowler's end but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Raina, 1 run, excellent shot, but it's an exceptional piece of fielding from the BLR skipper. Flighted delivery on the stumps, Raina advances and lofts it straight back over the bowler's head, Raina thought it was a certain boundary and did not run, but Kohli swiftly moved to his left and saved three]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to du Plessis, 1 run, on the leg stump, du Plessis tucks it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Raina, 1 run, flatter delivery outside off stump, guided down to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Raina, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, driven back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Raina, <b>SIX</b>, in the airrrrr and just over the rope. Raina races down the track and slogs, the timing is not all that great, but he manages to spilt Mitchell Starc (long-on) and Nic Maddinson (deep mid-wicket) to perfection]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kohli to Raina, 1 run, full delivery on the leg stump, flicked wide of long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kohli to Raina, no run, Raina drives the full toss very well, but the ball knocks out the middle stump at the bowler's end, du Plessis was out of his crease for a while, but luckily for him, Kohli didn't get a hand on it]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kohli to du Plessis, 1 run, nice and full from Kohli, du Plessis works it away through mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kohli to Raina, 1 run, fullish and outside off strump, Raina drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kohli to du Plessis, 1 run, short of length delivery on the off stump, du Plessis works it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kohli to du Plessis, 2 runs, yorker length delivery on the off stump, du Plessis digs it out to short mid-wicket, Kohli dives to his right and stops the ball, fires a throw but it's wide and they get an overthrow. Kohli dived on the practice pitches, that must have hurt, looks like he has injured his knee, he gets some attention and is fine to continue now]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Virat Kohli, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to du Plessis, 1 run, googly on the off stump, du Plessis tucks it to short mid wicket and takes off, Raina responds, Karthik takes his glove off and quickly gets to the ball, has a shy at the striker's end but misses. A <b>direct hit would have been curtains for Raina</b> and he gave up as he was a long way away]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Raina, 1 run, steps out and drives the flighted delivery to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Raina, 2 runs, flighted delivery on the stumps, Raina advances and slogs, doesn't get hold of it and luckily for him it doesn't carry to fielder, who was running to his left from long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Raina, no run, low full toss, Chahal fires it wide outside off stump on seeing Raina advance, Raina reaches out and drives it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Raina, no run, tossed up outside off stump, Raina defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to du Plessis, 1 run, flatter delivery on the off stump, du Plessis pushes it to cover-point off the back foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuzvendra Chahal [1.0-0-6-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, no run, on a good length and well outside off, driven straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, no run, the slower off-cutter from Harshal, Raina looks to nudge it towards the on-side and is struck high on the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, <b>wide</b>, another slower bouncer from Harshal, but it's a bit too high, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, no run, on a good length and angling into Raina, tucked away straight to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, <b>wide</b>, the slower bouncer from Harshal, but it's well wide outside off, left alone, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to du Plessis, 1 run, yorker length delivery and on the stumps, du Plessis jams his bat down and nudges it to the left of mid-on, calls for a quick single and gets it with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, 1 run, width on offer from Harshal, slapped away in front of square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to du Plessis, 1 run, on a good length and angling into du Plessis, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Raina, no run, pushed through and on Raina's pads, tucked away straight to short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, excellent cricket from Raina, takes a step down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and goes back over the non-striker's head, long-off is wide and the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, this is turning out to be a costly over from Abdulla, tossed up wider outside off, Raina gets down on his knee and goes inside out over extra cover, a couple of bounces and over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to du Plessis, 1 run, slower and just outside off, dabbed away to the right of point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to du Plessis, <b>SIX</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, this was tossed up and just outside off, du Plessis made room outside leg, goes down on his knees, connects with it beautifully and sends it high and over mid-wicket for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to du Plessis, no run, Abdulla follows du Plessis as he backed away, defended towards mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Mandeep is off the park, looks like he dislocated his finger]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, 2 runs, full and wide from Harshal, Raina slices it behind square on the off-side. Mandeep dives and gets a hand onto it, looks like he has injured himself in the process. The fielder at third man gets across, the batsmen take two]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Raina leans forward and check drives it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, <b>wide</b>, DK is left surprised as the wide has been signalled, that deflected off the thigh pad, not sure how the umpire didn't spot it, Raina was looking to pull and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Raina presses across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, no run, yorker length delivery and just outside off, Raina looks to run it down towards third man and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Raina looks to drive and gets a thick edge towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[Harshal Patel changes to round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to du Plessis, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, punched square on the off-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel [1.0-0-7-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to du Plessis, 1 run, Abdulla floats one on the stumps, eased down towards long-on for a single. 6 singles and a wide from the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Raina, 1 run, flighted delivery and well outside off, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to du Plessis, 1 run, slower and wider outside off, punched square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Raina, 1 run, pushed through by Abdulla, worked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Raina, <b>wide</b>, Abdulla drifts wider outside off, called by the umpire, DK looks perplexed]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to du Plessis, 1 run, tossed up and on the stumps, eased down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Abdulla to Raina, 1 run, full toss from Abdulla, punched down towards long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Iqbal Abdulla, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, 1 run, tad fuller and just outside off, dabbed away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, 2 runs, short of a length and on Raina's pads, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, no run, on a good length and just outside off, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Faf du Plessis, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Brendon McCullum, <b>out</b> Caught by I Abdulla!! Wiese has his man! McCullum falls after looking promising for a while. This was the slower off-cutter from Wiese, McCullum swivelled across on the pull, doesn't get hold of the shot, Abdulla was positioned at deep mid-wicket, he looks into the sun and holds onto a fine catch. CHN have lost both openers now. <b>Brendon McCullum c I Abdulla b Wiese 20(15) [4s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Wiese to Brendon McCullum, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, that's nicely played by McCullum, short of a length and just outside off, McCullum waits on it, opens the face of the bat and runs it past short third man for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, 1 run, almost dragged on! Wiese shortened the length as Raina gave the charge, he gets an inside edge on the heave, the ball rolls away behind square on the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, 1 run, very full and wide outside off, driven towards AB at sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, the off-cutter from Patel, nudged away in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[The keeper is up to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, 1 run, Harshal slips in the slower ball, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, no run, back of a length and on Raina's hips, he gets inside the line and tucks it towards short fine leg, wants a single and is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Raina presses across and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, classy from Raina, this was full and wide outside off, Raina leans into the drive and caresses it through extra cover for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Brendon McCullum, no run, short of a length and well outside off, McCullum goes hard on the cut and mistimes it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Brendon McCullum, no run, on a good length and just outside off, McCullum prods forward and defends it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[The keeper is up to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, dabbed away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, no run, Wiese shortens his length and gets this one to angle across the left-hander, he looks to dab it towards third man and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, no run, on a good length and well outside off, Raina leans into the drive and finds AB at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Wiese to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, nice way to get going, length delivery and on the middle stump line, Raina gets forward and tonks it over mid-on, almost went all the way, one bounce and over the ropes]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>David Wiese, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, fast hands from McCullum, this wasn't a bad ball by any means, fractionally wider outside off, McCullum waits on it, opens the face of the bat and cracks it square behind point for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, Starc goes for the yorker and offers a full toss on McCullum's pads, whipped away through the gap between mid-wicket and mid-on. Harshal gives the chase but the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Brendon McCullum, 2 runs, McCullum gives the charge to Starc, on a good length and well outside off, McCullum goes over extra cover. The timing isn't spot on and the batsmen get a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Brendon McCullum, no run, on a good length and just outside off, McCullum leans forward and defends it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Brendon McCullum, no run, back of a length and on the off-stump line, McCullum gets behind the line and defends it towards cover point]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's Starc vs McCullum now]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Raina, 1 run, tad too straight from Starc, ends up drifting onto Raina's pads, clipped away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Brendon McCullum, no run, much better from Chahal, slowed down the pace and gets this one to dip into McCullum, he was early into the drive, nearly spoons it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, that's much better from McCullum, this was tossed up and wider outside off, McCullum gets a good stride forward and lofts it over cover, a couple of bounces and over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Brendon McCullum, no run, nice drift from Chahal, pitched on middle and shaped across McCullum, he prods forward and pushes it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Brendon McCullum, no run, slower and just outside off, McCullum lunges forward and defends it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Raina, 1 run, tossed up and just outside off, Raina presses forward and drives it down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, tossed up and just outside off, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuzvendra Chahal, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Knocked him over! Smith was all at sea against Starc and his off-stump has been knocked out now. This was full and shaped away very late, Smith was shuffling across on the whip, is done in by the late movement, ends up playing all around the ball, the off-stump is flattened. The umpires check for the no-ball, but Starc is fine on that count as well. Dream start for BLR and Starc. <b>Dwayne Smith b Starc 0(6)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc to Dwayne Smith, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, no run, teasing line from Starc, fuller length delivery and shaping away with the angle, Smith plays away from his body and the ball beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, no run, this is excellent bowling from Starc, keeps it full and on a yorker length, Smith jams at that and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, no run, very full and in that channel outside off, Smith is late on the drive, the bat hit the ground as the ball zipped through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, no run, on a good length and shaping away from outside off, Smith covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Starc to Dwayne Smith, no run, short of a length and shaping away from outside off, Smith throws his bat at that and misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Smith and Brendon McCullum are at the crease. Dwayne Smith is on strike. Starc will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starc with the new ball, one slip in place..]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's scorching hot at the Chepauk and Kohli leads the team huddle. We are set for another clash between McCullum and Starc. Who will return victorious?]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai</b> (Playing XI): Dwayne Smith, Brendon McCullum, Suresh Raina, Faf du Plessis, MS Dhoni(w/c), Dwayne Bravo, Ravindra Jadeja, Pawan Negi, Mohit Sharma, Ashish Nehra, Ishwar Pandey]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore</b> (Playing XI): Nic Maddinson, Virat Kohli(c), AB de Villiers, Mandeep Singh, Dinesh Karthik(w), Sarfaraz Khan, David Wiese, Harshal Patel, Mitchell Starc, Iqbal Abdulla, Yuzvendra Chahal]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kohli:</b> 'We wanted to bat first as well. We have been chasing well, but we would have preferred to bat first. It's hard to maintain momentum, the boys have responded well and we are looking to do well again. <b>Chris Gayle</b> has been rested, <b>Nic Maddinson</b> is in. <b>Iqbal Abdulla</b> replaces <b>Varun Aaron</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhoni:</b> 'We will bat first. Looks like a good wicket, hot conditions, but we are used to it. It's difficult to predict the wicket. We do not want to get Ashwin back quickly. He will not play today. One change for us, <b>Ishwar Pandey</b> replaces <b>Ronit More</b>.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>toss</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-head:</b> CHN have held the upper hand when the two teams have met. They have won 10 out of the 18 games, while BLR have won 7 and the other being a no-result. So, can the men in red and gold register their 8th win? Or will it again be the yellow brigade? Stay tuned to find out. Toss and teams coming up in a few minutes....]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Team News:</b> BLR have not lost a game in their previous 4 matches. They haven't tinkered much with their team composition. So, we can expect them to play with the same side. Meanwhile, CHN lost Ashwin due to a finger injury, but he might be back for this crucial encounter. He might replace either Ravindra Jadeja or Mohit Sharma, the former didn't bowl a single over in the last game and the latter went for plenty.]]></line><line><![CDATA[On the other hand, CHN always remain the most consistent side in the IPL. They have played 9 games, won 6 and lost 3, with two of those losses coming in the previous two matches. The batting looks strong with Brendon McCullum and Dwayne Smith at the top, providing blazing starts. Faf, Raina, Dhoni and Bravo all have played a substantial innings at one point or the another. The only concern is their bowling, Nehra has been their best bowler and Bravo has been exceptional at the death, but apart from them the bowling looks mediocre.]]></line><line><![CDATA[BLR started their campaign with a win over defending champions KOL, but lost the next three games to HYD, MUM and CHN - all at home. However, since then they have played 4 games and are yet to lose one. Winning 3 and the other being abandoned due to rain. The arrival of Mitchell Starc has provided BLR some spark, which they were missing at the start of the season. Virat Kohli and ABD have done bulk of the scoring, with the likes of Sarfaraz Khan, Mandeep Singh and David Wiese chipping in. They now look a formidable side, who have a balanced look.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>14:45 Local Time, 09:15 GMT, 14:45 IST:</b> It is the South Indian derby that will kick-start proceedings on double-header Monday. It is Chennai taking on Bangalore at the Chepauk. This is the second time these two sides are facing each other this season. In the first encounter, CHN came out on top, thanks to Raina's fifty and Nehra's 4-wicket haul. Can BLR pull one back against their arch-rivals? Before we go further let us have a glance as to how these teams have shaped up so far...]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview</b><br/><br/>Bangalore are experiencing a resurgence in their fortunes after a poor start in the 2015 IPL. They finally won at home and have been in good form in away matches this season. They are in third position currently and will be aiming to topple Chennai in their Chepauk fortress. However, all that is easier said than done.<br/><br/>The MA Chidambaram stadium has not treated BLR well. They last won in Chepauk during the first edition of the IPL in 2008 and since then, they have tasted only defeat. The last two games at the venue have been heart-breaking for BLR. In 2012, they could not defend 205 as CHN snatched victory from the jaws of defeat by smashing 43 runs in the last two overs, and in 2013, an inspired knock from Ravindra Jadeja and a last ball no-ball from RP Singh gave CHN an unlikely victory.<br/><br/>This time, BLR will be looking to change the script. CHN are low on confidence after their loss against Hyderabad. In each of their three losses, CHN have failed to deliver in all departments but have demonstrated a remarkable ability to bounce back. They have won all their four games at home this season and although they are still at the top, CHN will be aware that a loss to BLR will rob them of serious momentum.<br/><br/>Venue: MA Chidambaram Stadium, Chennai<br/><br/>Date: May 4, 2015<br/><br/>Time: 16:00 IST<br/><br/>Weather: Hot conditions with a high of 36 degrees<br/><br/><b>Team news</b><br/><br/><b>Chennai</b><br/><br/>R Ashwin, who missed two games due to a finger injury, could come back in this important clash. The bowlers had a very bad day against Hyderabad, with Mohit Sharma in particular ending up with figures of 4-0-58-0. Ronit More, who also failed to impress in his first two games, could warm the bench and Ishwar Pandey might come back.<br/><br/>Probable XI<br/><br/>1. Dwayne Smith, 2 Brendon McCullum, 3 Suresh Raina, 4 Faf du Plessis, 5 MS Dhoni (c and wk), 6 Dwayne Bravo, 7 Ravindra Jadeja, 8 R Ashwin/Pawan Negi, 9 Mohit Sharma, 10 Ishwar Pandey/Ronit More, 11 Ashish Nehra<br/><br/><b>Bangalore</b><br/><br/>The team is peaking at the right time. The young guns in the batting department are doing very well. Sarfaraz Khan, the 17-year-old, made a name for himself thanks to his aggressive knock against Rajasthan while Mandeep Singh's blitz against Kolkata helped BLR achieve their first win at home this season. Combined with the destruction of Chris Gayle, Virat Kohli and AB de Villiers, the batting looks strong while the bowling looks solid. With momentum in their side, they might not change a winning combination.<br/><br/>Probable XI<br/><br/>1. Chris Gayle, 2 Virat Kohli (c), 3 AB de Villiers, 4 Mandeep Singh, 5 Dinesh Karthik (wk), 6 Sarfaraz Khan, 7 David Wiese, 8 Harshal Patel, 9 Mitchell Starc, 10 Varun Aaron, 11 Yuzvendra Chahal<br/><br/><b>Stats</b><br/><br/>Chris Gayle needs 52 runs to become the first overseas player to score 3,000 runs in the IPL.<br/>In five matches between CHN and BLR in Chepauk, CHN have won four times while BLR have won just once.<br/><br/><b>Quotes</b><br/><br/>"All the accomplished batsmen I have spoken to tell me one thing keep the game simple in your head." - Bangalore's Mandeep Singh after hismatch-winning knock against Kolkata.<br/><br/>"If the bowler is not bowling to the field, then it does not look good." - Chennai skipper MS Dhoni laments the poor bowling performance after his team's loss to Hyderabad]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai</b> (From): Dwayne Smith, Brendon McCullum, Suresh Raina, Faf du Plessis, MS Dhoni(c/w), Dwayne Bravo, Ravindra Jadeja, Pawan Negi, Ravichandran Ashwin, Ashish Nehra, Mohit Sharma, Ronit More, Baba Aparajith, Ishwar Pandey, Matt Henry, Mithun Manhas, Samuel Badree, Michael Hussey, Rahul Sharma, Kyle Abbott, Ankush Bains, Irfan Pathan, Pratyush Singh, Andrew Tye, Eklavya Dwivedi]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore</b> (From): Virat Kohli(c), Chris Gayle, AB de Villiers, Mandeep Singh, Dinesh Karthik(w), Sarfaraz Khan, David Wiese, Mitchell Starc, Harshal Patel, Varun Aaron, Yuzvendra Chahal, Nic Maddinson, Ashok Dinda, Vijay Zol, Abu Nechim, Sandeep Warrier, Yogesh Takawale, Rilee Rossouw, Iqbal Abdulla, Manvinder Bisla, S Badrinath, Darren Sammy, Sean Abbott, Sreenath Aravind, Jalaj Saxena, Shishir Bhavane]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>148</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>9</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Chennai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Smith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>M Starc</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7710</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Brendon McCullum</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>20</runs>
					<balls>15</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>D Wiese</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8589</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Iqbal Abdulla</fielder>
						<fielderId>1830</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Raina</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>52</runs>
					<balls>46</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Harshal Patel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8175</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7825</playerid>
					<name>Faf du Plessis</name>
					<batsman-name>du Plessis</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>du Plessis</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>24</runs>
					<balls>20</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Harshal Patel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8175</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhoni</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>29</runs>
					<balls>18</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>D Wiese</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8589</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mitchell Starc</fielder>
						<fielderId>7710</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<batsman-name>R Jadeja</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Chahal</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7910</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Virat Kohli</fielder>
						<fielderId>1413</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8281</playerid>
					<name>Pawan Negi</name>
					<batsman-name>Negi</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Negi</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>13</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>M Starc</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7710</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>242</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
					<batsman-name>DJ Bravo</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Starc</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7710</bowlerId>
						<fielder>David Wiese</fielder>
						<fielderId>8589</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Mohit Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mohit Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dinesh Karthik</fielder>
						<fielderId>145</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>269</playerid>
					<name>Ashish Nehra</name>
					<batsman-name>Nehra</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nehra</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8665</playerid>
					<name>Ishwar Pandey</name>
					<batsman-name>I Pandey</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>I Pandey</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>255</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>0</runs>
				<overs>0.6</overs>
				<batsman>Dwayne Smith</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>201</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>34</runs>
				<overs>5.3</overs>
				<batsman>Brendon McCullum</batsman>
				<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7825</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>98</runs>
				<overs>14.1</overs>
				<batsman>Faf du Plessis</batsman>
				<batsman-name>du Plessis</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>413</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>101</runs>
				<overs>14.6</overs>
				<batsman>Suresh Raina</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>587</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>122</runs>
				<overs>17.1</overs>
				<batsman>Ravindra Jadeja</batsman>
				<batsman-name>R Jadeja</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>265</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>139</runs>
				<overs>18.3</overs>
				<batsman>MS Dhoni</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>242</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>147</runs>
				<overs>19.4</overs>
				<batsman>Dwayne Bravo</batsman>
				<batsman-name>DJ Bravo</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8281</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>148</runs>
				<overs>19.5</overs>
				<batsman>Pawan Negi</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Negi</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8181</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>148</runs>
				<overs>20</overs>
				<batsman>Mohit Sharma</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mohit Sharma</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>5</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>5</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Bangalore">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7710</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
					<bowler-name>M Starc</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Starc</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>24</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7910</playerid>
					<name>Yuzvendra Chahal</name>
					<bowler-name>Chahal</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chahal</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8589</playerid>
					<name>David Wiese</name>
					<bowler-name>D Wiese</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Wiese</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>29</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8175</playerid>
					<name>Harshal Patel</name>
					<bowler-name>Harshal Patel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Harshal Patel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>19</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1830</playerid>
					<name>Iqbal Abdulla</name>
					<bowler-name>I Abdulla</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>I Abdulla</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>34</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<bowler-name>Kohli</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Kohli</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>6</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6261</playerid>
					<name>Nic Maddinson</name>
					<bowler-name>N Maddinson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Maddinson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>370</playerid>
					<name>AB de Villiers</name>
					<bowler-name>de Villiers</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>de Villiers</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6319</playerid>
					<name>Mandeep Singh</name>
					<bowler-name>Mandeep</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mandeep</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>145</playerid>
					<name>Dinesh Karthik</name>
					<bowler-name>D Karthik</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>D Karthik</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9429</playerid>
					<name>Sarfaraz Khan</name>
					<bowler-name>Sarfaraz Khan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sarfaraz Khan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>124</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>10</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>19.4</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Bangalore">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>6261</playerid>
					<name>Nic Maddinson</name>
					<batsman-name>N Maddinson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Maddinson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>I Pandey</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8665</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Kohli</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>48</runs>
					<balls>44</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dwayne Bravo</fielder>
						<fielderId>242</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>370</playerid>
					<name>AB de Villiers</name>
					<batsman-name>de Villiers</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>de Villiers</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>21</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>I Pandey</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8665</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Faf du Plessis</fielder>
						<fielderId>7825</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6319</playerid>
					<name>Mandeep Singh</name>
					<batsman-name>Mandeep</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mandeep</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Pawan Negi</fielder>
						<fielderId>8281</fielderId>
						<fielder2>MS Dhoni</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>265</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>145</playerid>
					<name>Dinesh Karthik</name>
					<batsman-name>D Karthik</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>D Karthik</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>23</runs>
					<balls>20</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Nehra</bowler>
					<bowlerId>269</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dwayne Smith</fielder>
						<fielderId>255</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9429</playerid>
					<name>Sarfaraz Khan</name>
					<batsman-name>Sarfaraz Khan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sarfaraz Khan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>8</runs>
					<balls>8</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Nehra</bowler>
					<bowlerId>269</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dwayne Smith</fielder>
						<fielderId>255</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8589</playerid>
					<name>David Wiese</name>
					<batsman-name>D Wiese</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Wiese</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>17</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>DJ Bravo</bowler>
					<bowlerId>242</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Pawan Negi</fielder>
						<fielderId>8281</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8175</playerid>
					<name>Harshal Patel</name>
					<batsman-name>Harshal Patel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Harshal Patel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Nehra</bowler>
					<bowlerId>269</bowlerId>
						<fielder>MS Dhoni</fielder>
						<fielderId>265</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7710</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Starc</name>
					<batsman-name>M Starc</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Starc</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mohit Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8181</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Suresh Raina</fielder>
						<fielderId>413</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1830</playerid>
					<name>Iqbal Abdulla</name>
					<batsman-name>I Abdulla</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>I Abdulla</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>DJ Bravo</bowler>
					<bowlerId>242</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Pawan Negi</fielder>
						<fielderId>8281</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7910</playerid>
					<name>Yuzvendra Chahal</name>
					<batsman-name>Chahal</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chahal</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6261</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>10</runs>
				<overs>2.1</overs>
				<batsman>Nic Maddinson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>N Maddinson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>370</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>34</runs>
				<overs>4.6</overs>
				<batsman>AB de Villiers</batsman>
				<batsman-name>de Villiers</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6319</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>34</runs>
				<overs>5.2</overs>
				<batsman>Mandeep Singh</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mandeep</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1413</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>97</runs>
				<overs>14</overs>
				<batsman>Virat Kohli</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>145</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>97</runs>
				<overs>14.1</overs>
				<batsman>Dinesh Karthik</batsman>
				<batsman-name>D Karthik</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9429</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>111</runs>
				<overs>16.4</overs>
				<batsman>Sarfaraz Khan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Sarfaraz Khan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8175</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>112</runs>
				<overs>16.6</overs>
				<batsman>Harshal Patel</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Harshal Patel</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7710</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>124</runs>
				<overs>18.6</overs>
				<batsman>Mitchell Starc</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Starc</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8589</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>124</runs>
				<overs>19.1</overs>
				<batsman>David Wiese</batsman>
				<batsman-name>D Wiese</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1830</playerid>
				<nbr>10</nbr>
				<runs>124</runs>
				<overs>19.4</overs>
				<batsman>Iqbal Abdulla</batsman>
				<batsman-name>I Abdulla</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>1</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>2</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Chennai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8665</playerid>
					<name>Ishwar Pandey</name>
					<bowler-name>I Pandey</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>I Pandey</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>28</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>269</playerid>
					<name>Ashish Nehra</name>
					<bowler-name>Nehra</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nehra</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>19</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8181</playerid>
					<name>Mohit Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Mohit Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mohit Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>29</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<bowler-name>R Jadeja</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>11</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8281</playerid>
					<name>Pawan Negi</name>
					<bowler-name>Negi</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Negi</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>19</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>242</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
					<bowler-name>DJ Bravo</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3.4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>17</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<bowler-name>Dwayne Smith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Smith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<bowler-name>B McCullum</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Brendon McCullum</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<bowler-name>Raina</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Raina</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7825</playerid>
					<name>Faf du Plessis</name>
					<bowler-name>du Plessis</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>du Plessis</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhoni</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhoni</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



