<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14598" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>5th Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Kolkata</home>
		<away>Bangalore</away>
		<teamsabbr>KOL vs BLR</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>KOL</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>BLR</awayabbr>
		<homeId>63</homeId>
		<awayId>59</awayId>
		<venue>Eden Gardens, Kolkata</venue>
		<startdate>11 04 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>11 04 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Bangalore</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Bangalore won by 3 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Bangalore</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>3</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>S Ravi</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Chettithody Shamsuddin</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Pashchim Pathak</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Javagal Srinath</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>14:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150411180047</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>BLR</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>KOL</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>179</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>7</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>19</batteamovers>
		<status>Bangalore won by 3 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>8175</playerid>
			<name>Harshal Patel*</name>
			<batsman-name>Harshal Patel</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Harshal Patel</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>9</runs>
			<balls-faced>4</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>1</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>6323</playerid>
			<name>Abu Nechim</name>
			<batsman-name>Abu Nechim</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Abu Nechim</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>5</runs>
			<balls-faced>2</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>2276</playerid>
			<name>Sunil Narine*</name>
			<bowler-name>Narine</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Narine</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>26</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>608</playerid>
			<name>Morne Morkel</name>
			<bowler-name>M Morkel</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>M Morkel</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>35</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>178</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>247</playerid>
<name>Chris Gayle</name>
<player-runs>96</player-runs>
<player-balls>56</player-balls>
<runs>171</runs>
<wicket-nbr>7</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>0</bowlerid>
<bowlername></bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>1</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>7</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>8</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[4 6 1 . 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>W1 Wd . . 6 6 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 4 2 1 . 6 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>6 W1 1 2 1 4 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/KOL_BLR_APR11/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[<b>Gambhir:</b> 'If you drop someone like Chris (Gayle), he will make you pay. He was also lucky on a number of occasions. Sometimes he mishit the ball and it didn't go into someone's hands. If you keep dropping catches, someone like Chris will hurt you. The bowlers tried their best, but we still lost. It doesn't matter that how many runs I score or the team scores. At the end of the day, the team points matter and not individual scores.']]></line><line><![CDATA[It was in the 17th over when he changed the complexion of the game by hammering Shakib for two sixes. He followed it up by taking the trump card in the opposition ranks, Narine to the cleaners. It took a brilliant piece of fielding from Manish Pandey on the boundary line to run out Gayle. However, by then, the match had slipped out of Kolkata's grasp. Earlier, Bangalore's poor fielding meant that Kolkata amassed a good score. Gautam Gambhir anchored the innings and Andre Russell landed mighty blows to give them genuine hopes of winning the game.  ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chris Gayle's whirlwind knock lifted Bangalore to a thrilling victory. Despite wickets falling at regular intervals, Gayle stood tall amidst the ruins to steer them home. Gayle started his innings on a cautious note, especially while facing up to Sunil Narine. However, once Gayle got set, he unfurled a series of powerful shots. He took a heavy toll of some poor bowling by Kishan Cariappa and Yusuf Pathan. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Gambhir is a disappointed man, but one can see the contrasting emotions on show as BLR players, including Gayle, Sammy and Kohli come out on the field. Players exchange hugs all around and Gayle is a delighted man. Kohli was extremely happy after the win as he jumped out of the dug out, Sammy chased him and clings onto Kohli's shoulders. <b>With this win, BLR also end KOL's 10-match winning run in IPL</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Abu Nechim, <b>FOUR</b>, that's it! <b>BLR win their first game of the season!</b> Coming back to the ball, it was short and wide outside off, Nechim goes hard at it, gets an outside edge that flies down to the third man fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Harshal Patel, 1 run, short of length delivery on the stumps, Patel tucks it away to short fine leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Harshal Patel, 2 runs, back of a length delivery just outside off, Patel guides it down towards third man, Chawla runs to his right from third man, picks the ball and fires in the throw at the striker's end. Patel was charging across for the second and even though the throw was right on the money, he makes his ground with a dive]]></line><line><![CDATA[Is there another run-out? Patel is the man in question. It is touch and go. This will be a difficult one for the umpire. Looks like it will be Not Out and it is 'not out'.]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Abu Nechim, 1 run, gives this one more width outside off, Nechim goes hard at it and chops it towards point, the batsmen charge through for a single and Gambhir doesn't throw it as there was no one backing up]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Abu Nechim, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Gayle, <b>out</b> Gayle Run Out!! 1 run completed. Gayle thought that he will get six for that, but Pandey at deep mid-wicket pulled off a stunning piece of fielding. It was another length ball from Morkel, Gayle heaved across the line and the ball was going over Pandey at deep mid-wicket, but Pandey leaps up high in the air, takes the catch and throws the ball back in play as he was falling over the ropes. He then was hobbling a little, but had the presence of mind to quickly pick up the ball and fire in the throw at the striker's end. Gayle wanted to come back for the second and was struggling to make his ground despite the dive. It was an accurate throw and Uthappa takes the bails off in a flash. Drama at the Eden Gardens continues. <b>Gayle run out (M Pandey/Uthappa) 96(56) [4s-7 6s-7]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[M Morkel to Gayle, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Has Gayle been run-out here? The third umpire has been called in and yes, he is short. Ohh dear! Is there a twist in the tale here? Can KOL win from here? Let's see]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Gayle, <b>SIX</b>, <b>take that Morkel!</b> It was a length ball and right in the slot for Gayle, who clears his front leg and smashes it over the long-on fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Morne Morkel [3.0-0-20-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Harshal Patel, <b>SIX</b>, looks like the talk between Gayle and Patel has worked wonders for them! Narine goes for a six off his last ball of the spell. It was right in the slot just outside off, Patel goes for the loft and goes downtown, clears the boundary with ease. BLR are easing towards a victory here]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Harshal Patel, no run, touch flatter and just outside off, Patel punches it straight to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[Gayle has a long chat with his partner in the middle of the pitch]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Gayle, 1 run, drifting on the pads once again, Gayle clips it through mid-wicket and this time he has to be content with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Gayle, 2 runs, goes down on one knee and laps this delivery on leg behind square on the on-side, good running ensures they come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Gayle, <b>FOUR</b>, another boundary for Gayle! This is just brilliant batting from him, one hand came off and it was from the bottom of the bat, but it still went for the boundary. It was tossed up on the stumps, Gayle slog swept it to deep mid-wicket for a four]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Gayle, <b>FOUR</b>, Gayle is on fire here and this time it's Narine, who bears the brunt. It was dragged slightly short from Narine and Gayle just pulls it to the deep mid-wicket fence. The fielder at deep mid-wicket ran to his right, but couldn't stop it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sunil Narine [3.0-0-9-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Gayle, 1 run, mistimes the loft off a tossed up delivery and just about survives. Morkel was charging in from long-off, he fails to get there in time and the batsmen take a single, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Gayle, <b>SIX</b>, high full toss from Shakib, Gayle slgs across the line and deposits over the deep mid-wicket fence, this one is massive as well as it went <b>101 metres into the crowd</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Gayle, <b>SIX</b>, he was not taking the single for this, it's a huge hit, <b>107 metres</b>, the biggest this season. Gayle went down on one knee and slog sweeps this flighted delivery over the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Gayle, no run, tossed up on middle stump line, Gayle drills it to long-on and turns down the single once again]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Gayle, no run, floated up on the stumps, Gayle drills it to mid-wicket and doesn't take the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Gayle, <b>wide</b>, that's a very wide delivery down leg, Uthappa did well to get his hand on it and stops it, Gayle doesn't go for the bye either]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Gayle, <b>out</b> Abbott Run Out!! 1 run completed. Abbott is out here, trying to sneak in a second run there. It was full and on the stumps, Gayle drives it to wide long-off and called Abbott back for the second. Morkel was quick to run across to his right, picks the ball up and fires the throw at the bowler's end. Abbott was struggling to make his ground and Shakib catches the throw and disturbs the stumps, with Abbott inches short of his ground. <b>Abbott run out (M Morkel/Shakib) 1(4)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Shakib to Gayle, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Gayle, 1 run, <b>has Morkel dropped the game here?</b> It was bowled flatter from Pathan and Gayle went for the big slog sweep through the on-side. Gayle went through with it after going across and it went straight into the hands of Morkel was running to his right from deep square leg. However, as quickly the ball went in his hands, it came out that quickly as Morkel fell over with the ball not in his hands. A chance goes begging for KOL and will it cost them the game? Only time will tell]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Abbott, 1 run, another poor ball from Pathan but he gets away with it this time, it was very short from Pathan, Abbott pulls it to the fielder at deep mid-wicket, the ball went on the bounce to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Abbott, no run, quicker and on the stumps, Abbott pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Gayle, 1 run, Gayle goes back in the crease and works it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Gayle, <b>SIX</b>, overcompensates the length as he bowls this one very full, Gayle gets under it and lofts it straight down the ground for another maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Gayle, <b>FOUR</b>, you can't bowl there when you start your new spell. This was bowled well short from Pathan, Gayle rocks back and pulls it to the deep mid-wicket fence for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yusuf Pathan [3.0-0-27-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Abbott, no run, gives this one more flight around off, Abbott was pushing at it off the front foot, gets an outside edge that rolls away towards point, where Chawla picks the ball and applauds Shakib's bowling effort in this over]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Abbott, no run, quicker one on the stumps, Abbott pushes it to the left of the bowler, Shakib runs across to his left and stops it]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sean Abbott, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sammy, <b>out</b> Stumped!! That's beautifully bowled from Shakib. He has done brilliantly there. Shakib gave this one more air as Sammy came down the track, the ball spins away as Sammy went through the shot, he misses and Uthappa disturbs the stumps in no time. The square leg umpire went upstairs, but that was the easiest decision for the TV umpire as Sammy was miles out of his crease. <b>Sammy st Uthappa b Shakib 7(9)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shakib to Sammy, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Stumped!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Gayle, 1 run, quicker one outside off, Gayle punches it down to long-off to get off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sammy, 1 run, touch shorter and well outside off, Sammy hangs back and cuts it square of the wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sammy, no run, floated up on the stumps, Sammy defends off the back foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Sammy, 1 run, was that a <b>run-out chance?</b> It was turning it towards Sammy, who helps it towards short fine and sets off, Gayle was struggling to make his ground at the striker's end and Uthappa might have taken the bails off without the ball in his mitts when the throw arrived. In fact, Gayle would have been home as replays showed]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Gayle, 1 run, slower through the air and on middle stump line, Gayle pushes at it, gets an outside edge that rolls away past slip towards short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Gayle, no run, another beauty to Gayle! It was turning away as Gayle was looking to push forward, beats the outside edge once again]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Sammy, 1 run, bowls the doosra this time, Sammy was pushing at it off the back foot, hits it uppishly but in the gap, gets a single as the ball rolls away to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Gayle, 1 run, Gayle brings up his <b>fifty</b> with this single, it was dropped short from Narine, Gayle rocks back and pulls it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Gayle, no run, good off spinner from Narine, Gayle prods forward and looks to defend, the ball turns away past the outside edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sunil Narine [2.0-0-5-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Gayle, 1 run, Gayle clears his front leg to another flatter one from Chawla, he pulls it to deep square leg, couldn't quite time it but it's good enough for a single, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Sammy, 1 run, drags it short and little wide outside off again, Sammy stays back and cuts it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Gayle, 1 run, flatter and slightly wide outside off, Gayle mistimes the punch down to long-off, one hand came off the bat as well when he was trying to play the shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Gayle, <b>SIX</b>, this is a real long hop from Chawla, Gayle had all the time in the world to go deep in the crease, he muscles the pull over the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Gayle, no run, googly on the stumps, Gayle defends it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Sammy, 1 run, starts off with a shortish delivery, Sammy rocks back and pulls it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Piyush Chawla, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for some leg-spin]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Gayle, <b>SIX</b>, poor ball to finish the over, it also brings up the team 100 for BLR. It was nothing but a low full toss and with the kind of power Gayle has, he just helps it straight down the ground for a maximum. Effortless hit from the big man]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Gayle, no run, slow turner on off, Gayle defends with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Sammy, 1 run, quicker and flatter from Pathan, Sammy stays back and punches it past a diving mid-wicket, can only take the single as there is protection in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Gayle, 1 run, pushed through on middle stump line, Gayle stays back and tucks it away behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Sammy, 1 run, flatter and just outside off, Sammy hangs back and punches it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Gayle, 1 run, drags his length back and Gayle rocks back and pulls, luckily for Gayle, the ball just falls short of a diving Morkel at deep square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Darren Sammy, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kishan Cariappa to de Villiers, <b>out</b> Stumped!! Cariappa has the final laugh in this over. His first wicket in the IPL comes after outfoxing de Villiers, de Villiers of all people. What a comeback from the youngster after being clobbered for 2 fours and a six in this over. Coming to the ball, it was the quicker and flatter one outside off, de Villiers came dancing down the track and wanted to cut it hard, he misses and Uthappa takes the bails off in a flash. The crowd roars and Cariappa is also pumped after taking that wicket. <b>de Villiers st Uthappa b Kishan Cariappa 28(13) [4s-3 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Kishan Cariappa to de Villiers, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Stumped!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kishan Cariappa to de Villiers, <b>SIX</b>, ohh dear! <b>Cariappa is being taken to the cleaners here!</b> It was floated up on the stumps, de Villiers clears his front leg and hammers it over the long-on fence for a six]]></line><line><![CDATA[Cariappa pulls away in his delivery stride]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kishan Cariappa to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, de Villiers is going nuts out there, gets another boundary as he lofts a tossed up delivery inside-out over extra cover once again, Russell from sweeper ran to his right, put his right hand out too, but couldn't stop it]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kishan Cariappa to Gayle, 1 run, drifting on the pads, Gayle clips it through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kishan Cariappa to de Villiers, 1 run, de Villiers was on the charge again, but this time he mistimes the drive to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kishan Cariappa to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, Cariappa comes back and de Villiers dispatches him for four first ball, he comes down the track and goes inside-out over a leaping extra-cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kishan Cariappa [1.0-0-12-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to de Villiers, 1 run, dances down the track and takes the flighted delivery on the full, swung away to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to de Villiers, <b>SIX</b>, top shot! de Villiers steps out, covers for the spin back into him, gets to the pitch of the ball as well and muscles it high over deep mid-wicket for a <b>104-metre</b> hit, the longest of the season]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Gayle, 1 run, flatter from round the wicket, Gayle works it away to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to de Villiers, leg byes, 1 run, de Villiers gets across a bit and tries to play behind square on the on-side, misses as the ball spins sharply and it rolls off the thigh pad towards backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Gayle, 1 run, down the leg-side, tucked away to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to de Villiers, 1 run, de Villiers advances and swings this flighted delivery away through square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to de Villiers, 1 run, oh dear! Gayle has taken a lot of pace off the ball. Low full toss, de Villiers drives it nicely, the ball hits Gayle's back leg, then hits the umpire and rolls towards long-off. No harm done though]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to de Villiers, no run, this is interesting, de Villiers advances and swings hard. BLR need to handle this well, they've just lost two quick wickets]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to de Villiers, <b>FOUR</b>, classy looking drive from de Villiers, although it was in the air for a while. It was most a controlled shot from de Villiers and he hit it in the gap between cover and mid-off. He picked the slower ball and timed it to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to de Villiers, no run, short and on the stumps, de Villiers lets it go, looks at the umpire for height and the umpire signals one for the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Gayle, 1 run, down the leg-side, tucked away to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Gayle, <b>FOUR</b>, Russell appeals for LBW, but the umpire signals runs and rightly so. Short of a length delivery on the leg stump, Gayle defends and gets a thick outside edge that runs away to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>AB de Villiers, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Mandeep, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Stay away from the coach and the captain Mandeep Singh. That was a ridiculous shot! What a bowling change by Gambhir. Pathan has got two wickets in the over. Nothing but a flighted delivery from Pathan, Mandeep goes for a needless reverse sweep, misses it completely and loses the leg stump. When you can hit lovely sixes down the track, why attempt such gallery shots and that too very early in the innings. BLR are under serious pressure now. <b>Mandeep b Y Pathan 6(3) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Y Pathan to Mandeep, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Mandeep, <b>SIX</b>, nice brave hit! Flighted delivery from Pathan, Mandeep advances, gets to the pitch of the ball and muscles it straight down the ground for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Mandeep, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Mandeep chips it uppishly to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mandeep Singh, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to D Karthik, <b>out</b> Bowled!! No Karthik, the shot wasn't on. It wasn't wide enough to employ the cut shot. Looked like the ball kept a bit low as well. Karthik gave some room and tried to cut it hard, but the ball spun back in and shattered the off stump. <b>D Karthik b Y Pathan 6(8) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Y Pathan to D Karthik, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Gayle, 1 run, loud shout for LBW again, but this time there was an inside edge. Gayle went down on one knee and tried to sweep, missed and got hit on the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Gayle, leg byes, 2 runs, flatter ball down the leg-side, Gayle misses the glance, the ball rolls off the pad to fine leg. Optimistic shout for LBW from Pathan as it pitched outside leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yusuf Pathan, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Gayle, 1 run, full and in the slot, Gayle drives that hard and uppishly to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sourav Ganguly is in the house]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to D Karthik, 1 run, shortish slower ball, Karthik pulls uppishly to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to D Karthik, no run, short of length delivery on the stumps, Karthik plays across the line and gets hit on the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to D Karthik, <b>FOUR</b>, short and down the leg-side, Karthik rocks back, gets inside the line and pulls, the ball hits the glove and then takes the bat on the followthrough before running away to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to D Karthik, no run, slower ball outside off stump, defended to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to D Karthik, no run, starts off with a fast and full delivery, Karthik defends it to mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kishan Cariappa to D Karthik, 1 run, flighted delivery on the leg stump, Karthik turns it to mid-wicket and keeps strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kishan Cariappa to Gayle, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Gayle drills it past a diving bowler, long-off runs to his left and stops the ball, the batsmen can only take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kishan Cariappa to Gayle, <b>FOUR</b>, "Catch it, Catch it" says Uthappa but it's gone just over the man at mid-on. Again too full from Cariappa and Gayle lifts it over the infield for four]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kishan Cariappa to Gayle, no run, flatter in trajectory, Gayle defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kishan Cariappa to Gayle, <b>SIX</b>, he tries to give this a lot of air but it's too full to trouble the batsman and Gayle muscles it straight down the ground into the sightscreen]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Kishan Cariappa to Gayle, no run, flighted delivery outside off stump, driven to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kishan Cariappa, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to D Karthik, no run, steeply rising short of length delivery outside off stump, Karthik hops and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dinesh Karthik, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Kohli, <b>out</b> Caught by Uthappa!! Oh no! The ploy to open the batting hasn't worked. This is a big wicket. With Morne Morkel in the opposition ranks, should Mandeep Singh have opened the innings? Well, I leave that debate to you. This is a body blow for BLR. Morkel cramps Kohli for room with a bouncer, Kohli tries to pull, but gloves it to the left of the keeper, who takes a simple catch. <b>Kohli c Uthappa b M Morkel 13(15) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[M Morkel to Kohli, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Kohli, no run, full and outside off stump, Kohli drives and picks out backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Gayle, 1 run, cramps Gayle for room as he opens up a bit, Gayle can only flick the short of length delivery through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Gayle, <b>FOUR</b>, that's an easy ball for Gayle. Length ball in the slot, there was room on offer as well and Gayle swings it back over the bowler's head for a one-bounce four. Effortessly done!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Kohli, 1 run, short of length delivery on the off stump, worked away to deep mid-wicket, interestingly Gayle wanted the second but Kohli sent him back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Gayle, no run, the incoming delivery this time, Gayle tries to glance it fine but the ball rolls off the thigh pad to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Gayle, no run, plays inside the line of this off-spinner and gets beaten as he looks to defend away from the body off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Gayle, no run, the straighter one this time but down the leg-side again, Gayle misses the flick and gets hit on the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Gayle, leg byes, <b>FOUR</b>, down the leg-side, Gayle tries to pull, but the ball brushes the pad and goes past Uthappa]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Gayle, no run, stays back and defends this off-spinner to the left of Narine, Kohli wants a quick single, but he has to be aware that Gayle is on strike and he's not a swift mover]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Kohli, 1 run, flighted delivery on the leg stump, Kohli flicks it behind square on the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Gayle, <b>FOUR</b>, he's not timed this properly but he's got enough wood to clear mid-on and it's a one-bounce four. Short again from Morkel, Gayle mistimes the pull, yet picks up a boundary. Slowly BLR are upping the ante]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Gayle, no run, short and angling away from the left-hander, Gayle tries to fetch the pull but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Kohli, 3 runs, goes for the big hit but doesn't make proper contact, luckily, it cleared the infield and cleared Gambhir at mid-off. Gambhir runs back, slides and flicks it back, recovers quickly to fire in the throw to save one run. Kohli came down the track to smash that short of length delivery, but the bat turned in his hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Kohli, no run, full and outside off stump, Kohli punches it away from the body to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Kohli, <b>SIX</b>, wow! What an authoritative shot from Kohli. Short from Morkel, but not high enough to trouble Kohli, who rocks back and nails the pull shot to perfection over deep mid-wicket. That will give him a lot of confidence]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Kohli, no run, Kohli gives the charge to Morkel and tries to deposit him over long-off but only connects with thin air]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Kohli, 1 run, down the leg-side, easily flicked through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Kohli, no run, short and wide outside off stump, Kohli goes for the cut, but chops it past the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Gayle, 1 run, reads this offie off the pitch, adjusts very late and pushes it through cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Kohli, 1 run, Kohli gets across the stumps and works the off-spinner through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[No slips in place for Kohli]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Gayle, 1 run, shortish and outside off stump, pushed off the back foot to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Narine to Gayle, no run, off-spinner to start off, Gayle defends with an angled bat towards point, Kohli wants a run but Gayle sends him back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[One slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sunil Narine, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Narine to share the new ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Kohli, no run, oh tentative footwork from Kohli and he almost chops one on. Short of a length delivery outside off stump, Kohli defends away from the body, doesn't move his front foot much, luckily the inside edge hit the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Kohli, no run, much fuller in length, Kohli watchfully drives it straight to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Kohli, no run, back of a length just outside off stump, Kohli gets right behind the line and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Kohli, no run, Morkel is hitting excellent lengths already. Short of a length delivery just outside off stump, Kohli leans forward and defends well]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Gayle, 1 run, good length delivery on the stumps, Gayle turns it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;M Morkel to Gayle, no run, full toss and he hits it straight to the fielder. Gayle should have done better with that one. It was a freebie but he drove it softly to cover after reaching out]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Gayle and Kohli are at the crease. Gayle is on strike. M Morkel will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back... Kohli to open the batting with Gayle.]]></line><line><![CDATA[On the other hand, Bangalore would rue the fact that their fielding was below par. Bangalore were let down by misfields, overthrows and even one of the best fielders going around, AB de Villiers, dropped a sitter as Gambhir survived. Among the bowlers, Yuzvendra Chahal, the leg-spinner, troubled the batsmen and was rewarded with the wicket of Gambhir. Abu Nechim too stood up to the challenge of bowling on a flat deck. Bangalore, with an impressive batting line-up at their disposal, can still chase down the target.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Gautam Gambhir's well-constructed half-century helped Kolkata to reach a sizeable total. Gambhir played a series of fluent shots to give them a rousing start. Robin Uthappa chipped in with an enterprising innings and gave Gambhir good support. Once Gambhir laid the platform for the middle-order batsmen, Manish Pandey and Andre Russell with their pyrotechnics made their presence felt. In fact, it was Russell's hefty blows in the end overs that gave Kolkata the much needed impetus.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Russell played a blinder there. His knock of 41 off 17 balls fired KOL to a competitive total. After a good start, they were struggling a little when they lost Yadav and Pandey off successive deliveries. But, Russell made sure that they reach close to somwehere around 180 with his blistering batting.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to A Russell, <b>FOUR</b>, Russell ends the innings on a high. Low full toss outside off, Russell slices it over backward point and collects four, KOL finish with <b>177/6</b> on the board]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Shakib, <b>wide</b>, <b>out</b> Shakib Run Out!! ohh dear! Shakib is run-out in trying to get Russell on strike, it was a bouncer down the leg-side, Shakib fails to connect and was looking to steal the bye, Karthik throws the ball to Aaron, who disturbs the stumps at the non-striker's end to catch Shakib short. <b>Shakib run out (D Karthik/Aaron) 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Shakib, no run, <b>run-out chance and Aaron misses!</b> It was a back of a length delivery just outside off, Shakib can't get it past the bowler and Russell was backing up, Aaron picks up the ball and has three stumps to fire at, he misses and luckily for him there was the fielder at mid-off, who was backing up. Either side of him, it would have been four extra overthrows]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to A Russell, 1 run, poor delivery from Aaron once again and he gets away with it, it was another full toss from Aaron, Russell slices it hard, the ball was going very fine, but Abdullah at third man dives to his right and stops the ball, good fielding effort as he saved three there]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to A Russell, <b>FOUR</b>, misses the yorker and ends up bowling a full toss, Russell drills it past the diving bowler and the fielder at long-on can't cut it off, another boundary for the Jamaican]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to A Russell, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>top-edge and four!</b> It was short and wide outside off once again, Russell went for the pull, gets a top-edge and the ball goes very fine over the keeper's head, just bounces in front of the ad-cushions]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Y Pathan, <b>out</b> Caught by Kohli!! Pathan goes after a short stay at the crease. It was a back of a length delivery well outside off, Pathan had enough room to free his arms there. However, the bat turns in his end and he ends up slicing it high in the air. Kohli from long-on runs forward to his left and takes the catch. Not a wicket-taking delivery, but BLR wouldn't mind it. <b>Y Pathan c Kohli b Aaron 3(4)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Aaron to Y Pathan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Varun Aaron [3.0-0-24-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to A Russell, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball to end your spell, it was on the pads and was rightly put away. He just waits for this full toss to arrive and helps it on its way to the fine leg fence, the fielder from fine leg runs to his right but didn't have any scope of stopping that]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to A Russell, no run, yorker right on the stumps from Patel, Russell squeezes it out back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Y Pathan, 1 run, full and just outside off, Pathan drills the drive past the non-striker, Kohli from long-off runs to his right, fumbles the ball but doesn't allow the batsmen to go back for the couple. Russell slipped while turning back and that's why they couldn't go back for a second]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to A Russell, byes, 1 run, slower ball bumper from Patel, Russell fails to connect with the pull, the keeper fires the throw at the striker's end, gets a direct hit but the batsman was well in. To make matters worse, the ball gets deflected off the stumps and the batsmen sneak in a bye comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to A Russell, 2 runs, ohh dear! BLR let go of another chance, Aaron just lost it somewhere in the sky, it was a low full toss on the stumps, Russell wanted to go on the on-side, but gets a leading edge that balloons up over cover, Aaron from mid-off runs to his left and overruns it completely, the ball falls well short of him and Kohli is not a happy man]]></line><line><![CDATA[Comes round the wicket now]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to A Russell, <b>SIX</b>, ohh! <b>Another huge blow from Russell!</b> It was the slower one outside off, it was on a length and Russell gets right under it. He just whacks it over the wide long-on fence. Doesn't flinch a muscle after that]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Nechim has gone off the field after completing his spell. He picked up a wicket for 28]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to A Russell, 1 run, Nechim comes round the wicket for the last ball and bowls almost a yorker on the stumps this time, Russell squeezes it out to long-on and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to A Russell, <b>SIX</b>, <b>hammered!</b> Russell makes it look so easy, it was full and in the slot outside off, Russell bends, gets under it and lofts it over the deep extra cover fence with ease, it went almost 20 rows back there]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to A Russell, no run, bumper from Nechim and it was outside off, Russell looks to pull, but can't lay bat on that]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to A Russell, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>thrashed!</b> That was smashed at some power, it was full and outside off, Russell clears his front leg and drills the drive past the bowler, the fielder at long-off wasn't too far away from the ball, but he can't stop it even after putting in the dive. Such was the power on that shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to A Russell, no run, yorker outside off, Russell fails to connect with the drive and Nechim is not looking comfortable after bowling that delivery]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nechim is continuing for now]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nechim is down on the pitch and I'm not sure whether he can continue. He was in some discomfort before this ball and now the physio is out to tend to him.]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to Y Pathan, 1 run, very full and on the stumps, Pathan drives it down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Nechim pulls out in his delivery stride. He holds his calf muscle as well as he looks to be struggling somewhat.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Abu Nechim [3.0-0-16-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Y Pathan, 1 run, a quick single to keep the strike, it was fullish just outside off, Pathan drops it to the left of the bowler and sets off]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to A Russell, 1 run, off-cutter from Patel, Russell pushes it towards point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to A Russell, <b>FOUR</b>, banged in short and well wide outside off, Russell went chasing after that as he looked to upper cut it, he gets a bottom edge that runs away past the keeper's dive and crashes into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to A Russell, no run, bowls this one from wide of the crease and gets it to angle in from outside off, Russell was looking for the cut, but fails to connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to M Pandey, <b>out</b> M Pandey Run Out!! ohh dear! What has happened there? Pandey goes off the very next ball. Yusuf Pathan is guilty of ball watching there. It was another slower one from Patel, Pandey was looking to work it through the on-side, gets a leading edge that goes past the diving bowler and crashes into the stump. Pandey was halfway down the track in search of a run as the ball got deflected to the left of the stumps, Kohli from mid-on charges in, picks the ball and fires in a direct-hit at the striker's end. Pandey put in the dive as well, but he was well short of the crease there. <b>M Pandey run out (Kohli) 23(15) [4s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Harshal Patel to M Pandey, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Yusuf Pathan, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Suryakumar Yadav, <b>out</b> Caught by Mandeep!! Patel is pumped after picking up the wicket of the dangerman Yadav. It was a length delivery on the stumps, Yadav went across and wanted to slog it over deep backward square leg. However, unlike the last game, he doesn't get the distance on it this time as he was fooled by the slower one there. Mandeep Singh takes a good catch right in front of the boundary line. <b>Suryakumar Yadav c Mandeep b Harshal Patel 11(9) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Harshal Patel to Suryakumar Yadav, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel [2.0-0-18-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Pandey, 2 runs, drags his length back once again and goes slightly wide just outside off, Pandey hangs on the back foot and cuts it square of the wicket, the batsmen take two before the fielder from sweeper gets around]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, quicker and on middle stump line, Yadav kneels down and sweeps it to backward square leg, the batsmen sneak in a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Suryakumar Yadav, <b>FOUR</b>, Yadav seems to be in good form, continuing from where he left in the last game. It was tossed up from Chahal, Yadav lofts it inside-out over extra cover for another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Suryakumar Yadav, no run, drops it slightly wide outside off, Yadav was looking to give the charge, but decides against it. He then was looking to guide it after reaching out, but fails to connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Pandey, 1 run, touch flatter and just outside off, Pandey waits for it and guides it to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, goes down on one knee and sweeps it to deep backward square leg, it was in the air for a little while but bounced well in front of the fielder]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abbott to M Pandey, <b>FOUR</b>, short again and Abbott got the punishment he deserved. Pandey was on the walk and he pulls it wide of mid-on, the ball crashes into the fence in no time, <b>14 runs came off the over</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abbott to M Pandey, <b>FOUR</b>, this is great batting, sensible and yet he got four for it. It was little wide outside off, Pandey waits inside the crease, opens the face of the bat and steers it to the deep backward point fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abbott to Suryakumar Yadav, 1 run, banged in short and at the batsman, Yadav pulls hard, but can't connect that well. The ball bounces in front of the deep square leg fielder who was running to his right to stop the ball, the batsmen can only take a single, good fielding in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abbott to Suryakumar Yadav, <b>FOUR</b>, Yadav gets off the mark with a boundary, it was short and outside off, Yadav waits for it and ramps it over the keeper, great shot from Yadav]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abbott to Suryakumar Yadav, no run, ohh dear? <b>How did that miss the stumps?</b> It was a length delivery on middle stump line, Yadav goes across and looks to flick it through the on-side, fails to connect and the ball just goes over the stumps. Lucky, but you need a little luck in this format]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abbott to M Pandey, 1 run, comes forward and looks to push, the ball rolls away towards cover off the outside half of the bat, the batsmen cross over for a quick run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sean Abbott [2.0-0-22-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Suryakumar Yadav, no run, googly from Chahal to end the over, Yadav waits for it inside the crease and blocks it out to Gayle at slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Pandey, 1 run, slower again and a little wide outside off, Pandey reached out, opens the face of the bat and knocks it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Pandey, <b>FOUR</b>, this time he gets the boundary he wanted, it was tossed up again but this time it was slightly quicker from Chahal, Pandey just lofts it straight over the bowler's head and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Pandey, no run, slower delivery tossed up just outside off and spinning away, Pandey goes for the drive and the ball turns past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Suryakumar Yadav, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Gambhir, <b>out</b> Caught by Mandeep!! Skipper Gambhir is gone after a fine fifty. It was the googly from Chahal on middle stump line, Gambhir went for the swipe across the line after going down on one knee, he didn't get it under it properly and offers a simple catch to Mandeep at deep mid-wicket. <b>Gambhir goes after becoming the batsman with most fifties in the IPL.</b> <b>Gambhir c Mandeep b Chahal 58(46) [4s-7 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chahal to Gambhir, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Gambhir, 2 runs, comes down the track as Chahal bowls it on the pads, Gambhir works it towards deep backward square leg and comes back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Gambhir, leg byes, 1 run, short delivery on leg, Gambhir fails to tuck it away into the on-side, the ball goes off his hip and rolls away towards fine leg, the batsmen sneak in a leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Gambhir, 2 runs, length delivery on off, Gambhir opens the face of the bat and pushes it towards point, he rushes towards the other end, the fielder at backward point picks it up quickly and fires in the throw at the striker's end, he misses and there was no one backing up, allows the batsmen to run on the overthrow]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Gambhir, <b>wide</b>, bumper from Aaron, but it's deemed to be too high. Gambhir didn't offer a shot and just allowed it to go past him after swaying away]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, super shot from Gambhir, it was short and wide, it deserved to be hit and Gambhir stays back in his crease and cuts it past backward point, the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to M Pandey, 1 run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Pandey looks to guide it down towards third man, but ends up chopping it to the right of the slip fielder, who runs across and dives to make a stop, he fires the throw at the non-striker's end, but the batsman was well in]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to M Pandey, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a great strike from Pandey, it was full and right in the slot for Pandey to clear his front leg, he just drills it to the left of mid-on, who had no chance of cutting that off]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Gambhir, 1 run, <b>second successive fifty</b> for Gambhir, it was a back of a length delivery angling in on off, Gambhir drops it to his left and sets off, completes the single with ease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Aaron comes round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Varun Aaron [2.0-0-11-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Pandey, no run, touch quicker and outside off once again, Pandey drives it back to the bowler off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Pandey, no run, slowish delivery just outside off, Pandey leans forward and pushes it to the right of the bowler, can't get the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Gambhir, 1 run, on the pads once again, Gambhir works it to short fine leg and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to M Pandey, 1 run, tossed up just outside off, Pandey drives it down to long-off to get off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place for Pandey]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Gambhir, 1 run, drifting on the pads, Gambhir clips it behind square on the on-side and gets the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Gambhir, 2 runs, Gambhir comes down the track to this flighted delivery on middle stump line, he goes for the loft, but gets it off the inside half of the bat, the ball rolls away to deep mid-wicket and good running ensures they come back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to M Pandey, no run, bumper from Nechim, Pandey ducks under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to Gambhir, 1 run, that could have been close! Pandey could well have been out without facing a ball there, but a dive saves him. It was a length delivery just outside off, Gambhir drops it towards the keeper and sets off, the keeper picks it up quickly and fires in the throw at the striker's end. Pandey dives in the end to save himself]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Manish Pandey, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to Uthappa, <b>out</b> Caught by Sammy!! Uthappa perishes while trying to go big. He was struggling a little in the last few overs. It was banged in short and outside off, Uthappa went for the pull but got more height than distance there. Sammy at long-on takes a comfortable catch. BLR though will be happy to see his back. <b>Uthappa c Sammy b Abu Nechim 35(28) [4s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Abu Nechim to Uthappa, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to Uthappa, 2 runs, fullish delivery outside off, Uthappa slices the drive over backward point after coming down the track, the batsmen come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to Gambhir, 1 run, bit of width on offer on this one and Gambhir goes hard on the cut, he gets it over the infield but there was sweeper in the deep, the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to Uthappa, 1 run, length delivery just outside off, Uthappa mistimes the heave to deep square leg off the inside half of the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Abu Nechim [2.0-0-11-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, tries to float on up but offers a low full toss, Gambhir smashes it along the ground through mid-wicket, beats Kohli's dive, AB runs to his left from long-on and dives, he had it covered but the ball escapes to the boundary after hitting his left hand. That should have been saved by AB's standards]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Gambhir, no run, Gambhir goes for the slog-sweep but misses the ball, luckily for him, it was just outside off stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Uthappa, 1 run, very full, Uthappa flicks it along the ground through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Gambhir, 1 run, steps out but doesn't get to the pitch of the ball, Gambhir guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Gambhir, no run, quicker delivery on the off stump, but Gambhir dangerously punches this off the back foot to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chahal to Uthappa, 1 run, shortish from Chahal, Uthappa drives it off the back foot through mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuzvendra Chahal, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, brave shot with the keeper standing up. Slower delivery outside off stump, Gambhir walks forward and lofts it back over the bowler's head and long-on was not even in the picture]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Gambhir, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Gambhir cuts and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Uthappa, leg byes, 1 run, Sammy claps in his appeal for LBW, he thought it was plumb, the impact was in line with the off stump but height was also an issue. Uthappa tried to work this slower delivery into the on-side, but gets hit high on the front pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Gambhir, 1 run, driven nicely but straight to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Uthappa, 1 run, full and down the leg-side, Uthappa flicks it along the ground through square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sammy to Gambhir, 1 run, driven along the ground to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Darren Sammy, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to Gambhir, 1 run, <b>AB de Villiers has dropped a sitter</b>. Yes, you read that right! Big moment in the game. Kohli can't believe it, but manages to smile. Short and on the stumps, Gambhir pulls, hits it straight to deep square leg, AB had it covered, it came straight him and it popped out. He tried to grab the rebound but it was too far away from him]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to Uthappa, 1 run, driven to mid-off, a quick release from the fielder but Uthappa was quick enough]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to Uthappa, no run, Uthappa looks to pull it for four, but mistimes the short ball to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to Uthappa, no run, short of length outside off stump, defended to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to Gambhir, 1 run, easily guided away to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to Uthappa, 1 run, short of length outside off stump, dabbed to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Gambhir, no run, 140.6kph short of length delivery on the leg stump, Gambhir defends it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, an ugly looking pull shot and the top edge flies over the keeper's head. Short ball on the leg stump, Gambhir bends and plays, luckily for him the edge didn't go to hand]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Gambhir, no run, short of length delivery just outside off stump, Gambhir defends it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Gambhir, no run, steeply rising short of length delivery, Gambhir hops and defends, Uthappa looks for a run and is halfway down the wicket, Gambhir sends him back and luckily for Uthappa, Aaron misfired the throw to mid-off. That looked funny. Almost similar to what Dwayne Bravo did in the previous game]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Uthappa, 1 run, a quick call from Uthappa after driving this good length delivery on the rise to mid-off and he makes his ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Uthappa, no run, short of length delivery on the off stump, Uthappa defends off the back foot, Gambhir wants a run but Uthappa sends him back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to Uthappa, 1 run, oh an inside edge but it doesn't go back onto the stumps. The ball hits the thigh pad and almost shaves the off stump, Gambhir wants a run, the keeper rushes in and under-arms the ball but misses. Anyway, Gambhir was in]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to Gambhir, 1 run, guides this off the front foot with an open face to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to Gambhir, no run, very full and on the stumps, defended nicely off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to Gambhir, no run, full and just outside off stump, Gambhir looks for the off-drive, but gets it on the inside half of the bat and it goes back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, on the pads, can't bowl there with fine leg inside the ring. Gambhir allows the ball to come and just glanced it fine past the man at 45 and it raced away across the turf. <b>Fifty partnership comes up</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abu Nechim to Uthappa, 1 run, outswing on this short of length delivery, guided to the right of third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Abu Nechim, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Gambhir, no run, bouncer to end the over, Gambhir ducks under it, looks for a wide but doesn't get it. Gambhir isn't happy with the call]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, full and in the slot, Gambhir stays leg-side of the ball and slogs it over mid-wicket for four. This was the shot he attempted earlier in the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[The man at slip has been removed]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Gambhir, no run, bumper outside off stump, Gambhir tries to guide it past the keeper but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Gambhir, no run, without moving his feet, Gambhir tries to flick this full ball over square leg but misses and gets hit on the pad. It was going down the leg-side though]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Uthappa, 1 run, driven nicely this time, but straight to point, where AB de Villiers fumbles. Well, that's a rarity. The misfield gives Uthappa a single, the fielder has a shy at the bowler's end but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Aaron to Gambhir, 1 run, a drop-and-run single, short of length delivery on the stumps, Gambhir taps it towards cover-point, looks at his partner and takes off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Varun Aaron, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, cut hard and cut in the gap. Again Patel bowls one short and outside off stump, Uthappa times it sweetly and it races away through point. He moves into the 20s in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Uthappa, no run, Uthappa tries to guide it fine past the keeper as Patel bangs it short and outside off stump but fails to make contact]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Gambhir, 1 run, flicked to mid-wicket for an easy run]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Uthappa, 1 run, wow! Nice looking on-drive but it hits Gambhir at the other end. Good length delivery on the off stump, Uthappa drives off the front foot, Gambhir jumped and tried to let it go between his legs but the ball hit the left thigh and rolled to mid-on. That was a certain boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, cut on the rise and Uthappa beats the fielder's dive at cover-point. Width on offer from Patel and Uthappa doesn't miss out, he got on top of the bounce and hit it very well]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Gambhir, 1 run, too close to cut but Gambhir gets away with it as he chops this towards gully]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Gambhir, <b>wide</b>, loses the radar and sprays it down the leg-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abbott to Gambhir, 1 run, short of length delivery on the leg stump, Gambhir flicks it through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abbott to Gambhir, no run, short of length delivery on the stumps, looks like this kept a bit low, Gambhir handles it well from the crease though]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abbott to Uthappa, 1 run, again surprises Uthappa with a bumper, the batsman pulls but the ball hits the splice of the bat, it was in the air for a while but it went well wide of short fine leg to his left]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abbott to Uthappa, no run, pacy back of a length delivery, 138.8kph in fact, Uthappa was trying to play on the on-side, but the extra bounce hit him on the glove]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abbott to Gambhir, 1 run, back of a length down the leg-side, Gambhir flicks it behind square on the on-side for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abbott to Gambhir, <b>SIX</b>, my word, that is some shot from the little left-hander. There was some inswing on this full length ball but Gambhir had it covered and flicked it handsomely over mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Gambhir, 1 run, back of a length delivery outside off stump, Gambhir taps it in front of cover for a sharp run]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Gambhir, no run, sharp bumper on the leg stump at 136.7kph, Gambhir gets inside the line and looks to pull but misses. He was surprised by the pace on that one]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Gambhir, no run, driven nicely off the front foot but straight to mid-off, Varun Aaron has a needless shy at the bowler's end but there was a man backing up]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Gambhir, no run, why is that not a wide? Maybe it flicked the trouser on its way. Short of a length down the leg-side, Gambhir tries to tickle it fine but doesn't make contact]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Uthappa, 1 run, a front foot drive to the left of mid-off for an easy run]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Harshal Patel to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, can't offer width to this man and he's in fine nick. Gentle outswinger outside off stump, Uthappa leans forward and looks to drive, the ball goes off the outside half of the bat and goes through cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Harshal Patel, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abbott to Uthappa, 1 run, Uthappa pushes this full ball on the move to cover, takes on the fielder and makes his ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abbott to Uthappa, 2 runs, again sloppy cricket, this is a nervy start from BLR. They need to settle down. Fullish and on the off stump, Uthappa pushes it to the right of the bowler and sets off, after seeing the bowler dive to his right, he hesitates for a while, but Abbott doesn't stop it cleanly and they get a run. The fielder at mid-on rushes in and fires a needless throw at the striker's end and the keeper had no chance even with a full length dive. An overthrow conceded]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abbott to Gambhir, 1 run, straying down the leg-side, Gambhir glances it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abbott to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, another fumble by BLR and this time it is Harshal Patel. Full and on the off stump, looked like it hurried Gambhir a bit, but he managed to flick, the ball went to the left of mid-wicket, but the fielder misfielded the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abbott to Uthappa, 1 run, good length delivery on the off stump, Uthappa pushes it to mid-on and takes off for a sharp run]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abbott to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, inauspicious start to the season for BLR. Short of a length delivery just swinging away outside off stump, Uthappa opens the face of the bat and runs it past slip to third man, it was an easy grab for Abu Nechim but he didn't get behind the line of the ball and fumbled]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Uthappa and Gambhir are at the crease. Uthappa is on strike. Abbott will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Just a one slip in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players are out in the middle. The countdown begins]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players are out in the middle. The countdown begins and we are ready to go.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore</b> (Playing XI): Chris Gayle, Mandeep Singh, Virat Kohli(c), Dinesh Karthik(w), AB de Villiers, Darren Sammy, Sean Abbott, Harshal Patel, Yuzvendra Chahal, Varun Aaron, Abu Nechim]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kolkata</b> (Playing XI): Gautam Gambhir(c), Robin Uthappa(w), Manish Pandey, Suryakumar Yadav, Yusuf Pathan, Shakib Al Hasan, Andre Russell, Piyush Chawla, Sunil Narine, Morne Morkel, Kishan Cariappa]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kohli</b>: "It's going to be an exciting season. It's a special ground for me. I got my first international hundred here. We've got some good of bowling options this year as well. Yeah, she would be (when Gavaskar cheekily asked "Is she (Anushka Sharma) here?"). We are going to bowl first, looks a pretty hard wicket so we are backing ourselves to chase down the target."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Gambhir</b>: "I think it was a clinical performance in the first game. We've got to play well this season. We have started well and hopefully we will carry the momentum forward. It (the pitch) is a bit dry, so hopefully it will turn. Kishan Cariappa replaces Umesh Yadav. No one has seen him so hopefully he'll do well today."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[On the other hand, defending champions KOL are looking very confident after extending their winning streak to 10 games with their thumping win over Mumbai in the season opener. Morne Morkel and Sunil Narine, two of their key bowlers, did well against MUM, while captain Gautam Gambhir led from the front with a fine fifty. With Manish Pandey and Suryakumar Yadav playing confidently, the batting line-up looks quite formidable. However, they would want to improve their fielding, having dropped a few catches the other day. Overall, this has all the makings to be a cracking contest.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Hello and welcome to game 2 of today's double-header. It's time for BLR to get their first taste of IPL-8. After revamping their squad with some smart buys in the auctions, they will be excited to take the field tonight and start well. Mandeep Singh, Dinesh Karthik, S Badrinath, Darren Sammy, Sean Abbott, Iqbal Abdulla, Manvinder Bisla, David Wiese, Sarfaraz Khan, Jalaj Saxena, Shishir Bhavane are few of the new additions. However, it is a big blow that they will miss Mitchell Starc for a few matches due to a knee injury. Captain Kohli though still believes that BLR have a good bowling attack despite the absence of Starc.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview</b><br/><br/>Bangalore (BLR) have a 'royal challenge' on their hands when they take on defending champions Kolkata (KOL) in the fifth match of IPL 8 at Eden Gardens on Saturday. KOL made a winning start to their title defence when they comfortably beat Mumbai on the opening day, and they will be keen on extending their winning start. They boast of a 10-match winning streak in the IPL and it will take a big effort from BLR to halt the run.<br/><br/>BLR brought in as many as nine players during the auctions earlier this year, including Dinesh Karthik for a dizzying INR 10.5 crore. As has been the case over the years, the side boasts of plenty of match-winners, but the team has failed to clicked as a unit on far too many occasions. Virat Kohli will hope that his side avoid the mistakes they made over the previous seasons and end their trophy drought this time around.<br/><br/>Venue: Eden Gardens, Kolkata<br/>Date: April 11, 2015<br/>Time: 20:00 IST<br/>Weather: Rain could play spoilsport. Otherwise, it will be a humid evening.<br/><br/>Team News:<br/><br/>KOL<br/><br/>Having comfortably seen off Mumbai in the opening encounter, KOL will not want to tinker with a winning combination. They will, however, be worried with the performance of their slower bowlers. Shakib Al Hasan, Sunil Narine and Piyush Chawla's combined 10 overs went for 92 runs with a solitary wicket to show for their efforts. Gautam Gambhir will want his spinners to put up a better show this time around.<br/><br/>Probable XI: 1 Gautam Gambhir (capt), 2 Robin Uthappa (wk), 3 Manish Pandey, 4 Suryakumar Yadav, 5 Yusuf Pathan, 6 Shakib Al Hasan, 7 Andre Russell, 8 Piyush Chawla, 9 Sunil Narine, 10 Umesh Yadav, Morne Morkel<br/><br/>BLR<br/><br/>With a number of new faces in the side, BLR will be unsure about their playing XI. Mitchell Starc - a shoo-in for any side in world cricket today - misses out through an injury, while his likely replacement in the side, Adam Milne, could also be unavailable. In the pair's absence, Varun Aaron, Ashok Dinda and Yuzvendra Chahal should find spots in the starting XI, while Sean Abbott and Darren Sammy should play ahead of David Wiese.<br/><br/>BLR's strength is definitely their batting, and the inclusion of Karthik adds a new, more potent dimension to the line-up. With the likes of Chris Gayle, Virat Kohli, AB de Villiers and Karthik in the batting order, BLR will be confident that they can beat any bowling attack. Mandeep Singh, S Badrinath, Vijay Zol and Manvinder Bisla will be left to fight it out for the two remaining slots in the line-up.<br/><br/>Probable XI: 1 Mandeep Singh, 2 Chris Gayle, 3 Virat Kohli (capt), 4 Dinesh Karthik (wk), 5 AB de Villiers, 6 S Badrinath, 7 Darren Sammy, 8 Sean Abbott, 9 Varun Aaron, 10 Ashok Dinda, 11 Yuzvendra Chahal<br/><br/>Quotes:<br/><br/>"This season is pretty different for us because for the last three or maybe four years myself, Chris [Gayle] and AB [de Villiers] have played under a lot of pressure because the batting revolved around the three of us. But, this time around we have got Dinesh Karthik, Darren Sammy, Badrinath and youngsters like Mandeep Singh coming into the batting line-up. It is a very strong batting unit this time and we have got really good depth" - Virat Kohli<br/><br/>"The past couple of months were mentally testing and trying. We have moved on now (from the WC loss) and my focus is now with the Kolkata and I want to deliver my best for this team. I know it is not going to always go my way and I realise it is a part of T20 cricket. But if it is my day, I am going to make sure that I cash in and take wickets for the team." - Morne Morkel]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangalore</b> (From): Mandeep Singh, Chris Gayle, Virat Kohli(c), Dinesh Karthik(w), AB de Villiers, S Badrinath, Darren Sammy, Sean Abbott, Yuzvendra Chahal, Varun Aaron, Ashok Dinda, Nic Maddinson, Harshal Patel, Vijay Zol, Abu Nechim, Sandeep Warrier, Yogesh Takawale, Rilee Rossouw, Iqbal Abdulla, Manvinder Bisla, David Wiese, Sarfaraz Khan, Jalaj Saxena, Shishir Bhavane]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kolkata</b> (From): Gautam Gambhir(c), Robin Uthappa(w), Manish Pandey, Suryakumar Yadav, Yusuf Pathan, Shakib Al Hasan, Andre Russell, Piyush Chawla, Sunil Narine, Morne Morkel, Umesh Yadav, Pat Cummins, Veer Pratap Singh, Kuldeep Yadav, Azhar Mahmood, Brad Hogg, Sumit Narwal, Sheldon Jackson, Aditya Garhwal, Kishan Cariappa, Vaibhav Rawal, Johan Botha, Ryan ten Doeschate]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>177</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>6</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Kolkata">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>527</playerid>
					<name>Robin Uthappa</name>
					<batsman-name>Uthappa</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Uthappa</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>35</runs>
					<balls>28</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Abu Nechim</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6323</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Darren Sammy</fielder>
						<fielderId>253</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>308</playerid>
					<name>Gautam Gambhir</name>
					<batsman-name>Gambhir</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Gambhir</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>58</runs>
					<balls>46</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Chahal</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7910</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mandeep Singh</fielder>
						<fielderId>6319</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1836</playerid>
					<name>Manish Pandey</name>
					<batsman-name>M Pandey</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M Pandey</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>23</runs>
					<balls>15</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Virat Kohli</fielder>
						<fielderId>1413</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7915</playerid>
					<name>Suryakumar Yadav</name>
					<batsman-name>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>11</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Harshal Patel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8175</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mandeep Singh</fielder>
						<fielderId>6319</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>790</playerid>
					<name>Yusuf Pathan</name>
					<batsman-name>Y Pathan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Y Pathan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Aaron</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6293</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Virat Kohli</fielder>
						<fielderId>1413</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7736</playerid>
					<name>Andre Russell</name>
					<batsman-name>A Russell</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>A Russell</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>41</runs>
					<balls>17</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>544</playerid>
					<name>Shakib Al Hasan</name>
					<batsman-name>Shakib</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shakib</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dinesh Karthik</fielder>
						<fielderId>145</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Varun Aaron</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>6293</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>466</playerid>
					<name>Piyush Chawla</name>
					<batsman-name>Chawla</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chawla</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2276</playerid>
					<name>Sunil Narine</name>
					<batsman-name>Narine</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Narine</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>608</playerid>
					<name>Morne Morkel</name>
					<batsman-name>M Morkel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M Morkel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10353</playerid>
					<name>Kishan Cariappa</name>
					<batsman-name>Kishan Cariappa</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Kishan Cariappa</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>527</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>81</runs>
				<overs>10.4</overs>
				<batsman>Robin Uthappa</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Uthappa</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>308</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>103</runs>
				<overs>13.2</overs>
				<batsman>Gautam Gambhir</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Gambhir</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7915</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>131</runs>
				<overs>16.1</overs>
				<batsman>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1836</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>131</runs>
				<overs>16.2</overs>
				<batsman>Manish Pandey</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Pandey</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>790</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>163</runs>
				<overs>19.1</overs>
				<batsman>Yusuf Pathan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Y Pathan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>544</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>173</runs>
				<overs>19.5</overs>
				<batsman>Shakib Al Hasan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Shakib</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>1</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>6</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Bangalore">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8136</playerid>
					<name>Sean Abbott</name>
					<bowler-name>S Abbott</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Abbott</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8175</playerid>
					<name>Harshal Patel</name>
					<bowler-name>Harshal Patel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Harshal Patel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>37</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6293</playerid>
					<name>Varun Aaron</name>
					<bowler-name>Aaron</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Aaron</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>38</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6323</playerid>
					<name>Abu Nechim</name>
					<bowler-name>Abu Nechim</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Abu Nechim</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>28</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>253</playerid>
					<name>Darren Sammy</name>
					<bowler-name>Sammy</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sammy</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>7</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7910</playerid>
					<name>Yuzvendra Chahal</name>
					<bowler-name>Chahal</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chahal</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>28</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>247</playerid>
					<name>Chris Gayle</name>
					<bowler-name>Gayle</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Gayle</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6319</playerid>
					<name>Mandeep Singh</name>
					<bowler-name>Mandeep</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mandeep</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<bowler-name>Kohli</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Kohli</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>145</playerid>
					<name>Dinesh Karthik</name>
					<bowler-name>D Karthik</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>D Karthik</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>370</playerid>
					<name>AB de Villiers</name>
					<bowler-name>de Villiers</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>de Villiers</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>179</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>7</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>19</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Bangalore">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>247</playerid>
					<name>Chris Gayle</name>
					<batsman-name>Gayle</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Gayle</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>96</runs>
					<balls>56</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>7</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Manish Pandey</fielder>
						<fielderId>1836</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Robin Uthappa</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>527</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Kohli</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>13</runs>
					<balls>15</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Morkel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>608</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Robin Uthappa</fielder>
						<fielderId>527</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>145</playerid>
					<name>Dinesh Karthik</name>
					<batsman-name>D Karthik</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>D Karthik</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>8</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Y Pathan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>790</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6319</playerid>
					<name>Mandeep Singh</name>
					<batsman-name>Mandeep</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mandeep</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Y Pathan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>790</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>370</playerid>
					<name>AB de Villiers</name>
					<batsman-name>de Villiers</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>de Villiers</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>28</runs>
					<balls>13</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[stumped]]></status>
					<bowler>Kishan Cariappa</bowler>
					<bowlerId>10353</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Robin Uthappa</fielder>
						<fielderId>527</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>253</playerid>
					<name>Darren Sammy</name>
					<batsman-name>Sammy</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sammy</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>7</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[stumped]]></status>
					<bowler>Shakib</bowler>
					<bowlerId>544</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Robin Uthappa</fielder>
						<fielderId>527</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8136</playerid>
					<name>Sean Abbott</name>
					<batsman-name>S Abbott</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Abbott</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Morne Morkel</fielder>
						<fielderId>608</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Shakib Al Hasan</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>544</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8175</playerid>
					<name>Harshal Patel</name>
					<batsman-name>Harshal Patel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Harshal Patel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6323</playerid>
					<name>Abu Nechim</name>
					<batsman-name>Abu Nechim</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Abu Nechim</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>5</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7910</playerid>
					<name>Yuzvendra Chahal</name>
					<batsman-name>Chahal</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chahal</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6293</playerid>
					<name>Varun Aaron</name>
					<batsman-name>Aaron</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Aaron</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1413</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>29</runs>
				<overs>4.5</overs>
				<batsman>Virat Kohli</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>145</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>50</runs>
				<overs>7.3</overs>
				<batsman>Dinesh Karthik</batsman>
				<batsman-name>D Karthik</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6319</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>56</runs>
				<overs>7.6</overs>
				<batsman>Mandeep Singh</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mandeep</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>370</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>93</runs>
				<overs>10.6</overs>
				<batsman>AB de Villiers</batsman>
				<batsman-name>de Villiers</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>253</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>119</runs>
				<overs>14.4</overs>
				<batsman>Darren Sammy</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Sammy</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8136</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>133</runs>
				<overs>16.1</overs>
				<batsman>Sean Abbott</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Abbott</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>247</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>171</runs>
				<overs>18.2</overs>
				<batsman>Chris Gayle</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Gayle</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>1</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>7</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>8</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Kolkata">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>608</playerid>
					<name>Morne Morkel</name>
					<bowler-name>M Morkel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M Morkel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2276</playerid>
					<name>Sunil Narine</name>
					<bowler-name>Narine</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Narine</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>26</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10353</playerid>
					<name>Kishan Cariappa</name>
					<bowler-name>Kishan Cariappa</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Kishan Cariappa</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>28</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7736</playerid>
					<name>Andre Russell</name>
					<bowler-name>A Russell</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>A Russell</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>16</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>790</playerid>
					<name>Yusuf Pathan</name>
					<bowler-name>Y Pathan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Y Pathan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>40</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>466</playerid>
					<name>Piyush Chawla</name>
					<bowler-name>Chawla</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chawla</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>10</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>544</playerid>
					<name>Shakib Al Hasan</name>
					<bowler-name>Shakib</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shakib</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>17</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>308</playerid>
					<name>Gautam Gambhir</name>
					<bowler-name>Gambhir</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Gambhir</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>527</playerid>
					<name>Robin Uthappa</name>
					<bowler-name>Uthappa</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Uthappa</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1836</playerid>
					<name>Manish Pandey</name>
					<bowler-name>M Pandey</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M Pandey</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7915</playerid>
					<name>Suryakumar Yadav</name>
					<bowler-name>Suryakumar Yadav</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Suryakumar Yadav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



