<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14638" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>45th Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Delhi</home>
		<away>Hyderabad</away>
		<teamsabbr>DEL vs HYD</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>DEL</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>HYD</awayabbr>
		<homeId>61</homeId>
		<awayId>255</awayId>
		<venue>Shaheed Veer Narayan Singh International Stadium, Raipur</venue>
		<startdate>09 05 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>09 05 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Hyderabad</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Hyderabad won by 6 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Hyderabad</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>6</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>S Ravi</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Vineet Kulkarni</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Richard Illingworth</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Ranjan Madugalle</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>14:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150509175909</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>DEL</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>HYD</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>157</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>4</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>20</batteamovers>
		<status>Hyderabad won by 6 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>1601</playerid>
			<name>Saurabh Tiwary*</name>
			<batsman-name>S Tiwary</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>S Tiwary</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>26</runs>
			<balls-faced>25</balls-faced>
			<fours>2</fours>
			<sixes>1</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>1851</playerid>
			<name>Kedar Jadhav</name>
			<batsman-name>K Jadhav</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>K Jadhav</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>63</runs>
			<balls-faced>34</balls-faced>
			<fours>8</fours>
			<sixes>2</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1726</playerid>
			<name>Bhuvneshwar Kumar*</name>
			<bowler-name>Bhuvneshwar</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Bhuvneshwar</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>20</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>702</playerid>
			<name>Ishant Sharma</name>
			<bowler-name>Ishant</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Ishant</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>39</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>164</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>211</playerid>
<name>Jean-Paul Duminy</name>
<player-runs>12</player-runs>
<player-balls>16</player-balls>
<runs>66</runs>
<wicket-nbr>4</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>1844</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Karn Sharma</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>1</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>3</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>4</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[. . 4 . 4 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 1 . . 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 L1 1 1 1 L1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 1 2 1 1 . ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/DEL_HYD_MAY09/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[That's it from us today. We enjoyed bringing you the two games. There is another double-header coming your way tomorrow. First, it is MUM taking on BLR at the Wankhede, then CHN face RAJ at the Chepauk. Join us for all the action from those games. Until then, rest well and Cya!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here are some of the best <b>tweets</b> pertaining to this game...]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Alt Cricket:</b> Well, that's one of the best death overs I've seen from an Indian bowler. Take a bow Bhuvneshwar Kumar!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sarang Bhalerao:</b> Bhuvneshwar Kumar has become a yorker machine!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Navneet Mundhra:</b> How many matches #DEL have lost on last ball of the match this year... I remember 3 off-hand... Lacks the punch to deliver coup de grace #IPL]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Saurabh Malhotra:</b> #PUN will have to win their three remaining games to hand over the wooden spoon to #DEL (if they lose both as expected).]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ayaz Memon:</b> Two last over finishes & another great day in IPL, though it will leave Punjab and Delhi unhappy. But who can they blame except themselves?]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Henriques:</b> "It is nice to get a run and that too an extended run. I was struggling early on and wanted to take it deep into the innings. To come in to bat at No. 3 or 4, you have to bat around the others and that is what I do back home. I was not as nervous as I used to be. I recognise that it is just a game of cricket. With a couple of good overs from Bhuvi and Ishant we swung it our way."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Moises Henriques</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his 46-ball 74.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Warner:</b> "It was a good fightback after the first 6 overs. It was a great innings from Moises there. Good support from Karn and Ravi. We knew they were going to come hard, credit to Quinny (de Kock) for taking us by surprise. Credit to Ishant Sharma for the way he came back after his first game against CHN. The leg-spin was coming nicely onto the bat, but with Jadhav's innings it was not possible to give Karn a bowl. Bhuvi was excellent once again. The wickets in India are suiting the slower bowlers, it is unfortunate that they (Steyn and Boult) are missing out. It is jam packed up there and we need to keep winning every game from now."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Duminy:</b> "Probably with three overs to go we thought we had a chance, but Bhuvi bowled an exceptional over. They batted extremely well and the way they ran kept us on the feet. We were in the game for the first 15th over, but all credit to Moises (Henriques) with the innings he played. We lost too many wickets up front. Kedar (Jadhav) played an exceptional innings to get us close, but it unfortunately didn't go our way. It was a pretty good wicket. We have to put in a good performance in the last two games."]]></line><line><![CDATA[HYD's total was mainly built on the back of a sterling fifty by Moises Henriques. He took his time before opening up his shoulders to play some eye-catching strokes. Jayant Yadav and Coulter-Nile gave a good account of themselves with the ball in hand. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Despite Kedar Jadhav essaying an impressive fifty, DEL slipped towards a gut-wrenching defeat. It was Bhuvneshwar Kumar and Ishant Sharma, who held their nerve with the ball to steer the visitors to a crucial win. With this win, HYD are now placed fourth in the points table. For DEL, Jadhav played with guts and determination to keep them in the hunt. It was in the 16th over when Jadhav cracked two sixes and a four off Praveen Kumar to give them genuine hopes of winning the game, but in the end, they weren't able to cross the finish line. It has to be also remembered that de Kock gave DEL a rousing start with a sparkling fifty.  <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Warner is elated as he comes running from the rope towards his team-mates. All the HYD players congratulate each other. Ishant also let out a roar after fielding the final ball. Moody also has a smile on his face. This defeat for DEL means they are <b>officially knocked out of the tournament.</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to K Jadhav, no run, <b>HYD win by 6 runs.</b> Superb delivery from Ishant. Yorker on off, Jadhav can't get under that, he digs it back to the bowler. Ishant fields the ball and throws it up in delight]]></line><line><![CDATA[DEL need 6 to tie and take it to the Super Over. Once again Warner and Ishant in the middle of a discussion]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to S Tiwary, 1 run, length delivery on the stumps, Tiwary mistimes the heave to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to K Jadhav, 1 run, <b>dropped!</b> But Praveen saved three runs. It was a very poor delivery from Ishant, short and down leg, Jadhav was backing away, he tries to help it on the way, doesn't middle it as the ball lobs to short fine, Praveen dives to his right, gets both hands, but it pops out]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to K Jadhav, 2 runs, banged in short and cramps the batsman for room, Jadhav splices the pull to mid-wicket, Henriques had to run in a long way, he picked it up with one hand and fired at the striker's end, Ojha takes the bails off, but Jadhav had made it home]]></line><line><![CDATA[TV umpire called for a run-out check. Has Jadhav been run-out? He has made it in. Some relief for the DEL fans.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Warner and Ishant have a chat now. They are discussing about the field placements. Fine leg in]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to S Tiwary, 1 run, this was also a length delivery, Tiwary mistimes the hoick, picks out the fielder at mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to S Tiwary, <b>FOUR</b>, great start to the over, just what DEL wanted. Pitched up delivery on off, Tiwary clears his front leg and drills it straight down the ground, Ishant tries to stop it with his boot, but to no avail]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[DEL need 16 to win of the final over. Who is going to bowl? Warner has a few options in Ishant, Henriques and Karn Sharma. Dhoni made a tactical error of giving Negi the 19th over last night, but Warner has gone with Ishant.]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to S Tiwary, leg byes, 1 run, Bhuvneshwar appeals for lbw, but umpire Ravi says going down. It was another low full toss on the stumps, Tiwary shuffles across and misses the lap shot, it hit the boot and deflected towards backward square. No way that was going down leg, it would have crashed into middle stump. Poor decision from Ravi]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to K Jadhav, 1 run, nice juicy full toss, Jadhav is hurried on the heave, mistimes it to long-on. He should have done better with that]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to S Tiwary, 1 run, another low full toss which Tiwary can't get under, flicked to deep square leg. He wanted two but Jadhav rightly sends him back. Ojha fires a needless throw at the bowler's end, but Bhuvi backs up well. He then tells the keeper to keep calm]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to K Jadhav, 1 run, so far so good for Bhuvi and HYD. Right in the blockhole just outside off, Jadhav squeezes it to short third man, for just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to S Tiwary, leg byes, 1 run, low full toss on the pads, Tiwary fails to get bat on ball, it brushes the pad and rolls to the right of Ojha, who dives and saves some runs for the team]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to K Jadhav, 1 run, short of length on the stumps, Jadhav backs away and flat-bats it over the bowler's head, Warner runs to his left and releases the ball quickly. He gave the batsmen no chance for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>23 off 12 balls</b>. The onus on Bhuvi to bowl the 19th over and leave enough for the one bowling the last over]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to K Jadhav, 1 run, takes the pace off the ball, Jadhav goes for the hoick to the leg-side, the ball takes the outside edge and runs down to third man, Rasool keeps them down to one]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to S Tiwary, 1 run, full toss and Tiwary has missed out, he drives to extra cover and picks up only a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to S Tiwary, no run, <b>run-out chance missed.</b> Yorker on the stumps, Tiwary digs it to the left of the bowler, don't know where he was going as there was no run, Ishant runs forward, takes his time and fails to hit timber. Tiwary was nowhere in the picture, he had given up. Ojha then fires again, but Tiwary had made it in by then]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to S Tiwary, no run, short of length and slanted across the left-hander, Tiwary goes for a wild swing to the leg-side, fails to connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to K Jadhav, 1 run, slower delivery around off, Jadhav shuffles across and nurdles it square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to K Jadhav, <b>FOUR</b>, the look on Moody's face says it all. He just looks at the ball reaching the fence. Jadhav jumps out of the crease, Ishant digs it short and just outside off, the top edged pull flies over the keeper's head]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ishant Sharma [2.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>29 runs from 18 balls</b>. On most days you bet on the team chasing, but can DEL hold their nerve to pull it off? We'll have to wait and watch. Ishant to bowl the crucial 18th over]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to K Jadhav, 1 run, low wide full toss from Bhuvi, Jadhav reaches out and squeezes it to extra cover, keeps strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to K Jadhav, <b>FOUR</b>, Jadhav registers his <b>second IPL fifty</b>. He has got it in 24 balls. It has been an extraordinary innings. The whole DEL team are up on their feet, applauding the knock. Full and wide outside off, Jadhav reaches out and slices it square of the wicket, beats the sweeper cover with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to K Jadhav, no run, Bhuvneshwar keeps it wide of the batsman, Jadhav came advancing and can't lay bat on ball. It was too far away from him]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to K Jadhav, <b>FOUR</b>, two dots and Jadhav gets a boundary off the third ball. He was expecting the yorker, was into position quickly, crouches low, opens the bat face and steers it between backward point and short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to K Jadhav, no run, Ojha appeals for caught behind, but nothing from umpire Ravi. Excellent yorker, Jadhav goes down and tries to squeeze it out, he misses and the ball goes through to Ojha. The sound was bat hitting the ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to K Jadhav, no run, oh he has missed out there, full delivery outside off, Jadhav throws everything at that, but fails to connect. Both him and Bhuvi have a smile on their face]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Bhuvneshwar Kumar [2.0-0-7-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[That over from Praveen cost HYD 22 runs and hence has brought the required run-rate below 10. If these two continue, no reason why DEL can't win this.]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to S Tiwary, 2 runs, Tiwary comes down the track, Praveen follows him with a full delivery, Tiwary manages to lift it over cover, Warner leaps but in vain, the ball rolls towards wide long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to S Tiwary, 2 runs, angling in from round the wicket, Tiwary clips it wide of long-on, called for two immediately and gets it comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to S Tiwary, <b>wide</b>, slips the slower one down leg, easy call for the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to K Jadhav, 1 run, drags the slower ball halfway down the wicket, Jadhav swats it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to K Jadhav, <b>SIX</b>, this is amazing hitting. Praveen is helping him by bowling freebies, full toss just below waist height, Jadhav comes down the track and heaves it high and over deep square leg for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to K Jadhav, <b>FOUR</b>, Jadhav is pre-meditating, he skips out of the crease, expects it to be a full delivery, takes it on the full and hammers it straight back over the bowler. No chance for the long-off or long-on fielders]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to K Jadhav, <b>SIX</b>, simply marvellous! This is a very difficult shot to play, but he made it look so easy and what's more he cleared the fence comfortably. Good length delivery just outside off, Jadhav backs away and lofts it inside out over extra cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Praveen Kumar [1.0-0-12-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to S Tiwary, no run, back of a length outside off, Tiwary guides it straight to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to K Jadhav, 1 run, Jadhav advances down the track, Henriques drops it short, pulled to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to K Jadhav, no run, back of a length around off, Jadhav bunts it in front of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to K Jadhav, no run, this one stops on the batsman, Jadhav checks his shot and knocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to K Jadhav, <b>FOUR</b>, bad delivery and deserved the treatment. Short and on leg-stump, Jadhav swivels on the pull and hits it behind square leg, fine leg had no chance of cutting that off]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to K Jadhav, 2 runs, slower full delivery outside off, Jadhav drives to deep extra cover and picks up two]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Moises Henriques [1.0-0-7-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to S Tiwary, 2 runs, Bopara comes round the wicket, angles it into the left-hander, Tiwary works it wide of long-on, called straightaway for two and gets it easily, even though Warner was the fielder. An expensive first over from Bopara, 15 runs off it]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to K Jadhav, 1 run, slower delivery around off, Jadhav dabs it to the left of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to K Jadhav, <b>FOUR</b>, third boundary of the over. Bopara has been very poor in this over, drops it short at his pace, Jadhav pulls it towards deep mid-wicket, beat the two fielders in the deep to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to K Jadhav, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! Shortens the length just outside off, Jadhav goes back and punches it in front of square on the off-side, Morgan runs across from sweeper cover, but can't get there as it was timed sweetly]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to K Jadhav, no run, on a length just outside off, Jadhav is beaten on the drive and Ojha whips the bails off. However, Jadhav was always in the crease. In fact, it was the back of the hand slower delivery that hit the seam and held its line]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to K Jadhav, <b>FOUR</b>, deftly done. Back of a length delivery angling in on off, Jadhav stays in the crease, opens the bat face at the last instant and runs it down to third man, the fielder was inside the ring and he was square]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravi Bopara, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Tiwary, no run, googly around off, Tiwary knocks it to the off-side, Jadhav was halfway down the wicket for the single before he was sent back, Ojha runs across and fires at the non-striker's end, he misses and Jadhav makes it in. A direct hit would have been interesting]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Tiwary, <b>SIX</b>, fabulous shot! Great use of the feet. He is showing some intent. Tiwary dances down the wicket, gets to the pitch of the ball and lofts it handsomely over long-on for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Tiwary, no run, Ojha goes up for an lbw appeal, but umpire Ravi is unmoved. The tossed up delivery turns back in, Tiwary ekes out an inside edge onto the pad, that was the only thing that saved him]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to K Jadhav, 1 run, flighted on off, Jadhav wrists it down to long-on, Tiwary wanted two but is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Tiwary, 1 run, drifting onto the pads, Tiwary nudges it behind square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to K Jadhav, 1 run, nice loopy delivery, Jadhav kneels down and sweeps to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to S Tiwary, no run, floated up outside off, Tiwary drives and finds cover. Rasool finishes a superb spell, he should have had more than one, but in the end the scorecard will read: <b>4-0-20-1</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to S Tiwary, no run, skids on after pitching, keeps a bit low as well, Tiwary manages to bring his bat down and jam it to the right of the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to K Jadhav, 1 run, <b>dropped!</b> Ojha has grassed one. Pushed through just outside off, Jadhav opens the bat face and runs it off the face of the bat, Ojha didn't follow the ball, it hits the glove and rolls away to short third man. That was a regulation take for the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to S Tiwary, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Tiwary leans into the drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to S Tiwary, <b>FOUR</b>, what a way to open ones account. Flighted delivery outside off, Tiwary shimmies down the wicket and drills the drive wide of long-off, Warner had few yards to cover, but he can't get there]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket for Tiwary]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to K Jadhav, 1 run, works it with the turn to backward square leg, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Tiwary, no run, appeal for LBW, not given. Was it sliding down the leg-side? Flighted delivery on the stumps, Tiwary fails to defend, gets hit in line with middle and leg and gets away with it]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Tiwary, no run, on the stumps, punched back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Tiwary, no run, googly from Karn Sharma, Tiwary defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to S Tiwary, no run, on the stumps, turned to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Saurabh Tiwary, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Duminy, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Is that the game for HYD? This is precisely why de Kock's shot was needless. DEL have lost 3 wickets in the space of 12 balls. de Kock was batting so well with Duminy and the duo looked in complete control, but his dismissal has opened the floodgates. Flighted delivery pitching just outside off stump, Duminy plays inside the line, tries to run it down to third man off the back foot, the ball goes past the outside edge and shaves the off stump. <b>Duminy b Karn Sharma 12(16)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Karn Sharma to Duminy, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Has Duminy been bowled? He's walking, but he's been told to wait by the umpires as they have sent it upstairs. No issues with Karn Sharma's footing. Oh yes! <b>That's bowled</b>. Bye bye JP Duminy!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to K Jadhav, 1 run, shortish and outside off stump, Jadhav cuts it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kedar Jadhav, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to Yuvraj, <b>out</b> Caught by Karn Sharma!! This is an irresponsible shot from a senior player like Yuvraj Singh. Nothing but a flighted delivery on the stumps, a gentle drive along the ground was the need of the hour, instead, Yuvraj comes down the track. He doesn't look for a big shot either, just lofts the drive gently and times it so sweetly that long-on didn't have to move an inch. Davey Warner is delighted and he pumps his fist. <b>Yuvraj c Karn Sharma b P Rasool 2(7)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[P Rasool to Yuvraj, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to Yuvraj, no run, tossed up just outside off stump, Yuvraj mistimes the drive back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to Yuvraj, no run, slider on the stumps, blocked]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to Duminy, 1 run, fired full and on the leg stump, driven down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to Yuvraj, 1 run, low full toss on the leg stump, Yuvraj flicks it to mid-wicket, where Ishant dives to his left and half-stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to Duminy, 1 run, tossed up on the off stump, Duminy drives it down to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Yuvraj, no run, on the off stump, Yuvraj defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Duminy, 1 run, turns it with the spin to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Yuvraj, 1 run, on the stumps, Yuvraj drives it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Yuvraj, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Yuvraj defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Yuvraj Singh, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to de Kock, <b>out</b> Stumped!! Needless from de Kock. It's not going to be easy for the new batsman, especially with the ball getting older. He comes down the track and looks to slog, doesn't get to the pitch of the ball, it keeps a bit low as well and the keeper did the rest. <b>de Kock st N Ojha b Karn Sharma 50(31) [4s-9 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Karn Sharma to de Kock, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Stumped!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to de Kock, no run, short and outside off stump, de Kock cuts it to short third man, Ishant makes a diving save to his left, the ball just rolled away from him, de Kock took off for a run, Duminy didn't respond, as Ishant took time to recover and get to the ball de Kock gestured to Duminy that there was a run on, but Duminy asks him to go back to his crease. de Kock then wears a smile on his face]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Karn Sharma, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to Duminy, no run, can't call that a dropped chance. Flatter delivery outside off stump, Duminy goes for the cut, toe-ends it, the ball hits the keeper's pad and rolls to short third man. There was hardly any time for the keeper to react]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to Duminy, no run, low full toss, Duminy tries to paddle it fine but gets an edge onto his front pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to de Kock, 1 run, short and outside off stump, de Kock rocks back and cuts it to the man at sweeper to get to his <b>maiden IPL fifty</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to Duminy, 1 run, on the leg stump, Duminy tucks it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to de Kock, 1 run, tossed up outside off stump, de Kock mistimes the lofted drive and it goes on the bounce to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to Duminy, 1 run, spinning away outside off stump, Duminy cuts it to the left of backward point, who dives and makes a half stop]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Parvez Rasool [1.0-0-6-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Quinton de Kock's onslaught means HYD have called for an early <b>time-out</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to de Kock, <b>FOUR</b>, he's a little man but he can strike the ball very hard. The bat made a crunching sound as it made contact with the ball. Too short from Henriques, the only poor ball of the over and it spoils the party. de Kock rocks back and pulls over mid-wicket, beats the man at deep square leg as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to de Kock, no run, low full toss, the slower ball again, de Kock mistimes the slog to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Duminy, 1 run, waits for the length ball to come and guides it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to de Kock, 1 run, slower ball yorker, squeezed out to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Duminy, 1 run, slower delivery very full, Duminy looks to drive, gets an inside edge onto boot and it rolls to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Duminy, no run, starts off with an inswinging yorker on the leg stump, dug out to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Moises Henriques, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to de Kock, <b>SIX</b>, de Kock knew that Ishant was going to bowl a short ball two weeks ago. He was waiting for it! The line is on the leg stump, with fine leg inside the ring, de Kock goes across the stumps and helps it on its way and clears the fine leg boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to de Kock, <b>FOUR</b>, a fumble and it's gone for four. Bopara the culprit, shortish and just outside off stump, de Kock cuts it to cover-point, Bopara gets down on one knee to stop the ball but it bounces over the right shoulder]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to de Kock, no run, slower delivery following the batsman as he makes room, de Kock flicks it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to de Kock, no run, de Kock tries to be cheeky and walks right across the stumps, tries to help it on its way but gets hit on the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to de Kock, <b>FOUR</b>, de Kock is looking ominous. Poor bowling from Ishant, he's allowing the batsman to camp on the back foot, short of a length delivery just outside off stump, de Kock muscles the pull hard over mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to Duminy, 1 run, mistimed pull shot, but luckily it went wide of the man at mid-wicket. Shortish delivery on the off stump, it was there to be put away but Duminy didn't get the timing right]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ishant Sharma [1.0-0-8-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to de Kock, no run, yorker length delivery on the off stump, de Kock digs it out, Praveen tries to kick the ball onto the stumps but missed and it rolled to mid-on. Expensive over from Praveen]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to de Kock, <b>FOUR</b>, take that! Full and in the slot, de Kock drives very hard and it rockets to the fence between mid-off and extra-cover. He's looking very good in his first match of the season]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to de Kock, no run, good length delivery on the off stump, de Kock drives it to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to de Kock, <b>FOUR</b>, too short from round the wicket, asking to be hit, de Kock waits for the ball to come and nails the pull shot to perfection over mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to de Kock, <b>FOUR</b>, de Kock goes right across the stumps, Praveen follows him with a bumper, de Kock pulls it over short fine leg and gets four runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Duminy, leg byes, 1 run, short of length delivery down the leg-side, Duminy fails to tickle it, the ball rolls to short fine, the fielder fumbles but it doesn't cost an extra run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Praveen Kumar, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to Duminy, 1 run, advances and flicks the flighted delivery through mid-wicket to mid-wicket and keeps strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to Duminy, 2 runs, flighted delivery on the stump, Duminy gets down on one knee and sweeps it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to de Kock, 1 run, a fumble by Dhawan at point allows a run, de Kock cut it hard, straight to the fielder and that should have been stopped]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to de Kock, no run, tossed up outside off stump, de Kock pushed to the right of the bowler, who runs and dives to his right to stop the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to de Kock, 2 runs, in the airrrrr and Ishant doesn't get there. Flighted delivery on the off stump, de Kock dances down the track and goes for the loft, gets it on the bottom of the bat, it goes high in the air, Ishant runs back from mid-on but the ball lands safely]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Rasool to de Kock, no run, flighted delivery just outside off stump, de Kock defends]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Parvez Rasool, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[One slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to de Kock, 1 run, a late call for a quick single but de Kock escapes. A <b>direct-hit would have been very close</b>. de Kock mistimes the flick to the right of mid-wicket, takes a while and then decides to set off, the fielder picks it up with one hand and has a shy at the bowler's end, had one stump to aim at and he missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Duminy, 1 run, on the leg stump, Duminy turns it to backward square leg and opens his account]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jean-Paul Duminy, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Shreyas Iyer, <b>out</b> Caught&Bowled!! This was on the cards. He was never comfortable against Bhuvneshwar and he offers a return catch. Short delivery on the off stump, Iyer goes for the pull, but the ball hits the splice of the bat and goes up in the air, Bhuvi called for it, didn't have to move much and he took it easily. That climbed steeply onto Iyer and he couldn't control the shot. Early wicket for HYD. <b>Shreyas Iyer c and b Bhuvneshwar 0(7)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bhuvneshwar to Shreyas Iyer, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught&Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Shreyas Iyer, no run, bumper on the off stump, Iyer tries to pull but only connects with thin air]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Shreyas Iyer, no run, nice shape away from the right-hander, Iyer tries to cut and gets beaten again]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Shreyas Iyer, no run, outswinger outside off stump, Iyer goes for the cut but doesn't make contact]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to de Kock, <b>FOUR</b>, this time the use of the feet from de Kock, converts this into a length ball, also makes a bit of room, it was widish again from Ishant, de Kock lofts it over cover and picks up his third boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to de Kock, no run, oh no! Quinton de Kock! This is a metre outside off stump and for some reason he opts to pull than dab/cut it. It's very risky but he gets away with it again]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to de Kock, no run, beaten again! Ishant gets his line right, the first two deliveries were very wide, this time he keeps it close to the off stump, the angle away from the left-hander is troubling de Kock and the ball almost takes the outside edge again]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to de Kock, no run, well bowled! Ishant had de Kock poking at that one. Good length delivery just moving away outside off stump, de Kock tries to defend, checks his shot and gets beaten as the ball bounces extra]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to de Kock, <b>FOUR</b>, now he gets his shot selection right. Short of a length outside off stump, de Kock waits for the ball and cuts it nicely off the back foot and beats backward point to his right]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ishant to de Kock, no run, oopsy! Ugly shot from de Kock. This short of length delivery was way outside off stump, Ishant's angle from over the wicket takes it further away from the batsman, de Kock tries to fetch the pull when he could have cut it easily and gets beaten]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ishant Sharma, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Shreyas Iyer, no run, tries the away-going this time, probably keeps a bit low as well, Iyer just manages to keep it out from the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Shreyas Iyer, no run, covers the inswing and nudges this short of length delivery to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Shreyas Iyer, no run, big inswinger into the right-hander, Iyer misses the flick, the ball goes uppishly to square leg off the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to de Kock, 1 run, <b>almost dragged on</b>. Good length delivery nipping back in, de Kock jams his bat down at the last moment and chops it towards the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to de Kock, <b>FOUR</b>, that ball races away between two diving fielders. Width on offer outside off stump, de Kock is very strong square of the wicket on the off-side, goes for the cut, gets it on the bottom of the bat, yet the ball beats short cover-point and backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to de Kock, no run, bit of outswing on this short of length delivery, de Kock is opened up by the movement but he manages to defend it off the back foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>de Kock and Shreyas Iyer are at the crease. de Kock is on strike. Bhuvneshwar will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back for the run chase. Bhuvi to open the attack for HYD. How many slips does he have? Just one. Backward point, short cover-point, extra-cover and mid-off is the field on the off-side.]]></line><line><![CDATA[When required, Henriques' bat swung in a straight arc and then in the 19th over, took a heavy toll off Albie Morkel by thwacking him for two sixes. He also completed his maiden fifty in the IPL in 39 balls. DEL have a task on their hands, as it is not an easy track to bat on. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Moises Henriques played a well-measured knock to guide HYD to a good total. On a track that gave the seamers a bit of assistance, the likes of Zaheer Khan and Coulter-Nile bowled economical spells up front and were rewarded with wickets. Even Jayant Yadav, the offspinner, made his presence felt by dismissing Eoin Morgan. However, Henriques twinned rotation of strike and essayed fine shots to steady the innings. Ravi Bopara gave him valuable support with a handy knock. <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Bopara, 1 run, Bopara takes a step down the wicket, takes it on the full and toe-ends the loft on the bounce to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Henriques, 1 run, too full and close to off, Henriques squeezes the drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Henriques, 2 runs, in the blockhole, Henriques digs it out to mid-wicket for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Henriques, <b>SIX</b>, Henriques is dealing in sixes now. Short delivery just outside off, Henriques flat-bats it straight down the ground, Tiwary runs to his left, stretches out his left-hand and tries to parry it back, but in vain]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Henriques, no run, yorker length around off, Henriques squeezes it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Bopara, 1 run, short delivery at the batsman, Bopara gloves the pull that lands in front of the short fine leg fielder. Bopara signals to Henriques that it rose steeply]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Zaheer Khan [3.0-0-22-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Henriques, <b>SIX</b>, consecutive sixes for Henriques. They are upping the ante. Length delivery in the slot, Henriques opens himself up and tonks it over cow corner. He is packing some power behind these hits as they are clearing the rope with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Henriques, <b>SIX</b>, massive! It was not off the meat of the bat, but shows you the power of Henriques. Morkel goes short, Henriques hangs back and pulls it over deep mid-wicket for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Henriques, 2 runs, where is the energy to run the twos? Yorker on the stumps, Henriques clears his front leg and digs it in front of deep mid-wicket, another easy two]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Bopara, 1 run, dug in short and at the batsman, Bopara miscues the pull to square leg, Duminy keeps them down to one]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Bopara, 2 runs, once more brilliant running. The slower delivery just outside off, Bopara walks across and nurdles it to deep backward square leg, he had to put in the dive to make the crease and he does it comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Bopara, <b>FOUR</b>, smashed! Bopara shimmies down the wicket, Morkel bowls a length delivery, Bopara drills it to the left of the bowler, the power on that beat the dive from the long-off fielder as well]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Henriques, 2 runs, <b>maiden IPL fifty</b> for Henriques. Coach Tom Moody applauds from the dug-out. Full delivery on leg-stump, Henriques flicks it to deep mid-wicket and the duo take another two, have lost count now of how many doubles these two have ran]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Henriques, <b>wide</b>, round-armish and darted outside off, Henriques lets it go and umpire calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Henriques, 2 runs, another full toss on the pads, Henriques eases it between deep mid-wicket and long-on for a double]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Bopara, 1 run, flatter and just outside off, Bopara flat-bats it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Henriques, 1 run, fired, full and on the stumps, Henriques drives it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Henriques, 2 runs, low full toss on leg-stump, Henriques flicks it wide of long-on, comes back for the second before Tiwary can get to the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Henriques, no run, pushed through from round the wicket, Henriques slaps it straight to extra cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jean-Paul Duminy [1.0-0-7-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Henriques, 1 run, full on off and middle, Henriques clips it to deep mid-wicket, Iyer fumbles but the batsmen don't risk the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Henriques, 2 runs, full and on the stumps, Henriques shuffles across and flicks it wide of long-on for another brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Bopara, 1 run, off-cutter from Morkel, Bopara closes the bat face a little early, the leading edge rolls to the right of point]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Henriques, 1 run, drags the slower ball halfway down the wicket, Henriques manages to adjust and pull it behind square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Bopara, 1 run, fullish and just outside off, Bopara drives towards cover and runs as soon as he played that]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Bopara, 2 runs, fourth two in a row. Slower delivery on off, Bopara nudges it to mid-wicket and comes back for the second. These two making use of the long boundaries]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Albie Morkel [1.0-0-6-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Henriques, 2 runs, Mishra is not happy with the fielding effort. That is a hat-trick of twos. Flighted on off, Henriques wrists it in front of long-on, it was once again Bopara who pushed his partner. The arrival of Bopara has certainly improved the running]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Henriques, 2 runs, pushed through close to off, Henriques punches it to deep extra cover, Bopara pushed Henriques for the second and the Australian had to put in the long yards. Iyer was a bit slow to get to the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire pressed into service for a run-out chance. Henriques is safe.]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Henriques, 2 runs, flatter, fuller and on middle, Henriques works it to mid-wicket, Bopara sprinted back for the second as the throw came to his end]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Henriques, <b>SIX</b>, Mishra has been poor on a wicket that has aided the spinners. Half tracker just outside off, Henriques goes deep in the crease and pulls it over mid-wicket for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Bopara, 1 run, tossed up around off, Bopara drives along the ground to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Bopara, 2 runs, floated up on off, Bopara kneels down and paddles it to long leg, QdK anticipated that and moved to his left, but it was well wide of him]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Amit Mishra [2.0-0-19-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravi Bopara, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Karn Sharma, <b>out</b> Caught by Jayant Yadav!! NCN finishes his spell with a wicket. Short delivery around off, Karn makes room to the leg-side and is hurried on the pull, the ball hits the splice of the bat and balloons over backward point, Yadav runs back and takes a very good catch. <b>Karn Sharma c Jayant Yadav b Coulter-Nile 16(13) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Coulter-Nile to Karn Sharma, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place for Karn]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Henriques, 1 run, good length ball just outside off, Henriques dabs it to backward point and sets off, the fielder doesn't shy at the stumps as there was no one backing up]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Karn Sharma, 1 run, banged in halfway down the wicket, Karn backs away and splices the pull to the left of mid-on, in the air but short of Zak]]></line><line><![CDATA[Changes to round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Henriques, 1 run, Coulter-Nile persists with the short delivery, this time a bit quicker, Henriques mistimes the pull to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Henriques, <b>FOUR</b>, top shot! Can't bowl short to an Australian. It was back of a length around off, Henriques was quick to transfer his weight on the back foot and pulls in front of square, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Henriques, no run, goes wide of the crease and spears in a yorker, Henriques fails to dig it out, it was very close to the off-pole. Coulter-Nile has his hands on his head, he knew how close it was]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Karn Sharma, no run, another slower delivery, Karn guides it towards backward point and sets off, Henriques shouts a loud "no"]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Henriques, 1 run, shortish and outside off, Henriques cuts to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Henriques, 2 runs, change of pace from Morkel, Henriques nudges it with soft hands to mid-wicket, calls for two and gets it easily as the fielder had to come in a long way from the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Henriques, no run, Henriques races down the wicket, Morkel drags the length back, flat-batted straight to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Karn Sharma, 1 run, back of a length on the stumps, Karn is early into the pull, gets a top-edge that falls well in front of the deep square leg fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Morkel to Karn Sharma, 2 runs, good length ball just outside off, Karn drives it in the air over cover, comes back for the second before the ball is hunted down]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Albie Morkel, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Slight delay in play as Albie Morkel comes onto bowl. The umpires had a chat with Duminy, don't know what was it about]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Karn Sharma, 1 run, Coulter-Nile has not pitched a single delivery up to the batsman in this over, keeps it short of length outside off, Karn glides it off the face of the bat to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Karn Sharma, no run, short of length and rising onto the batsman, Karn gets on top of the bounce and defends to the off-side, he wanted the single but Henriques says no]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Henriques, 1 run, short of length just outside off, Henriques steers it down to third man with an angled bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Karn Sharma, 1 run, again, Coulter-Nile bowls it short and around off, Karn drops it in front of cover and hares across for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Karn Sharma, no run, back of a length on off, Karn has no room to work with, taps it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Karn Sharma, <b>FOUR</b>, "catch it" shouted Coulter-Nile, but it was well wide of QdK. Starts from round the wicket, keeps it short and around off, Karn opens the bat face and runs it just wide of the keeper, QdK dived to his left but in vain]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Nathan Coulter-Nile [2.0-0-11-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Henriques, no run, quicker and outside off, Henriques plays a wristy drive to cover, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Henriques, <b>SIX</b>, smashed! It takes a lot to clear the big boundaries at Raipur, but Henriques did it with ease. Flighted on the stumps, Henriques gets to the pitch of the ball and whips it over wide long-on for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Henriques, 2 runs, nice floaty delivery outside off, Henriques drives it to the right of sweeper cover for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Karn Sharma, leg byes, 1 run, drifting onto the pads, Karn doesn't get anything on the glance, the batsmen sneak in a leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Karn Sharma, <b>FOUR</b>, floated up on middle and leg, Karn paddles it fine and beats the fielder at long leg. That was played extremely well from the leg-spinner. He is picking Mishra]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Karn Sharma, 2 runs, too straight from Mishra, Karn nudges it square of the wicket on the leg-side, picks up two]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Henriques, no run, flighted outside off, Henriques pushes it back to the bowler. End of a fine spell from Jayant Yadav, he finishes with figures: <b>4-0-19-1</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Henriques, no run, slightly quicker and just outside off, Henriques goes hard on the drive, mistimes it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Karn Sharma, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Eoin Morgan, <b>out</b> Caught by Coulter-Nile!! Maiden IPL wicket for Jayant Yadav. He has bowled well and deserved that wicket. Tosses it up on middle, Morgan moves away to the leg-side and wanted to go inside out, hits it a lot straighter than he would have liked, NCN runs forward from long-off and takes a good low catch. He had to put in the dive to get there. <b>Eoin Morgan c Coulter-Nile b Jayant Yadav 22(25) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Jayant Yadav to Eoin Morgan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Eoin Morgan, no run, tossed up on off, Morgan knocks it to the on-side, Henriques wanted the run but Morgan says no as Yadav gets to the ball quickly]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Henriques, 1 run, flatter and around off, Henriques swats it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, slower and on middle, Morgan chips it to the vacant mid-wicket region, Yadav tidies up himself]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, fires this full, Morgan easily drives it to long-on. He'll keep strike with that]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Henriques, 1 run, slider on the leg stump, hurries Henriques, who manages to punch it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, punches this googly off the back foot to deep backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Eoin Morgan, no run, Morgan goes early into the reverse-sweep, Mishra bowls this slower through the air, gets it to turn and hits Morgan on the body. No harm done though]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Henriques, 1 run, not much of turn on this short ball, punched to deep cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mishra to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, on the leg stump, Morgan turns it with the spin to square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Amit Mishra, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[During the break. Gary Kirsten, Zak and Duminy were having a chat, while Tom Moody was seen talking to Morgan and Henriques.]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's time for the <b>time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Henriques, no run, on the off stump, defends it with the spin to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Henriques, no run, pushed through, Henriques drives off the back foot, Jayant Yadav moves to his right and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Henriques, no run, flatter delivery just outside off stump, punched back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Henriques, 2 runs, deft touch, Zak gives chase from short third and hunts it down. Henriques opens the face of the bat at the last moment to guide it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Henriques, no run, waits for the ball to spin back in and softly punches it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, short ball, Morgs backs away, doesn't bother exposing his sticks and cuts, hits it in the air but there was no one at backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, down the track this time to drive it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Eoin Morgan, no run, Morgan looks to give the charge to the bowler, but Duminy fires it flat and forces Morgs to push it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Eoin Morgan, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Morgan defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Eoin Morgan, <b>FOUR</b>, reverse-sweep and that has been hit over backward point. Very full from Duminy, Morgan plays it nicely from the middle of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Henriques, 1 run, in the airrrrr and again doesn't go to hand. Duminy sees Henriques advancing and drops it short, Henriques gets a leading edge as he closes the face of the bat while trying to nudge it on the on-side, but it goes to the left of Albie Morkel at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[Long-on, deep mid-wicket and deep square leg in place for Henriques]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Duminy to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, nicely floated up on the leg stump, Morgan drives it straight to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jean-Paul Duminy, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, again Morgs checks his shot, somehow the ball splits short cover and cover-point to perfection. It was in the air for a long time and it could have so easily gone to hand. The ball spun away sharply and foxed the batsman on that occasion]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Eoin Morgan, 2 runs, on the leg stump, easily tickled down to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Henriques, 1 run, lovely looking back foot punch from Henriques to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, checks his shot and it goes uppishly, luckily for Morgs, it doesn't carry to the bowler and beats his dive to his right before escaping to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Henriques, 1 run, spinning back in, Henriques turns it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Henriques, no run, flighted delivery on the leg stump, Henriques pushes it to the right of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jayant Yadav [1.0-0-8-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Oops! Zak did not pick up a wicket against Rajasthan. Ignore that stat. My bad.]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Eoin Morgan, <b>FOUR</b>, he's not missing it this time. Shortish delivery on the leg stump, Morgan whips it over square leg and it runs away for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Eoin Morgan, no run, he was thrashing these the other day, but he's very watchful today and misses out on a leg stump length ball, turned straight to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Henriques, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off stump, punched with an angled bat to square third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, slight hesitation in running between the wickets, but they complete the run. Morgan defends with an angled bat, the ball goes off the outside half of the bat and rolls to point, Morgan takes a step forward and then stops for a moment but Henriques was always keen to get back on strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Henriques, 1 run, hint of inswing on this good length delivery, Henriques covers the off stump, looks to drive, gets it on the inside half of the bat and goes wide of mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Henriques, <b>wide</b>, oops! Tries to angle one into the right-hander and sprays it down the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, inside edge onto pad as Morgs is slightly beaten by the movement back into him, it rolls behind square on the on-side after brushing the thigh pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, off the mark now, turns this short of length delivery to mid-wicket and keeps strike as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Eoin Morgan, no run, this time gets nicely behind the line and defends well]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Eoin Morgan, no run, is that a good leave or bad leave? I'll leave it to you. Good length delivery angling into the left-hander, probably Morgan trusted the bounce and let it go. However, he did not cover the stumps and it almost shaved the off pole]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Eoin Morgan, no run, back of a length and steeply rising, Morgan hops and defends it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Eoin Morgan, no run, short of length delivery on the off stump, Morgan defends off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Eoin Morgan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[One slip in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Warner, <b>out</b> Caught by S Tiwary!! This is a big blow for HYD. Warner is their key player but he's thrown it away. Warner is not happy with himself as he walks back. Having lost Dhawan, Warner needed to bat deep but he's gone early. Coulter-Nile follows Warner with a short of length delivery as he makes room, Warner slogs, but the bat turns in his hands, short mid-wicket jumps and takes a sharp catch above his head. <b>Warner c S Tiwary b Coulter-Nile 17(15) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Coulter-Nile to Warner, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket now!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Since his comeback in this IPL, Zak has taken the first wicket to fall in all matches.]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Warner, 1 run, on the leg stump, turned to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Warner, <b>wide</b>, Zaheer loses the radar and bowls down the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Moises Henriques, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Dhawan, <b>out</b> Caught by A Morkel!! That's catching practice for Albie. Dhawan tries to be cheeky and perishes. Absolutely needless from the left-hander. Nothing but a short of length delivery on the leg stump, Dhawan moved across the sticks and tried to play a stylish flick, mistimed it completely, mid-wicket moved to his left to take an easy catch. Had Dhawan not walked across the stumps, he could have whipped it away easily like he did on two occasions previously. <b>Dhawan c A Morkel b Zaheer 13(10) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Zaheer to Dhawan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Dhawan, no run, bit of extra bounce on this short of length delivery, Dhawan defends it off the splice of the bat to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Dhawan, no run, full and on the leg stump, Dhawan flicks it straight to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, in the airrrrr and just over the fielder at backward square leg. Can't bowl leg stump line with no fine leg, Dhawan whips it and doesn't bother to keep it down, the fielder jumps and tries to grab it with his left hand, but the ball escapes]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Dhawan, no run, no room whatsoever on this short of length delivery, defended to the left of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Slip has been removed.]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Dhawan, 3 runs, punched in the air but in the gap as well. Fullish in length and outside off stump, Dhawan checks his drive and ends up punching it, goes wide of Duminy at mid-off and he hunts it down to save a run for his side]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Warner, 1 run, races down the track, Coulter-Nile drags his length back and also cramps him for room, Warner looks to cut again, gets an under edge and it bounces over the stumps, Dhawan calls for a quick single and makes it before QdK fired a direct-hit]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Warner, no run, short of length delivery on the off stump, Warner gives himself a bit of room and cuts well, but straight to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Warner, <b>SIX</b>, top edge and the edge of the bat is thick enough to clear the boundary. Short ball steeply rising on Warner, who goes for the hook, doesn't control it and gets away with the edge as it goes over the fine leg boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Warner, no run, fullish and on the leg stump, Warner pushes it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Coulter-Nile to Warner, no run, beaten! A lazy little slash from Warner without feet movement, luckily for HYD, he didn't drag this good length delivery back onto the sticks. The ball beat the inside edge on that occasion]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[One slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Nathan Coulter-Nile, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Dhawan, no run, Dhawan gives the charge to the bowler and looks to play on the on-side, but this short of length delivery hits him on the pad. No appeal from DEL as it was sliding down the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, poor line and Dhawan helps himself to a boundary. Short of a length delivery on the leg stump, no one at fine leg, Dhawan gets inside the line and plays the pick up shot, sends it behind square on the on-side and it bounces just inside the line]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Warner, 3 runs, that is bread and butter for Davey Warner. Much more confident this time. Short of a length and shaping away, just a bit of width on offer outside off stump and that was good enough for Warner to get on top of the bounce and drive it through cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Warner, no run, top nut from Zak! Warner was on the move towards the bowler, Zaheer shortens his length, the ball hits the seam, moves away and bounces extra as well, Warner was found fishing on a cricket pitch and he's so lucky not to have kissed it to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Warner, no run, fullish and asking Warner to go for the drive, the bat turns in Warner's hands and it rolls straight to mid-off. It wasn't all that a confident stroke from Warner]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Zaheer to Warner, no run, just a hint of outswing on this good length delivery, it was around the leg stump line, Warner was slightly opened up by the movement away from him but he manages to defend it off the back foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[One slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Zaheer Khan, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Warner, 1 run, watchfully drives this flighted delivery down to long-off and keeps strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, edged but wide of the man at slip. Flighted delivery on the off stump, Warner looks to drive gets a thick edge but it goes well wide of the fielder catching at slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Warner, no run, nice and full again, Warner digs it out towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Dhawan, 1 run, very full and on the leg stump, Dhawan drives it down to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[One slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Warner, 1 run, very full and on the off stump, Warner drives it down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[Jayant Yadav takes the new ball on his IPL debut.]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jayant Yadav to Dhawan, 1 run, flighted delivery outside off stump, Dhawan drives it towards cover, the fielder dives and pushes the ball away to allow the run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhawan and Warner are at the crease. Dhawan is on strike. Jayant Yadav will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players are making their way out to the middle. The countdown begins. We are all set for the action to begin.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Delhi</b> (Playing XI): Shreyas Iyer, Quinton de Kock(w), Jean-Paul Duminy(c), Kedar Jadhav, Yuvraj Singh, Saurabh Tiwary, Albie Morkel, Jayant Yadav, Nathan Coulter-Nile, Amit Mishra, Zaheer Khan]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hyderabad</b> (Playing XI): David Warner(c), Shikhar Dhawan, Moises Henriques, Eoin Morgan, Naman Ojha(w), Ravi Bopara, Karn Sharma, Parvez Rasool, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Praveen Kumar, Ishant Sharma]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Duminy</b>: "We would have batted as well. We just got to concentrate game by game. Three changes for us. Quinton de Kock, Nathan Coulter-Nile and Jayant Yadav come in."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Warner</b>: "Runs on the board is going to be key. Defending is our strength. Our bowlers have been generally very good in the death. One change, Vihari out for Rasool."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hyderabad have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Stay tuned as we bring you the much awaited captain views and team news as the toss is not too far away.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather Update: </b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's been a scorching hot day in the city often referred to as the "Rice bowl of India." Clouds are predicted to settle in with temperature hovering around a high of 30 degrees celsius during the course of play.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-head:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[In 5 previous occasions, DEL have won only one game while HYD sealed the remaining four. DEL's only win against HYD came in this season and they would be hoping to emulate the same.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Team news:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[HYD took a bold call in their last game by leaving out Trent Boult and Dale Steyn citing depth in the middle order and the gamble paid off. We might see the same playing XI today unless Warner decides to strengthen his bowling wing with Boult or Steyn.]]></line><line><![CDATA[DEL replaced Manoj Tiwary with Mayank Agarwal in their previous clash and the former failed to capitalize on a decent start. Albie Morkel, who came in for Coulter-Nile, will most likely retain his spot unless JPD has other plans.]]></line><line><![CDATA[HYD are surely boosted and are searing with confidence after successive wins against two massive teams CHN and RAJ. David Warner and Shikhar Dhawan have scored more than 45 percent of the runs for the team which shows how consistent the opening duo have been. Middle order, which has been a major concern, came good in the last 2 games and guess what! Typical Eoin Morgan has arrived in the last game and reminded how dangerous a player he is. Their death bowling, arguably, has been the best this season with BK and PK delivering more often than not.]]></line><line><![CDATA[DEL have only themselves to blame as they let a few games slip despite having firm control for most part of the game. It's going to be a do-or-die situation for them as they can't afford to lose a game. A defeat for DEL will also mean their exit from this IPL. DEL, however, will draw some positives as they emerged victorious against HYD in the earlier encounter at Visakhapatnam. Their strength lies in Young Shreyas Iyer and Skipper JPD who have been consistent  throughout and yet again they will rely on their spin duo, Tahir and Mishra to make a game changing impact.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sloppy fielding, lackluster approach towards the target, poor bowling and big players failing to find the rhythm - there are one too many reasons for DEL to ponder about. With an outside chance of making it to the playoffs, will DEL put these problems to bed and grab the much needed win? Not many would have expected the steep rise of HYD despite a poor start to the tournament. They have sent a strong message to other teams by putting up a dominant show against CHN and RAJ. Barring MUM, HYD is the only team to beat both CHN and RAJ in this IPL.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>19:00 Local Time, 13:30 GMT, 19:00 IST:</b> Delhi team survived a near disaster a day ago while landing at Raipur airport as one flight had to evacuate the runway in order to prevent a collision. Thankfully nothing miserable took place and hopefully such incidents don't occur any further. On the other hand T20 extravaganza continues as resurgent HYD take on the unpredictable DEL in Raipur. Greetings and warm welcome to our coverage for the 45th game of the Indian Premier League.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview</b><br/><br/>There is a lot riding on Hyderabad when they take on Delhi. The David Warner-led side still have a chance to qualify for the Playoffs - a victory will stand them in good stead and it should be a little easier against Delhi, who are languishing in the bottom half of the points table. Even victories in their three remaining games will not assure Delhi of a spot in the Playoffs.<br/><br/>It is quite evident then that Hyderabad will be giving it their all but can the Delhi manage to upset the applecart? A lot of other results have to go in their favour but there is still a slim chance and JP Duminy's team will be using that as motivation to do well. Pulling themselves up when hopes are slim will be a tough job for the support staff and their captain. On the other hand, it could act as a weight removed and some players will be playing with a lot more freedom. It sets up the contest quite nicely.<br/><br/>Venue: Shaheed Veer Narayan Singh International Stadium, Raipur<br/><br/>Date: May 9, 2015<br/><br/>Time: 20:00 IST<br/><br/>Weather: Partly cloudy evening with a low of 28 degrees<br/><br/><b>Team news</b><br/><br/><b>Delhi</b><br/><br/>The match is a 'home' game for Delhi even though it will be played in Raipur. The change of venue might be welcome for the Delhi who have lost three out of five games they played at the Feroz Shah Kotla. They have won the two IPL games played in Raipur previously and will be keen to extend that run. Even though they have lost three games on the trot, Delhi might not tinker too much with the combination. There have been noteworthy individual contributions despite the lack of a collective team show. The only probable change could be the inclusion of Nathan Coulter-Nile in place of Albie Morkel.<br/><br/>Probable XI: 1. Manoj Tiwary, 2. Shreyas Iyer, 3. JP Duminy (capt), 4. Kedar Kadhav (wk), 5. Yuvraj Singh, 6. Angelo Mathews, 7. Saurabh Tiwary, 8. Nathan Coulter-Nile, 9. Zaheer Khan, 10. Amit Mishra, 11. Imran Tahir<br/><br/><b>Hyderabad</b><br/><br/>Having won three out their last four games, the Hyderabad have momentum and confidence going into an important clash. Shikhar Dhawan and David Warner have been the lynchpins of the batting unit but a rejuvenated Eoin Morgan adds a lot of depth to the team. The middle-order looks brittle without contributions from the Indian batsmen but they will be banking on the likes of Naman Ojha to pull up their socks as the stakes get higher. They went in with a predominantly Indian attack against Rajasthan and almost paid the price for it. Rajasthan came very close to chasing down a total of 201. HYD will look to find a way to fit in Trent Boult even if it comes at the cost of dropping Moises Henriques or Ravi Bopara, who have both done reasonably well. HYD may also look at including Lokesh Rahul at the expense of Hanuma Vihari who has had a lacklustre tournament so far.<br/><br/>Probable XI: 1. David Warner (capt), 2. Shikhar Dhawan, 3. Lokesh Rahul, 4. Eoin Morgan, 5. Naman Ojha (wk), 6. Moises Henriques/Ravi Bopara, 7. Ashish Reddy, 8. Karn Sharma, 9. Bhuvneshwar Kumar, 10. Trent Boult, 11. Ishant Sharma<br/><br/><b>Trivia</b><br/><br/>Delhi may have won both their games in Raipur previously but the Man of the Match on both occasions was David Warner, the current HYD skipper. He's yet to be dismissed in Raipur and has scored 117 runs so far.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hyderabad</b> (From): David Warner(c), Shikhar Dhawan, Moises Henriques, Eoin Morgan, Naman Ojha(w), Ravi Bopara, Hanuma Vihari, Karn Sharma, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Praveen Kumar, Ishant Sharma, Dale Steyn, Trent Boult, Lokesh Rahul, Parvez Rasool, Ashish Reddy, Ricky Bhui, Chama Milind, Kane Williamson, Bipul Sharma, Prasanth Padmanabhan, Siddarth Kaul]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Delhi</b> (From): Shreyas Iyer, Manoj Tiwary, Jean-Paul Duminy(c), Kedar Jadhav(w), Yuvraj Singh, Angelo Mathews, Saurabh Tiwary, Albie Morkel, Zaheer Khan, Amit Mishra, Imran Tahir, Nathan Coulter-Nile, Quinton de Kock, Mayank Agarwal, Shahbaz Nadeem, Jayant Yadav, Jaydev Unadkat, Gurinder Sandhu, Chidhambaram Gautam, Travis Head, Srikar Bharat, Marcus Stoinis, Domnic Joseph, KK Jiyas]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>163</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>4</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Hyderabad">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1446</playerid>
					<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhawan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhawan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>13</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Zaheer</bowler>
					<bowlerId>71</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Albie Morkel</fielder>
						<fielderId>484</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1739</playerid>
					<name>David Warner</name>
					<batsman-name>Warner</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Warner</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>17</runs>
					<balls>15</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Coulter-Nile</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7774</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Saurabh Tiwary</fielder>
						<fielderId>1601</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1437</playerid>
					<name>Moises Henriques</name>
					<batsman-name>Henriques</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Henriques</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>74</runs>
					<balls>46</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>5</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>624</playerid>
					<name>Eoin Morgan</name>
					<batsman-name>E Morgan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Eoin Morgan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>22</runs>
					<balls>25</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Jayant Yadav</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8182</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Nathan Coulter-Nile</fielder>
						<fielderId>7774</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1844</playerid>
					<name>Karn Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Karn Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Karn Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>16</runs>
					<balls>13</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Coulter-Nile</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7774</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Jayant Yadav</fielder>
						<fielderId>8182</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>571</playerid>
					<name>Ravi Bopara</name>
					<batsman-name>R Bopara</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bopara</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>17</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1599</playerid>
					<name>Naman Ojha</name>
					<batsman-name>N Ojha</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>N Ojha</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8837</playerid>
					<name>Parvez Rasool</name>
					<batsman-name>P Rasool</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>P Rasool</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1726</playerid>
					<name>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</name>
					<batsman-name>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>592</playerid>
					<name>Praveen Kumar</name>
					<batsman-name>P Kumar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>P Kumar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>702</playerid>
					<name>Ishant Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Ishant</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ishant</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1446</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>29</runs>
				<overs>3.5</overs>
				<batsman>Shikhar Dhawan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dhawan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1739</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>31</runs>
				<overs>4.1</overs>
				<batsman>David Warner</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Warner</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>624</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>64</runs>
				<overs>10.4</overs>
				<batsman>Eoin Morgan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>E Morgan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1844</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>99</runs>
				<overs>14.6</overs>
				<batsman>Karn Sharma</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Karn Sharma</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>4</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Delhi">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8182</playerid>
					<name>Jayant Yadav</name>
					<bowler-name>Jayant Yadav</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Jayant Yadav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>19</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>71</playerid>
					<name>Zaheer Khan</name>
					<bowler-name>Zaheer</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Zaheer</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>33</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7774</playerid>
					<name>Nathan Coulter-Nile</name>
					<bowler-name>Coulter-Nile</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Coulter-Nile</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>211</playerid>
					<name>Jean-Paul Duminy</name>
					<bowler-name>Duminy</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Duminy</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>16</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1454</playerid>
					<name>Amit Mishra</name>
					<bowler-name>A Mishra</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mishra</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>34</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>484</playerid>
					<name>Albie Morkel</name>
					<bowler-name>A Morkel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>A Morkel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9428</playerid>
					<name>Shreyas Iyer</name>
					<bowler-name>S Iyer</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shreyas Iyer</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8520</playerid>
					<name>Quinton de Kock</name>
					<bowler-name>de Kock</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>de Kock</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1851</playerid>
					<name>Kedar Jadhav</name>
					<bowler-name>K Jadhav</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>K Jadhav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>69</playerid>
					<name>Yuvraj Singh</name>
					<bowler-name>Yuvraj</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Yuvraj</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1601</playerid>
					<name>Saurabh Tiwary</name>
					<bowler-name>S Tiwary</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Tiwary</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>157</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>4</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Delhi">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8520</playerid>
					<name>Quinton de Kock</name>
					<batsman-name>de Kock</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>de Kock</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>50</runs>
					<balls>31</balls>
					<fours>9</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[stumped]]></status>
					<bowler>Karn Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1844</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Naman Ojha</fielder>
						<fielderId>1599</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9428</playerid>
					<name>Shreyas Iyer</name>
					<batsman-name>S Iyer</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shreyas Iyer</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Bhuvneshwar</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1726</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Bhuvneshwar</fielder>
						<fielderId>1726</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>211</playerid>
					<name>Jean-Paul Duminy</name>
					<batsman-name>Duminy</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Duminy</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>12</runs>
					<balls>16</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Karn Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1844</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>69</playerid>
					<name>Yuvraj Singh</name>
					<batsman-name>Yuvraj</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Yuvraj</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>P Rasool</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8837</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Karn Sharma</fielder>
						<fielderId>1844</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1851</playerid>
					<name>Kedar Jadhav</name>
					<batsman-name>K Jadhav</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>K Jadhav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>63</runs>
					<balls>34</balls>
					<fours>8</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1601</playerid>
					<name>Saurabh Tiwary</name>
					<batsman-name>S Tiwary</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Tiwary</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>26</runs>
					<balls>25</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>484</playerid>
					<name>Albie Morkel</name>
					<batsman-name>A Morkel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>A Morkel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8182</playerid>
					<name>Jayant Yadav</name>
					<batsman-name>Jayant Yadav</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Jayant Yadav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7774</playerid>
					<name>Nathan Coulter-Nile</name>
					<batsman-name>Coulter-Nile</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Coulter-Nile</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1454</playerid>
					<name>Amit Mishra</name>
					<batsman-name>A Mishra</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mishra</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>71</playerid>
					<name>Zaheer Khan</name>
					<batsman-name>Zaheer</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Zaheer</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9428</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>13</runs>
				<overs>2.4</overs>
				<batsman>Shreyas Iyer</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Iyer</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8520</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>60</runs>
				<overs>8.2</overs>
				<batsman>Quinton de Kock</batsman>
				<batsman-name>de Kock</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>69</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>65</runs>
				<overs>9.6</overs>
				<batsman>Yuvraj Singh</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Yuvraj</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>211</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>66</runs>
				<overs>10.2</overs>
				<batsman>Jean-Paul Duminy</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Duminy</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>1</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>3</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>4</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Hyderabad">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1726</playerid>
					<name>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</name>
					<bowler-name>Bhuvneshwar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bhuvneshwar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>20</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>702</playerid>
					<name>Ishant Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Ishant</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ishant</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>39</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8837</playerid>
					<name>Parvez Rasool</name>
					<bowler-name>P Rasool</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>P Rasool</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>20</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>592</playerid>
					<name>Praveen Kumar</name>
					<bowler-name>P Kumar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>P Kumar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>34</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1437</playerid>
					<name>Moises Henriques</name>
					<bowler-name>Henriques</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Henriques</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>14</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1844</playerid>
					<name>Karn Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Karn Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Karn Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>12</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>571</playerid>
					<name>Ravi Bopara</name>
					<bowler-name>R Bopara</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bopara</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>15</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1739</playerid>
					<name>David Warner</name>
					<bowler-name>Warner</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Warner</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1446</playerid>
					<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhawan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhawan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>624</playerid>
					<name>Eoin Morgan</name>
					<bowler-name>E Morgan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Eoin Morgan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1599</playerid>
					<name>Naman Ojha</name>
					<bowler-name>N Ojha</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>N Ojha</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



