<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14646" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>53rd Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Punjab</home>
		<away>Chennai</away>
		<teamsabbr>MOH vs CHN</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>MOH</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>CHN</awayabbr>
		<homeId>65</homeId>
		<awayId>58</awayId>
		<venue>Punjab Cricket Association Stadium, Mohali</venue>
		<startdate>16 05 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>16 05 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Punjab</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Chennai won by 7 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Chennai</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>7</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Chettithody Shamsuddin</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Nandan</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Johanes Cloete</Name>
			<Country>RSA</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Javagal Srinath</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>10:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150516133710</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>CHN</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>MOH</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>134</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>3</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>16.5</batteamovers>
		<status>Chennai won by 7 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>413</playerid>
			<name>Suresh Raina*</name>
			<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Raina</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>41</runs>
			<balls-faced>34</balls-faced>
			<fours>4</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>265</playerid>
			<name>MS Dhoni</name>
			<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Dhoni</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>25</runs>
			<balls-faced>16</balls-faced>
			<fours>2</fours>
			<sixes>2</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1876</playerid>
			<name>Anureet Singh*</name>
			<bowler-name>Anureet Singh</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Anureet Singh</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>2.5</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>30</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>9490</playerid>
			<name>Beuran Hendricks</name>
			<bowler-name>B Hendricks</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Beuran Hendricks</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>3</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>25</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>131</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>7825</playerid>
<name>Faf du Plessis</name>
<player-runs>55</player-runs>
<player-balls>41</player-balls>
<runs>102</runs>
<wicket-nbr>3</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>8616</bowlerid>
<bowlername>R Dhawan</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>6</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>6</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[2 Wd 2 W . . . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 1 1 4 2 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 . . . 4 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. 6 6 1 4 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/MOH_CHN_MAY16/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[That's it from this game. There is a crucial encounter coming up involving Rajasthan and Kolkata. The winner of that game will be through to the playoffs. Switch tabs to follow that game. For now, goodbye and cheers..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Negi:</b> "I am feeling very good. I was just trying to bowl in the right areas. He (Jadeja) is a great fielder and a good bowler, he took a brilliant catch. First time in IPL I bowled with a new ball, so I was a bit excited."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pawan Negi</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his figures of 2/25.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhoni:</b> "I think it just gives you one extra match, if you have a bad game. We took it as another game and didn't think too much about it. The opposition was under pressure on such a wicket. That David Miller's catch was very important and Jadeja made it look easy. The great fielders are ones that make it look easy for the spectators. We have made it quite simple, we adapt, we improve, we have had the same group of cricketers. We are not like other teams who give chance to youngsters, but we groom captains. We have quite a few leaders in our side. The core of the side has remained the same and everyone has learned a lot over the years."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bailey:</b> "It has been a disappointing season. Hopefully the next year will be a better one. We haven't had anyone who has had a good season. We haven't got anyone in the batting leaderboard or the bowling leaderboard. You should not get too far ahead of yourselves. The good sides in T20s don't have much gap during their good and bad times. That is where we were poor. There have been plenty of positives, like some of the young Indian players have had a good season."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, CHN's bowlers put up a professional show and never allowed the home team to up the scoring rate. Pawan Negi picked up a couple of key wickets for the visitors. CHN ended the league phase as the table-toppers, while PUN were consigned to a wooden spoon finish. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Faf du Plessis and Suresh Raina played with a calm head on their shoulders to guide CHN to a facile win. Michael Hussey and Brendon McCullum were dismissed cheaply. However, Raina and du Plessis twinned caution with aggression and bisected the gaps with utmost ease. du Plessis then reached a well-constructed half-century. For PUN, Sandeep Sharma bowled a fine spell with the new ball. The hosts would rue the fact that Glenn Maxwell dropped a catch off his own bowling as Raina survived.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>CHN complete the formalities.</b> They win by 7 wickets and will finish the league stage as <b>table toppers</b>. Full and outside off, Raina reaches out and squeezes it off the outside half to short third man, Hendricks misfields and allows the ball to reach the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Dhoni, 1 run, short of length around off, Dhoni steers it down to third man and leaves Raina to score the winning run]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Dhoni, <b>SIX</b>, Dhoni wants to finish it off. Charges down the wicket, takes it on the full and hammers it over long-off for another six, the fielder leapt up but in vain]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Dhoni, <b>SIX</b>, wow! Something that I have not seen from Dhoni. Short delivery on off, Dhoni shuffles a long way across his stumps, gets inside the line and scoops it over fine leg, it was rising steeply and he did well to get enough wood]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Dhoni, no run, back of a length close to off, Dhoni guides it to backward point with an angled bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Dhoni, 1 run, fuller and just outside off, Dhoni leans into the drive, cover dives after the ball passes him]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Dhoni, <b>FOUR</b>, PUN bowlers keep bowling it short and feeding Dhoni, who keeps dispatching it. The slower delivery that is dragged short, Dhoni had all the time to pull it in front of square, no one protecting the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Dhoni, no run, short of length on off, Dhoni tucks it to mid-wicket with one leg in the air]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Dhoni, no run, back of a length on off, Dhoni plays the short-arm pull to mid-wicket, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Dhoni, no run, change of pace from Hendricks, Dhoni stays back and knocks it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Raina, 1 run, banged in halfway down the wicket, Raina pulls it on the bounce to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Beuran Hendricks [2.0-0-19-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Dhoni, no run, yorker on off, Dhoni digs it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Dhoni, 2 runs, again, Anureet keeps it short, Dhoni has plenty of time to ride the bounce and pull to deep backward square, Hendricks runs to his left, slides and keeps it to a double]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Dhoni, <b>FOUR</b>, Anureet drops it short and pays the price. No pace or the height to trouble the CHN skipper, he rocks back and pulls it behind square leg, split the two men in the deep to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Raina, 1 run, dug in midway down the wicket, Raina swivels and mistimes the pull in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Dhoni, 1 run, too straight, on middle and leg, Dhoni nurdles it to deep backward square leg and opens his account]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Raina, 1 run, back of a length on off, Raina steers it to the right of backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Anureet Singh [1.0-0-4-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Dhawan to Dhoni, no run, keeps it tad short and outside off, Dhoni guides it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Dhawan to Dhoni, no run, back of a length on off and middle, Dhoni gets inside the line and tucks it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Dhawan to Dhoni, no run, full toss around off, Dhoni pushes it gently to mid-off, that should have been put away]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>MS Dhoni, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Dhawan to du Plessis, <b>out</b> Bowled!! End of a fine innings. Dhawan has something to cheer about and so do the PUN supporters. du Plessis advances down the wicket and yorks himself, he can't keep it out and the ball crashes into the base of off-stump. The partnership is also broken, but it is a bit too late for the home side. <b>du Plessis b R Dhawan 55(41) [4s-5 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[R Dhawan to du Plessis, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Dhawan to du Plessis, 2 runs, once more those strong wrists coming into play, back of a length on off, du Plessis stands tall and plays a whippy pull to wide long-on, Miller tidies up near the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Dhawan to du Plessis, <b>wide</b>, Faf gives the charge and Dhawan bangs it short and outside off, too far for the batsman, easy call for the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Dhawan to du Plessis, 2 runs, short of length and on the pads, du Plessis whips it to deep backward square leg, nice use of the wrists. Sandeep Sharma does well to run to his right, dive and save a couple of runs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rishi Dhawan [1.0-0-7-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to du Plessis, 1 run, another full toss from Gurkeerat, du Plessis drives to the left of the bowler, who gets a hand and parries it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to du Plessis, no run, leans forward and turns it gently to short mid-wicket, can't beat the fielder there]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Raina, 1 run, nice friendly full toss and Raina has mistimed it completely, heaves it to deep mid-wicket for just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Raina, 2 runs, goes round the wicket, slants it onto the pads, Raina glances it fine and the batsmen scamper back for the second, Faf wanted the third but Raina says no]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to du Plessis, 1 run, Faf registers his <b>6th IPL fifty</b>. It is his first this season. The entire CHN squad are on their feet, applauding the effort. Slower and turning in, du Plessis works it with the spin to backward square leg. Raina walks up to his partner and congratulates him]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to du Plessis, no run, tossed up outside off, du Plessis shuffles across and misses the nudge, is rapped on the pads but the impact was outside off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to du Plessis, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, du Plessis milks it square on the leg-side and retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, Axar drops it trifle short, du Plessis uses the depth of the crease, goes right back and pulls it just wide of mid-wicket, who dived in vain. Miller can't get across from long-on as the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to du Plessis, no run, Faf comes down the track, closes the bat face and the soft leading edge rolls to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to du Plessis, no run, dabbed away to backward point, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to du Plessis, <b>SIX</b>, fabulous shot! It has taken more than 11 overs to hit the first six of the innings. Faf uses his feet, meets the pitch of the ball and lofts it handsomely straight down the ground, pings the sightscreen on the full]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to du Plessis, no run, quicker and on the stumps, du Plessis stays leg-side and pushes it to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Raina, no run, slower and around off, Raina drops it wide of cover, wanted the run and was midway before Faf sent him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Raina, 2 runs, flighted from round the wicket, Raina comes down the track and chips it over the bowler's head, easy two. That was a controlled shot from Raina]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to du Plessis, 1 run, quicker, fuller and on off, du Plessis nurdles it behind square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Raina, 1 run, drifting down leg, swept to long leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Raina, no run, short and outside off, Raina cuts it late and straight to backward point, he is disappointed with himself for not putting it away]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to du Plessis, 1 run, tossed up on off, du Plessis leans forward and works it square on the leg-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Gurkeerat Singh Mann [1.0-0-12-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to du Plessis, 1 run, flighted and just outside off, du Plessis makes room and chopped it to the right of point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Raina, 1 run, tossed up and on Raina's pads, whipped away towards deep mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to du Plessis, 1 run, slower and just outside off, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Raina, 1 run, pushed through quicker as Raina charged down the track, he mistimes the heave and drags it down towards long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to du Plessis, 1 run, tossed up and just outside off, du Plessis makes room and works it to the left of cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, Axar drops this one halfway down the track, du Plessis rocks back and pulls it high and over mid-wicket for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to du Plessis, 1 run, on a good length and well outside off, steered away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to du Plessis, no run, du Plessis comes down the track to a full ball and punches it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Raina, 1 run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Raina, no run, on a good length and angling away from outside off, Raina gets his bat and pad forward as he pushes it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to du Plessis, 1 run, short of a length and well outside off, dabbed to the left of backward point. Maxwell fumbles once again and allows a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anureet Singh to Raina, 1 run, on a good length and on the stumps, punched down towards long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Anureet Singh, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to du Plessis, 2 runs, Axar gives this one more air, du Plessis goes down on his knees and laps it very fine, back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Raina, 1 run, tossed up and on Raina's pads, nudged behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to du Plessis, 1 run, Axar drops one short and on the stumps, du Plessis rocks back and pulls it towards deep mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to du Plessis, <b>wide</b>, pushed through flatter and down the leg-side as du Plessis went for the lap sweep, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Raina, 1 run, this one is given more air, driven down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to du Plessis, 1 run, pushed through and on du Plessis' pads, worked behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Raina, 1 run, flighted and just outside off, Raina nudges it to the right of short third man for a run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Axar Patel, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to du Plessis, no run, the drifter from Maxwell, stayed a tad low as well, du Plessis backs away and chops it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Raina, 1 run, pushed through by Maxwell, Raina makes room and cuts it to the right of point for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Raina, no run, tossed up and on the stumps, Raina prods forward in defence]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Raina, no run, <b>Maxwell has dropped a dolly</b>, this was flatter and just outside off, Raina went back and punched it to the right of the bowler. Maxwell went at it casually and with one hand, the ball hit his wrists and popped out, he can't grab the rebound as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to du Plessis, 1 run, tossed up and well outside off, du Plessis gets down on his knees and laps it over the keeper. Miller gets across from short third man and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Back over the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, flatter and on du Plessis' pads, he goes back and nudges it very fine. The man at fine-leg is very square, he puts in the dive but can't stop the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Maxwell to Raina, <b>2 wides</b>, Maxwell tosses one well down the leg-side, Raina looks to sweep and misses, so does Saha, a couple of wides]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Glenn Maxwell, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Dhawan to Raina, 1 run, too straight from Dhawan, worked away in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Dhawan to Raina, <b>wide</b>, short and angling well down the leg-side, left alone, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Dhawan to du Plessis, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, du Plessis nudges it in front of cover and calls for a quick single. Miller makes a direct hit at the striker's end, but Raina was well in. The third umpire has a look]]></line><line><![CDATA[Saha is up to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Dhawan to du Plessis, no run, short of a length and just outside off, du Plessis shimmies down the track and mistimes the pull towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Dhawan to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, that's powerfully struck! Tad fuller and just outside off, du Plessis comes down the track, plays the flat-batted drive past the bowler and into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Dhawan to du Plessis, no run, short of a length and angling into du Plessis, he was early in closing the face of the bat, gets a soft leading edge towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;R Dhawan to du Plessis, no run, on a good length and just outside off, driven to the right of extra cover. Miller is quick onto the ball, du Plessis wanted a single and is sent back by Raina]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rishi Dhawan, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, fraction too short from Gurkeerat, Raina rocks back and punches it through mid-wicket, the timing is sublime and the ball races away to the fence in a hurry]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to du Plessis, 1 run, this was tossed up and on the stumps, du Plessis comes down the track, takes it on the full and drives it back towards the bowler. He deflects it away towards mid-wicket, the batsmen bump into each other as they cross across for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Raina, 1 run, flighted and on the stumps, nudged in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Raina, 2 runs, pushed through by Gurkeerat, Raina went down on his knees and swept it hard, Bailey dives at backward square leg, gets a hand onto it and saves a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, that's nicely played by Raina, shimmied down the track, got too close to the pitch but goes through with the lofted on-drive, clears mid-on and races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gurkeerat Singh to Raina, no run, tossed up and on the off-stump line, pushed towards mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Gurkeerat Singh Mann, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Raina, 1 run, fraction too short and too straight from Hendricks, worked behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to du Plessis, 3 runs, that was close! A half-hearted pull from du Plessis, manages to bisect the gap between mid-on and mid-wicket, Gurkeerat gives the chase and keeps them down to three runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Raina, 1 run, back of a length and in that channel outside off, steered away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Raina, <b>wide</b>, the bouncer from Hendricks, Raina shuffled across on the pull and missed, it was close to the gloves and is harshly called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to du Plessis, 1 run, tad fuller and on the off-stump line, dabbed with an open face towards third man, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to du Plessis, no run, back of a length and just outside off, du Plessis dabs it with an open face towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to du Plessis, <b>FOUR</b>, width on offer from Hendricks, du Plessis stands tall and punches it square past cover, no need to run for those]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Raina, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Raina gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Raina, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, fraction short of a length and just outside off, Raina leans forward, presents the full face of the bat and pushes it through extra cover for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Raina, 2 runs, short of a length and on Raina's pads, worked away in front of square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Raina, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, whipped away straight to Bailey at mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to du Plessis, 1 run, short of a length and on du Plessis' pads, tucked away past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to du Plessis, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, left alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Raina, no run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Raina leans forward and caresses it towards extra cover. The fielder fumbles but Gurkeerat was backing him up at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Brendon McCullum, <b>out</b> Bowled!! CHN have lost both openers now. This was banged in short and angled across the right-hander, McCullum was hopping across as he looked to nudge it down towards third man, he played with an angled bat and the inside edge is found, the off-stump is rattled and McCullum walks away for the final time in this season's IPL. <b>Brendon McCullum b Beuran Hendricks 6(6) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Beuran Hendricks to Brendon McCullum, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>top-edge and four</b>, Hendricks drops one short as McCullum gave the charge, he throws the bat at that and gets a thick top-edge. The third man was inside the ring and the ball goes over his head and into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Brendon McCullum, no run, short of a length and shaping away from outside off, McCullum drops his wrists and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to du Plessis, 3 runs, tad too straight from Hendricks, ends up drifting onto du Plessis' pads, worked away in front of square on the on-side. Gurkeerat gives the chase and pulls the ball back in before the ropes, du Plessis is off and running with three]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Beuran Hendricks to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, dabbed in front of cover for a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Beuran Hendricks, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Faf du Plessis, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to M Hussey, <b>out</b> Caught by W Saha!! Edged and caught! Not a happy comeback for Hussey, tad fuller and slanting across the left-hander, Hussey was pushing forward from the crease, gets a thick edge through to the keeper. PUN needed early wickets and Sandeep has provided them one in the first over of the innings. <b>M Hussey c W Saha b Sandeep Sharma 1(4)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sandeep Sharma to M Hussey, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to M Hussey, no run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to M Hussey, no run, on a good length and on the off-stump line, Hussey watchfully defends it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, fraction too straight from Sandeep, worked behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to Brendon McCullum, no run, short of a length and just outside off, McCullum is cramped for room as this one nipped back in, chopped straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[Saha is up to the stumps for McCullum]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sandeep Sharma to M Hussey, 1 run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, draws Hussey into the drive, the edge is found but there's no second slip. Hussey is off and running with a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>M Hussey and Brendon McCullum are at the crease. M Hussey is on strike. Sandeep Sharma will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place for Sandeep]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. A new opening partnership for CHN. Michael Hussey is batting for the first time in this season. Can PUN defend 130?]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jadeja:</b> "It was a good change from the skipper (starting with Negi). Everybody bowled pretty well. Now we have to bat sensibly and chase it down. If we play normal cricket, we should win it. The skipper told me to be ready and I knew he was going to hit it there (referring to Miller's catch). This is a crucial game for us as we need to finish in the top two."]]></line><line><![CDATA[The deck is surprisingly offering turn, however, the hosts have to play out of their skins to upset the apple-cart  and register a consolation victory. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[All of CHN's bowlers chipped in with wickets to restrict the home team to a modest total. In fact, none of PUN's batsmen made an impact. For the visitors, Pawan Negi snared two wickets. Ashish Nehra and Ravichandran Ashwin also bowled well and were rewarded with wickets. Only Axar Patel made his presence felt in the slog overs by playing with a calm head on his shoulders.<br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to R Dhawan, 1 run, shortish and around off, Dhawan clears his front leg and pulls to deep mid-wicket, Hendricks wanted the second but is sent back, he just makes it in as the throw comes to his end]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to R Dhawan, <b>SIX</b>, Nehra misses the yorker and is dispatched into the crowd. Nice juicy full toss, Dhawan kneels down, picks his spot and hammers it flat and over wide long-on. That was hit pretty hard]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to R Dhawan, no run, too full and on the stumps, Dhawan makes room and squeezes the drive to mid-off, doesn't risk taking the run]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to R Dhawan, no run, bouncer following the batsman, Dhawan backs away and can't connect with the pull, he got into all tangle while trying to play that]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Beuran Hendricks, 1 run, banged in short and outside off, Hendricks flat-bats it over extra cover, Bravo from mid-off tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Beuran Hendricks, no run, back of a length just outside off, Hendricks tries the steer down to third man, fails to connect]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashish Nehra [2.0-0-9-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Beuran Hendricks, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to A Patel, <b>out</b> Caught by Dhoni!! Wicket No. 20 for Bravo. It was once again the slower delivery that deceives the batsman. Bravo bowled it well wide of off, Axar reaches out, looks to go leg-side, the top-edge goes straight up and to the left of MS, who calls for it and takes it calmly. A good innings from Axar comes to an end. <b>A Patel c Dhoni b Dwayne Bravo 32(29) [4s-2 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dwayne Bravo to A Patel, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to R Dhawan, 1 run, full and on the stumps, Dhawan charges down and squeezes the drive to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to R Dhawan, <b>SIX</b>, hammered! Bravo was too predictable. Another off-speed delivery, Dhawan shimmies down the wicket, spots the slower one and smashes it with the turn over wide long-on for the second six of the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to A Patel, 1 run, low full toss just outside off, Axar backs away to the leg-side, toe-ends the drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to A Patel, no run, fired full and well wide of off, Axar makes room and can't reach it, that was just inside the tramline]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to A Patel, <b>SIX</b>, wow! What an effort from Faf. Slower ball just outside off, Axar drags the loft towards long-on, got plenty of wood to clear the rope. Faf leapt up, went with his right-hand, but the ball eludes him. Even if he had saved the six, it would have been a top effort]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to A Patel, 1 run, tossed up on off, Axar kneels down and sweeps it to deep backward square leg, Negi does well to keep it down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to A Patel, <b>FOUR</b>, full, quick and in the slot, Axar clears his front leg and tonks it over the non-striker's head, one bounce and into the fence. No chance for the long-on fielder to stop that]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to R Dhawan, 1 run, Dhawan takes a couple of steps out of the crease, Jadeja drags the length back, dabbed to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to A Patel, 1 run, right in the blockhole, Axar digs it out to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to A Patel, no run, Axar comes down the track and slaps it to extra cover, Hussey dives and stops the ball, Axar wanted the run and was halfway down, but Hussey is slow to release the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to R Dhawan, leg byes, 1 run, pushed through on leg-stump, Dhawan misses the nudge, wears it on the pad and the ball dribbles to the off-side, Axar calls for a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja [2.0-0-11-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to R Dhawan, 1 run, nice loopy off-cutter to end the over, Dhawan bends down and swipes it to long-on, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to A Patel, 1 run, shortish and around off, Axar plays the short-arm pull to deep mid-wicket, Hussey tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to R Dhawan, 1 run, Dhawan gives the charge, almost yorks himself, squeezes it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to A Patel, 1 run, back of a length just outside off, Axar punches to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to R Dhawan, 1 run, off-cutter just outside off, Dhawan drops it in front of backward point, easy single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Bravo to A Patel, 1 run, fuller and outside off, Axar toe-ends the drive past the diving extra cover fielder, the man at sweeper backs up]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Bravo, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to R Dhawan, no run, slower and around off, Dhawan defends with an open bat face to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to R Dhawan, no run, touch quicker and just outside off, Dhawan guides it to short third, he wanted the run but is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to R Dhawan, 2 runs, shortish and turning away, Dhawan backs away and dabs it wide of the slip fielder, Jaddu gives chase and keeps it to a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to R Dhawan, no run, floated up outside off, Dhawan drives and finds Baz at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to R Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, good shot! PUN need plenty more of this, if they have to put up a respectable score on the board. Tossed up on off, Dhawan kneels down and sweeps it in front of square, beats the fielder at deep mid-wicket with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to A Patel, 1 run, flighted outside off, Axar skips out of the crease and drives to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to A Patel, <b>wide</b>, turning down leg, Axar fails to get bat on the glance, extra added to the total]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to A Patel, 1 run, flatter and around off, punched down to long-off, retains strike with that single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to A Patel, <b>FOUR</b>, super shot! Axar uses his feet, almost yorks himself, but manages to whip it between deep mid-wicket and long-on, the fielder in the deep had no chance of stopping that]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to R Dhawan, 1 run, fraction short and outside off, Dhawan cuts it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to R Dhawan, no run, pushed through just outside off, Dhawan leans forward and knocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to R Dhawan, no run, slower and turns back in, Dhawan dabs it past the keeper, he wanted the run but Axar sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to A Patel, 1 run, drifting onto the pads, nurdled away to square leg, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to A Patel, <b>wide</b>, darted down the leg-side, easy call for the umpire]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to R Dhawan, no run, slower on off and middle, Dhawan stays back and drops it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rishi Dhawan, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to D Miller, <b>out</b> Caught by Ravindra Jadeja!! Stunner! Jaddu has taken a blinder. Not much celebration from him, just points to someone after grasping it. Negi drops it short, Miller goes leg-side and nails the pull, it was hit flat and to the left of deep mid-wicket, Jaddu dived full length and pulls off a spectacular catch. Even gets an applause from Dhoni. CHN continue to take some terrific catches. <b>D Miller c Ravindra Jadeja b Negi 11(15) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Negi to D Miller, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to A Patel, 1 run, slower through the air, Axar comes down the track and nudges it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to D Miller, leg byes, 1 run, quicker and outside off, Miller misses the flick, the ball rolls off the pads to the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to D Miller, byes, <b>FOUR</b>, fired in full, Miller was shaping to play the sweep, he yorks himself and fails to dig it out, Dhoni too is beaten and the chase from Raina goes in vain]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to A Patel, 1 run, floated up on off and middle, Axar kneels down and sweeps it to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Pawan Negi [2.0-0-15-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to D Miller, no run, flatter and on the stumps, Miller gets his bat in front of the pads and knocks it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to A Patel, 1 run, pushed through on middle, Axar jams it square of the wicket on the leg-side, he was almost beaten for pace there]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to A Patel, no run, very well bowled, gives this plenty of air and invites the batsman to drive, Axar obliges and goes for the booming drive, the ball turns past the outside edge and MS whips the bails off. Axar had dragged his foot out, but made it back in time]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire called in for a stumping check. No issuses with Ashwin's front foot. Axar has made it in. He survives!]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to D Miller, 1 run, slower and outside off, Miller had to wait for it and paddles it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to D Miller, no run, nice floaty delivery, Miller bunts it in front of cover, no chance for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to A Patel, 1 run, quicker and on the stumps, Axar nudges it off the inner part to backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to D Miller, 2 runs, Jadeja sees the batsman advance and fires it outside leg, Miller does well to adjust and work it to the left of mid-wicket, Baz runs across, dives over it and that allowed the batsmen to collect two]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to D Miller, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! Maxwell tried the reverse sweep and missed a couple of times, but not Miller, he kneels down and middles it perfectly behind square on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to A Patel, 1 run, flatter on middle, Axar gets inside the line and milks it behind square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to A Patel, no run, turns it gently to short mid-wicket, they don't take on Baz]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to D Miller, 1 run, uses his feet, doesn't get to the pitch, manages to nudge it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to A Patel, 1 run, works it away with the turn to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to A Patel, 1 run, pushed through on middle and leg, Axar manages to bring his bat down and knock it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to A Patel, no run, bit of extra bounce on this occasion, Axar comes forward and plays it with soft hands, the ball lobs up and drops in the vacant silly point region]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to A Patel, no run, nicely tossed up on off, Axar defends with an angled bat to the left of the slip fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to D Miller, 1 run, floated up around off, Miller drives it down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to A Patel, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, Axar nudges it square of the wicket on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to A Patel, no run, slower through the air and around off, Axar presses forward and blocks]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to A Patel, 1 run, drops this one in front of short cover and sets off, Ashwin fires a throw at the non-striker's end, but the batsman had made his ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Axar Patel, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Maxwell, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Maxwell's poor IPL finally comes to a halt. Another disappointing show today from him. This one was bowled slower on middle stump line and turns away ever so slightly. Maxwell was on the back foot looking to work it through the on-side, the ball turns away and hits top of off and middle. Jadeja is pumped up. <b>Maxwell b Ravindra Jadeja 6(14) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ravindra Jadeja to Maxwell, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Maxwell, no run, once again goes for the reverse sweep, but the turn away fools him all ends up, the ball goes off the pad to the right of the leg slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to Maxwell, no run, goes for the reverse sweep this time, the ball hits the glove and drops to his right]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to D Miller, 1 run, gets this one to turn in from outside off, Miller goes across and flicks it past the leg slip, who dives to his right but fails to get a hand on that]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ravindra Jadeja to D Miller, no run, goes across and flicks this uppishly towards mid-wicket, the ball goes on the bounce to the fielder]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[A leg slip in place for Jaddu]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravindra Jadeja, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to D Miller, 1 run, goes down on one knee and paddles it towards fine leg to get off the mark, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to D Miller, no run, drifting in around off, Miller pushes hard at that, gets an inside edge onto the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to D Miller, no run, looks to work this one on the on-side, fails to connect and wears it high on the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>David Miller, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place for Miller]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic timeout</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Gurkeerat Singh, <b>out</b> Stumped!! Another one bites the dust. This was bowled beautifully from Ashwin. Gurkeerat gives the charge and Ashwin gets this one to turn past the leg stump, Gurkeerat can't lay bat on that, Dhoni collects it and whips the bails off in a flash. Good piece of bowling from Ashwin to get his man. <b>Gurkeerat Singh st Dhoni b Ashwin 15(14) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ashwin to Gurkeerat Singh, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Stumped!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Gurkeerat Singh, <b>FOUR</b>, shortish delivery outside off, Gurkeerat goes on the back foot and cuts it to the right of short third man, who gave up knowing that he was never going to reach the ball, it races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Gurkeerat Singh, <b>wide</b>, down the leg-side, called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Gurkeerat Singh, no run, looks to work this one through the on-side, but fails to connect. The ball lobs up off the pad and Dhoni collects, half an appeal from both the bowler and the keeper, but the umpire was not interested]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Maxwell, no run, bowls this slower ball a little wide outside off, Maxwell pokes at that, but the ball once again goes past the blade]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Gurkeerat Singh, 1 run, on middle and leg stump line this time around, Gurkeerat nudges it towards mid-wicket and gets off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Gurkeerat Singh, no run, good ball from Nehra, this was on a length and holds it line outside off, Gurkeerat pushes at it, the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Gurkeerat Singh, no run, opens the face of the bat and checks his push to the left of backward point, Maxwell was looking for the single there but has to rush back in as Jadeja fires a throw at the non-striker's end]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Gurkeerat Singh, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>beautifully timed!</b> It was on a length and on middle stump line, Gurkeerat punches it with the straightest of bats, gets it to the left of mid-on and the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Gurkeerat Singh, no run, on a good length and on the stumps, Gurkeerat bunts it to mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashish Nehra [1.0-0-4-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Gurkeerat Singh, 1 run, slower outside off, Gurkeerat opens the face of the bat and guides it past backward point, he retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Gurkeerat Singh, no run, touch quicker and on off stump line, Gurkeerat comes across and bunts it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Maxwell, 1 run, goes across this time and sweeps this flighted delivery behind square on the on-side, gets to the other end with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Maxwell, no run, gives the charge this time and Ashwin drags his length back, Maxwell pushes it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Maxwell, no run, flighted delivery on off and middle stump line, Maxwell goes across and turns it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ashwin to Maxwell, no run, flatter and turning in on off, Maxwell leans forward and blocks it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Ashwin vs Maxwell time!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravichandran Ashwin, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Gurkeerat Singh, <b>FOUR</b>, on a length and shaping away slightly just outside off, Mann leans forward, drives it on the rise and gets it in the gap between backward point and cover-point, there was no stopping that ball after it went through the infield]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Gurkeerat Singh, no run, on a good length and outside off, Mann opens the face of the bat and pushes it to the left of backward point, can't get the single away]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Maxwell, 1 run, almost a yorker around off, Maxwell squeezes it out towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Gurkeerat Singh, 1 run, just short of a good length and outside off, Mann opens the face of the bat and guides it towards backward point, who misfields and allows the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Gurkeerat Singh, no run, back of a length delivery angling in on middle stump line, Gurkeerat looks to work it away on the on-side, closes the bat face a little too early and gets a soft leading edge that rolls away towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Gurkeerat Singh Mann, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Vohra, <b>out</b> Caught by Nehra!! PUN are in trouble here, lose their third wicket with just 35 runs on the board. It was on a length and well outside off, Vohra goes hard on the lofted drive and gets a thick outside edge. The ball flies towards third man, where Nehra takes two steps forward, steadies himself and takes a simple catch. <b>Vohra c Nehra b I Pandey 4(7)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[I Pandey to Vohra, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Maxwell, no run, gives more width on offer this time, Maxwell looks to cut but fails to connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Maxwell, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>stand and deliver!</b> It was a short delivery from Nehra, Maxwell rocks back and pulls it over mid-wicket for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Maxwell, no run, on a length and on top of off, Maxwell gets behind the line and defends it to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Maxwell, no run, that's a good ball from Nehra, this one was angled across off, Maxwell looks to play at that, the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Maxwell, no run, full delivery with a hint of inswing around off, Maxwell looks to drive, gets an inside edge that rolls away towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Glenn Maxwell, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nehra to Bailey, <b>out</b> Caught by Dhoni!! Nehra strikes first ball after his return from injury. This one was on a length and was angling away outside off, Bailey looks to force it through the off-side, gets an outside edge, Dhoni dives to his right and takes a good low catch. Nehra is delighted to see the back of PUN's captain. Out comes the Big Show. <b>Bailey c Dhoni b Nehra 12(7) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Nehra to Bailey, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ashish Nehra, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Vohra, 2 runs, comes down the track and wanted to go inside-out over cover, but ends up getting a thick outside edge that flies to the right of third man, Nehra almost overran it in the deep, the batsmen take two before he finally collects the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Vohra, no run, on a length and gets this one to shape away ever so slightly outside off, Vohra has a waft at it, but the ball goes past the blade]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Vohra, no run, on a length and outside off, Vohra opens the face of the bat and drives it towards backward point, Jadeja bends down to field it and gets hit on the knee, he's looking in some pain there as the physio walks out to take a look. The magic spray would probably take the pain away]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Bailey, 1 run, slower back of a length delivery on the stumps, Bailey gets an inside edge onto the thigh pad as he looks to work it away on the on-side, the batsmen take a quick single as the ball drops to the left of Bailey]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Bailey, no run, this time it's short and bowled even wider outside off, Bailey cuts it hard, but straight to McCullum at cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Bailey, <b>FOUR</b>, short and outside off, Bailey transfers his weight on the back foot and pulls it over a leaping mid-wicket, the ball hurries across the turf and crashes into the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Bailey, 1 run, tucks this delivery on middle stump line through backward square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Bailey, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a poor, poor ball from Negi. It was flatter and on the leg stump line, Bailey swivels and pulls it to the left of short fine leg, who had no chance of stopping that and Bailey collects four]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Bailey, 2 runs, Bailey gives charge to this delivery drifting in on middle stump line, he works it away to the left of short fine leg, Nehra gives chase and the batsmen take a couple in the meantime]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Vohra, 1 run, touch slower and on off, Vohra turns it through mid-wicket and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>George Bailey, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to W Saha, <b>out</b> Caught by Brendon McCullum!! PUN lose their first wicket. He bowled this one flatter and gets it to turn away outside off, Saha was looking to go inside-out over cover, but has to reach out for it. He ends up hitting it in the air off the toe-end of the bat, McCullum from extra cover runs to his left and takes a simple catch. <b>W Saha c Brendon McCullum b Negi 15(12) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Negi to W Saha, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to W Saha, 2 runs, drags this one short, Saha rocks back and pulls it through mid-wicket, the batsmen take a couple before the fielder in the deep runs to his left and stops the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to W Saha, 1 run, glides this short of length delivery outside off to third man after jumping in the crease, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to W Saha, <b>SIX</b>, short delivery from Pandey and Saha takes full toll of it, he had enough room there to free his arms as he muscles the pull over the deep mid-wicket fence for the first maximum of the innings]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to Vohra, 1 run, opens the face of the bat to this back of a length delivery in the channel outside off, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to W Saha, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off, there was some extra bounce as well, Saha hops in the crease, gets on top of the bounce and runs it down to third man after opening the face of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to W Saha, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Saha drops it with soft hands in front of point, he was looking for the single there but Vohra is not interested]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I Pandey to W Saha, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Saha goes on the back foot to cut, but mistimes it towards point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[There is a slip in place for Pandey]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ishwar Pandey, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to Vohra, no run, flighted delivery on off stump line, Vohra wristily works it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to W Saha, 1 run, darted on the pads, Saha glances it to short fine leg and the batsmen pinch a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to W Saha, <b>FOUR</b>, first boundary for Saha, it was a shortish delivery and there was enough width on offer for Saha to go back, he cuts it up and over the fielder at cover, the ball runs away to the deep extra cover fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to W Saha, no run, touch quicker and around off, Saha mistimes the drive to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to W Saha, no run, floated up on off, Saha leans forward and drives it straight to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Negi to W Saha, no run, flatter and just outside off, Saha punches it towards cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>W Saha and Vohra are at the crease. W Saha is on strike. Negi will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[CHN players break out of the huddle and are making their way out to the middle, followed by PUN's openers. Negi will start the proceedings. Saha will be on strike first up. There is a slip in place. Here we go then...]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai</b> (Playing XI): Brendon McCullum, Michael Hussey, Suresh Raina, Faf du Plessis, MS Dhoni(w/c), Dwayne Bravo, Pawan Negi, Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Ishwar Pandey, Ashish Nehra]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Punjab</b> (Playing XI): Wriddhiman Saha(w), Manan Vohra, Glenn Maxwell, David Miller, George Bailey(c), Axar Patel, Gurkeerat Singh Mann, Rishi Dhawan, Beuran Hendricks, Anureet Singh, Sandeep Sharma]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhoni:</b> "You want to top the table, because it gives you the extra chance if you have a bad day or an individual in the opposition ranks has a great day. We will try to focus on the process. If we win, we win or we will have to grind it out like we normally do. We have made a couple of changes, Doctor (Dwayne) Smith is not playing today, Hussey comes in and Ashish Nehra is fit and back in place of Mohit."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bailey:</b> "I am going to bat. It was nice, we obviously worked hard. We didn't have much to show for a few weeks, but it was good to get some reward the last time around. We'll try and play the same way. That can give us a bit of momentum for next year. We want to finish on a high, beating a team that are already through. We have the same eleven."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Punjab have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Toss and the team news are not far away. Stay tuned.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Team News:</b> With Brendon McCullum set to leave for national duty, it will be interesting to see if CHN give Michael Hussey a chance before the playoffs. McCullum's form has been instrumental for CHN's success this season and CHN might play him one last time, considering the top position is at stake. At the same time, Hussey hasn't played a game yet in this year's IPL and making him play directly in the playoffs could well turn out to be risky. PUN though might be willing to give a few Indian youngsters an opportunity to showcase their talent today.]]></line><line><![CDATA[CHN's last outing was an affair to forget. Playing against the seventh placed Delhi, CHN's batting failed miserably and they could only muster 119 runs in 20 overs. In reply, Shreyas Iyer and Yuvraj Singh starred with the bat and helped the Delhi win by 6 wickets. CHN though are a formidable unit and it will be a mistake to count them out because of a loss in their last game.]]></line><line><![CDATA[In their last game against BLR, PUN showed us why they can't be taken lightly even though they are languishing at the bottom of the table. In a game curtailed by rain, PUN managed to score 106 runs in their 10 overs. Their bowlers then came to the party as they restricted a strong BLR batting line-up to 84/6, winning the game by 22 runs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[CHN though have other things to look forward to. If they win today, they will move to 18 points and that will cement their place at the top of the points table, meaning they'll get two chances to reach the final this time around. On the other hand, PUN are playing for some pride and they wouldn't mind finishing their disappointing season on a high.]]></line><line><![CDATA[After a humdinger last night in Hyderabad, the IPL bandwagon now moves to Mohali, where the two Kings - Punjab and Chennai, will lock horns in their final league game. CHN have already qualified for the playoffs, while PUN have already been confirmed as the wooden spoon holders. Hello and a warm welcome to Match 53 of the Indian Premier League.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/>Amidst the hubbub of teams scampering for a play-off berth, Chennai and Punjab have a sense of serenity about them. And that is because they are not in the 11th hour race to make the cutoff. While MS Dhoni's men have been assured of a place in the final four for the eighth successive season, Punjab, last season's losing finalists, face the ignominy of ending up with the wooden spoon.<br/><br/>The clash at Mohali will, however, be significant in the larger scheme of things for the Chennai who'd dearly want to seal a spot in the top-two, a standing that would give them the luxury of a second chance at making the final should they falter in the first qualifier. Punjab, following their shock defeat of Bangalore, also have the incentive of ending, what has been a disastrous campaign, on a high.<br/><br/><b>Venue:</b> Punjab Cricket Association Stadium, Mohali<br/><br/><b>Date:</b> May 16, 2015<br/><br/><b>Time:</b> 16:00 IST<br/><br/><b>Weather:</b> Dry and sunny with a high of 41 degree Celsius.<br/><br/><b>Team News:</b><br/><br/><b>Punjab</b><br/><br/>Punjab experimented with Wriddhiman Saha in the opening slot to great effect against the Bangalore and will be tempted to play the same opening combination in a full game. That move should allow Glenn Maxwell, who has a fine record against the men in yellow, to take up his favoured No. 3 slot, a position that is expected to rekindle happier memories for the Australian. Meanwhile, Beuran Hendricks' bowling effort from two nights ago may just edge Thissara Perera out.<br/><br/>Probable XI:<br/><br/>Manan Vohra, Wriddhiman Saha (wk), Glenn Maxwell, David Miller, George Bailey (c), Axar Patel, Gurkeerat Singh Mann, Rishi Dhawan, Beuran Hendricks, Anureet Singh, Sandeep Sharma<br/><br/><b>Chennai</b><br/><br/>Not known to chop and change too much, Chennai will be expected to field a largely similar team. Ashish Nehra is likely to return in place of Ishwar Pandey after missing the game against Delhi with the flu. The think-tank could consider bringing in Michael Hussey for Brendon McCullum (scheduled to fly back at the end of the league stage) or run the risk of the former Australian cricketer playing his first game of the season straight in the knockouts.<br/><br/>Probable XI:<br/><br/>Dwayne Smith, Brendon McCullum/Michael Hussey, Suresh Raina, Faf du Plessis, MS Dhoni (c&wk), Pawan Negi, Dwayne Bravo, Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Mohit Sharma, Ashish Nehra.<br/><br/><b>Stats and Trivia:</b><br/><br/>- Glenn Maxwell scored 71 runs off 27 balls against R Ashwin in IPL 2014 at a strike-rate of 262.96.<br/><br/>- MS Dhoni is 83 short of recording 3000 IPL runs. He will become only the second CHN batsman, after Suresh Raina, to achieve the feat.<br/><br/><b>Quotes:</b><br/><br/>"The most important thing is that we don't chop and change the team. We try and stick to a core of players. Therefore the camaraderie and the team unity is there and that's most important."<br/><br/>- Dwayne Bravo reiterates CHN's success-mantra<br/><br/>"I have made my India debut but I can't just sit on that. I would like to continue being part of the team. So the IPL is important to me from that point of view as well. And then, the World T20 is also there, so in that sense too, performing well in the IPL is important"<br/><br/>- Axar Patel talks about the importance of keeping up the good performances.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chennai</b> (From): Brendon McCullum, Dwayne Smith, Suresh Raina, Faf du Plessis, MS Dhoni(c/w), Pawan Negi, Dwayne Bravo, Ravindra Jadeja, Ravichandran Ashwin, Ishwar Pandey, Mohit Sharma, Ashish Nehra, Baba Aparajith, Matt Henry, Mithun Manhas, Samuel Badree, Ronit More, Michael Hussey, Rahul Sharma, Kyle Abbott, Ankush Bains, Irfan Pathan, Pratyush Singh, Andrew Tye, Eklavya Dwivedi]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Punjab</b> (From): Manan Vohra, Murali Vijay, Wriddhiman Saha(w), Glenn Maxwell, David Miller, George Bailey(c), Gurkeerat Singh Mann, Axar Patel, Beuran Hendricks, Anureet Singh, Sandeep Sharma, Rishi Dhawan, Karanveer Singh, Parvinder Awana, Shardul Thakur, Shivam Sharma, Thisara Perera, Virender Sehwag, Nikhil Naik, Yogesh Golwalkar]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>130</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>7</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Punjab">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1465</playerid>
					<name>Wriddhiman Saha</name>
					<batsman-name>W Saha</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>W Saha</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>15</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Negi</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8281</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Brendon McCullum</fielder>
						<fielderId>201</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8358</playerid>
					<name>Manan Vohra</name>
					<batsman-name>Vohra</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Vohra</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>I Pandey</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8665</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ashish Nehra</fielder>
						<fielderId>269</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1440</playerid>
					<name>George Bailey</name>
					<batsman-name>Bailey</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bailey</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>12</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Nehra</bowler>
					<bowlerId>269</bowlerId>
						<fielder>MS Dhoni</fielder>
						<fielderId>265</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7662</playerid>
					<name>Glenn Maxwell</name>
					<batsman-name>Maxwell</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Maxwell</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>R Jadeja</bowler>
					<bowlerId>587</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8298</playerid>
					<name>Gurkeerat Singh Mann</name>
					<batsman-name>Gurkeerat Singh</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Gurkeerat Singh</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>15</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[stumped]]></status>
					<bowler>Ashwin</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1593</bowlerId>
						<fielder>MS Dhoni</fielder>
						<fielderId>265</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6349</playerid>
					<name>David Miller</name>
					<batsman-name>D Miller</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>D Miller</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>11</runs>
					<balls>15</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Negi</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8281</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ravindra Jadeja</fielder>
						<fielderId>587</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8808</playerid>
					<name>Axar Patel</name>
					<batsman-name>A Patel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>A Patel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>32</runs>
					<balls>29</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>DJ Bravo</bowler>
					<bowlerId>242</bowlerId>
						<fielder>MS Dhoni</fielder>
						<fielderId>265</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8616</playerid>
					<name>Rishi Dhawan</name>
					<batsman-name>R Dhawan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>R Dhawan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>25</runs>
					<balls>20</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9490</playerid>
					<name>Beuran Hendricks</name>
					<batsman-name>B Hendricks</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Beuran Hendricks</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1876</playerid>
					<name>Anureet Singh</name>
					<batsman-name>Anureet Singh</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Anureet Singh</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8356</playerid>
					<name>Sandeep Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Sandeep Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sandeep Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1465</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>16</runs>
				<overs>2.2</overs>
				<batsman>Wriddhiman Saha</batsman>
				<batsman-name>W Saha</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1440</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>31</runs>
				<overs>4.1</overs>
				<batsman>George Bailey</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Bailey</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8358</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>35</runs>
				<overs>5.1</overs>
				<batsman>Manan Vohra</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Vohra</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8298</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>53</runs>
				<overs>8.3</overs>
				<batsman>Gurkeerat Singh Mann</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Gurkeerat Singh</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7662</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>55</runs>
				<overs>9.5</overs>
				<batsman>Glenn Maxwell</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Maxwell</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6349</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>78</runs>
				<overs>13.5</overs>
				<batsman>David Miller</batsman>
				<batsman-name>D Miller</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8808</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>122</runs>
				<overs>18.6</overs>
				<batsman>Axar Patel</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Patel</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>4</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>9</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Chennai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8281</playerid>
					<name>Pawan Negi</name>
					<bowler-name>Negi</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Negi</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8665</playerid>
					<name>Ishwar Pandey</name>
					<bowler-name>I Pandey</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>I Pandey</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>22</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>269</playerid>
					<name>Ashish Nehra</name>
					<bowler-name>Nehra</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nehra</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>17</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<bowler-name>Ashwin</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ashwin</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>14</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<bowler-name>R Jadeja</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>18</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<bowler-name>Raina</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Raina</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>8</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>242</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
					<bowler-name>DJ Bravo</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>20</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<bowler-name>B McCullum</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Brendon McCullum</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>4772</playerid>
					<name>Michael Hussey</name>
					<bowler-name>M Hussey</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M Hussey</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7825</playerid>
					<name>Faf du Plessis</name>
					<bowler-name>du Plessis</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>du Plessis</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhoni</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhoni</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>134</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>3</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>16.5</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Chennai">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>4772</playerid>
					<name>Michael Hussey</name>
					<batsman-name>M Hussey</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M Hussey</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Sandeep Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8356</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Wriddhiman Saha</fielder>
						<fielderId>1465</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Brendon McCullum</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>B Hendricks</bowler>
					<bowlerId>9490</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7825</playerid>
					<name>Faf du Plessis</name>
					<batsman-name>du Plessis</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>du Plessis</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>55</runs>
					<balls>41</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>R Dhawan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8616</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Raina</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>41</runs>
					<balls>34</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhoni</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>25</runs>
					<balls>16</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>242</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Bravo</name>
					<batsman-name>DJ Bravo</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Bravo</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8281</playerid>
					<name>Pawan Negi</name>
					<batsman-name>Negi</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Negi</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>587</playerid>
					<name>Ravindra Jadeja</name>
					<batsman-name>R Jadeja</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ravindra Jadeja</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1593</playerid>
					<name>Ravichandran Ashwin</name>
					<batsman-name>Ashwin</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ashwin</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8665</playerid>
					<name>Ishwar Pandey</name>
					<batsman-name>I Pandey</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>I Pandey</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>269</playerid>
					<name>Ashish Nehra</name>
					<batsman-name>Nehra</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nehra</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>4772</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>2</runs>
				<overs>0.6</overs>
				<batsman>Michael Hussey</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Hussey</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>201</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>10</runs>
				<overs>1.5</overs>
				<batsman>Brendon McCullum</batsman>
				<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7825</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>102</runs>
				<overs>13.3</overs>
				<batsman>Faf du Plessis</batsman>
				<batsman-name>du Plessis</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>6</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>6</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Punjab">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8356</playerid>
					<name>Sandeep Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Sandeep Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sandeep Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>9</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9490</playerid>
					<name>Beuran Hendricks</name>
					<bowler-name>B Hendricks</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Beuran Hendricks</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8298</playerid>
					<name>Gurkeerat Singh Mann</name>
					<bowler-name>Gurkeerat Singh</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Gurkeerat Singh</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>22</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8616</playerid>
					<name>Rishi Dhawan</name>
					<bowler-name>R Dhawan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>R Dhawan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>12</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7662</playerid>
					<name>Glenn Maxwell</name>
					<bowler-name>Maxwell</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Maxwell</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>8</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8808</playerid>
					<name>Axar Patel</name>
					<bowler-name>A Patel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>A Patel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>28</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1876</playerid>
					<name>Anureet Singh</name>
					<bowler-name>Anureet Singh</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Anureet Singh</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2.5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>30</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1465</playerid>
					<name>Wriddhiman Saha</name>
					<bowler-name>W Saha</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>W Saha</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8358</playerid>
					<name>Manan Vohra</name>
					<bowler-name>Vohra</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Vohra</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6349</playerid>
					<name>David Miller</name>
					<bowler-name>D Miller</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>D Miller</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1440</playerid>
					<name>George Bailey</name>
					<bowler-name>Bailey</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bailey</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



