<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14632" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>38th Match</gameDesc>
		<series>Indian T20 League 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Kolkata</home>
		<away>Hyderabad</away>
		<teamsabbr>KOL vs HYD</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>KOL</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>HYD</awayabbr>
		<homeId>63</homeId>
		<awayId>255</awayId>
		<venue>Eden Gardens, Kolkata</venue>
		<startdate>04 05 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>04 05 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Hyderabad</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Kolkata won by 35 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Kolkata</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>35</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Marais Erasmus</Name>
			<Country>RSA</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Anil Chaudhary</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Krishnamachari Srinivasan</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Rajendra Jadeja</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>14:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150504180315</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>HYD</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>KOL</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>132</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>9</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>20</batteamovers>
		<status>Kolkata won by 35 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>508</playerid>
			<name>Dale Steyn*</name>
			<batsman-name>Steyn</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Steyn</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>1</runs>
			<balls-faced>1</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>1726</playerid>
			<name>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</name>
			<batsman-name>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>11</runs>
			<balls-faced>4</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>1</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1858</playerid>
			<name>Umesh Yadav*</name>
			<bowler-name>Umesh</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>U Yadav</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>34</runs>
			<wickets>2</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>7736</playerid>
			<name>Andre Russell</name>
			<bowler-name>A Russell</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>A Russell</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>2</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>10</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>168</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>592</playerid>
<name>Praveen Kumar</name>
<player-runs>12</player-runs>
<player-balls>16</player-balls>
<runs>131</runs>
<wicket-nbr>9</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>7736</bowlerid>
<bowlername>A Russell</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>4</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>4</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[1 1 1 . 1 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>6 6 6 2 Wd W . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 6 1 . 2 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. . . W 1 . ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_T20_LEAGUE/KOL_HYD_MAY04/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[<b>Warner:</b> 'We wanted to keep them under 150-160, but they managed to acore 167. However, when you lose so many wickets under the first 10 overs, it is hard to come back. Their spinners bowled really well during the middle overs. Our next few games are on good wickets. Our bowlers need to step up there and  hopefully, we can start well with the bat there.']]></line><line><![CDATA[The hosts reached a competitive total mainly on the back of useful hands played by Robin Uthappa, Gautam Gambhir and Manish Pandey. KOL are now placed third in the points table with 11 points from 10 games.  ]]></line><line><![CDATA[HYD's batsmen put up a listless show as they hurtled towards a defeat. Once Umesh Yadav struck twice in a single over to send David Warner and Naman Ojha back to the pavilion, the visitors never recovered. The spin duo of Piyush Chawla and Brad Hogg then tied the batsmen in knots to take the game away from HYD's grasp. By the time Karn Sharma and Bhuvneshwar Kumar unfurled a series of shots, the game was all but over.  <br/>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Bhuvneshwar, no run, <b>KOL win by 35 runs! This is their fifth win of the campaign.</b> It was bowled in the channel outside off, Bhuvneshwar goes for a big slog and fails to connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Steyn, 1 run, full on the stumps, Steyn drills it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dale Steyn, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to P Kumar, <b>out</b> Caught by U Yadav!! Short slow delivery outside off, Praveen was looking to ramp it over the keeper but can only hit it high in the air. Short third man moves to his left and takes a simple catch. <b>P Kumar c U Yadav b A Russell 12(16) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A Russell to P Kumar, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Russell is bowling here without lifting his left hand]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to P Kumar, no run, Russell bowls this one well outside off, Praveen can't reach out as he was backing away at first, the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to P Kumar, no run, another slower short ball from Russell, Praveen backs away and looks to pull it hard, but fails to connect yet again]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to P Kumar, no run, slower ball from Russell, Praveen backs away and looks to go big once again, fails to lay bat on it and the ball goes past the off stump]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell [1.0-0-9-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to P Kumar, 1 run, short of length delivery on the stumps, Praveen clears his front leg and goes for the slog, doesn't connect too well and the ball rolls away to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to P Kumar, 2 runs, shortish and slightly wide outside off, Praveen slaps it to the right of long-off, Russell makes a tumbling stop once again and the batsmen take two in the meantime]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to P Kumar, no run, slower ball from Umesh, Praveen goes for a big slog over mid-wicket, but fails to connect. The ball goes over the off stump and rolls away towards the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bhuvneshwar, 1 run, just short of a good length and outside off, Bhuvneshwar guides it to the left of backward point, the batsmen cross over for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bhuvneshwar, <b>SIX</b>, Bhuvi comes down the track and does well to send it over the long-off fence, Umesh bowls it slightly short and Bhuvi tonks it over the fence for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bhuvneshwar, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a nice way to get off the mark, it was a length delivery outside off, Bhuvneshwar lofts it inside-out over extra cover and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav [3.0-0-20-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to P Kumar, no run, flighted delivery just outside off, Praveen pushes it to the left of the bowler, he wanted the single but is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bhuvneshwar Kumar, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Karn Sharma, <b>out</b> Caught by Suryakumar Yadav!! Finally, Botha has the last laugh as Karn makes his way back to the hut. He went for another slog sweep this time but had to reach out for the shot as the ball was tossed up well outside off, he drags it straight down the throat of the fielder at long-on, who takes it easily in the end. <b>Karn Sharma c Suryakumar Yadav b J Botha 32(20) [6s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[J Botha to Karn Sharma, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Karn Sharma, <b>wide</b>, bowls this one well wide outside off, Karn can't lay bat on it and the umpire exercises his arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Karn Sharma, 2 runs, kneels down once again and drags the slog sweep from well outside off, the ball falls in the gap between long-on and deep mid-wicket, the batsmen take two before long-on runs to his left and stops it]]></line><line><![CDATA[There was a little delay as the ball was returned by the crowd after some time]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Karn Sharma, <b>SIX</b>, <b>third consecutive six for Karn</b>, it was a flighted delivery from Botha, Karn kneels down and slog sweeps it over the deep mid-wicket fence. These are some big blows from the leggie]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Karn Sharma, <b>SIX</b>, this time Botha drags his length back outside off, Karn rocks back and pulls it magnificently over the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Karn Sharma, <b>SIX</b>, tossed up on the stumps, Karn goes for a big loft over long-off, doesn't connect too well. Pandey at the rope, jumps up and tries to take the catch, but can only manage to parry it over the fence. Nice effort though]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to P Kumar, no run, another googly and once again Praveen fails to pick it up, he looks to push at it and the ball goes past the outside edge yet again]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Karn Sharma, 1 run, doesn't pick the googly this time, but manages to get his bat down in time to keep it out, the ball rolls away to square leg and the batsmen cross over]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Karn Sharma, no run, slower through the air and Karn gets down on one knee to sweep, the ball turns away past the blade and the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to P Kumar, 1 run, tossed up just outside off, Praveen drills the drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Karn Sharma, 1 run, gets this one to turn away from just outside off, Karn stays back and nudges it towards short third man, who fails to pick it cleanly. The batsmen comfortably complete the single in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to P Kumar, 1 run, shortish outside off, Praveen cuts it to backward point and the batsmen pinch a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to P Kumar, 1 run, darts this one just outside off, Praveen jams out the drive to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Karn Sharma, 1 run, drifting on middle stump line, Karn works it away through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Karn Sharma, no run, play and a miss! It was tossed up outside off and turns away, Karn was pushing at it and the ball goes past the outside edge. The keeper can't collect it cleanly either]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to P Kumar, 1 run, bowls it in the blockhole wide outside off, Praveen reaches out and squeezes it towards the cover-point region for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Back to over the wicket for the right-hander]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Karn Sharma, 1 run, touch slower this time around, Karn guides it towards short third man and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Karn Sharma, no run, <b>dropped!</b> Uthappa has put this down, it was floated up outside off and turns away, Karn looks to run it down towards third man, but gets an outside edge and Uthappa can't hang onto it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Johan Botha [2.0-0-7-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to P Kumar, <b>FOUR</b>, Praveen fails to pick the googly once again, Praveen pushes at it, gets an outside edge that runs away past short third man, who dives to his right but fails to stop it]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Karn Sharma, 1 run, drags his length back this time, Sharma goes for the pull but mistimes it towards long-on, it was in the air for a little while but falls in no man's land]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to P Kumar, 1 run, on the pads this time, Praveen clips it to deep square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to P Kumar, no run, this one turns back in sharply, Kumar was looking to flick but fails to connect and wears it on the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Karn Sharma, 1 run, googly from Hogg, Karn clips it through square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Praveen Kumar, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Henriques, <b>out</b> Caught by M Pandey!! Henriques goes first ball after the strategic time-out. HYD are falling apart here. It was tossed up on the stumps, Henriques goes for a big swipe across the line but ends up slicing it high. Pandey calls for the catch, runs back and to his right and takes the catch. He judged it really well. <b>Henriques c M Pandey b B Hogg 41(33) [4s-2 6s-2]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[B Hogg to Henriques, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Brad Hogg [2.0-0-6-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Henriques, 1 run, floated up just outside off, Henriques drives it to deep extra cover and he will retain the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Karn Sharma, 1 run, on middle stump line this time, Sharma goes across slightly and works it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Henriques, 1 run, Henriques clears his front leg and mistimes the slog completely, the ball rolls away to long-on. He was looking at the toe-end of the bat after playing that shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Karn Sharma, 1 run, drifting on middle and leg, Sharma works it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Henriques, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Henriques drives it down to long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Karn Sharma, 1 run, drags this short and outside off, Sharma rocks back and pulls it to deep mid-wicket for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Karn Sharma, 1 run, yorker on off, Sharma squeezes it out to backward point, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Henriques, 1 run, goes for a slog this time, but mistimes it completely. The ball goes on the bounce to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Karn Sharma, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off, Karn waits on the back foot, opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Henriques, 1 run, banged in short this time, Henriques swivels on the pull and sends it towards fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Karn Sharma, 1 run, guides this delivery outside off towards third man and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Henriques, 1 run, on a good length and on the stumps, Henriques pushes it down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav [2.0-0-14-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Karn Sharma, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Bipul Sharma, <b>out</b> Bipul Sharma Run Out!! 1 run completed. This is disastrous from HYD. Another one goes down. Bipul Sharma worked this delivery off his pads past square leg, the batsmen decide to take the second but Bipul Sharma was slow to turn back for his second, the fielder from deep mid-wicket runs to his left and fires a flat throw at the striker's end. Uthappa does the rest. <b>Bipul Sharma run out (Umesh Yadav/Uthappa) 1(2)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chawla to Bipul Sharma, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire called in for another run-out check. He is out of his crease as Uthappa whips the bails off. Uthappa might have dislodged a bail before collecting the ball or did the ball clip the stumps before going into Uthappa's gloves? Not sure about it. It is a difficult one for the third umpire. Replays are in and it looks like Uthappa might have dislodged the bail with the ball in contact with the gloves. Third umpire is taking his own sweet time to decide.  The decision is <b>OUT</b> and Bipul Sharma has to go]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Bipul Sharma, no run, goes across to this delivery on middle and leg and clips it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bipul Sharma, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Vihari, <b>out</b> Stumped!! Half the side is back in the hut now. Vihari gives the charge and Chawla drags his length back seeing him come down the track, he fails to lay bat on the drive as it goes past the inside edge of the bat, the keeper collects and takes the bails off in a flash. Vihari's struggle comes to an end. <b>Vihari st Uthappa b Chawla 6(12)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chawla to Vihari, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Stumped!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Henriques, 1 run, flatter and wide outside off, Henriques reaches out for it and mistimes the cut towards cover, the batsmen take a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Henriques, no run, flighted delivery just outside off, Henriques pushes it to the left of the bowler, the fielder from cover moves to his right to stop the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Vihari, 1 run, comes down the track and Vihari clips this one down to long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Vihari, 1 run, floated up outside off, Vihari drives it to sweeper cover and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Vihari, no run, wrong' un from Hogg, Vihari doesn't read it and ends up mistiming it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Henriques, 1 run, quicker one on the middle stump line, Henriques works it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Henriques, no run, Hogg bowls this one flatter outside off, the ball turns back in as Henriques goes for a slog, he fails to connect and drags his foot out for some time, but he fails to connect. He drags his foot back in though just in time before Uthappa takes the bails off]]></line><line><![CDATA[A stumping chance has been sent upstairs. Henriques is the man in question. Was his foot in the air? Looks like he dragged it back in. Uthappa was fairly confident but Henriques has made his ground here. He should be Not Out and it is <b>Not Out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Vihari, 1 run, tossed up just outside off, Vihari drives it to long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Vihari, no run, turns in from outside off, there was extra bounce on the ball as Vihari tries to guide it past slip, but he ends up chopping it past the off stump and towards the keeper]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brad Hogg [1.0-0-3-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Vihari, 1 run, wrong 'un around off, Vihari crouches low and wrists it in front of long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Vihari, no run, slower and on off, Vihari goes back and knocks it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Henriques, 1 run, bit short and turning away, Henriques goes deep in the crease, nurdles it off the inner part, just wide of leg-stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Vihari, 1 run, tossed up on off, Vihari comes down the track and works it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Vihari, no run, flighted on middle, Vihari closes the bat face early on the flick, the leading edge rolls towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Henriques, 1 run, googly just outside off, Henriques drags the drive to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;ten Doeschate to Henriques, 1 run, bit of width on this delivery, Henriques slaps square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;ten Doeschate to Henriques, no run, fuller and around off, Henriques mistimes the drive to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;ten Doeschate to Vihari, 1 run, wicket-to-wicket from Tendo, Vihari gets inside the line and nudges it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;ten Doeschate to Vihari, <b>wide</b>, sprays it well down leg, Uthappa does well to get glove to that, saved a certain boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[Robin is standing up to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;ten Doeschate to Vihari, no run, on a length just outside off, Vihari gets behind the line and defends back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[Good news for KOL supporters as Russell is back on the field. His left shoulder has been heavily strapped.]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;ten Doeschate to Henriques, 1 run, good length ball on off, Henriques nurdles it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hanuma Vihari, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;ten Doeschate to Eoin Morgan, <b>out</b> Eoin Morgan Run Out!! An unnecessary wicket thrown away by HYD. Short and outside off, Morgan cracks the cut towards backward point, GG fumbles and Henriques wanted the run, Morgan was never interested but has to go as Henriques was halfway down the wicket, Gambhir throws the ball to Tendo, who does the rest. Morgan was nowhere in the picture. <b>Eoin Morgan run out (Gambhir/ten Doeschate) 5(11)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[ten Doeschate to Eoin Morgan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ryan ten Doeschate, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire pressed into service for a run-out chance. Morgan the man in question. He is a long way out of the crease. HYD lose their 4th wicket and Morgan is the latest to walk back to the pavilion.]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, wrong 'un outside leg, Morgan goes back and flicks to deep square leg, called for two but settles with one as the fielder got there quickly]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Henriques, 1 run, trifle short and outside off, Henriques cuts square of the wicket, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Henriques, no run, flighted delivery close to off, Henriques presses it to cover after coming forward]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, quicker and around off, Morgan prods forward to defend, the ball squirts off the inside edge to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Eoin Morgan, no run, Chawla is also getting some turn, Morgan misses the nudge, the ball lobs off the pads and lands on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chawla to Eoin Morgan, no run, googly just outside off, Morgan hangs back and cuts to backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Piyush Chawla, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Henriques, no run, Pathan goes round the wicket, tosses it up on off, defended back down the wicket, he also gets the approval from Uthappa, who tells him to bowl like this]]></line><line><![CDATA[The umpires are changing the ball. Looks like it has gone out of shape. Uthappa was furious when Pathan conceded the second six]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Henriques, <b>FOUR</b>, Pathan tries to overcompensates, drags the length back, Henriques was waiting for that, he rocks back and pulls it to deep mid-wicket, split the two fielders to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Henriques, <b>SIX</b>, Henriques sees Pathan as the weak link in the bowling line-up, takes him on and gets the second six of the over, this time gets to the pitch and whips it flat and over wide long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Henriques, 2 runs, tossed up around off, Henriques chips it wide of long-on for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Henriques, <b>SIX</b>, superb shot! Henriques is not afraid to play his shots. He races down the wicket, doesn't get to the pitch, but still goes through with the shot, sends it sailing over deep mid-wicket for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Y Pathan to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, starts from round the wicket, drops it short and outside off, Morgan cuts to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yusuf Pathan, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, fullish and on off, Morgan drives down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Henriques, 1 run, tossed up around off, Henriques comes down the track and knocks it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, drifting onto the pads, Morgan tucks it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Eoin Morgan, no run, quicker and on off, Morgan pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Eoin Morgan, no run, flighted from round the wicket, gets a bit of turn, Morgan pushes at that, the ball takes the outer half and rolls to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Henriques, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, Henriques eases it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Eoin Morgan, no run, huge shout for lbw, but umpire Erasmus walks forward and hands the cap to Hogg. The googly to welcome the new batsman, Morgan didn't pick it, stayed back and fails to get bat on ball, is struck above the kneeroll, would have gone over the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Eoin Morgan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Dhawan, <b>out</b> Caught by M Pandey!! Dhawan has hit a half-tracker straight to the fielder. He can't believe he has picked out the fielder, but Hogg is chuffed to bits, he knows that was a lucky breakthrough. A real long hop on middle and leg, Dhawan goes deep in the crease, it should have been put away, but he pulls it straight to backward square leg. Pandey didn't move an inch to take that. <b>Dhawan c M Pandey b B Hogg 15(15) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[B Hogg to Dhawan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Dhawan, no run, fraction short and just outside off, Dhawan cuts it on the bounce to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Henriques, 1 run, skids on after pitching, Henriques hangs back, gets his bat down in time and works it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Dhawan, 1 run, the wrong 'un, Dhawan didn't have a clue about that, he was shaping to play the pull, gets an inside edge onto the pad, the ball dribbles to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;B Hogg to Henriques, 1 run, slightly short in length, Henriques goes back and flicks to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brad Hogg, left-arm chinaman, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Henriques, 1 run, fires it full and just outside off, Henriques whips it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Dhawan, 1 run, slower through the air, Dhawan skips out of the crease and nudges it in front of mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Dhawan, no run, tossed up around off, Dhawan comes down the track and push-drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Dhawan, no run, quicker and goes on with the angle, Dhawan flicks and gets an inside edge onto the pad, the ball rolls to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Dhawan, no run, flighted on off, Dhawan presses forward and defends to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[Botha goes round the wicket to Dhawan]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Botha to Henriques, 1 run, pushed through on off and middle, Henriques works it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Johan Botha, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dhawan, no run, Umesh comes round the wicket, keeps it full and just outside off, Dhawan drives and picks out cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[Russell has hurt himself while trying to stop the ball. He didn't move after rolling over the rope. Looks like he has damaged his left shoulder. He landed badly and the physio is taking him off the field. Hopefully, it is not serious as Russell is a key member of this KOL outfit. Cummins is on as a substitute.]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, once more Dhawan times it superbly. Umesh drifts onto the pads, Dhawan stays back and flicks it to deep square leg, Russell runs to his right and dives, he flicks the ball in but it still rolls and touches the ad cushions]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dhawan, no run, back of a length around off, Dhawan knocks it in front of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dhawan, no run, too full and on the stumps, Dhawan squeezes it to extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dhawan, no run, slanted across the left-hander, Dhawan has a loose poke at that, the angle beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, overpitched and Umesh pays the price. Dhawan gets a good stride forward and drives past extra cover, the bat turned in his hands, but he still gets the desired timing]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Henriques, no run, cracking shot for nothing. Again the length is short and outside off, Henriques stands tall and punches, finds cover-point to perfection. Either side and that would have been four more]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Henriques, no run, drags the length back around off, Henriques punches it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Henriques, <b>FOUR</b>, top shot! Banged in midway down the pitch, the Aussies are very good with dealing with such deliveries, he rocks back and pulls powerfully in front of square. The ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Henriques, no run, short of length around off, Henriques gets behind the line and defends to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhawan, 1 run, back of a length around off, Dhawan opens the bat face and guides it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Dhawan, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! Dhawan watched two of his partners walk back to the pavilion, he gets off the mark with a fabulous shot. Good length delivery just outside off, Dhawan comes half forward and creams it through cover, the timing takes it away from the chasing fielders]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Moises Henriques, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to N Ojha, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Another one for Umesh. HYD in trouble as Ojha departs without troubling the scorers. After a few that left the batsman, he gets this one to nip back in from a length, Ojha prods forward to defend, is beaten off the inside edge, the ball castles into off-stump. Dream start for Umesh and KOL. <b>N Ojha b U Yadav 0(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[U Yadav to N Ojha, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to N Ojha, no run, excellent delivery, short of length moves away just outside off, Ojha has a tentative poke at that and then withdraws his bat, he was clearly beaten there]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to N Ojha, no run, shortish and outside off, shapes away further, Ojha lets it go, looks at the ump for a wide, but it was just inside the tramline]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to N Ojha, <b>wide</b>, splays it down leg, too far away for Ojha to reach it, another run added to the total]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Naman Ojha, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Warner, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Castled! The Eden Gardens goes berserk. Umesh is delighted as he goes on a celebratory run. Full delivery shapes away from the left-hander, Warner is opened up a touch, he tries to defend, the ball seams away and beats the outside edge, the off-stump is pegged back. Super start for the hosts. <b>Warner b U Yadav 4(3) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[U Yadav to Warner, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Warner, <b>FOUR</b>, Warner is off and running. Can't bowl short to this man, banged in halfway down the wicket, Warner rocks back and pulls it in front of square, the man in the deep had no chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[No slip in place..]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Warner, no run, fuller and on the stumps, Warner pushes it to mid-off, calls "wait on" for the single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Warner, <b>wide</b>, wayward start from Umesh, sprays it well wide of off, Warner goes chasing after it, still can't reach it, easy call for the umpire]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Warner and Dhawan are at the crease. Warner is on strike. U Yadav will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back... The KOL players are out in the middle. Warner and Dhawan follow them closely. There is a bit of spin and KOL have 3 spinners. Will HYD register their third successive win? Answer coming up in a couple of hours. Umesh to start proceedings..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Henriques</b>: "They got off to a good start, but our spinners pulled things back. The pitch is a little slow. I think we should take 167. It's very humid out there."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bipul Sharma and Karn Sharma bowled well in tandem. Moises Henriques too bowled tidily. With three main spinners in KOL's ranks, it would be interesting to see how they will bowl on this deck. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Robin Uthappa, Gautam Gambhir and Manish Pandey essayed fluent knocks to pilot KOL to a competitive total. Gambhir and Uthappa gave the home team a rousing start. Manish then showcased exemplary footwork to counter the spinners. However, once Manish was run out, the visitors were able to curtail the run flow to some extent. Yusuf Pathan then played a handy innings to lift the scoring rate towards the end.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Y Pathan, 2 runs, fine yorker, Pathan digs it out to mid-wicket and Chawla races back for the second run. It was turning out to be a great over, but Bhvi lost it in the second half of the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Y Pathan, <b>FOUR</b>, four more! These are handy runs for KOL. Short ball on the leg stump, Pathan pulls and sends it through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Y Pathan, <b>FOUR</b>, short and wide outside off stump, Pathan waits for the ball and slaps it hard over extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Chawla, 1 run, Chawla goes across the stumps, Bhuvneshwar bowls a full toss following him, Chawla tries to paddle it fine, but gets the toe-end of the bat and it rolls to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Y Pathan, 1 run, top edge, but it doesn't carry to short fine leg. Bhuvneshwar bangs this slower ball short, Pathan tries to hook, but only manages to get the edge, the ball lands safely at backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Chawla, 1 run, fine yorker length delivery just outside off stump, Chawla gets an inside edge onto pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Chawla, 1 run, yorker on the leg stump, Chawla digs it out to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Y Pathan, 1 run, full toss but Pathan has hit it straight to the man sweeping on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Chawla, 1 run, Steyn takes pace off the ball, but Chawla goes leg-side and guides it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Y Pathan, 1 run, Pathan swings hard at this full ball, but mistimes it to the man at sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Chawla, 1 run, slower delivery on the off stump, Chawla looks to defend, gets an inside edge and it rolls to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Chawla, <b>FOUR</b>, friendly ball from Steyn and Chawla gets off the mark in style. Good length delivery down the leg-side, Chawla whips it away past short fine leg and it runs away for four]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dale Steyn [3.0-0-28-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Piyush Chawla, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Suryakumar Yadav, <b>out</b> Caught by Henriques!! Tries to be cheeky with a reverse-sweep, but only manages to get the toe-end of the bat and backward point runs in to take an easy catch. Bhuvneshwar dragged his length back on seeing Suryakumar attempt the shot and gets his second wicket. <b>Suryakumar Yadav c Henriques b Bhuvneshwar 6(3) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bhuvneshwar to Suryakumar Yadav, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Suryakumar Yadav, <b>FOUR</b>, that is his favourite shot. Good length delivery on the leg stump, Suryakumar Yadav gets inside the line and helps it on its way, fine leg runs to his left but the ball wins the race]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Suryakumar Yadav, 2 runs, gets his front foot across the stumps and flicks it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Suryakumar Yadav, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to J Botha, <b>out</b> Bowled!! The reverse sweep costs him his wicket this time. This was a short of length delivery well outside leg stump, Botha tries to send it fine past short third man, gets an under edge and it crashes into the leg stump. <b>J Botha b Bhuvneshwar 12(6) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bhuvneshwar to J Botha, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to J Botha, <b>SIX</b>, that's a lucky six for Botha and KOL. Bhuvneshwar misses the yorker and bowls a low full toss, Botha gets down on one knee and tries to reverse paddles it, connects well and the ball flies over the keeper's head for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Y Pathan, 1 run, slower delivery on the off stump, flicked just behind square for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Bhuvneshwar Kumar [2.0-0-16-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Y Pathan, 3 runs, short of length delivery just outside off stump, Pathan looks to play off the back foot, gets an inside edge that goes past the stumps, Praveen Kumar dives to his right at short fine leg but deflects the ball, Bipul Sharma gives chase from short third man and just pulls it back inside the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to J Botha, 1 run, slower delivery on the off stump, Botha turns it through square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Y Pathan, 1 run, short of length delivery on the off stump, punched towards long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to J Botha, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Botha chops the cut to the right of the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Y Pathan, leg byes, 1 run, slower delivery just moving back in, Pathan misses the flick, gets hit on the thigh pad and Botha races to take strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Y Pathan, <b>FOUR</b>, full and on the off stump, Pathan walks across the stumps and flicks it nicely off his pads over mid-wicket and gets it in the gap]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Time-out</b>. KOL have scored 40 runs and lost 3 wickets in the last 5 overs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to J Botha, <b>FOUR</b>, inside edge and it's gone for four. Shortish and on the off stump, Botha rocks back and looks to pull, gets an edge and it luckily escapes past the stumps to the fine leg boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to J Botha, no run, good length delivery outside off stump, Botha swings and misses, the ball beats the inside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Y Pathan, 1 run, a <b>direct-hit would have been curtains</b> for Pathan, in fact he gave up. Shortish and on the off stump, Pathan mistimes the pull to mid-wicket, Vihari has a shy at the bowler's end but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Y Pathan, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Pathan cuts it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Y Pathan, <b>wide</b>, short and outside off stump, Pathan reaches out for the cut but it was too wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Y Pathan, <b>FOUR</b>, full delivery outside off stump, Pathan leans forward and drives it past the bowler, mid-off had no chance. Remember Dale Steyn v Yusuf Pathan last year?]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Y Pathan, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Pathan cuts it to the left of backward point, who makes an excellent stop]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Johan Botha, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dale Steyn [2.0-0-18-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to ten Doeschate, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Big shout for LBW and he's got a wicket. Short of a length delivery on the stumps, it keeps a bit low, ten Doeschate was shaping up for the pull, but is beaten by the lack of bounce, gets hit on the pad and it was plumb in front. KOL need to be careful. <b>ten Doeschate lbw b Henriques 8(7)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Henriques to ten Doeschate, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Y Pathan, 1 run, good length delivery on the off stump, Pathan flicks it through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Y Pathan, no run, slower delivery on the off stump, Pathan defends it back to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Y Pathan, no run, back of a length delivery outside off stump, Pathan punches it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to ten Doeschate, 1 run, low full toss, worked away to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to ten Doeschate, 2 runs, slower delivery outside off stump, ten Doeschate looks to defend, the ball brushes the pad before hitting the bat, HYD appeal for LBW but rightly the umpire says no as the impact was well wide of off stump]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Moises Henriques [1.0-0-6-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to Y Pathan, 2 runs, on the leg stump, Pathan flicks it to mid-wicket, Bipul runs to his right and has a shy at the bowler's end but the throw was wild and they get an overthrow]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Yusuf Pathan, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to M Pandey, <b>out</b> M Pandey Run Out!! Needless run attempted by Pandey. He was playing well but the rush of blood has cost him his wicket. Flighted delivery just outside off stump, Pandey drives it towards the bowler, Bipul dives to his left and half-stops the ball, Pandey tries to steal a quick single, but ten Doeschate is not keen, Pandey tries to get back but he was halfway down the track, Bipul fired a throw adjacent to the stumps and Ojha made no mistake. <b>M Pandey run out (Bipul Sharma/N Ojha) 33(26) [4s-1 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bipul Sharma to M Pandey, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to ten Doeschate, 1 run, steps out and nudges the flighted delivery to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to M Pandey, 1 run, ugly shot from Pandey. Bipul Sharma bowls this wide outside off stump on seeing Pandey advance, but the batsman manages to fetch and sweep it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to ten Doeschate, 1 run, pushed away to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to M Pandey, 1 run, nicely floated up outside off stump, Pandey waits for the ball and slaps it to deep extra-cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to ten Doeschate, 2 runs, on the stumps, hangs back and tucks it though square leg and quickly retuns for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to M Pandey, 1 run, on the leg stump, Pandey punches it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to ten Doeschate, 1 run, flatter delivery outside off stump, ten Doeschate defends off the back foot to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to M Pandey, 1 run, low full toss on the leg stump, Pandey flicks it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to M Pandey, <b>FOUR</b>, short and spinning away outside off stump, Pandey waits for the ball and cuts fiercely, backward point dives to his right but the ball escapes]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to M Pandey, <b>SIX</b>, brave hit from Pandey. Not close to the pitch of the ball after coming down the track, yet he goes through with the loft and hits it straight back over the bowler's head]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ryan ten Doeschate, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to A Russell, <b>out</b> Caught by Eoin Morgan!! The big hitting Andre Russell is gone! Big wicket for HYD. Flighted delivery just outside off stump, Russell goes for the slog-sweep, but gets it on the toe-end of the bat, long-on didn't have to move this time and he made no mistake. <b>A Russell c Eoin Morgan b Bipul Sharma 1(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bipul Sharma to A Russell, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to M Pandey, 1 run, races down the track, Bipul Sharma drags his length back, Pandey pushes it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to M Pandey, 2 runs, that is a <b>brilliant bit of fielding by Eoin Morgan</b>. Flighted delivery on the leg stump, Pandey steps out and lofts, gets it on the inside half of the bat, Morgan runs to his right from long-on, jumps and takes the catch but before he lands over the rope, he releases the ball, Hanuma Vihari stayed close to him after running to his left, but Morgan couldn't push it back to him]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to A Russell, 1 run, hangs back and punches it off the back foot to long-off to get off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to A Russell, no run, shortish and outside off stump, punched to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to M Pandey, 1 run, steps out and flicks the flighted delivery wide of long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Uthappa, <b>out</b> Caught by Warner!! That is a sensational catch by the HYD skipper. Flighted delivery spinning away outside off stump, Uthappa goes leg-side and slaps very hard, Warner dives to his right and takes it with both hands at cover. That ball was travelling, but he did well to hold on. <b>Uthappa c Warner b Karn Sharma 30(27) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Karn Sharma to Uthappa, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to M Pandey, 1 run, waits for the ball to spin away and pulls it on the bounce to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to M Pandey, no run, on the leg stump, pushed back to the bowler, Karn Sharma dives to his right and deflects it towards mid-on, Uthappa looks for a run, but Pandey sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Uthappa, 1 run, backs away and slices the drive through cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to M Pandey, 1 run, tossed up outside off stump, Pandey drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Uthappa, 1 run, advances and drives, Karn Sharma gets a hand on it, but it doesn't go back onto the stumps, had it hit the stumps, Pandey would have been out as he was outside the crease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to Uthappa, 1 run, tossed up and on the stumps, Uthappa goes down on his knees, rolls his wrists and sweeps it past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to M Pandey, 1 run, leading edge and safe! Manish was early on the flick, the ball stopped on him and he ends up getting a thick leading edge wide of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to Uthappa, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, Uthappa makes room and cracks it square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to Uthappa, no run, pushed through by Bipul, Uthappa backs away and cuts it straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to Uthappa, no run, the skidder from Bipul, went through with the arm, Uthappa made room for the cut and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to M Pandey, 1 run, Manish comes down the track, doesn't get to the pitch and ends up dragging it towards long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to M Pandey, 1 run, Karn tosses one on the stumps, Manish shuffles across and works it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Uthappa, 1 run, floated on the middle stump line, worked behind square on the on-side for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to M Pandey, 1 run, Karn Sharma drops one short and gets it to spin away, nudged in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to M Pandey, 2 runs, this one is given more air, Pandey gets a big stride forward and shovels it over wide mid-wicket. Steyn gets across and pushes the ball back in, saves a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to M Pandey, no run, Karn drifts one just outside off, pushed straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to M Pandey, no run, pushed through and just outside off, slapped straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to Uthappa, no run, pushed through flatter and on Uthappa's pads, he was shaping for the lap sweep, gets a bottom edge that rolled off the pads and towards the on-side. He wants a single and is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to M Pandey, 1 run, this one is given more air, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to M Pandey, no run, Bipul Sharma slows down the pace, Manish lunges forward and defends it back at the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to M Pandey, <b>SIX</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, Manish shimmies down the track, gets to the pitch and goes high and over long-on, that went back a fair way, not a bad way to start your innings]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to M Pandey, no run, flighted and just outside off, defended towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bipul Sharma to Uthappa, 1 run, tossed up slower and wider outside off, eased square on the off-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Bipul Sharma, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to M Pandey, no run, slower and just outside off, Manish prods half forward and blocks, a successful over from Karn]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to M Pandey, no run, this one is given more air, Manish lunges forward and drives it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Uthappa, 1 run, the leg-break from Karn, Uthappa goes back and works it to the right of point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Uthappa, 2 runs, tossed up and on Uthappa's pads, nudged away in front of square on the on-side, takes on the fielder and gets back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Manish Pandey, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Gambhir, <b>out</b> Caught by Eoin Morgan!! Rush of blood has cost Gambhir. This was tossed up invitingly by Karn, Gambhir went down on his knees as he looked to clear the boundary, gets underneath the ball, gets the elevation but not the distance. Morgan was placed perfectly at deep mid-wicket, he doesn't drop those. <b>Gambhir c Eoin Morgan b Karn Sharma 31(23) [4s-5]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Karn Sharma to Gambhir, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Karn Sharma to Gambhir, 2 runs, Gambhir shimmies down the track to a well flighted delivery and whips it with the spin, gets it wide of mid-wicket for a couple of runs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Karn Sharma, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>strategic break</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Uthappa, no run, width on offer from Henriques, Uthappa leans into the steer, hits it straight to the fielder at extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Gambhir, 1 run, short of a length and on the stumps, pulled awy behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Gambhir, leg byes, <b>FOUR</b>, this is poor bowling from Henriques, slips this one on Gambhir's pads as he gave the charge, he looks to flick and misses, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, too full and well outside off, Gambhir gets a big stride forward and drills it back past the bowler, he stands and admires the shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Gambhir, no run, the slower off-cutter from Henriques, rolled his fingers around it, Gambhir looks to cut and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Henriques to Uthappa, 1 run, leg-stump half-volley from Henriques, Uthappa shuffles across a long way and flicks it behind square on the on-side, it was the attempted slower ball from Henriques]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Moises Henriques, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Gambhir, no run, much better from Steyn, tighter line on off, defended with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, fraction too full from Steyn, ends up as a half-volley outside off, laced through extra cover for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Gambhir, no run, short of a length and well outside off, Gambhir cracks it straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Gambhir, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Gambhir closed the face of the bat slightly, gets a soft leading edge towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Steyn, fine leg was inside the ring and Steyn drifts this one on Gambhir's pads, flicked away behind square on the on-side for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Uthappa, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, driven towards mid-off for a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dale Steyn [1.0-0-9-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Uthappa, 1 run, Praveen has been too straight this over, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Gambhir, 1 run, Praveen drifts one onto Gambhir's pads, clipped away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Uthappa, leg byes, 1 run, shout for LBW, but Uthappa had got himself outside off and was struck high on the pads as well, the length was a fraction fuller and hit Uthappa high on the pads as he looked to flick and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Uthappa, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Uthappa prods across and pushes it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, that's almost an action replay, too straight from Praveen, Uthappa shuffles across, picks up the length and flicks it behind square on the on-side for another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;P Kumar to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, Uthappa is looking in lovely touch, fraction too full and just outside off, Uthappa shuffles across and flicks it behind square, beats the man in the ring and races away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Praveen Kumar, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Uthappa, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, punched to the left of cover-point for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Uthappa, no run, Bhuvneshwar shortens his length outside off, pushed back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Gambhir, 1 run, tad fuller and just outside off, worked to the left of mid-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, that's easy pickings for Gambhir, length ball and on his pads, clipped away behind square on the on-side for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Gambhir, no run, Bhuvneshwar shortens the length as Gambhir gave the charge, dabbed towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Gambhir, <b>FOUR</b>, too straight from Bhuvneshwar, no swing on it either, Gambhir prods across and clips it past square leg, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Uthappa, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, overpitched and well outside off, Uthappa leans forward, presents the full face of the bat and caresses it past extra cover for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Gambhir, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Gambhir plays with a closed face and gets it past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Gambhir, 2 runs, too straight from Steyn, Gambhir closes the face of the bat and works it past mid-wicket, the fielder gives chase and keeps them down to a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Gambhir, no run, loud shout for a <b>caught behind</b>, but Erasmus says NO. Replays suggest that the umpire was right, this one seamed away after pitching around the leg-stump line, squared Gambhir up and deviates past the bat. The keeper was confident, so was the bowler, but the umpire got it spot on]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Gambhir, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, driven towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Steyn to Gambhir, 2 runs, on a good length and just outside off, Gambhir plays with an open face and guides it behind square on the off-side, runs hard and gets back for the second run. The keeper throws the stumps down, the third umpire is called for, but Gambhir was well in]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dale Steyn, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Gambhir, 1 run, too straight from Bhuvneshwar, drifts onto Gambhir's pads, clipped away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Gambhir, no run, lovely delivery from Bhuvneshwar, on a good length and shaping away from outside off, draws Gambhir into a lame poke and beats his outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Uthappa, 5 runs, bonus runs for KOL, on a good length and just outside off, Uthappa leans forward and drives it towards mid-off, sets off for a quick single. The fielder shies at the bowler's end and misses, the back-up is poor and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Uthappa, no run, Gambhir would have been struggling had there been a direct hit, on a good length and nipping back into Uthappa, he tucked in front of mid-wicket. Gambhir was backing up a long way, Steyn flicks at the bowler's end and misses, a direct hit might have had him short]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Uthappa, no run, Bhuvneshwar shapes this one from well outside off, Uthappa plays away from his body and nearly edges it to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Uthappa, no run, on a good length and shaping away from outside off, Uthappa covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Uthappa and Gambhir are at the crease. Uthappa is on strike. Bhuvneshwar will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players are in the middle. We had a short turnaround after the first match went overtime..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Gambhir</b>: "We would have batted. We wanted to put runs on the board. We are playing three spinners and we know it is going to grip later."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Warner</b>: "We are going to bowl first. We've got two changes. Bipul Sharma is in for Ashish Reddy, who has a sore shoulder. Dale Steyn is in for Trent Boult."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kolkata</b> (Playing XI): Gautam Gambhir(c), Robin Uthappa(w), Manish Pandey, Ryan ten Doeschate, Yusuf Pathan, Suryakumar Yadav, Andre Russell, Piyush Chawla, Johan Botha, Brad Hogg, Umesh Yadav]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hyderabad</b> (Playing XI): Shikhar Dhawan, David Warner(c), Moises Henriques, Naman Ojha(w), Eoin Morgan, Hanuma Vihari, Bipul Sharma, Karn Sharma, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Dale Steyn, Praveen Kumar]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hyderabad have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Stay tuned! We will bring you the captain views and team news in a little while as the toss is not too far away.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Head-to-head:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[In 5 previous encounters, KOL have won 3 games, while HYD have sealed 2 wins.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Weather update:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Weather hasn't been that promising in the cultural capital of India with majority of the day being affected with thunderstorm. However, things are predicted to be promising during the scheduled course of play with temperature hovering around 30 degree Celsius. Let's hope that the rain doesn't have a say in this game.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Team news:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[HYD brought in Eoin Morgan for Ravi Bopara in their last game citing 2 left-arm spinners in the opposition. Morgan played a responsible knock and remained unbeaten. He would most likely clinch his spot in the playing XI. They might be tempted to bring in Parvez Rasool in place of Karn Sharma. It won't come as a surprise if they stick to the same XI.]]></line><line><![CDATA[KOL might consider bringing in Morne Morkel in place of Pat Cummins. Rest of the unit looks settled and any other changes are unlikely to happen.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Both teams will bank on their senior players to make a game-changing impact as a win from this game will enhance the chances of making it to the playoffs. Both teams are led by aggressive left-handed openers and are among the top four in most fifties scored in the IPL. Who will have the last laugh? We'll find out soon...]]></line><line><![CDATA[KOL rather had a mixed season with 4 wins and as many losses with one being a no result. Uthappa and Gambhir made decent contributions with Russell chipping in with a few handy knocks, if and when needed. They still seem a little unsettled with their bowling combination as Pat Cummins managed only one wicket in 3 games. Brad Hogg justified his selection and will yet again play a key role at the spin friendly conditions at the Eden Gardens.]]></line><line><![CDATA[HYD skipper, David Warner has been in belligerent form and ensured that he took his side home more often than not. HYD have won four games and Warner has scored 50 on all four occasions. Naman Ojha and Ashish Reddy looked good in patches. HYD, however, will rely on their opening duo to do most of the scoring yet again. Bowling has been top class with Trent Boult, Praveen Kumar and Bhuvneshwar Kumar bowling in the right areas at the death.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>19:00 Local Time, 13:30 GMT, 19:00 IST:</b> After a rain-marred last over defeat at the Chinnaswamy, the defending champions are all set to take on the resurgent HYD at the Eden Gardens. Hello and a very warm welcome to our coverage of the 38th game of the Indian Premier League. Three of the five KOL games have been rain affected and they are desperately hoping for the rain to stay away for their clash against HYD. On the other hand, HYD are searing with confidence after achieving two comprehensive victories against PUN and CHN.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/>The last time Kolkata and Hyderabad locked horns in IPL 2015, it was David Warner's 91 that proved to be the difference between the two sides. On Monday, both teams will land in Kolkata having played their respective matches on Saturday. While Kolkata lost to Bangalore in a last-over finish, Hyderabad trumped table-toppers Chennai. In the previous five games between the two sides, KOL have defeated Hyderabad thrice, and the advantage of playing at home will certainly work in their favour. But after what transpired in Visakhapatnam on Saturday, all that will have little impact.<br/><br/>Having now posted three wins in their last four games, Hyderabad have jumped to fifth in the points table, right below Gautam Gambhir's team which has a superior net run-rate. The main reason behind their resurgence has been the form of Warner. The skipper has led from the front with five half-centuries in eight matches, four of which have come in wins. On Saturday, he cracked a superlative 28-ball 61 against Chennai that allowed his team to notch up their highest IPL total this season - 192. Shikhar Dhawan has also done remarkably well at the top, and Trent Boult, along with Praveen Kumar, has headed the bowling department well.<br/><br/>Kolkata, on the other hand, have hit a small slump of late. They did well to topple Chennai, but then lost ground in Bangalore. With just five more matches left to play, Kolkata will need to get their act together in order to make it to the play-off. Their top order has raised a few concerns. Robin Uthappa's unbeaten 80 against Chennai is his only 50-plus score this season and he needs to carry it forward and give support to his skipper. The bowling looks slightly better but Gambhir needs to fix his four-foreigner dilemma soon. He's shuffled them far too often - barring Andre Russell - and this has prevented them from putting their best foot forward. <br/><br/>On current form, Hyderabad go into the match as favourites but they can't afford to take the defending champions lightly.<br/><br/><b>Venue:</b> Eden Gardens, Kolkata<br/><br/><b>Date & Time:</b> May 4, 2000 IST<br/><br/><b>Weather:</b> Clear sky, with temperature touching 28 degree Celsius<br/><br/><b>Team News:</b> <br/><br/><b>Kolkata</b><br/><br/>Their biggest threat is Warner. Getting him out early will win them half the battle, and for that Morne Morkel will need to make his way back in the team. The tall South African has dismissed Warner six times in international cricket and twice in the IPL. He is an ideal replacement for Pat Cummins, who hasn't quite grabbed the brass ring, picking up just one wicket in the three games he's played so far.<br/><br/>Probable XI: 1 Gautam Gambhir (capt), 2 Robin Uthappa (wk), 3 Suryakumar Yadav, 4 Manish Pandey, 5 Andre Russell, 6 Ryan ten Doeschate, 7 Yusuf Pathan, 8 Piyush Chawla, 9 Morne Morkel, 10 Brad Hogg, 11 Umesh Yadav<br/><br/><b>Hyderabad</b><br/><br/>Hyderabad's spin stock has found itself difficult to get going. Karn Sharma has four wickets in eight matches and the Eden Gardens pitch has always offered some purchase for the spinners. Perhaps the legspinner can be benched for Parvez Rasool, who can also chip in with the bat.<br/><br/>Probable XI: 1 David Warner (capt), 2 Shikhar Dhawan, 3 Moises Henriques, 4 Eoin Morgan, 5 Naman Ojha (wk), 6 Ashish Reddy, 7 Hanuma Vihari, 8 Karn Sharma/Parvez Rasool, 9 Bhuvneshwar Kumar, 10 Praveen Kumar, 11 Trent Boult/Dale Steyn<br/><br/><b>Stats:</b><br/><br/>Warner has the highest number of half-centuries in the IPL - 21, while his KOL counterpart Gambhir needs 70 runs to reach 2,000 runs.<br/><br/><b>Quotes:</b><br/><br/>It's been travel-play, travel-play and travel-play for us. The competition is condensed, but that's how it is for everyone. We had a quiet week in the middle, after the second game, I think. So it just happens that the busy period is now. In terms of fitness and being ready, everyone has been prepared, that's not been an issue: Kolkata allrounder Ryan ten Doeschate on the hectic IPL schedule.<br/><br/>We certainly hope that that is going to turn around. We need to complement the confidence both David (Warner) and Shikhar (Dhawan) give: Hyderabad coach Tom Moody expects more contribution from the middle order.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hyderabad</b> (From): Shikhar Dhawan, David Warner(c), Hanuma Vihari, Moises Henriques, Naman Ojha(w), Eoin Morgan, Ashish Reddy, Karn Sharma, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Praveen Kumar, Trent Boult, Dale Steyn, Ishant Sharma, Lokesh Rahul, Parvez Rasool, Ricky Bhui, Chama Milind, Kane Williamson, Ravi Bopara, Bipul Sharma, Prasanth Padmanabhan, Siddarth Kaul]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kolkata</b> (From): Gautam Gambhir(c), Robin Uthappa(w), Manish Pandey, Suryakumar Yadav, Andre Russell, Ryan ten Doeschate, Yusuf Pathan, Piyush Chawla, Pat Cummins, Umesh Yadav, Brad Hogg, Sumit Narwal, Sheldon Jackson, Aditya Garhwal, Kishan Cariappa, Vaibhav Rawal, Johan Botha, Azhar Mahmood, Kuldeep Yadav, Veer Pratap Singh, Morne Morkel, Sunil Narine]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>167</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>7</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Kolkata">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>527</playerid>
					<name>Robin Uthappa</name>
					<batsman-name>Uthappa</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Uthappa</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>30</runs>
					<balls>27</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Karn Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1844</bowlerId>
						<fielder>David Warner</fielder>
						<fielderId>1739</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>308</playerid>
					<name>Gautam Gambhir</name>
					<batsman-name>Gambhir</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Gambhir</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>31</runs>
					<balls>23</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Karn Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1844</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Eoin Morgan</fielder>
						<fielderId>624</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1836</playerid>
					<name>Manish Pandey</name>
					<batsman-name>M Pandey</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M Pandey</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>33</runs>
					<balls>26</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Bipul Sharma</fielder>
						<fielderId>6296</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Naman Ojha</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>1599</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7736</playerid>
					<name>Andre Russell</name>
					<batsman-name>A Russell</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>A Russell</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Bipul Sharma</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6296</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Eoin Morgan</fielder>
						<fielderId>624</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>640</playerid>
					<name>Ryan ten Doeschate</name>
					<batsman-name>ten Doeschate</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>ten Doeschate</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>8</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Henriques</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1437</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>790</playerid>
					<name>Yusuf Pathan</name>
					<batsman-name>Y Pathan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Y Pathan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>30</runs>
					<balls>19</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>487</playerid>
					<name>Johan Botha</name>
					<batsman-name>J Botha</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>J Botha</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>12</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Bhuvneshwar</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1726</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7915</playerid>
					<name>Suryakumar Yadav</name>
					<batsman-name>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Bhuvneshwar</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1726</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Moises Henriques</fielder>
						<fielderId>1437</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>466</playerid>
					<name>Piyush Chawla</name>
					<batsman-name>Chawla</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chawla</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>140</playerid>
					<name>Brad Hogg</name>
					<batsman-name>B Hogg</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>B Hogg</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1858</playerid>
					<name>Umesh Yadav</name>
					<batsman-name>Umesh</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>U Yadav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>308</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>57</runs>
				<overs>6.2</overs>
				<batsman>Gautam Gambhir</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Gambhir</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>527</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>81</runs>
				<overs>10.6</overs>
				<batsman>Robin Uthappa</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Uthappa</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7736</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>86</runs>
				<overs>11.6</overs>
				<batsman>Andre Russell</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Russell</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1836</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>105</runs>
				<overs>13.5</overs>
				<batsman>Manish Pandey</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Pandey</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>640</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>111</runs>
				<overs>14.6</overs>
				<batsman>Ryan ten Doeschate</batsman>
				<batsman-name>ten Doeschate</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>487</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>139</runs>
				<overs>17.3</overs>
				<batsman>Johan Botha</batsman>
				<batsman-name>J Botha</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7915</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>145</runs>
				<overs>17.6</overs>
				<batsman>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Suryakumar Yadav</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>1</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>6</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Hyderabad">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1726</playerid>
					<name>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</name>
					<bowler-name>Bhuvneshwar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bhuvneshwar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>42</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>508</playerid>
					<name>Dale Steyn</name>
					<bowler-name>Steyn</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Steyn</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>37</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>592</playerid>
					<name>Praveen Kumar</name>
					<bowler-name>P Kumar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>P Kumar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>10</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1437</playerid>
					<name>Moises Henriques</name>
					<bowler-name>Henriques</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Henriques</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>20</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1844</playerid>
					<name>Karn Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Karn Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Karn Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>29</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6296</playerid>
					<name>Bipul Sharma</name>
					<bowler-name>Bipul Sharma</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bipul Sharma</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>23</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1446</playerid>
					<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhawan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhawan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1739</playerid>
					<name>David Warner</name>
					<bowler-name>Warner</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Warner</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1599</playerid>
					<name>Naman Ojha</name>
					<bowler-name>N Ojha</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>N Ojha</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>624</playerid>
					<name>Eoin Morgan</name>
					<bowler-name>E Morgan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Eoin Morgan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8424</playerid>
					<name>Hanuma Vihari</name>
					<bowler-name>Vihari</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Vihari</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>132</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>9</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Hyderabad">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1739</playerid>
					<name>David Warner</name>
					<batsman-name>Warner</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Warner</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Umesh</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1858</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1446</playerid>
					<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhawan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhawan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>15</runs>
					<balls>15</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>B Hogg</bowler>
					<bowlerId>140</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Manish Pandey</fielder>
						<fielderId>1836</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1599</playerid>
					<name>Naman Ojha</name>
					<batsman-name>N Ojha</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>N Ojha</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Umesh</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1858</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1437</playerid>
					<name>Moises Henriques</name>
					<batsman-name>Henriques</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Henriques</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>41</runs>
					<balls>33</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>B Hogg</bowler>
					<bowlerId>140</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Manish Pandey</fielder>
						<fielderId>1836</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>624</playerid>
					<name>Eoin Morgan</name>
					<batsman-name>E Morgan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Eoin Morgan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>5</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Gautam Gambhir</fielder>
						<fielderId>308</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Ryan ten Doeschate</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>640</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8424</playerid>
					<name>Hanuma Vihari</name>
					<batsman-name>Vihari</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Vihari</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[stumped]]></status>
					<bowler>Chawla</bowler>
					<bowlerId>466</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Robin Uthappa</fielder>
						<fielderId>527</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6296</playerid>
					<name>Bipul Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Bipul Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bipul Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Umesh Yadav</fielder>
						<fielderId>1858</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Robin Uthappa</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>527</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1844</playerid>
					<name>Karn Sharma</name>
					<batsman-name>Karn Sharma</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Karn Sharma</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>32</runs>
					<balls>20</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>J Botha</bowler>
					<bowlerId>487</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Suryakumar Yadav</fielder>
						<fielderId>7915</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>592</playerid>
					<name>Praveen Kumar</name>
					<batsman-name>P Kumar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>P Kumar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>12</runs>
					<balls>16</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>A Russell</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7736</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Umesh Yadav</fielder>
						<fielderId>1858</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1726</playerid>
					<name>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</name>
					<batsman-name>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>11</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>508</playerid>
					<name>Dale Steyn</name>
					<batsman-name>Steyn</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Steyn</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1739</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>5</runs>
				<overs>0.3</overs>
				<batsman>David Warner</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Warner</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1599</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>6</runs>
				<overs>0.6</overs>
				<batsman>Naman Ojha</batsman>
				<batsman-name>N Ojha</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1446</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>29</runs>
				<overs>4.5</overs>
				<batsman>Shikhar Dhawan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dhawan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>624</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>55</runs>
				<overs>8.1</overs>
				<batsman>Eoin Morgan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>E Morgan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8424</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>68</runs>
				<overs>11.4</overs>
				<batsman>Hanuma Vihari</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Vihari</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6296</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>69</runs>
				<overs>12</overs>
				<batsman>Bipul Sharma</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Bipul Sharma</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1437</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>81</runs>
				<overs>14.1</overs>
				<batsman>Moises Henriques</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Henriques</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1844</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>117</runs>
				<overs>17.5</overs>
				<batsman>Karn Sharma</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Karn Sharma</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>592</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>131</runs>
				<overs>19.4</overs>
				<batsman>Praveen Kumar</batsman>
				<batsman-name>P Kumar</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>4</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>4</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Kolkata">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1858</playerid>
					<name>Umesh Yadav</name>
					<bowler-name>Umesh</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>U Yadav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>34</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7736</playerid>
					<name>Andre Russell</name>
					<bowler-name>A Russell</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>A Russell</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>10</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>487</playerid>
					<name>Johan Botha</name>
					<bowler-name>J Botha</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>J Botha</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>32</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>140</playerid>
					<name>Brad Hogg</name>
					<bowler-name>B Hogg</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>B Hogg</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>17</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>790</playerid>
					<name>Yusuf Pathan</name>
					<bowler-name>Y Pathan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Y Pathan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>19</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>466</playerid>
					<name>Piyush Chawla</name>
					<bowler-name>Chawla</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chawla</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>16</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>640</playerid>
					<name>Ryan ten Doeschate</name>
					<bowler-name>ten Doeschate</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>ten Doeschate</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>4</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>308</playerid>
					<name>Gautam Gambhir</name>
					<bowler-name>Gambhir</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Gambhir</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>527</playerid>
					<name>Robin Uthappa</name>
					<bowler-name>Uthappa</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Uthappa</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1836</playerid>
					<name>Manish Pandey</name>
					<bowler-name>M Pandey</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M Pandey</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7915</playerid>
					<name>Suryakumar Yadav</name>
					<bowler-name>Suryakumar Yadav</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Suryakumar Yadav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



