<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="13745" >
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>1st ODI</gameDesc>
		<series>New Zealand tour of England, 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>England</home>
		<away>New Zealand</away>
		<teamsabbr>ENG vs NZ</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>ENG</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>NZ</awayabbr>
		<homeId>9</homeId>
		<awayId>13</awayId>
		<venue>Edgbaston, Birmingham</venue>
		<startdate>09 06 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>09 06 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>New Zealand</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>England won by 210 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>England</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>210</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Michael Gough</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Bruce Oxenford</Name>
			<Country>Aus</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Steve Davis</Name>
			<Country>Aus</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Javagal Srinath</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>13:00</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150609194246</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>NZ</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>Eng</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>198</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>10</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>31.1</batteamovers>
		<status>England won by 210 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>8117</playerid>
			<name>Trent Boult</name>
			<batsman-name>T Boult</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Boult</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>0</runs>
			<balls-faced>0</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
			<batsman>
				<name />
				<runs />
				<balls-faced />
				<fours />
				<sixes />
			</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>6532</playerid>
			<name>Chris Jordan*</name>
			<bowler-name>C Jordan</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Jordan</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>5.1</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>33</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>6317</playerid>
			<name>Steven Finn</name>
			<bowler-name>Finn</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Finn</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>7</overs>
			<maidens>1</maidens>
			<runs>35</runs>
			<wickets>4</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>409</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>7624</playerid>
<name>Mitchell McClenaghan</name>
<player-runs>2</player-runs>
<player-balls>2</player-balls>
<runs>198</runs>
<wicket-nbr>10</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>6532</bowlerid>
<bowlername>C Jordan</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>8</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>10</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>18</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[L4 Wd W . . . . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. 4 . 1 W 2 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. . . . Wd . W <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>W ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_ENG_NZ/ENG_NZ_JUN09/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[So England have gained early momentum in the 5-match series. The two sides will meet again for the second ODI at The Oval on Friday. Can England play a similar brand of cricket and do well? Or, will New Zealand bounce back in style? Brendon McCullum has said that fans can expect some exciting cricket from both sides for the rest of the series. Let's hope that we have a cracking game in a couple of days time. Until then, take care, goodbye!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Buttler</b>: "With 400 on the board, we could be really attacking as they were under immense pressure. A really pleasing win. At 200/6 Brendon (McCullum) used up a lot of his frontline bowlers looking for the wickets of myself and Adil (Rashid) to try and bowl us out. I think we managed to get through that period which allowed us, in the last 10 overs, to really cash in. Adil bowled very well today. He spun the ball both ways and bowled with great control as well."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jos Buttler</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Morgan</b>: "The guys were outstanding for us today. To come and hit the straps like that at the start of the series is outstanding, considering the group we have inside and what we asked them two days ago, we've certainly started well. The youngsters handled themselves very well. I know how tough it is for a young guy to play international cricket. Joe Root was outstanding, followed by an unbelievable innings from Jos Buttler. Adil (Rashid) can spin it both ways and he is a great asset to have in the side. I thought the guys were brilliant today. You can look back and say anything about the World Cup, but for me I am looking forward and I am really excited. Today, it encouraged me even more to look further down the line and give guys more of a chance to grow as cricketers. I think it is about 90-95 one-dayers before the next World Cup and the more games we can give our youngsters before then, the more experienced performances they can put in, it holds a lot of weight come the next World Cup. They (Billings and Roy) have been identified through a system, Sam Billings and Jason Roy are the calibre of athletes that we want in our one-day team and it's going to take them some time to settle."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>McCullum</b>: "The game changed pretty quickly. Joe Root and Jos Buttler were outstanding. I think it didn't swing much. They were outstanding with the bat and ball, it was a complete performance from England and we've got some work to do. You've got to accept when you get it wrong. The way the ball was holding up in the second innings showed that we got the toss wrong. We had to take wickets and to reduce them to 200 odd for 6 was good, but they played with no fear and put on a great partnership. We need to get a bit more accurate with the ball. We didn't expect that they would get 400. We created a couple of opportunities but then the game quickly slipped away from us. Tim (Southee) should be fine for the next one. The last time we played England, we were on the right side of things of a one-sided affair, today we are not. I think the crowds are going to witness some exciting cricket in the next few weeks."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ross Taylor and Grant Elliott shared a fifty partnership, but the latter was run-out attempting a needless second run to give England the advantage. Rashid then removed debutant Mitchell Santner and Luke Ronchi off successive balls to put his side on top and soon New Zealand lost their way and lost the game by a massive margin of 210 runs. In fact, they lost their last 6 wickets for 13 runs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chasing 409, the visitors did not get off to the best of starts as they lost skipper Brendon McCullum in the very first over of the innings. When McCullum hit back-to-back fours off Steve Finn, it looked like he was continuing from where he left at the Cake Tin - McCullum thrashed Finn to all corners in that World Cup game - but the tall bowler bounced back in style by knocking McCullum's off pole out off the very next ball. Martin Guptill and Kane Williamson attacked for a while, but the former threw his wicket away. Williamson looked good, but perished while trying to up the ante.]]></line><line><![CDATA[What a game for this team, which has been termed as "New England." After a disastrous 2015 World Cup, the pressure was on England to prove their mettle in ODIs and the new look team has registered a massive win against New Zealand, who thrashed them in the multi-nation event a few months ago.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The England team is extremely happy and why not. The hosts form a huddle as they congratulate each other. The dressing room is absolutely ecstatic as well. The New Zealand players come out and shake hands with the home side. Meanwhile, a section of the crowd is seen dancing as they celebrate this huge win.]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to McClenaghan, <b>out</b> Caught by Hales!! In the airrrrr and that's straight to the man in the deep. <b>This is the largest victory in terms of runs for England in ODIs</b>. Good length delivery on the leg stump, McClenaghan flicks, doesn't bother to keep it down and deep mid-wicket didn't have to move an inch. Hales has his hands aloft after taking the catch as the crowd celebrate in the background. <b>McClenaghan c Hales b Jordan 2(2)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Jordan to McClenaghan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Jordan [5.0-0-33-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Trent Boult, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Nathan McCullum, <b>out</b> Caught by Jordan!! Edged and that's gone straight into the hands of Jordan at second slip. In fact, the replay showed that he juggled but he held on to it. Nothing great about this delivery. A back of a length delivery outside off stump, McCullum pokes at it as he tries to push, gets a thick edge and it goes to second slip at a good height. <b>Nathan McCullum c Jordan b Finn 5(10) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Finn to Nathan McCullum, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Nathan McCullum, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, McCullum looks to punch off the back foot, gets an inside edge onto pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Nathan McCullum, <b>wide</b>, full and down the leg-side, easy call for the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time Southee runs out with three bats as McCullum needs a change of bat. The umpires call out for <b>drinks</b> in the meantime.]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Nathan McCullum, no run, short and slightly wide outside off, McCullum mistimes the cut to the right of point]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Nathan McCullum, no run, back of a length delivery on top of off, McCullum hops in the crease and blocks it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Nathan McCullum, no run, just short of a good length and on off stump line, McCullum hangs back and defends it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Nathan McCullum, no run, full just outside off, McCullum goes for the drive and misses it completely, the keeper collects]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place for Finn]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to McClenaghan, 2 runs, full toss from Rashid, McClenaghan works it wide of mid-on for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip, gully, leg slip and a FSL in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Matt Henry, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Rashid can do no wrong today, picks his fourth wicket of the night. It was the googly turning in on middle and leg, Henry fails to defend it into the on-side and the ball hits him low on the pad, there was a huge appeal and the umpire raised his finger after taking some time. The ball should have gone on to hit the leg stump. <b>Matt Henry lbw b Adil Rashid 0(5)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Adil Rashid to Matt Henry, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Nathan McCullum, 1 run, flighted delivery outside off, McCullum goes for a big slog, the ball bounces extra and takes the outside edge that flies to the right of backward point, Finn can't get there in time though]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Nathan McCullum, no run, flatter and spinning away just outside off, McCullum goes deep in the crease and nudges it into the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Nathan McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Rashid, bowls a full toss outside off, McCullum drives it to the left of mid-off, who dives but it goes in vain]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Nathan McCullum, no run, flighted delivery spinning away outside off, McCullum comes across and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[A slip, leg slip, FSL and a short extra cover in place. <b>Hat-trick ball coming up..</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Matt Henry, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Henry defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Matt Henry, no run, length delivery outside off, Henry looks to force it through the off-side and beats him on the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Matt Henry, no run, on a length and around off, Henry gets an inside edge onto the pad and the ball rolls away to his right]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Matt Henry, no run, short and wide outside off, Henry looks to play the upper-cut and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Matt Henry, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Ross Taylor, <b>out</b> Lbw!! This is a big blow, probably the end of the Kiwi hopes, if there were any left till now. Full and angling in on middle stump line, Taylor goes across and misses the clip, wears it on the pad and the umpire raised his finger after giving it a thought. Taylor reviewed it, but it was clipping the leg stump. <b>Ross Taylor lbw b Finn 57(54) [4s-5 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Finn to Ross Taylor, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Taylor has been <b>given out lbw</b>. He has decided to review it. The front foot is fine. 'There seems to be no bat involved. There is nothing on RTS. We have double checked that. Can we go to ball tracking please? It's pitching in line, hitting in line and it's umpire's call at the wickets as it is clipping leg stump,' says the third umpire. The original decision is upheld.]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Ross Taylor, <b>wide</b>, angling down the leg-side, the umpire calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Ross Taylor, leg byes, <b>FOUR</b>, angling in on middle and leg stump line, Taylor fails to clip it fine but the ball rolls away to the fine leg fence off the pad. There was a loud appeal for lbw from the bowler and the keeper, but it was going down leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Steven Finn [5.0-1-33-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Nathan McCullum, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ronchi, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Rashid is on a hat-trick. This was another googly outside off from Rashid, he gave this one more air as well. Ronchi kneels down and goes for a big slog first up, he misses it completely and the ball crashes into the off stump. <b>Ronchi b Adil Rashid 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Adil Rashid to Ronchi, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Luke Ronchi, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Mitchell Santner, <b>out</b> Caught by Jordan!! Rashid picks his second wicket of the match. These are also his career-best figures. This was the googly from Rashid that bounces extra, Santner rocks back to cut but can only manage an outside edge that flies to the left of Jordan at slip, he juggles it but managed to hold on. The ball was travelling there, but he did well to take it on the second attempt. <b>Mitchell Santner c Jordan b Adil Rashid 15(23) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Adil Rashid to Mitchell Santner, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Mitchell Santner, no run, advances and goes for another loft over mid-on, doesn't get under it properly and the ball goes on the bounce to the fielder at mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Mitchell Santner, <b>FOUR</b>, good strike for Santner, this was tossed up on the stumps, Santner comes down the track and lofts it straight down the ground for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Mitchell Santner, no run, flighted delivery turning in on leg, Santner looks to drive, gets an inside edge onto the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, 1 run, slower outside off, Taylor drops it into the off-side with gentle hands, gets a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, <b>wide</b>, down the leg-side, called a wide]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Ross Taylor, 1 run, short and slightly wide outside off, Taylor mistimes the cut to the left of cover, who gives chase and stops the ball. The batsmen take an easy single in the meantime]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Ross Taylor, 2 runs, full and angling in on the stumps, Taylor clips it to mid-wicket, where Jordan misfields and allows the batsmen to come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Mitchell Santner, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off, Santner opens the face of the bat and punches it to the right of backward point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Mitchell Santner, no run, angling away outside off and on a fuller length, Santner looks to drive but fails to connect, the ball goes through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Ross Taylor, 1 run, back of a length delivery on the stumps, Taylor hops and punches it in front of mid-wicket off the inside half of the bat, calls for a quick single and makes it easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Mitchell Santner, 1 run, back of a length delivery outside off, Santner guides it to third man after opening the face of the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Mitchell Santner, 1 run, goes across and turns this flighted delivery through square leg fror a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Mitchell Santner, <b>FOUR</b>, bowls this googly short and outside off, Santner hangs back and punches it wide of mid-off, the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Mitchell Santner, no run, once again charges down the track and is beaten in the flight. He looks to defend and misses it, wears it on the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Mitchell Santner, 2 runs, comes down the track and hoicks the googly over mid-wicket and mid-on, the batsmen take two before the fielder from deep mid-wicket stops it before the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Mitchell Santner, no run, bowls this well wide outside off, Santner reaches out and under-edges the cut towards slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Mitchell Santner, no run, googly from Rashid, Santner didn't pick it up, he looks to push at it off the back foot, the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Mitchell Santner, 1 run, just short of a good length and on middle and leg, Santner nudges it in front of mid-on and sets off, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Mitchell Santner, no run, low full toss on the stumps, Santner whips it straight to Morgan at mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Mitchell Santner, no run, short of length delivery on off stump line, Santner gets solidly behind it and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Mitchell Santner, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Santner hangs back and punches it to the right of cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[The magic spray is being applied, while the English players have a few drinks in the meantime]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Mitchell Santner, no run, yorker length ball on the stumps, Santner squeezes it out to mid-on, Morgan fires a needless throw at the non-striker's end and that catches Taylor on his left glove. He looks in some pain there, the physio walks out and is currently tending to him. Morgan apologised to Taylor after the whole incident]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Mitchell Santner, no run, that's a great ball at this stage. It was a length ball angled across off, Santner leans forward to defend and the ball goes past the outside edge. Was only inches away from the blade]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Ross Taylor, <b>2 wides</b>, down the leg-side, Santner fails to clip it fine and Buttler doesn't collect it cleanly and almost deflected it onto the helmet behind him, the batsmen take an extra run before Buttler hunts it down]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Mitchell Santner, no run, advances and was almost beaten in the flight there, could have been the googly. Santner just about manages to defend it into the off-side off the outside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Mitchell Santner, no run, flatter on the stumps, Santner gets behind the line and blocks it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, 1 run, slower one on the stumps, Taylor goes deep in the crease and guides it to point, calls for a quick single and gets it]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Mitchell Santner, 1 run, takes a step forward to this fullish delivery on the leg stump line, works it through mid-wicket to get off the mark in international cricket]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Mitchell Santner, no run, flatter outside off, Santner punches it to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and leg slip in place for Santner]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, 1 run, full toss from Rashid, Taylor drives it down to mid-on and sets off, the fielder fires a quick throw at the non-striker's end, but the batsman was in]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Santner, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Elliott, <b>out</b> Elliott Run Out!! 1 run completed. Elliott has to go, trying to take a needless second there. It was a length ball outside off, Elliott opens the face of the bat and guides it to the right of third man. He decides to come back for the second, but Billings was quick to reach the ball and fires a quick throw at the striker's end. Buttler does the rest and Elliott was well short of the crease. <b>Elliott run out (S Billings/Buttler) 24(27) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Stokes to Elliott, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire pressed into service to check a run-out decision. Elliott is the man in question. '<b>Happy with that, that is out</b>,' says the third umpire.]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Elliott, <b>wide</b>, bumper around off, Elliott drops his wrists and lets it pass. The umpire calls it a wide and it was a delayed signal from him, Stokes wasn't too happy with the call]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Elliott, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Elliott gets behind the line and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Ross Taylor, 1 run, Taylor brings up his <b>31st ODI fifty</b> with this single. It was full on the stumps, Taylor drives it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Ross Taylor, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a great shot by Taylor. He goes across to this full delivery angling in from outside off, he picks it up from there and paddles it past short fine leg for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Elliott, 1 run, goes across and turns this length ball through square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Elliott, <b>FOUR</b>, that's poor fielding from the English skipper. It was full and outside off, Elliott drives it off the front foot to mid-off, Morgan misfields and allows the ball to escape through to the fence. That effort wouldn't please the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, no run, advances and Rashid bowls a quicker one, Taylor pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, <b>FOUR</b>, comes down the track and hoicks it over mid-off, didn't time it too well, the fielder gives chase and tried to haul the ball back in before the rope, but his effort goes in vain]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, no run, shortish outside off, Taylor cuts it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Elliott, 1 run, comes down the track and takes this loopy delivery on the full, works it to the right of mid-on and calls for a quick single. The fielder fires a quick throw at the striker's end and Taylor has to rush back]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Elliott, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Elliott pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Elliott, 2 runs, kneels down and sweeps this delivery on middle and leg through mid-wicket, good running ensures that they come back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Ross Taylor, <b>FOUR</b>, good shot from Taylor to end the over. He clears his front leg, gets under this length ball and mows it over the long-on fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Ross Taylor, 2 runs, <b>in the air and safe!</b> This was banged in short, Taylor pulls it in the air over square leg, Hales runs forward from the boundary rope but the ball drops right in front of him, he did well to get a hand on it, the batsmen take a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Ross Taylor, no run, goes fuller this time, Taylor drives it to mid-on, can't get the single away]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Elliott, leg byes, 1 run, back of a length delivery on the pads, Elliott fails to connect with the tuck and sneaks in a leg bye as the ball rolls away to his left off the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Ross Taylor, 1 run, length delivery outside off, Taylor punches it to the left of short cover and sets off, the fielder quickly gets across, turns fast and fires a throw at the non-striker's end, Taylor had to charge to the other end and it could have been close had that been a direct-hit]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stokes to Ross Taylor, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Taylor waits and opens the face of the bat, guides it to the left of backward point, who dives and stops the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ben Stokes, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Elliott, no run, <b>that missed almost everything!</b> This was the googly from Rashid, Elliott was playing for the leg-break and misses it, the keeper can't collect it cleanly either. It wasn't that far away from the off stump and just went over it]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Elliott, 2 runs, floated up around off, Elliott goes for a lofted drive, he ends up slicing it and the ball goes in the air to the right of backward point, the batsmen come back for the second with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Elliott, no run, slower through the air this time, Elliott leans forward and blocks with soft hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Elliott, no run, works this fullish delivery on middle and leg to the left of mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Elliott, no run, <b>almost a return catch!</b> This was floated up on the stumps, Elliott comes down the track and drives it straight back at the bowler, but it bounces in front of him]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, 1 run, tossed up on leg and turning in on middle, Taylor drives it towards mid-on and sets off, gets to the other end with ease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Ross Taylor, 1 run, another one that's short and just outside off, Taylor transfers his weight on the back foot and pulls it through square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Ross Taylor, no run, banged in short and around off, Taylor pulls it to the right of mid-wicket, who dives to his right and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Ross Taylor, <b>SIX</b>, great shot from Taylor, it was full and outside off, Taylor reaches to the pitch of the ball and tonks it over the long-on fence for a six]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Ross Taylor, <b>FOUR</b>, ugly slog from Taylor but it fetches him a boundary. This was on a good length and outside off, Taylor slogs it wide of mid-on, the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Elliott, 1 run, angling in from outside off, Elliott nudges it through mid-wicket and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Elliott, <b>wide</b>, angles this one down leg, Elliott can't flick it fine and the umpire signals a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Ross Taylor, 1 run, drifting on the pads, Taylor works it to deep square leg for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Elliott, no run, fullish and quicker from Rashid, Elliott drives it to short cover, who fires in the throw towards Buttler and Elliott has to rush back in]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, 1 run, flatter outside off, Taylor guides it square of the wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, 2 runs, full toss on the stumps, Taylor whacks it through mid-wicket, comes back for the second with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, no run, flatter and outside off, Taylor defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, no run, pitches outside leg and this turns back, Taylor fails to connect with the sweep and wears it on the pad, there was an appeal but it pitched outside leg. Morgan asks his bowler where it pitched, Rashid tells him not to review as it pitched outside leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, no run, floated up on the stumps, Taylor pushes it to the right of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for a <b>drinks</b> break.]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Ross Taylor, 1 run, again, the length is short, Taylor chops the cut wide of point, it was too close to the body and hence he didn't get the timing right]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Elliott, 1 run, short of length on off, Elliott nurdles it behind square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Elliott, no run, sharp short delivery, Elliott takes his eyes off the ball, takes a blow on the shoulder. He doesn't show any sign of pain. In fact, gives a thumbs up to Rosco]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Ross Taylor, leg byes, 1 run, Taylor missed out there, full ball on the pads, he can't connect with the flick, wears it on the pad and it rolls wide of Buttler]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Ross Taylor, no run, shortens the length, Taylor cuts it late to backward point, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Ross Taylor, no run, fuller and on off, Taylor knocks it to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, 1 run, tossed up on off, Taylor leans forward and nudges it wide of mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Elliott, 1 run, Rashid gets away with one, full toss outside off, Elliott drives it towards cover, the fielder gets a hand and takes the pace off the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Elliott, 2 runs, googly outside off, Elliott stretches forward and drives, the ball takes the inside edge and goes past the leg slip fielder, Morgan gives chase and keeps it to a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Elliott, 2 runs, floated up outside off, Elliott drives it to deep extra cover for couple more]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Elliott, no run, flatter and on the stumps, Elliott goes back and whips it to mid-wicket, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and leg slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, 1 run, low full toss around off, Taylor goes down on his knee and paddles it to long leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Elliott, no run, this one seams back in from a length, Elliott doesn't cover his sticks completely as he lets go. In the end, it was a good leave]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Elliott, 2 runs, Elliott comes forward to the length delivery, drives it through extra cover and picks up a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Elliott, no run, on a length outside off, Elliott has a feel for it away from the body, pulls the bat in just at the last instant]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Elliott, <b>FOUR</b>, shortish and outside off, Elliott can't get on top of the bounce as he cuts, hits it in the air just wide of Root at gully, he hit hard and the ball raced away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Elliott, no run, good length ball around off, Elliott presses it to cover after coming forward]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Elliott, no run, back of a length on off, Elliott defends to the right of Plunkett]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Elliott, <b>wide</b>, splays it down leg, Elliott can't meet with the glance, wide given]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, 2 runs, the wrong 'un, Taylor didn't pick it at first, shuffles across and nurdles it off the inner part to long leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Grant Elliott, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Williamson, <b>out</b> Caught by J Root!! Big wicket for England. The in-form Williamson departs. Rashid picks his first of the innings. Floated up around off, Williamson charges down the wicket, doesn't get to the pitch and still goes through with the loft, mistimes it towards long-off, Root runs forward and takes it comfortably. <b>Williamson c J Root b Adil Rashid 45(43) [4s-8]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Adil Rashid to Williamson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Williamson, no run, tossed up on the stumps, Williamson turns it gently to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Williamson, no run, Rashid sees the batsman advance, pulls the length back, guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, 1 run, Taylor shimmies down the wicket, Rashid drags the length back, chips it to mid-on, he sets off for a run, there was a slight collision between Williamson and Rashid, the former was late to take off, but gets there in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Williamson, 1 run, flighted delivery on off, Williamson drives inside out towards cover, Morgan dives to his right and makes a half stop]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Ross Taylor, no run, fullish and on off, Taylor pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Williamson, 1 run, back of a length just outside off, Williamson steers it to third man with an angled bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Ross Taylor, 1 run, too full and outside off, Taylor squeezes the drive to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Ross Taylor, 2 runs, banged in halfway down the wicket, Taylor rocks back and pulls in front of square, easy two taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Ross Taylor, no run, good length around off, Taylor defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Williamson, 1 run, full on middle and leg, Williamson flicks it in the air wide of mid-wicket, the fielder in the deep tidies up, they wanted two but Taylor says no]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, no run, flighted delivery on off, Taylor drives it straight into Williamson, who couldn't get out of the way]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Williamson, 1 run, straighter one on the stumps, Williamson nudges it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, tossed up outside off, Williamson comes down the track, the ball turns away and he did well to reach out and loft it over mid-off, couple of bounces and into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, 1 run, floated up on leg-stump, Taylor toe-ends the paddle sweep to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Williamson, 1 run, fraction short and outside off, Williamson cuts to deep backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Adil Rashid to Ross Taylor, 1 run, flighted on off, Taylor eases it to the right of the bowler, Rashid dives and gets a hand to it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Adil Rashid, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, Williamson is so good when he is hitting down the ground. Not all that full, he goes for drive through the line, hits it in the air and to the right of mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[A wide slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Williamson, no run, shortens the length just outside off, Williamson mistimes the punch to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, much better. Pitched up on the stumps, Williamson presents the full face of the bat and lofts it past the non-striker, the timing on that takes it to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Williamson, no run, Plunkett is certainly getting some swing into the batsman, Williamson once more goes for it without any footwork, ekes out an inside edge onto the pad, the ball rolls to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Ross Taylor, 1 run, good length ball on off and middle, Taylor nurdles it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Plunkett to Ross Taylor, no run, full and tails into the batsman, Taylor wrists it to mid-on, slight confusion between the two batsmen, in the end they don't go for the run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Liam Plunkett, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Williamson, no run, fullish and outside off, Williamson goes for the booming drive, fails to connect as the ball beats the inside edge. That was loose from KW as he went for it without any footwork]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Williamson, no run, on a length close to off, Williamson pushes it off the inner part to silly mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Williamson, no run, back of a length on off, blocked down the wicket off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Williamson, 2 runs, too straight, on middle and leg, Williamson gets inside the line and flicks to deep mid-wicket for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Williamson, no run, back of a length just outside off, Williamson goes hard on the punch, mistimes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Williamson, no run, good length ball on off, Williamson defends solidly off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Ross Taylor, <b>FOUR</b>, Taylor survives another nervy moement. Short delivery just outside off, he goes for the pull and gets a top-edge, luckily for him he gets it fine and wide of the fielder in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Ross Taylor, no run, Finn probes away in and around off, Taylor pushes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Ross Taylor, no run, on a length close to off, Taylor comes half-forward and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Ross Taylor, no run, Finn has his hands on his head. Banged in halfway down the wicket, Taylor goes for the pull, toe-ends it wide of off-stump, Buttler dives to his left and collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Ross Taylor, no run, shortens the length around off, Taylor knocks it to cover off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Ross Taylor, no run, good length ball on off, Taylor bunts it in front of mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Ross Taylor, 1 run, full and on leg-stump, Taylor flicks it down to fine leg, keeps strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Williamson, 1 run, fullish and on off, Williamson drives off the inside half to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, Jordan errs in line, slips it on leg-stump, Williamson gets inside the line and glances it off the inner part of the bat, Buttler dives to his left but it was too far for him]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Williamson, no run, back of a length on off, Williamson stays back and knocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Williamson, no run, on a length close to off, Williamson blocks it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, pitched up outside off, Williamson drives it uppishly, just eludes the diving mid-off fielder. Some Englishmen shouted "catch", but it was wide of the Morgan, he dived full length to his left in vain]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Williamson, 1 run, on a length just outside off, dabbed away to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Williamson, no run, good length ball on off, Williamson gets right behind the line and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[Silly mid-on and silly mid-off in place for Williamson]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Ross Taylor, 1 run, back of a length on the stumps, Taylor shuffles across and tucks it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ross Taylor, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Guptill, <b>out</b> Caught by Buttler!! Guptill has thrown it away! He was looking good and goes playing a needless shot. Finn picks up his second wicket. This was just short of good length, Guptill moves away to the leg-side, wanted to go inside out, can only manage an outside edge which is gobbled up by Buttler. The partnership had started to flourish, but it has been broken. <b>Guptill c Buttler b Finn 22(18) [4s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Finn to Guptill, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Guptill, 2 runs, Guptill goes for the loft on the rise, he got it high on the bat, spoons it over the bowler's head, splits mid-on and mid-off to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Guptill, <b>FOUR</b>, short of length on off, Guptill backs away to the leg-side, he just went through with the shot, flays it through extra cover, the fast outfield does the rest]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, almost dragged on! Plenty of oohs and aahs. This one nips back in from a length, Williamson pushes at it away from the body, the inside edge misses the off-pole and beats Buttler's dive to his left]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Williamson, no run, good length ball close to off, Williamson dead-bats it in front of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, glorious shot! Williamson presses half-forward, presents the full face of the bat and drives through the line, beats Guptill and mid-on and collects four more]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Guptill, 1 run, just a hint of inward movement, Guptill goes hard on the drive, ekes out an inside edge onto the pad, the ball rolls to the off-side and Williamson calls for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Guptill, no run, good length ball on off, defended off the front foot towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Guptill, no run, on a length close to off, Guptill stays back and drops it in front of backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Williamson, no run, shortish and outside off, Williamson mistimes the cut to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Williamson, no run, on a length just outside off, Williamson dabs it in front of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, how well was that timed? Finn drifts one on middle and leg, Williamson flicks it through square leg, itwas just a mere nudge and the ball raced away from the chasing fielders]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Guptill, 1 run, back of a length around off, Guptill mistimes the pull wide of mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Guptill, <b>FOUR</b>, fabulous shot! It was not all that short, Guptill raises his front leg and plays the short-arm pull to the deep backward square leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Williamson, 1 run, full and on leg-stump, Williamson whips it down to fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Williamson, 3 runs, too straight, on off and middle, Williamson gets inside the line, leans forward and flicks it through mid-wicket, the duo picks up three comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Williamson, no run, this one nips back in sharply from short of length, Williamson is rooted to the crease, misses the clip and is struck on the back thigh. The ball rolls wide of slip, the fielder from second slip goes across, dives and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Williamson, no run, Jordan keeps it tight, on the off-stump, Williamson knocks it to mid-on after coming forward]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Guptill, 1 run, good length ball on off, Guptill presses forward and nurdles it off the inside half to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Williamson, leg byes, 3 runs, wrong line from Jordan, slides another one on the pads, Williamson shuffles across and tickles it fine, Finn runs to his right from fine leg, dives and saves a run for the team]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Guptill, leg byes, 1 run, shortish and on leg-stump, Guptill gets inside the line, misses the tuck and wears it on the thigh pad, the ball dribbles behind square]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Williamson, no run, <b>maiden</b> from Finn. Short and outside off, Williamson goes for the pull, he can't connect as the ball slips under the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Williamson, no run, back of a length around off, Williamson gets nicely behind it and defends down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Williamson, no run, fuller and close to off, Williamson goes hard on the drive, the bat face closes and he drags it to mid-on off the inner part of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Williamson, no run, Williamson missed out there, Finn drifts onto the pads, Williamson can't connect with the flick, wears it on the thigh pad, ball rolls towards square leg, Guptill wanted the run and was halfway down the wicket before being sent back. No harm done]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Williamson, no run, short of length on the fourth stump line, Williamson goes back and knocks it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Williamson, no run, Finn attacks the stumps with the length delivery, Williamson leans forward and turns it gently to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Guptill, no run, drags the length back close to off, Guptill looks to force it through the off-side, the inside edge thuds into the back pad. That would have so easily gone back onto the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Guptill, <b>FOUR</b>, superb shot! That stroke just shows how good a wicket this is. On a length just outside off, Guptill drives on-the-up and pierces the off-side field, places it between backward point and cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Guptill, no run, inside edge and safe! Guptill has no option but to play his shots. Goes for the drive on-the-up, the inside edge is found and it goes on the bounce to Buttler, who dives to his left to glove it]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Guptill, no run, Buttler and the slip cordon went up for an lbw appeal, but nothing from umpire Gough. It was just short of good length, Guptill shuffles across and misses the flick, is rapped on the pads but the ball was sliding down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Guptill, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! It was a bad ball but still had to be put away. Long half volley outside off, Guptill gets a good stride forward and creams it through extra cover, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jordan to Guptill, no run, back of a length, hint of away swing outside off, Guptill lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Jordan, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kane Williamson, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Brendon McCullum, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Cleaned up! Finn is delighted, goes on his knee and exults. It just shows how badly he needed that wicket. It was nothing but a straight delivery, McCullum shimmies down the pitch and goes for a mighty swing, he misses and the ball hits the top of off-stump. Just the start England would have hoped for. <b>Brendon McCullum b Finn 10(4) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Finn to Brendon McCullum, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, McCullum is off and running, short and plenty of width on offer, McCullum cuts it up and over the infield, clears the field and picks up his second boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, short and not much venom, McCullum was expecting it to bounce much more, he swivels and pulls it behind square leg for his first boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Brendon McCullum, 2 runs, McCullum gives the charge, goes for a heave across the line, the inside edge goes past leg-stump and runs down to fine leg, he wanted two and sprints across quickly to get it. A direct hit from Rashid, but Baz had made it in]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire called in for a run-out check. England think they have their man, Baz seems confident and why not. He has made it in comfortably. Steve Davis says he is happy to give that not out.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Finn vs McCullum. Remember the 2015 World Cup, where Finn was taken to the cleaners from Baz?]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Guptill, 1 run, quick single taken. Fuller and around off, Guptill push-drives it to mid-off, takes on Morgan and gets it easily in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Guptill, no run, first ball and it comes right off the middle, full and on the stumps, Guptill leans forward and flicks, unfortunately picks out the fielder at mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Guptill and Brendon McCullum are at the crease. Guptill is on strike. Finn will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Hello again. New Zealand have their task cut out. With the brand of cricket they are playing, we can expect them to come hard at this target. Guptill and Baz are out in the middle. England take the field after a small huddle. Finn has the new ball in his hand. He has couple of slips in place....]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Buttler</b>: "It was a great start for us. Right throughout the innings it was fantastic. It was how we wanted to play. It's a good wicket. It will be tough to defend and we'll have to bowl well as well. This knock boosts my confidence. It was really pleasing for us. Now we need to take wickets and win this game."]]></line><line><![CDATA[At that stage it looked like New Zealand will be able to contain the Englishmen for a below par total, but Rashid walked out and along with Buttler, both batsmen took the sails out of the Kiwi attack. Both of them played without any fear and kept finding the gaps, while the Black Caps bowlers kept banging it short. Both of them put on 177 for the 7th wicket, a record in ODIs, with Buttler cracking his second ODI ton off just 66 balls. He now owns the record for the fastest and the second fastest ODI hundred by an Englishman. Rashid too continued to play his shots, reaching his maiden ODI fifty in the process as well. Even though both Buttler and Rashid went trying to up the ante, two lusty blows from Plunkett saw England going past 400, their highest total in ODI history.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Root continued to play aggressively and soon reached his 5th ODI ton, that too off just 71 balls, making it the 3rd fastest ton by an Englishman at that time. Root though soon edged one off Boult and that opened the floodgates for New Zealand. After being 171/2 at one stage, England were stuttering at 202/6, when the debutant, Sam Billings was given out lbw on review.]]></line><line><![CDATA[England got off to the worst start possible, losing Jason Roy off the first ball of the innings. However, that didn't deter Hales and Root from playing their shots as both put on a 50-run stand before Hales top-edged a pull to Henry. Root though continued to play some brilliant shots and Morgan gave him good support from the other end. They put on 121 for the third wicket and their partnership was broken by McClenaghan, who trapped Morgan lbw after the English captain reached his fifty.]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Plunkett, 1 run, yorker from Elliott, Plunkett jams it out to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Plunkett, <b>SIX</b>, slower ball on the stumps and Plunkett had played the pick-up shot to perfection. He hoicks it over deep mid-wicket and it carries the distance]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Plunkett, <b>wide</b>, bowls this slower and well wide outside off, called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Plunkett, <b>SIX</b>, Plunkett starts off with a maximum. It was a full toss, Plunkett lofts it over the long-on fence for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Steven Finn, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Adil Rashid, <b>out</b> Caught by Guptill!! Rashid goes now, but he walks off to another standing ovation. This was the slower ball from Elliott, Rashid wanted to smack the pull out of the park, but picks out Guptill at deep mid-wicket. <b>Adil Rashid c Guptill b Elliott 69(50) [4s-7 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Elliott to Adil Rashid, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Liam Plunkett, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Jordan, <b>out</b> Caught by Boult!! Elliott gets his first wicket in the last over, but NZ are not celebrating. This was full and slightly wide outside off, Jordan goes for a big booming drive, but gets an outside edge. Short third man goes back and takes the catch. <b>Jordan c Boult b Elliott 2(4)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Elliott to Jordan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Adil Rashid, 1 run, full delivery outside off, Rashid drives it through the covers and gets to the other end]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Grant Elliott [4.0-0-42-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, 1 run, backs away and squeezes this full delivery towards point, racs to the other end and makes it easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, <b>FOUR</b>, this is <b>England's highest score in ODIs now</b>. Rashid gives the charge and Santner drops it short, Rashid flat-bats it through extra cover and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Jordan, 1 run, drives this fullish delivery to deep extra cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, 1 run, sweeps this through square leg and gets to the other end with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Jordan, 1 run, pushes this flighted delivery down to long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Jordan, no run, looks to work this through the on-side, fails to connect with it, the ball rolls away into the off-side off the boot. No appeal for lbw as it was outside leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Santner [7.0-0-56-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Adil Rashid, no run, yorker from McClenaghan, Rashid jams it out back to the bowler, can't get the single away]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Adil Rashid, <b>FOUR</b>, just short of a good length and outside off, Rashid slogs hard and gets it in the gap between deep mid-wicket and long-on, the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Adil Rashid, 2 runs, short ball from McClenaghan, Rashid pulls it behind square on the on-side after jumping it, comes back for the second with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Jordan, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, <b>out</b> Caught by Matt Henry!! Buttler departs after a sensational knock. He walks off the field after raising his bat to the standing ovation from the Edgbaston crowd. It was banged in short by Henry, Buttler rises with the bounce and goes for the pull, his bottom hand came off the bat and he ended up getting a top-edge. Henry from mid-wicket runs to his right, takes the catch and did well to hold on as he tumbled over. <b>Buttler c Matt Henry b McClenaghan 129(77) [4s-13 6s-5]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[McClenaghan to Buttler, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, <b>SIX</b>, that looked like he didn't time it too well, but it went the distance. It was full outside off, Buttler reaches out for it without any feet movement, slams it over the long-on fence for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Adil Rashid, 1 run, overpitching outside off, Rashid jams out the drive to mid-off and gets to the other end with a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [9.0-0-80-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Buttler, <b>FOUR</b>, great shot to end the over, this was full on the stumps, Buttler whips it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Buttler, 2 runs, slower ball on the stumps, Buttler goes early into the slog but managed to come back for the second as the ball rolls away through square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Buttler, <b>FOUR</b>, full outside off, Buttler drives it hard and gets it to the left of mid-off, who gives chase but the ball wins the race]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Adil Rashid, 1 run, slower ball from Elliott, Rashid goes for a big hit but toe-ends it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Buttler, 1 run, low full toss from Elliott, Buttler helps it to deep mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Buttler, <b>SIX</b>, <b>effortless six!</b> This was full outside off, Buttler leans forward and lofts it over long-off for a six. Mid-off was inside the circle and that's why it was a good shot from Buttler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Grant Elliott [3.0-0-24-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Adil Rashid, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>150 of the partnership</b> comes up with this four. Another short delivery from Henry, Rashid goes for the pull and gets a top-edge that goes over the keeper's head and runs away to the fence. This is now the <b>highest ODI total at this ground</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Adil Rashid, no run, short delivery outside off, Rashid looks to upper-cut it, but fails to make contact as he jumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Adil Rashid, no run, pulls this short ball once again, but this time he picks out mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Adil Rashid, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>maiden ODI fifty</b> for Rashid and he has played a superb knock. It was short again from Henry, Rashid rocks back and pulls it over mid-wicket for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Buttler, 1 run, bowls this full and around off, Buttler drills it towards mid-on, who dives to his right and makes a half-stop, saved some runs for his team there]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Buttler, no run, slower and fuller from Henry, Buttler drives it to mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, 1 run, just short of a good length and on the stumps, Buttler makes room and punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Adil Rashid, 1 run, works this through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Adil Rashid, 2 runs, <b>dropped!</b> It's Brendon McCullum, who has dropped this one. This was a short of length delivery outside off, Rashid wanted to flat-bat it over mid-off but doesn't get the desired distance, the fielder runs back to his left, tries to take it but the ball bursts through his hands, allowing the batsmen to come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, 1 run, slower ball from McClenaghan, Buttler gets an inside edge onto the thigh pad, the ball rolls away to square leg and the batsmen cross over]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, <b>FOUR</b>, Buttler had the <b>fastest hundred for England in ODIs, now he has the second fastest too</b>. He drives this full delivery past the diving short cover and mid-off too didn't have a chance of cutting that off, crashes into the fence in no time. He takes off his helmet, waves his bat to the crowd and soaks in the applause as his team-mates are up on their feet too, Morgan looks extremely pleased]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, <b>FOUR</b>, Buttler reaches 99 with this boundary. This is now the <b>highest 7th wicket partnership in ODIs</b>. This was full and angling down leg, Buttler scoops it to the left of the keeper and gets it fine, races away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [8.0-0-67-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[McClenaghan comes round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Adil Rashid, no run, good ball to end the over. It was bowled in the channel outside off, Rashid looks to guide this one down to third man but fails to connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Adil Rashid, 2 runs, good length delivery outside off, Rashid goes hard on the loft, doesn't connect too well but just gets it over short extra cover and to the left of mid-off. The batsmen take two before McCullum hunts it down]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Adil Rashid, no run, length ball outside off, Rashid drills hard but picks out mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Buttler, 1 run, Buttler rocks back and pulls this short delivery on the bounce to Taylor at deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Buttler, <b>wide</b>, bumper well wide outside off, it sails over Buttler's head as well as he leaves it alone. The umpire calls it a wide for height]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Buttler, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>dropped!</b> This was on a good length and outside off, Buttler heaves it over mid-wicket but didn't get the distance on it, Taylor runs forward from deep mid-wicket, but the ball bursts through his hands as he tried to put in the slide. To make matters worse, the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Buttler, <b>wide</b>, this time it's a wide. It was short and well wide outside off, Buttler leaves but the umpire signals it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Buttler, no run, that was close to a wide, but rightly not called so as it was just inside the tramline. Buttler leaves and the umpire deems it a legal ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Buttler, 1 run, bowls another flatter delivery, on the stumps this time. Buttler pulls it behind square on the leg-side and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Buttler, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from McCullum, he drops it short, Buttler goes deep in the crease and cuts it through extra cover, the ball crashes into the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Buttler, <b>FOUR</b>, third full toss in a row and Buttler dispatches it to the fence. He drives it to the left of short cover, who dives to his left but it goes in vain. The ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Buttler, no run, another full toss from McCullum, Buttler drives and picks out mid-off once again]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Buttler, no run, full toss from McCullum, Buttler backs away and drives it straight to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Adil Rashid, 1 run, on the pads, Rashid works it through backward square leg, Rashid was looking for the second there but slips in the process, decides against it at the end]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Buttler, no run, once again it is short wide outside off, Buttler cuts it straight to extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Buttler, no run, once again Henry bowls it wide outside off, Buttler goes for the cut but fails to connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Buttler, 2 runs, shortish once again and Buttler goes for the cut this time, he mistimes it through extra cover but he had enough time to come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Buttler, <b>SIX</b>, <b>handsome!</b> This was once again short from Henry, Buttler rocks back and pulls it magnificently over the deep mid-wicket fence for a maximum. That sounded very sweet as the ball made contact with the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Adil Rashid, 3 runs, short and on the stumps, Rashid pulls it through mid-wicket and mid-off, Nathan McCullum gives chase and pulls the ball back in time to save a run. McClenaghan then fired the ball at the non-striker's end and it looked as if it was a direct-hit, but it was Henry who had knocked the bails off without the ball in his hands. Rashid survives]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire called in to check a run-out appeal. Rashid is the man in question. The third umpire is first checking for the boundary, Nathan McCullum looks fine on that count. Did Henry disturb the bails there. 'Just run that through and keep the ball going. I am going to give that not out as I think his hands took the bails off,' says third umpire.]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Adil Rashid, no run, length delivery outside off, Rashid drives it to mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Buttler, 2 runs, <b>100 of the partnership comes up with that couple</b>. He tucks this through mid-wicket and good running ensures that they come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Buttler, <b>SIX</b>, tossed up outside off, Buttler reaches to the pitch of the ball and handsomely lofts it over the wide long-off fence for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Buttler, <b>wide</b>, quicker and down the leg-side, Buttler can't put it away and the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Buttler, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a super shot from Buttler, it was floated up, Buttler kneels down and reverse-sweeps it to the right of short third man, who could just see the ball run away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Buttler, no run, flighted delivery outside off, Buttler defends it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Adil Rashid, 1 run, <b>run-out chance missed!</b> This was pushed through on the stumps, Rashid works it to the right of mid-wicket, who dives and half-stops the ball. The batsmen were ball-watching and were stranded in the middle of the pitch. McCullum though couldn't collect it cleanly and the batsmen go through with the single easily in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Adil Rashid, no run, flatter and turning in on leg, Rashid wristily works it towards mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Nathan McCullum [5.0-0-42-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>56 runs</b> came off the batting powerplay.]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Adil Rashid, 1 run, shortish once again from Henry, Rashid pulls it behind square on the leg-side for another run]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Adil Rashid, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Rashid mistimes the punch into the off-side, his bottom hand came off as he made contact with the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Buttler, 1 run, cuts this widish delivery to sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Adil Rashid, 1 run, <b>in the air and safe!</b> This was another bumper outside off from Henry, probably it was over Rashid's head, he jumps up and drags the pull to the right of mid-on, it was in the air for sometime but was out of the reach of the fielder. Not called a no-ball by the umpire, he thought the height was fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Buttler, 1 run, shortish and slightly wide outside off, Buttler knocks it to sweeper cover and gets to the other end with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Just a slip in place for Henry]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Adil Rashid, 1 run, Henry bangs this one short and at the batsman, Rashid pulls it along the ground to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Matt Henry [6.0-0-39-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, no run, length delivery outside off, Buttler leans forward and drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, 2 runs, McClenaghan bowls this one slightly wide outside off, Buttler goes hard at it, ends up slicing it square of the wicket, the fielder in the deep misfields and that allows the batsmen to come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, <b>FOUR</b>, poor bowling from McClenaghan. Buttler was expecting it to be short, McClenaghan obliged and Buttler swivels on the pull, sends it through square leg and the ball races away]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, 2 runs, leans forward and drives this fullish delivery through extra cover, gets back for the second with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, <b>FOUR</b>, Buttler gets to his <b>8th ODI fifty</b> with this boundary. This was bowled short and wide outside off, Buttler stays back and cuts it late, gets it over backward point and the ball runs away]]></line><line><![CDATA[Fine leg is back on the rope now]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, no run, Buttler walks right across his stumps and wanted to scoop this over the keeper as fine leg was inside the circle, he misses the ball completely and wears it on the thigh pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, <b>FOUR</b>, Santner is being taken to the cleaners here. This was dropped short by him, Rashid had all the time in the world to rock back, he pulls it over mid-wicket and the ball hurries across the turf and crashes into the fence, <b>19 runs</b> came off the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, no run, quicker outside off, Rashid backs away slightly and guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, <b>SIX</b>, Rashid is playing a good knock here. This was floated up by Santner, Rashid reaches out to the pitch of the ball and tonks it straight down the ground for another six]]></line><line><![CDATA[McCullum and Santner are having a chat. A slip comes in place now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Buttler, 1 run, knocks this flighted delivery through extra cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Buttler, 2 runs, cuts this shortish delivery through extra cover, sweeper tidies up in the deep but the batsmen had ample time to take a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Buttler, <b>SIX</b>, <b>great hit!</b> Santner bowls this full on the stumps, Buttler gets under it and tonks it over the long-on fence for a maximum]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, 1 run, back of a length delivery on middle and leg, Buttler drops it to the right of the bowler and sets off, reaches the other end comfortably and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, no run, short of length delivery outside off, Buttler rocks back and cuts it to the left of backward point, who dives and stops the ball, prevents the single too]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four!</b> This was on a back of a length and well outside off, Buttler looks to guide it, gets an outside edge that splits the keeper and the widish slip, runs away to the fence in a hurry]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Adil Rashid, 1 run, banged in short and at the batsman, Rashid hooks it towards fine leg, the fielder in the deep runs to his right and tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, 1 run, drags his length back and bowls it slightly wide outside off, Buttler stays back and knocks it to sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a beautiful shot, this was pitched up outside off, Buttler comes forward, reaches to the pitch of the ball and drives it to the left of mid-off, who had no chance of stopping that]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, <b>wide</b>, bowls this well wide outside off, Buttler leaves it alone and the umpire exercises his arms]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[McClenaghan to continue from round the wicket. Just a slip in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, no run, presses forward and drives this fullish delivery to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, <b>FOUR</b>, Santner pays the price for dropping this short, Rashid goes deep in the crease and muscles the pull over mid-wicket, runs away to the fence in a jiffy]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, no run, floated up outside off, Rashid kneels down and drives it to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Buttler, 1 run, full toss outside off, Buttler drives it to wide long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, 3 runs, short and outside off, Rashid reaches out and cuts it through extra cover, the fielder from cover gives chase, hauls it back in time to save a run for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, no run, tossed up outside off, Rashid steps out and drives it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>batting powerplay</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, 2 runs, short delivery that doesn't rise as much as expected, Buttler swivels and pulls it behind square on the on-side, comes back for the second easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, no run, shortish and well outside off, Buttler goes for the cut off the back foot, gets an under-edge that goes on the bounce to the left of the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, no run, back of a length delivery angling in on the stumps, Buttler gets behind the line and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four!</b> This was bowled full and outside off, Buttler leans forward and goes for the drive, the ball takes the outside edge and runs away to the right of the fielder at slip, runs away to the third man fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Buttler, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Buttler goes on the back foot and defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Adil Rashid, 1 run, comes round the wicket and bowls this just short of a good length and outside off, Rashid hangs back, opens the face of the bat and guides it to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [5.0-0-36-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, 1 run, pushed through on middle, Rashid nudges it square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, <b>SIX</b>, lovely shot! Rashid was itching to go after the bowler and finally he gets one out of the middle. Flighted on off, Rashid shimmies down the wicket, doesn't get to the pitch but still goes through with the loft, clears long-on with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, no run, trifle short and outside off, Rashid cuts it to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, no run, sees the batsman come down the wicket and drags the length back, Rashid adjusts and taps it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, no run, nicely tossed up, Rashid was backing away to hoick it over the leg-side, but decides against it and dabs it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, no run, tossed up on off, defended to silly point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Adil Rashid, 1 run, angled across the right-hander, Rashid goes for the drive and toe-ends it to third man. Boult finishes his spell and he keeps impressing all the time. Ends with: <b>10-0-55-4</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Buttler, 1 run, fuller and just outside off, Buttler drives it through cover, there is protection in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[Goes back over the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Adil Rashid, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Rashid drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Buttler, 1 run, back of a length just outside off, Buttler eases it past the diving backward point fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Buttler, 2 runs, shortish and outside off, Buttler arches back and guides it wide of third man, the fielder runs to his right and fields the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Buttler, 2 runs, low full toss outside off, Buttler drives hard and towards deep extra cover, McClenaghan dives full length and stops the boundary, saved two there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, <b>FOUR</b>, edged and four! Fired in quicker and outside off, Rashid goes for the square drive, the outside edge goes wide of Taylor at slip and runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Buttler, 1 run, slower through the air, Buttler eases it to the left of cover and takes off for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Buttler, no run, flatter and on off, Buttler hangs back and knocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, 1 run, tossed up on off, Rashid rolls his wrists and works it through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, no run, floated up outside off, Rashid skips out of the crease and drives, drills it straight to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Adil Rashid, no run, flighted on off, Rashid defends with the bat in front his pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Buttler, no run, back of a length on off, Buttler opens the bat face and guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Buttler, no run, fraction short and outside off, Buttler goes hard on the cut, chops it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Buttler, no run, short of length outside off, Buttler is happy to let it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Buttler, 2 runs, pitched up outside off, Buttler leans into the drive and caresses it through cover for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Buttler, no run, fuller and angling in, Buttler wrists it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Buttler, no run, back of a length just outside off, left alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Adil Rashid, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to S Billings, <b>out</b> Lbw!! England are falling apart here. The debutant the latest to make his way back to the hut. <b>Maiden wicket</b> for Santner as well. It was a full delivery, quicker and on the stumps, Billings misses the flick and is struck on the pad, umpire Oxenford didn't think it was straightening to hit the stumps. However, New Zealand went for the review and got it spot on. Good use of technology. <b>S Billings lbw b Mitchell Santner 3(6)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mitchell Santner to S Billings, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[New Zealand are reviewing for an lbw appeal against Billings. "Fair delivery and we can move on to spin vision, doesn't seem to be bat involved. Can we check HotSpot? Doesn't seem anything on the HotSpot. Just wait for the RTS to confirm that. Happy that there is no bat. Pitching in-line, impact in-line and hitting. You will have to reverse your decision Bruce (Oxenford)," says the third umpire.]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Buttler, 1 run, flatter and around off, Buttler punches it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to S Billings, 1 run, Santner doesn't help his cause, drags the length back and allows Billings to get off strike, nudged away to right of mid wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[Baz comes in at silly point. Puts pressure on the debutant]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Buttler, 1 run, too full and on the stumps, Buttler drives inside out to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to S Billings, 1 run, Billings comes down the track, takes it on the full and works it wide of mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Buttler, 1 run, goes on with the angle from round the wicket, glanced away to short fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Buttler, 1 run, shortens the length just outside off, Buttler rides the bounce and glides it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Billings, 1 run, Boult comes round the wicket, keeps it full and around off, Billings drives it gently to mid-off and sets off for a sharp run, gets off the mark in ODIs]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Billings, no run, yorker outside off, Billings fails to dig it out, the ball goes past the blade]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and leg slip in place...]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to S Billings, no run, short of length around off, Billings gets nicely behind the line and defends to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sam Billings, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Stokes, <b>out</b> Bowled!! England have lost half their side now. Boult picks up his fourth wicket of the innings. Stokes is disappointed with himself as he walks back to the pavilion. Short delivery outside off, Stokes goes for the pull, inside edge deflects off the left thigh onto the off-stump. New Zealand have done extremely well to get back into the game. <b>Stokes b Boult 10(15) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Boult to Stokes, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Buttler, 1 run, too full and just outside off, Buttler squeezes the drive to square third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Stokes, no run, slower and on the stumps, Stokes chips it to short mid-wicket, Baz dives forward but still can't there. Nervy moment for Stokes]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Stokes, no run, pushed through on leg-stump, Stokes glances and picks out short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Buttler, 3 runs, nice floaty delivery, Buttler goes leg-side and chips it inside-out over cover, the timing was excellent as the ball was racing to the fence before Nathan McCullum intercepted with a dive from long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Buttler, no run, tossed up on off, Buttler push-drives it back to Santner]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Buttler, no run, flatter and on off, Buttler knocks it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Stokes, 1 run, slower and on the stumps, Stokes wrists it down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Stokes, 1 run, went for the inswinging yorker, ends up bowling a full toss, Stokes whips it to fine leg and retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Stokes, no run, another full and swinging delivery, nips back in sharply, Stokes clips it to short mid-wicket, finds the fielder there]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Stokes, no run, stifled appeal from Boult for an lbw, the yorker that tails back in, Stokes falls over on the flick and is struck on the pad, the ball was sliding down leg and New Zealand don't want to waste their only review]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Stokes, no run, again, nothing pitched up from Boult, punched to mid-off, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Buttler, 1 run, short of length around off, Buttler stands tall and punches to deep cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Buttler, no run, on a length just outside off, Buttler watches it carefully and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Buttler, 1 run, eases the drive along the ground to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Stokes, 1 run, goes straight on from round the wicket, Stokes closes the bat face early, the soft leading edge rolls down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Stokes, no run, quicker and fuller, Stokes drives it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Stokes, <b>FOUR</b>, pre-meditated! Floated up around off, Stokes kneels down and plays the reverse sweep, he gets a top-edge that flies over short third man and reaches the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Stokes, no run, tossed up on off, blocked down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mitchell Santner to Buttler, 1 run, full and on the stumps, Buttler flicks it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell Santner, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here comes New Zealand's debutant, Santner]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Stokes, no run, tight line from Boult, on off-stump, Stokes pushes it back to the bowler, who makes a half stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Buttler, 1 run, fullish and outside off, Buttler drives it sweetly, but picks out the man at sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Buttler, no run, short of length around off, Buttler defends it to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jos Buttler, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, <b>out</b> Caught by Ronchi!! This is a huge wicket for New Zealand. They have got rid of both set batsmen in a space of 11 balls. The centurion departs with over half the innings left. Boult bowls it with a scrambled seam, it was outside off, Root gives the charge and slashes, the outside edge goes to Ronchi, who snaffles it with ease. The visitors slowly clawing their way back into the game. <b>J Root c Ronchi b Boult 104(78) [4s-13 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Boult to J Root, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, no run, comes round the wicket, back of a length around off, defended to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Stokes, 3 runs, short of length on off, Stokes stays beside the line and whips it through vacant mid-wicket, Elliott gives chase from mid-on, slides and flicks it back in for his team-mate]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Trent Boult [5.0-0-36-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to J Root, no run, fuller and on the stumps, Root works it to mid-wicket, picks out the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to J Root, <b>FOUR</b>, trifle short and Root is onto it in a flash, he goes back and pulls it in front of square, beating the fielder at deep square leg with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to J Root, no run, again, short and outside off, cut straight to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to J Root, no run, short of length around off, Root hangs back and knocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to J Root, no run, turned to mid-wicket off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to J Root, 2 runs, the ground echoes of "Roooootttt". It has been a fabulous innings. Everyone in the crowd are on their feet and so are the England team, applauding the knock. Root raises his bat and acknowledges it as he brings up his <b>5th ODI hundred</b>. It is also the <b>3rd fastest ton</b> by an England batsmen. Coming to the ball, too full and on off, Root eases it past the diving mid-on fielder, Baz gives chase and hauls it in just before rope]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Matt Henry [5.0-0-33-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Stokes, no run, on a length close to off, Stokes presses it to mid-off after coming forward]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place for the new batsman]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ben Stokes, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Eoin Morgan, <b>out</b> Lbw!! A much needed wicket for New Zealand. Morgan was set and looking dangerous. It was a straight delivery, on off and middle, Morgan shuffles across and misses the flick, is rapped on the pads and the ball would have crashed into middle stump. Umpire Gough took his time before raising the finger. Morgan discussed with Root and opted for the review, but the onfield decision remained. <b>Eoin Morgan lbw b McClenaghan 50(46) [4s-1 6s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[McClenaghan to Eoin Morgan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Morgan has been given out LBW. He has reviewed it. "First we will have a look at the front foot, fair delivery. We'll go to spin vision. There is nothing on the bat with HotSpot. Can we go to ball tracking. Impact in-line and hitting. You can stay with your decision," says the third umpire.]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Root, 1 run, back of a length angled across off, dabbed away to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Root, <b>FOUR</b>, the timing on the shot was simply superb. McClenaghan provides bit of room, Root uses the pace of the ball and cracks it wide of backward point, Guptill dives in vain and third man had no chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Root, no run, good length ball on off, Root defends off the front foot to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Root, no run, full and outside off, almost a yorker, squeezed to backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to J Root, 1 run, touch too straight, on middle and leg, Root tucks it behind square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to J Root, <b>SIX</b>, fantastic shot! Length delivery just outside off, Root frees his arms and takes the aerial route, hits it through the line and sends it sailing over long-off for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, Morgan brings up his <b>23rd ODI fifty</b>. It has been a wonderful innings from the skipper. He goes up and shakes hands with Root. Slower delivery on off, eased off the back foot to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to J Root, 1 run, full and sliding onto the pad, Root glances it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, drops it short, Morgan swivels and pulls to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[Elliott and Baz have a chat.]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Eoin Morgan, no run, tucks the batsman for room, Morgan defends to the left of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, McClenaghan keeps bowling it short and wide, Morgan slaps it to deep backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Eoin Morgan, <b>SIX</b>, the 100-run stand comes up. Morgan gets his third six of the innings. It was a streaky shot though. Short and outside off, Morgan charges down, reaches out and slashes, the thickish outside edge flies towards third man, Southee leaps up but the ball evades him comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Eoin Morgan, no run, short of length on off, Morgan hops across and knocks it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Eoin Morgan, no run, back of a length close to off, Morgan defends in front of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Root, 1 run, again, McClenaghan keeps it short of length, Root swivels and pulls towards deep square leg, didn't time it that well]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Root, <b>FOUR</b>, top shot! Root was expecting it to be short, he got into position quickly and pulled in front of square on the leg-side, no one protecting the boundary over there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Eoin Morgan, no run, Morgan moves away to the leg-side, Elliott keeps him calm by following him, pushed back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to J Root, 1 run, Root steps down the wicket, swipes it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to J Root, no run, another cutter just outside off, Root steers it to short third, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to J Root, no run, fullish and on off, Root drives off the inner part to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to J Root, no run, back of a length on off, Root turns it gently to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to J Root, <b>FOUR</b>, poor delivery, the split finger delivery, down leg, Root stays inside the line and tickles it fine, the fielder was square and had no chance. He shows Morgan what kind of delivery was that]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Eoin Morgan, no run, effort delivery, Morgan gives the charge and McClenaghan digs it in short, rises steeply and beats Morgan's attempted pull. Nice carry through to Ronchi]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Eoin Morgan, no run, good length ball outside off, Morgan covers the line and shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Eoin Morgan, 2 runs, tad straight, on off and middle, Morgan nudges it through the vacant mid-wicket region and picks up two]]></line><line><![CDATA[Still a slip in place..]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Root, 1 run, short delivery right at the batsman, Root rolls his wrists and pulls along the ground behind square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Root, no run, fuller and close to off, Root drives it to cover, the bat turned and he didn't time it well]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Root, <b>FOUR</b>, short and just a bit of width on offer, Root cuts it hard into the ground, the ball bounces over the backward point fielder and races away to the boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Eoin Morgan, no run, drags the length back, Morgan defends it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Eoin Morgan, no run, slower and outside off, Morgan push-drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Eoin Morgan, <b>SIX</b>, fabulous shot! This is a calculated hit from the England skipper. The mid-off fielder was inside the circle, Elliott comes round the wicket, bowls it fuller and around off, Morgan backs away and lofts it handsomely over long-off for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ronchi is up to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to J Root, 1 run, back of a length on off, punched down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to J Root, no run, takes the pace off the ball, Root advances, is deceived by the lack of pace, chips it to mid-on, the ball lands well in front of the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to J Root, 2 runs, full and drifting onto the pads, Root leans forward and flicks to deep square leg, the fielder from deep mid-wicket runs to his right and tidies up]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Grant Elliott, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for a <b>drink</b>. Baz has his players in a huddle. The England batsmen are waiting and so are the umpires. Now they disperse and straightaway there is a bowling change. Elliott comes on to replace Nathan McCullum..]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Root, 1 run, shortish and on the off stump, Root pulls it behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, short and way outside off stump, cut to deep backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Eoin Morgan, <b>wide</b>, width on offer outside off stump, Morgan looks to cut but gets beaten. That's a harsh call from the umpire, it wasn't all that wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Eoin Morgan, no run, defended off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Root, 1 run, short delivery on the off stump, Root gets on top of the bounce and pulls it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, oh that could have easily gone back onto the stumps, Morgan looks to drive off the back foot but gets an inside edge and this short of length delivery goes past the stumps and rolls to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Eoin Morgan, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Morgan defends it towards point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to J Root, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Root advances and drives it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to J Root, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>dropped</b>, a poor effort from Taylor, this time at long-on. Flighted delivery just outside off stump, Root goes for the slog-sweep again but he hits this very straight, Taylor runs to his right from long-on, he didn't move quick enough and in the end tried to go for it with his right hand and spilled it. How costly is that going to be?]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to J Root, <b>SIX</b>, handsome hit! No intent to keep it down but he hit it very well. Flighted delivery just outside off stump, Root slog-sweeps it from the middle of the bat and sends it over deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, gently driven with an angled bat to deep backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Eoin Morgan, <b>FOUR</b>, inside-out and just over the fielder at cover. Flighted delivery from Nathan McCullum, Morgan goes leg-side and drives over cover and gets four]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to J Root, 1 run, flighted delivery outside off stump, Root fetches the slog-sweep, the fielder at short mid-wicket makes a half-stop diving to his left]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Root, 1 run, Root gives himself a bit of room and steers the length to third man. There was a bit of risk involved as he exposed his sticks on that occasion]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Root, no run, driven off the back foot towards cover-point this time]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Root, no run, short of length outside off stump, Root knocks it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Root, <b>wide</b>, good length delivery down the leg-side, Root fails to tickle it on its way]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Root, <b>FOUR</b>, oh no! Slip and the keeper were just ball-watching. Well, Root wouldn't mind as it allows him to reach his <b>9th ODI fifty</b>. Short of a length delivery angling away from the right-hander, Root pokes and gets a thick edge, Taylor was very square at slip and even Ronchi didn't have a go at it. It went at a catchable height as well. Meanwhile, Root raises his bat to the crowd and the dressing room to acknowledge the applause]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Root, no run, short of length delivery on the leg stump, Root hops and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, in the airrrr, but past the man at shortish backward point. Short of a length delivery outside off stump, Morgan cuts uppishly, the man in the deep tidies up]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Finally, we get to see McClenaghan.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, flatter delivery on the leg stump, Morgan backs away and cuts it through point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Eoin Morgan, no run, advances and looks to go over the top, but McCullum fired it full and Morgan got an inside edge onto boot. He could have been easily stumped there, had the ball rolled back towards the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Eoin Morgan, no run, backs away and drives the flighted delivery to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to J Root, 1 run, floated up outside off stump, punched off the front foot with an angled bat through cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, steps out and pushes the flatter ball to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to J Root, 1 run, flatter delivery just outside off stump, punched off the back foot to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to J Root, 1 run, pulled in front of square on the on-side as the length is short, but it's only a single though]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Eoin Morgan, 3 runs, oh shot! He doesn't try to hit that hard, just leans forward and plays an extended forward push, mid-off is very square, once again it's that man Baz, who races across the turf and makes a diving save just inside the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Eoin Morgan, 2 runs, no one at mid-wicket, Morgan tucks one through the vacant region, Baz gives chase from mid-on and saves two]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to J Root, 1 run, short of length delivery on the off stump, Root taps it to short mid-wicket for an easy run]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to J Root, 2 runs, full and on the leg stump, Root flicks it behind square on the on-side, fine leg tidies up running to his left]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to J Root, no run, shortish ball outside off stump, Root goes on the back foot to pull, gets an inside edge and hits him on the body. No harm done though]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Eoin Morgan, no run, once again Morgan gives himself a bit of room, McCullum goes full and towards Morgan, who drives it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Eoin Morgan, no run, Morgan goes leg-side but McCullum follows him and cramps him for room, punched to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Eoin Morgan, 2 runs, down the track again and then a gentle drive along the ground through cover for a couple of quick runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to J Root, 1 run, oh the fancy looking reverse-paddle from Root, but the fielder at short third man moves swiftly to his left to save three]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, flighted delivery on the off stump, Morgan looks to off-drive the ball but gets an inside edge that goes to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Eoin Morgan, <b>SIX</b>, that is a nice positive blow from the England skipper. Flighted delivery outside off stump, Morgan advances, but doesn't get to the pitch of the ball, yet goes through with the loft and nails it way back over long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Nathan McCullum [2.0-0-12-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[No one at slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, punched on the rise to cover for a run and he'll keep strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Eoin Morgan, no run, Henry cramps Morgan for room with a short of length delivery as he advances, blocked to short cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Eoin Morgan, no run, very close to the off stump, Morgan cuts and picks out backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to J Root, 1 run, Root gets right on top of the ball and punches this short of length delivery to the man sweeping on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to J Root, <b>wide</b>, short ball on the off stump, Root ducks under it and the umpire doesn't like the height on that]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Eoin Morgan, 1 run, steps out and drives the short of length delivery gently to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Eoin Morgan, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, left alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[This (68) is the best mandatory powerplay score for England at home since 2011.]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely front foot drive, full and outside off stump, Root leans forward and drives it through cover to move into the 40s]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Eoin Morgan, 3 runs, good length delivery on the off stump, Morgan dances down the track and looks to drive, gets an inside edge that rolls to deep mid-wicket, a lot of open spaces on the leg-side they get three]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shortish backward point, point, shortish cover-point and cover is the field for Morgan]]></line><line><![CDATA[Some disturbance behind the bowler's arm and it's sorted now]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Eoin Morgan, no run, Morgan hops out and defends the short of length delivery off the back foot towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, 1 run, allows the ball to come and flicks it wide of mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, <b>FOUR</b>, Root is looking very good. Just a mere push off the front foot, good length delivery just outside off stump, Root places it to the left of mid-off, where Baz does not manage to stop the ball despite a full length dive]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, 2 runs, short of length delivery outside off stump, Root goes on the back foot punches it through cover for a couple of runs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Eoin Morgan, 2 runs, short of length delivery on the leg stump, Morgan glances it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Eoin Morgan, 2 runs, full and just outside off stump, Morgan drives it past the bowler, who tries to stop the ball with his right hand in his followthrough, mid-off gives chase and saves two]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Eoin Morgan, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Morgan cuts it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Eoin Morgan, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, tapped to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Eoin Morgan, no run, short of length delivery on the off stump, Morgan defends it towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Eoin Morgan, no run, first ball Morgan gives the charge to the bowler and drives it towards short cover, Root sets off for a run but Morgan sends him back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Matt Henry [2.0-0-16-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, no run, fuller length delivery outside off stump, Root shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, no run, Root gets on top of the bounce and drives the short of length delivery nicely off the back foot, but another good save by Marty Guptill at backward point meant it was just a dot ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, no run, beaten! A loose shot from Root. Full and way outside off stump, Root reaches out to drive but only connects with thin air]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, no run, well, this is interesting. Bit of extra lift for Boult on this short of length delivery, Root was late in taking the bat out of the way, but he managed to keep the bat away from ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Eoin Morgan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Hales, <b>out</b> Caught by Matt Henry!! Hales throws it away. He was looking good before playing this rash shot. Banged in halfway down the wicket, the line was outside off, Hales fetches it from there, the top-edge goes over short fine, Henry runs back and holds on. He hung on even as he tumbled over. England lose a wicket just after the 50-run stand. <b>Hales c Matt Henry b Boult 20(20) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Boult to Hales, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, 1 run, Boult stays round the wicket, keeps it back of a length around off, Root runs it down to third man with an angled bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Hales, no run, flighted on off, Hales leans forward and pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to J Root, 1 run, slower and around off, Root opens the bat face and eases it wide of cover, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Hales, 1 run, takes a step out of the crease, push-drives to mid-off and sets off for the run]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Hales, 2 runs, fraction short and on off, Hales goes back and pulls, mid-on gets a hand and manages to parry it to the fielder at deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to J Root, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, Root goes deep in the crease and works it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to J Root, <b>FOUR</b>, Root continues to be positive. Tossed up delivery on off, Root stretches forward and lofts it straight down the ground, that came right off the meat as the ball raced away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Hales, no run, good length delivery outside off stump, driven to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Hales, no run, inside edge onto the pad, could have easily dragged that back onto the sticks. Hales is trying to cut ones that aren't all that short and he gets away with another one]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Hales, <b>FOUR</b>, edged but there is no one at third slip. Good length delivery outside off stump, Hales looks to cut, it wasn't all that short, gets a thick edge that flies past the man at first slip, Elliott gives chase at third man but loses the race]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Hales, no run, poor ball but Boult gets away with it, short and wide, probably would have been a wide but he opted to reach out and cut, only to find cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, 1 run, steered down to third man along the ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, no run, fullish and outside off stump, Root drives it to the left of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket with a man at slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Trent Boult [2.0-0-16-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Hales, no run, tossed up just outside off stump, defended towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to J Root, 1 run, a wristy flick from Root, but it goes straight to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to J Root, no run, steps out and drives it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Hales, 1 run, down the leg-side, flicked along the ground through mid-wicket for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to Hales, no run, flighted delivery just outside off stump, Hales defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[Short mid-wicket in now, a man at leg gully as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nathan McCullum to J Root, 1 run, flighted delivery on the leg stump, Root flicks it wide of long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Nathan McCullum, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ah! An off-spinner comes into the attack. Baz and his innovative moves. Let's see if it works! One slip in place and Nathan will bowl from round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to J Root, 1 run, Root moves across the stumps and glances the short of length delivery to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to J Root, no run, excellent diving save from Guptill, saved a certain boundary. Root slightly gave himself some room to drive this short of length delivery off the back foot, Guptill dived full length to his right to stop the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to J Root, <b>FOUR</b>, cracking back foot punch from Root, hit that hard onto the ground and hit it to the left of the fielder at short cover. Once again Root errs on the shorter side and pays the penalty]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to J Root, 2 runs, nicely tucked off the back foot through mid-wicket for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Hales, 1 run, friendly ball, shortish and on the leg stump, Hales flicks it behind square on the on-side, but only for a single though]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Hales, no run, full and outside off stump, Hales shoulders arms]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, no run, good leave, covered the off stump and left the length ball alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, <b>FOUR</b>, excellent shot! Full and in the slot, Root leans forward and drives well, doesn't try to over-hit the ball, transfers the weight nicely onto the front foot and sends it to the right of Baz, who was very wide at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now there is a fielder at short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, no run, good length delivery on the stumps, blocked towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, <b>FOUR</b>, driven off the back foot, again a big gap at cover and Root timed that to perfection. Interestingly, Boult tried the scrambled seam delivery, but it didn't work as the length was too short]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, no run, full and asking Root to drive/play away from the body, but the batsman lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, no run, not much of swing on this short of length delivery, just goes across the right-hander with the angle from over the wicket, Root lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Hales, no run, good leave, made the call very late to leave the ball alone but he judged it to perfection. Fullish and just outside off stump, Hales covers the stumps and shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Hales, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot, Hales presents the full face of the bat and gets full value for the shot. Full and on the stumps, Hales leans forward and punches it through mid-on, the fielder was square and he had no chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Hales, no run, fullish and angling into the right-hander, Hales gets an inside edge onto pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[Just mid-off and point in front of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Hales, <b>FOUR</b>, width on offer outside off stump and Hales drives well off the back foot through cover-point. Baz has set an attacking field and hence there are a lot of open spaces on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Hales, no run, much closer to the off stump now, Hales defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Matt Henry to Hales, no run, good length delivery just outside off stump, Hales defends]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Now three slips for Henry]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Matt Henry, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Hales, 3 runs, full and swinging back in, Hales drives it along the ground through mid-off, Baz was very square, but he gives chase, oh he's racing after that and puts in anexcellent dive to pull it back just inside the rope. Great effort that from the New Zealand skipper]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, 1 run, oh Root almost hit that to the fielder there. Inswinger on a good length, Root tries to work it on the on-side, plays very late, doesn't control the shot and hits it uppishly, Santner dives to his left at leg gully, but it evades him]]></line><line><![CDATA[There is man at leg slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, 2 runs, too full and on the pads, Root flicks it behind square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, no run, good length delivery outside off stump, Root shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to J Root, 2 runs, now there is a man at cover, but Root drives along the ground to the left of the fielder to get England off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Joe Root, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Boult to Jason Roy, <b>out</b> Caught by Guptill!! Oh dear! What a poor start for Jason Roy and he can't believe what he's done. With just mid-off and point in front of square on the off-side, Roy has picked out the latter. Nothing but a gentle inswinger on a fuller length, on seeing that big gap at cover, Roy wanted to send the drive off the front foot through that region, but he hit it much more squarer and Guptill dived forward to complete a low catch. A <b>golden duck</b> for Roy. <b>Jason Roy c Guptill b Boult 0(1)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Boult to Jason Roy, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jason Roy and Hales are at the crease. Jason Roy is on strike. Boult will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's time for the action to begin. Alex Hales and Jason Roy make their way out to the middle. How many slips will Baz have for his new ball bowlers? He had at least three and sometimes four during the World Cup. Trent Boult to open the attack and he has only two slips in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[New Zealand have rested Tim Southee for this game, while Corey Anderson, who missed the second Test, is yet to fully recover from a back injury.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>New Zealand</b> (Playing XI): Martin Guptill, Brendon McCullum(c), Kane Williamson, Ross Taylor, Grant Elliott, Mitchell Santner, Luke Ronchi(w), Nathan McCullum, Matt Henry, Mitchell McClenaghan, Trent Boult]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>England</b> (Playing XI): Alex Hales, Jason Roy, Joe Root, Eoin Morgan(c), Ben Stokes, Jos Buttler(w), Sam Billings, Adil Rashid, Chris Jordan, Liam Plunkett, Steven Finn]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Morgan</b>: "The last year or so has been really poor, but the future looks promising with a few young guys coming in. The group of players that we have picked can play the brand of cricket that we want to play moving forward. <b>Sam Billings</b> is making his debut, he is an exciting player and he's going to be very good to watch in the middle-order."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>McCullum</b>: "We are going to bowl first. The conditions are overcast, hopefully our boys can swing it early on and take some early wickets. <b>Mitchell Santner</b> is making his debut. This wicket looks great. I think overall our philosophy is still very much about playing a positive brand of cricket. The World Cup was outstanding for us. Now we've got an opportunity to continue the good work."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>New Zealand have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[It's <b>toss time</b> folks!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Although England are playing at home, the pressure is slightly more on them to put up an improved show in the 50-over format after a disastrous World Cup campaign. Team vice-captain and wicket-keeper Jos Buttler has asked his mates to play 'no-fear-cricket', while interim coach Paul Farbrace has said that the side needs to play with freedom in the 5-match ODI series. England have had a decent build-up to the series as a few of the players did well in the Natwest T20 Blast. However, they are not fielding a full strength squad as the likes of James Anderson, Stuart Broad, Ian Bell and Moeen Ali have been rested for the series.]]></line><line><![CDATA[England then made a few changes to their coaching staff, drew the Test series against West Indies, Andrew Strauss was appointed the new ECB director and then England played a hard-fought Test series against New Zealand in which they shared honours. After the conclusion of the Test series, McCullum said "1-1 was a fair reflection." New Zealand played a warm-up match against Leicestershire to practice for the ODI series, in which Ross Taylor, Grant Elliott and Luke Ronchi played aggressively. Taylor, who has not been in the best of forms of late, has hinted that he would make a conscious effort to be more positive with the bat.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The last time these two sides met in an ODI, Tim Southee picked up a record 7-wicket haul, while Brendon McCullum scored a breezy fifty. Yes, it was at the 2015 World Cup that New Zealand thrashed England at the Cake Tin in a game that lasted a total of just 45.4 overs. A lot has happened since then. McCullum continued to bludgeon bowling attacks at the top throughout the World Cup and then continued his show in the IPL as well. New Zealand had an excellent time at the multi-nation event, barring the final, while England failed to make it to the quarter-finals.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/>After his team were thrashed by Australia in the World Cup final at the Melbourne Cricket Ground on March 29, New Zealand captain Brendon McCullum was asked by a reporter if he and his team would change the aggressive brand of cricket that had taken them to their maiden tournament final, built on a stunning winning streak of ten matches.<br/><br/>His reply came fast, without hesitation. "No, no, you don't change your style of play," said McCullum with the same seriousness and conviction with which he had rolled up to every press conference during a memorable World Cup campaign. "For us to develop into the team that we want to be in international cricket, we have to play like that. I think there's an element of fearlessness about how we play, which has been an effect on other teams, as well, and I think if you ask most of the teams in this tournament what they think of how we've played the game, they would be very respectful of how we've gone about it.<br/><br/>"It's what gives us our greatest pleasure, as well, and sometimes we're going to come undone, but for us to compete against the big teams on regular occasions and for us to be able to develop into the team we want to be, we need to keep playing this brand of cricket, and we'll get better at doing it the more we become accustomed to it, and I guess a stronger depth of players we develop in the same sort of mould of cricket as we have. So yeah, we're not going to change."<br/><br/>That attacking, joyous brand of cricket was extended in the Test arena recently. New Zealand owned much of the first Test at Lord's by playing aggressive cricket, and it was during one such attacking passage that they let the match slip. But McCullum's men stuck to that same approach at Leeds and it earned them a 1-1 series scoreline to extend their unbeaten run further. Now, they will ditch the whites to don black, the colour they wore so passionately during the World Cup. The format in which they bossed opposing teams in the World Cup until the final, the format in which they are ranked third, the format in which they have the best chance to keep winning. England have reason to be worried. Very worried.<br/><br/>A run of ten unbeaten ODIs ended at the MCG on March 29, when a ruthless Australia shoved them aside for a fifth World Cup title. After two Tests against England, the Black Caps warmed up for the limited-overs leg of their tour with a 198-run hammering of Leicestershire on Friday. In that 50-over fixture, the tourists were in a spot of bother at 152 for 5 but surged to 373 without further loss through a superb partnership of 221 in just 25 overs from centurions Grant Elliott and Luke Ronchi.<br/><br/>Elliott is, of course, the allrounder who shone during that unforgettable World Cup semi-final at Eden Park on March 24, hitting the winning runs in a nail-biting chase over South Africa to spark scenes of delirium. Elliott followed that special innings with a brisk half-century in the final, the only innings of note from a limp New Zealand display. Now, as New Zealand and England begin a five-match series with the first ODI at Birmingham on June 9 (Tuesday), the likes of Elliott - not part of the Test squad - will hope to reproduce such batting form as the Black Caps get back to their strongest suite against a team which put up its most tepid World Cup campaign ever.<br/><br/>From the XI that played the World Cup final at the MCG, the most likely change will be Nathan McCullum coming in for the retired Daniel Vettori. Corey Anderson's back is being closely monitored, so should he not be passed fit then the spin-bowling allrounder Mitchell Santner could get a debut. With left-arm quick Mitchell McClenaghan joining the touring party from a successful IPL season of winners Mumbai, then taking four wickets against Leicestershire, New Zealand's bowling has added zing. Tim Southee, Trent Boult and Matt Henry bowled a lot of overs during the Tests and so having a fresh McClenaghan could be the way the team management tilts.<br/><br/>Eoin Morgan's England have lost seven of 11 ODIs this year, sitting at sixth on the ICC's list for ODI teams. The new selection panel dumped regulars James Anderson, Stuart Broad, Ian Bell and Gary Ballance while resting Moeen Ali, opting to bring in some fresh faces. There are some aggressive hitters in the new squad, but how they fare against a superb New Zealand bowling attack remains to be seen. It will not be easy.<br/><br/>During the World Cup, McCullum's Black Caps set the bar for all ODI teams apart from Australia. If they replicate that exciting and aggressive brand across the next two weeks, they should comfortably add another ODI series and a one-off Twenty20 international to their burgeoning kitty. So sit back and get ready to enjoy the ride.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>England</b> (From): Alex Hales, Jason Roy, James Taylor, Joe Root, Eoin Morgan(c), Jos Buttler(w), Ben Stokes, Adil Rashid, Chris Jordan, Mark Wood, Steven Finn, Liam Plunkett, Sam Billings, David Willey]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>New Zealand</b> (From): Brendon McCullum(c), Martin Guptill, Kane Williamson, Ross Taylor, Corey Anderson, Grant Elliott, Luke Ronchi(w), Nathan McCullum, Tim Southee, Mitchell McClenaghan, Trent Boult, Matt Henry, Tom Latham, Mitchell Santner, Ben Wheeler]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>408</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>9</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>50</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="England">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>6534</playerid>
					<name>Jason Roy</name>
					<batsman-name>J Roy</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Jason Roy</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>T Boult</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8117</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Martin Guptill</fielder>
						<fielderId>1457</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6734</playerid>
					<name>Alex Hales</name>
					<batsman-name>A Hales</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Hales</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>20</runs>
					<balls>20</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>T Boult</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8117</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Matt Henry</fielder>
						<fielderId>9067</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8019</playerid>
					<name>Joe Root</name>
					<batsman-name>J Root</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>J Root</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>104</runs>
					<balls>78</balls>
					<fours>13</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>T Boult</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8117</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Luke Ronchi</fielder>
						<fielderId>1396</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>624</playerid>
					<name>Eoin Morgan</name>
					<batsman-name>E Morgan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Eoin Morgan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>50</runs>
					<balls>46</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>McClenaghan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7624</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6557</playerid>
					<name>Ben Stokes</name>
					<batsman-name>Stokes</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Stokes</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>10</runs>
					<balls>15</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>T Boult</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8117</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2258</playerid>
					<name>Jos Buttler</name>
					<batsman-name>J Buttler</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Buttler</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>129</runs>
					<balls>77</balls>
					<fours>13</fours>
					<sixes>5</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>McClenaghan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7624</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Matt Henry</fielder>
						<fielderId>9067</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7990</playerid>
					<name>Sam Billings</name>
					<batsman-name>Sam Billings</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Billings</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Mitchell Santner</bowler>
					<bowlerId>10100</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1742</playerid>
					<name>Adil Rashid</name>
					<batsman-name>Adil Rashid</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Adil Rashid</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>69</runs>
					<balls>50</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Elliott</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1064</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Martin Guptill</fielder>
						<fielderId>1457</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6532</playerid>
					<name>Chris Jordan</name>
					<batsman-name>C Jordan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Jordan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Elliott</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1064</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Trent Boult</fielder>
						<fielderId>8117</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>479</playerid>
					<name>Liam Plunkett</name>
					<batsman-name>L Plunkett</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Plunkett</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>13</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6317</playerid>
					<name>Steven Finn</name>
					<batsman-name>Finn</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Finn</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6534</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>0</runs>
				<overs>0.1</overs>
				<batsman>Jason Roy</batsman>
				<batsman-name>J Roy</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6734</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>50</runs>
				<overs>7.2</overs>
				<batsman>Alex Hales</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Hales</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>624</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>171</runs>
				<overs>22.5</overs>
				<batsman>Eoin Morgan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>E Morgan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8019</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>180</runs>
				<overs>24.3</overs>
				<batsman>Joe Root</batsman>
				<batsman-name>J Root</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6557</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>195</runs>
				<overs>28.2</overs>
				<batsman>Ben Stokes</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Stokes</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7990</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>202</runs>
				<overs>29.6</overs>
				<batsman>Sam Billings</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Sam Billings</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>2258</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>379</runs>
				<overs>47.3</overs>
				<batsman>Jos Buttler</batsman>
				<batsman-name>J Buttler</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6532</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>394</runs>
				<overs>49.2</overs>
				<batsman>Chris Jordan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>C Jordan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1742</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>394</runs>
				<overs>49.3</overs>
				<batsman>Adil Rashid</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Adil Rashid</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>8</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>8</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="New Zealand">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>8117</playerid>
					<name>Trent Boult</name>
					<bowler-name>T Boult</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Boult</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>55</runsoff>
					<wickets>4</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9067</playerid>
					<name>Matt Henry</name>
					<bowler-name>M Henry</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Matt Henry</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>73</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>579</playerid>
					<name>Nathan McCullum</name>
					<bowler-name>N McCullum</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nathan McCullum</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>66</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7624</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell McClenaghan</name>
					<bowler-name>McClenaghan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>McClenaghan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>93</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1064</playerid>
					<name>Grant Elliott</name>
					<bowler-name>Elliott</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Elliott</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>57</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10100</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Santner</name>
					<bowler-name>Mitchell Santner</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mitchell Santner</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>64</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1457</playerid>
					<name>Martin Guptill</name>
					<bowler-name>M Guptill</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Guptill</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<bowler-name>B McCullum</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Brendon McCullum</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6326</playerid>
					<name>Kane Williamson</name>
					<bowler-name>Williamson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Williamson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>521</playerid>
					<name>Ross Taylor</name>
					<bowler-name>Ross Taylor</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ross Taylor</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1396</playerid>
					<name>Luke Ronchi</name>
					<bowler-name>Ronchi</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ronchi</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>198</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>10</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>31.1</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="New Zealand">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1457</playerid>
					<name>Martin Guptill</name>
					<batsman-name>M Guptill</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Guptill</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>22</runs>
					<balls>18</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Finn</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6317</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Jos Buttler</fielder>
						<fielderId>2258</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Brendon McCullum</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>10</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Finn</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6317</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6326</playerid>
					<name>Kane Williamson</name>
					<batsman-name>Williamson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Williamson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>45</runs>
					<balls>43</balls>
					<fours>8</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Adil Rashid</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1742</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Joe Root</fielder>
						<fielderId>8019</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>521</playerid>
					<name>Ross Taylor</name>
					<batsman-name>Ross Taylor</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ross Taylor</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>57</runs>
					<balls>54</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Finn</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6317</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1064</playerid>
					<name>Grant Elliott</name>
					<batsman-name>Elliott</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Elliott</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>24</runs>
					<balls>27</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sam Billings</fielder>
						<fielderId>7990</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Jos Buttler</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>2258</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10100</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell Santner</name>
					<batsman-name>Mitchell Santner</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mitchell Santner</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>15</runs>
					<balls>23</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Adil Rashid</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1742</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Chris Jordan</fielder>
						<fielderId>6532</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1396</playerid>
					<name>Luke Ronchi</name>
					<batsman-name>Ronchi</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ronchi</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Adil Rashid</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1742</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>579</playerid>
					<name>Nathan McCullum</name>
					<batsman-name>N McCullum</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nathan McCullum</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>5</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Finn</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6317</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Chris Jordan</fielder>
						<fielderId>6532</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9067</playerid>
					<name>Matt Henry</name>
					<batsman-name>M Henry</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Matt Henry</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Adil Rashid</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1742</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7624</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell McClenaghan</name>
					<batsman-name>McClenaghan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>McClenaghan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>C Jordan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6532</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Alex Hales</fielder>
						<fielderId>6734</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8117</playerid>
					<name>Trent Boult</name>
					<batsman-name>T Boult</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Boult</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>201</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>11</runs>
				<overs>0.6</overs>
				<batsman>Brendon McCullum</batsman>
				<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1457</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>52</runs>
				<overs>6.3</overs>
				<batsman>Martin Guptill</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Guptill</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6326</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>94</runs>
				<overs>13.5</overs>
				<batsman>Kane Williamson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Williamson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1064</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>160</runs>
				<overs>23</overs>
				<batsman>Grant Elliott</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Elliott</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>10100</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>185</runs>
				<overs>27.5</overs>
				<batsman>Mitchell Santner</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mitchell Santner</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1396</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>185</runs>
				<overs>27.6</overs>
				<batsman>Luke Ronchi</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Ronchi</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>521</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>190</runs>
				<overs>28.2</overs>
				<batsman>Ross Taylor</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Ross Taylor</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9067</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>195</runs>
				<overs>29.5</overs>
				<batsman>Matt Henry</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Henry</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>579</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>198</runs>
				<overs>30.6</overs>
				<batsman>Nathan McCullum</batsman>
				<batsman-name>N McCullum</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7624</playerid>
				<nbr>10</nbr>
				<runs>198</runs>
				<overs>31.1</overs>
				<batsman>Mitchell McClenaghan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>McClenaghan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>8</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>10</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>18</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="England">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>6317</playerid>
					<name>Steven Finn</name>
					<bowler-name>Finn</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Finn</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>4</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6532</playerid>
					<name>Chris Jordan</name>
					<bowler-name>C Jordan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Jordan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5.1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>33</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>479</playerid>
					<name>Liam Plunkett</name>
					<bowler-name>L Plunkett</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Plunkett</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>37</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1742</playerid>
					<name>Adil Rashid</name>
					<bowler-name>Adil Rashid</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Adil Rashid</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>55</runsoff>
					<wickets>4</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6557</playerid>
					<name>Ben Stokes</name>
					<bowler-name>Stokes</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Stokes</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>28</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6734</playerid>
					<name>Alex Hales</name>
					<bowler-name>A Hales</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Hales</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6534</playerid>
					<name>Jason Roy</name>
					<bowler-name>J Roy</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Jason Roy</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8019</playerid>
					<name>Joe Root</name>
					<bowler-name>J Root</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>J Root</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>624</playerid>
					<name>Eoin Morgan</name>
					<bowler-name>E Morgan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Eoin Morgan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2258</playerid>
					<name>Jos Buttler</name>
					<bowler-name>J Buttler</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Buttler</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7990</playerid>
					<name>Sam Billings</name>
					<bowler-name>Sam Billings</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Billings</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



