<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="15887" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>2nd Qualifying Final (3 v 4)</gameDesc>
		<series>Pakistan Super League, 2016</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Islamabad United</home>
		<away>Karachi Kings</away>
		<teamsabbr>ISU vs KRK</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>ISU</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>KRK</awayabbr>
		<homeId>330</homeId>
		<awayId>332</awayId>
		<venue>Dubai International Cricket Stadium, Dubai</venue>
		<startdate>20 02 2016</startdate>
		<enddate>20 02 2016</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Islamabad United</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Islamabad United won by 9 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Islamabad United</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>9</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Ahsan Raza</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Aleem Dar</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Joel Wilson</Name>
			<Country>WI</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Roshan Mahanama</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>16:00</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20160220190011</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>ISU</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>KRK</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>115</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>1</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>14.2</batteamovers>
		<status>Islamabad United won by 9 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>255</playerid>
			<name>Dwayne Smith*</name>
			<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Smith</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>50</runs>
			<balls-faced>48</balls-faced>
			<fours>7</fours>
			<sixes>1</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>159</playerid>
			<name>Brad Haddin</name>
			<batsman-name>Haddin</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Haddin</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>52</runs>
			<balls-faced>29</balls-faced>
			<fours>4</fours>
			<sixes>3</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1120</playerid>
			<name>Sohail Khan*</name>
			<bowler-name>S Khan</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Sohail Khan</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>3.2</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>25</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>8366</playerid>
			<name>Mir Hamza</name>
			<bowler-name>Mir Hamza</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Mir Hamza</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>2</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>11</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>112</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>9052</playerid>
<name>Sharjeel Khan</name>
<player-runs>9</player-runs>
<player-balls>9</player-balls>
<runs>18</runs>
<wicket-nbr>1</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>1120</bowlerid>
<bowlername>S Khan</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>1</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>3</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>4</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[1 1 1 1 1 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 1 . L2 . . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 4 1 1 . . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 4 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2016/2016_PSL/ISU_KRK_FEB20/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[That will be it for today. Join us tomorrow for a potential semi-final between Peshawar Zalmi and Islamabad United same time at the same venue. Until then, as ever, goodbye and good night!!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Sami</b> expectedly is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his tremendous spell with the ball. His figures read: 4-0-8-5 = <b>B-R-I-L-L-I-A-N-T</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The chase was just a stroll in the park. Islamabad United never looked like losing the game. After Sohail Khan consumed Sharjeel Khan in the fourth over, Haddin and Smith bludgeoned the bowlers all over the park and scripted an easy win for their team. Haddin, in particular, was aggressive and used his feet well against the spinners. Both batsmen compiled fifties and put paid to Karachi Kings' winning hopes. Must say Karachi Kings lost the game in the first half as they crumbled for a low score on a relatively good batting surface and jeez! How can one forget that game-changing spell from Mohammad Sami...]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, That's that - Smith completes the formalities. <b>Islamabad United enter PSL's third qualifying final and will compete with Peshawar Zalmi for a spot in the final tomorrow.</b> Smith half-turns and pulls this short ball (through square leg) with utter disdain to steer his side home...]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Haddin, 1 run, walks across and pulls a short ball, went on the bounce to the fielder at long-on, didn't time it that well]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mir Hamza to Dwayne Smith, no run, shortish again, Smith skips out and mistimes the pull back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mir Hamza to Dwayne Smith, no run, short ball just outside off, Smith pulls and fails to connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mir Hamza to Haddin, 1 run, very full outside off, Haddin opens the blade to run it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mir Hamza to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, outside off, Smith seeks to drive but gets an inside edge to short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mir Hamza to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, Slightly short and Smith picks the length early - Swivels and rolls his wrists on the pull, sped away to the deep square fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mir Hamza to Haddin, 1 run, well played Brad Haddin! <b>Fifty</b> for him. Just taps this flat delivery to the off-side and sets off for a quick single. Hamza looks to effect a direct hit at the bowler's end but misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Dwayne Smith, no run, another one dug in short and yet again Smith is hit on the helmet, but not before he got an inside edge on the pull. Shares a wry smile with the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Dwayne Smith, no run, this time Smith decides to sit under a pacy bouncer]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Dwayne Smith, leg byes, 2 runs, off-speed delivery on the stumps, Smith fails to tickle and it runs off the pads towards fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Dwayne Smith, no run, baaaaang! Smith is pinged on the helmet. A lifter hurried into Smith who was trying to pull, gets into a bit of tangle as he was beaten for pace. Hit on the helmet and the bowler puts his hand up to convey his apology]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Haddin, 1 run, off-cutter on off, Haddin taps it to cover for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, backs away and goes hard on the cut, takes the under-edge and rolls towards the keeper]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sohail Khan [2.0-0-18-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mir Hamza to Haddin, no run, looks to muscle this length ball to the cow corner fence but the ball shapes away late and beats him on the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mir Hamza to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, steered to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mir Hamza to Haddin, 1 run, back of a length in the outside off channel, Haddin late-cuts to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mir Hamza to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, shortish around middle, Smith clips it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mir Hamza to Haddin, 1 run, at the hip, tucked to short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mir Hamza to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, back of a length wide of off, glided down to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mir Hamza, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Usama Mir to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, short ball and sat up nicely for Smith who half-turns and pulls through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Usama Mir to Haddin, 1 run, on the stumps, swiped to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Usama Mir to Haddin, <b>SIX</b>, Haddin jumps out and smites this quicker delivery over the long-on fence. EASY PEASY for Haddin!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Usama Mir to Haddin, <b>FOUR</b>, well executed! Steps out, gets to the pitch of this flighted delivery and lifts the drive over a leaping cover, neatly done!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Usama Mir to Haddin, no run, advances and pushes a flat delivery back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Usama Mir to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, quicker on the stumps, clipped away to square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Usama Mir [1.0-0-7-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Haddin, no run, fullish on off, pushed back]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, the slower stuff continues and Smith drops this in front of cover to squeeze a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, slower back of a length delivery outside off, clever stuff from Dwayne Smith who opens the bat face and angles it to the right of short third man. Smart cricket this!]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, off-cutter outside off, full in length and Smith does what he's well known for. Keeps his head still and bullets a drive through cover, no point chasing that lads!]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Haddin, 1 run, another slower short delivery outside off but this time Haddin finds short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bopara to Haddin, <b>FOUR</b>, Bopara trundles in and bowls a slower delivery around fifth stump channel, Hadds welcomes him by playing it with soft hands and sterring it to the thirf man boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravi Bopara, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Haddin, 1 run, offers width outside off and Haddin is content with a single through cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Haddin, <b>SIX</b>, PLEASE REFER TO 8.2. THE ONLY DIFFERENCE WAS Haddin GOT MUCH CLOSER TO THE PITCH OF THE BALL THIS TIME]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, <b>run-out chanced missed.</b> Smith chops this to cover and calls his partner through for a quick single. Haddin was a bit late to take off and Bopara helps his cause by sending a poor throw. An accurate throw and Haddin would have been on his bike...]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Haddin, 3 runs, short and plenty of room on offer, Haddin pounces on it as he rocks back and cuts to deep point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Haddin, <b>SIX</b>, that's Brad Haddin for you. Did any of you see him bashing Mohammad Shami for a first ball six at SCG in 2015 (In a Test match). Well! If you haven't, I would suggest to do so. Brilliant foot work from Hadds who jumps out and tonks a flatter delivery over the long-on fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, and there's the <b>fifty for Islamabad United.</b> Smith swipes one to fine leg and ticks the team's first milestone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Usama Mir to Haddin, no run, looped up full, Haddin drives hard and cover does well to stop a certain single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Usama Mir to Haddin, <b>FOUR</b>, nah, nah! Cannot bowl such stuff to Haddin. That's a candyfloss and Haddin would have smacked that in his dream as well. Dishes out a full toss and Haddin is quick on his feet to clobber that through cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Usama Mir to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, non-turning delivery outside off, Smith sends the cut past point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Usama Mir to Haddin, 1 run, full on middle and leg, wristed past mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Usama Mir to Haddin, no run, pitched around off and spun away, Haddin cuts but finds cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Usama Mir to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, full and a hint of width outside off, Smith muscles it down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Usama Mir, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Haddin, no run, advances and negates the spin on this tossed up delivery]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, allows the ball to spin away and then drives to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Dwayne Smith, no run, floated up just outside off, Smith blocks it back]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Haddin, 1 run, shortish outside off, Haddin chops it past point]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, full and straight, Smith sweeps behind square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Haddin, 1 run, floated up on middle, Haddin jumps out and loft-drives to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, shot! What should I say. Just the previous ball he made himself look like a student who doesn't know how to spell numbers and now he solves an algebra equation. Full ball on off- Hittable alright. But he still has to put that away, Smith sends a smashing drive through cover sans any feet movement. That's from Sehwag's textbook]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Dwayne Smith, no run, I've lost the count of number of balls Smith has been beaten outside off today. Length ball shaped in slightly, Smith flashes hard and misses by a country mile]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Dwayne Smith, no run, that's much better, bowls a stump-to-stump line delivery and Smith couldn't do much about it, blocked back]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Dwayne Smith, no run, another short one speared at an uncomfortable height, Smith hooks but could't get it past short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Dwayne Smith, <b>wide</b>, dug in short and slipping down leg, Smith lets it be]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Haddin, 1 run, steered down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, fullish around off, Smith nudges to the off-side and nabs a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Amir [2.0-0-6-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Haddin, no run, woof! How about that? That's an absolute bonzer from Imad Wasim. Pitched around middle and off and spun past a poking blade of Haddin. Just a hair's breadth distance from grazing the off-peg. Haddin looks absolutely miffed]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, another one that kept low outside off, Smith copes with the low bounce and eases a drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Dwayne Smith, no run]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Dwayne Smith, no run, dragged down and spun away just around the tramline, kept low too, should have been called a wide but the umpire has other ideas]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Dwayne Smith, <b>SIX</b>, whew! Smithy - You beauty. Such nonchalant stuff I must stay. Just stays solid inside the crease and smokes a flighted delivery over the long-on fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Dwayne Smith, no run, full and wide, driven to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Imad Wasim, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Haddin, <b>FOUR</b>, lucky boundary that! Haddin makes room to a good length delivery - Was a tad late in doing so. As a result he was cramped for room and ends up playing a nothing shot, just pushes at it tamely and the inside edge does the rest - Raced away to the fine leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, shortish, just outside off, Smith chops it behind square on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Haddin, 1 run, and straightaway Haddin tries to confuse the bowler, with his nimble feet movement, shuffles and forces Sohail Khan to alter his length and when it's kept short Haddin cuts late to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Brad Haddin, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Sharjeel Khan, <b>out</b> Caught by Iftikhar Ahmed!! There's the first wicket and Sohail Khan is jubilant. Serves up a full delivery on the pads - Nearly a half-volley. The ball held on the pitch a little and Sharjeel was committed to the flick shot. Sends it off the bottom half and mid-wicket leaps to clasp a simple chance. <b>Sharjeel Khan c Iftikhar Ahmed b Sohail Khan 9(9) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sohail Khan to Sharjeel Khan, <b>THAT'S OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Sharjeel Khan, no run, ooh! This swung back in sharply, a yorker on the stumps and dug out towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Sharjeel Khan, <b>FOUR</b>, don't bowl there to Sharjeel Khan. He will keep picking you all day. Full on the pads and Sharjeel says "Thank you" and twirls his wrists over the flick, a couple of bounces and into the fine leg fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Dwayne Smith, no run, hint of swing again, darted back in, full length, Smith drives and finds extra cover to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Sharjeel Khan, 1 run, back of a length on and around off, Sharjeel rises on his toes and whips square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Sharjeel Khan, no run, scissored back in from a length, blocked back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Sharjeel Khan, no run, curled in from a good length, Sharjeel wrists it gently in front of mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Sharjeel Khan, <b>FOUR</b>, ah, shot! Hops inside the crease and cuts this length delivery past a diving backward point, sublime timing!]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Sharjeel Khan, no run, good length delivery came in with the angle, Sharjeel had no room to work with, ended up pushing it back towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Dwayne Smith, no run, and again! Smith looks to dispatch this over cover but the outswing beats his bashing blade]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, streaky but a boundary nonetheless! Shortish and well wide of off, Smith slogs and the inside edge evades a diving keeper to his left]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Dwayne Smith, <b>FOUR</b>, finally he connects with one! No feet whatsoever - Stand and deliver stuff - Sees width and flays it over point for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Dwayne Smith, no run, a swing and a miss! Smith is struggling to lay bat on ball here. Manufactures some room and skates down the track, the ball nips away sharply and beats him on the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Dwayne Smith, no run, in the outside off channel, Smith's firm drive is intercepted at extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail Khan to Dwayne Smith, no run, whoa! Brilliant start from the Karachi bowlers. They aren't offering any freebies to the batsmen. This was an away swinger landed on perfect line and line - Good length outside off, Smith has a big woosh and could only manage thin air]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sohail Khan, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Sharjeel Khan, no run, drags his length back and provides a bit of width, Sharjeel looks to drive but under-edges it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Dwayne Smith, 1 run, Amir keeps it full again, Smith goes with hard hands - Looks to drive but could only manage an inside edge which dribbles away to short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Dwayne Smith, no run, pacy full delivery around fifth stump channel, Smith dabs to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Dwayne Smith, no run, width outside off, Smith push-drives to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Dwayne Smith, no run, another jaffa! Swung back in sharply and raps Smith on the pads as he fails to connect with the flick, no real appeal as the ball hit him high on the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Amir to Dwayne Smith, no run, peach! Length delivery that swung back in around off and Smith had no clue about that, looks to push that tentatively and is beaten neck and crop, the ball sneaks through the bat-pad gate]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Smith and Sharjeel Khan are at the crease. Dwayne Smith is on strike. Amir will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back! Mohammad Amir will start the proceedings...]]></line><line><![CDATA[The innings really never got going. Resembled your lazy weekend after a hectic work week. The first over was a run-drought maiden and the first run came off the 9th ball. Malik, sans his captaincy tiara, registered a 4-ball duck to let the scores read 29/3. Bopara resisted with run-a-ball 37 but then Sami sent him back, and ten Doeschate in the same over to all but broom Karachi away. He ended up with surreal figures of <b>4-0-8-5</b> and Russell chipped in with his 2 wickets and the perennial acrobatics to hold Karachi to a paltry 111. Not predicting an easy chase; that's not been the flavour of the season here in Dubai. Expect a tough battle for that opportunity to lock horns with Peshawar. Join us in a few minutes..]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Sohail Khan, <b>out</b> Caught by Khalid Latif!! This was coming. A wicket last ball sums up the miseries. <b>Karachi end up on a miserly Nelson.</b> Length ball, Sohail Khan dug deep into his crease and aimed a tonk over mid-wicket. Mistimed and it finds the fielder in the deep. <b>Sohail Khan c Khalid Latif b A Russell 7(10)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A Russell to Sohail Khan, <b>THAT'S OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Sohail Khan, no run,]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Amir, leg byes, 1 run, that's been taken by Haddin behind - with a dive to his left but it's off the pad. All happening there. The ball cut back in at Amir who was flummoxed in his crease-bound turn. Didn't connect, the ball took the pad and Haddin pouched it. But for some wood on that..]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Amir, no run, short ball bowled at a much slower pace than Amir expected. Pulls but is early into the shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Amir, <b>FOUR</b>, a low full toss and Amir manages to get behind this. Lets out a drive that pierces the extra cover position]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Amir, no run, robbed of all pace. Slower delivery outside off, Amir swings across the line but <b>misses</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Last over...how much more can they add?]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sohail Khan, leg byes, <b>FOUR</b>, hurls a straight one at the pads, Sohail Khan shuffles around and misses. Is rapped on the pads, invites an appeal that's turned down. Ball pads away to evade Haddin and scampers to the fine leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Amir, 1 run, length ball angled across, Amir opens the face of the bat and guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sohail Khan, 1 run, such a downer. Length ball is pushed into the off-side and he runs through]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Amir, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Usama Mir, <b>out</b> Caught by A Russell!! <b>Sami has a five-for</b>! What a day he has picked out! Short ball, Usama Mir mistimes the pull and Russell runs across from long-on to pouch that. A golden duck and <b>Sami is on a hat-trick</b>. <b>Usama Mir c A Russell b Sami 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sami to Usama Mir, <b>THAT'S OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Usama Mir, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Imad Wasim, <b>out</b> Caught by Asif Ali!! And Sammy grabs his fourth of the day to help himself to his <b>100th T20 wicket</b>. Short, wide and it's been helped to backward point with a cut! Connected it well but times it straight to the man hawking that fielding position. <b>Imad Wasim c Asif Ali b Sami 6(4) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sami to Imad Wasim, <b>THAT'S OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sohail Khan, 1 run, shortish outside off, Sohail moves around in his crease, reaches out to this ball and tucks it into the leg-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[This innings has been such a struggle for Karachi...2 more overs to go]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Imad Wasim, <b>FOUR</b>, full and that's been bulleted away. Uses his wrists and twirls the ball through cow corner]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Sohail Khan, 1 run, pushes the ball upto the batsman and Sohail Khan lifts it towards long-off for a joggy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Sohail Khan, 2 runs, compensates this time with a more convincing pull. Russell bangs this one again, Sohail Khan connects the pull and gets it to the man at deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Sohail Khan, no run, pulls and doesn't connect! Goes swiveling and the ball eagles over his bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Imad Wasim, 1 run, this one's tucked off the pads to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Sohail Khan, 1 run, back of a length and outside off, Sohail Khan steers it to backward point and completes an urgent single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell [2.0-0-8-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sohail Khan, 1 run, length and around off, Sohail Khan works it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sohail Khan, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to ten Doeschate, <b>out</b> Caught by Haddin!! This perhaps is the sickening blow that will send shudders down Karachi's spine. Second in the over. Falls like his ex-captain did. Looks to mow it across the line, ekes out an under-edge and Haddin grabs it convincingly. <b>ten Doeschate c Haddin b Sami 16(23)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sami to ten Doeschate, <b>THAT'S OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Imad Wasim, 1 run, length just outside off, he opens his blade a touch and guides the ball to backward point to get off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Imad Wasim, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Bopara, <b>out</b> Caught by Dwayne Smith!! After all the no-ball check and the lurking anti-climax, Bopara is gone. Sami foxes him with a slower ball that's banged in, Bopara stands tall and just pulls. Didn't read and resultingly wait for the ball to arrive, let out the pull and Smith ran in at deep mid-wicket and dived in front to pouch a good, low catch. <b>Bopara c Dwayne Smith b Sami 37(36) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sami to Bopara, <b>THAT'S OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to ten Doeschate, 1 run, good length delivery outside off, ten Doeschate stays his ground and reaches out for a pushy single to the sweeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to ten Doeschate, no run, pacy, pacy ball. Hurls lot of his shoulder into this short ball, ten Doeschate takes it on with a pull but fails to connect. Sees the ball whistle over his swivel]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Sami [2.0-0-2-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Bopara, 2 runs, this was close! The shortish delivery wasn angled in, Bopara pulls it awkwardly and uppishly. Just beyond the reach of short mid-wicket and it runs away for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to ten Doeschate, 1 run, short and wide, ten Doeschate has enough time to cut it in front of square, straight to deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Bopara, byes, 1 run, this was cleverly done. Bopara had his dancing shoes on. Came down, Irfan cowled it slow and Bopara was befuddled. Fails to connect and Haddin fails to collect it cleanly behind]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Bopara, no run, there was an iota of width on this and Bopara had connected the cut well. Just couldn't place it and found point]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to ten Doeschate, 1 run, bangs this in. No venom but ten Doeschate mistimes the pull to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Bopara, 1 run, starts by dishing out a full toss, Bopara executes a tap-and-run to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Irfan [3.0-1-19-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Irfan will start from round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to ten Doeschate, 2 runs, on the pads, ten Doeschate stays put, twirls his wrists and works the ball to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Bopara, 1 run, dances down the track and works this length ball through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to ten Doeschate, 1 run, some width, ten Doeschate mistimes the cut and chops it towards point...wide enough to get a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Bopara, 1 run, closer to the batsman and Bopara flogs it straight down the ground for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Bopara, 2 runs, speared down the leg-side, Bopara turns and ticks it away to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dwayne Smith to Bopara, no run, off-pace outside off, Bopara bunts it back to Dwayne Smith]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Dwayne Smith, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imran Khalid to ten Doeschate, no run, comes down the track but the delivery doesn't turn, cramps him and ten Doeschate can only defend it]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imran Khalid to ten Doeschate, 2 runs, overpitched, ten Doeschate drive-defends it through cover and collects a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imran Khalid to Bopara, 1 run, manufactures room but then works the ball into the leg-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imran Khalid to Bopara, <b>SIX</b>, there's the UFO. There's the Haley's comet. There's the SIX! Makes room outside off, protracts his hands and clouts this ball over long-off. Good enough connection to let it sail over]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imran Khalid to ten Doeschate, 1 run, walks down the pitch and eases this arm-ball in front of mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imran Khalid to Bopara, 1 run, this is on the pads and it's been milked to long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to ten Doeschate, 2 runs, dragged down outside off, he stands tall and flat-bats it to long-off for an easy couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to ten Doeschate, 2 runs, kind of overpitched, ten Doeschate manages to connect the sweep and gets it to fine leg for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to Bopara, 1 run, bends inside his crease and whips the ball through square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to ten Doeschate, leg byes, 1 run, shimmies down to wrist the ball away, misses and the ball rolls into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to Bopara, 1 run, spots the google early, waits for it to turn and then helps it to mid-wicket for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to Bopara, 2 runs, pushed through on middle, Bopara clips it off his pads to deep square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imran Khalid to ten Doeschate, no run, wanted to help this leg-side delivery with a sweep. Missed it altogether and the ball takes the body en route to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imran Khalid to Bopara, 1 run, flatter outside off, Bopara drives to long-off and sets off]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imran Khalid to Bopara, 2 runs, gets across and drives this flighted delivery through cover. Pushes for the second and makes it back easily in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imran Khalid to Bopara, no run, gets this to pitch wide of off, Bopara gets behind and defends it back]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imran Khalid to Bopara, no run, goes with the angle and Bopara bunts it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imran Khalid to Bopara, 2 runs, pushed through just outside off, Bopara drives it down the ground for a brace]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to ten Doeschate, no run, flighted outside off, ten Doeschate shuffles to get behind it. Ball stays a touch low than anticipated and ten Doeschate defends it down off the bottom-edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to ten Doeschate, <b>wide</b>, fired down the leg-side, signalled a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to Bopara, 1 run, stoops and brooms this leg-stumpish delivery to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to ten Doeschate, 1 run, this turned a little. Not many have tonight and not many have been intended either. Guides it with the turn to backward point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to ten Doeschate, no run, reads this google arrowing in. Gets forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to ten Doeschate, no run, works this one around his pads and to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to Bopara, 1 run, fired in on the pads, Bopara slides bacl and tucks it to backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imran Khalid to Bopara, 1 run, easy peasy. Veering dowm, Bopara tucks it to deep mid wicket and retains the strike with that run]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imran Khalid to Bopara, no run, another one to the cover fielder. Tossed up, shorter too and could have been pulled. But Bopara pushes it to his favourite fielder in the off-side ring]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imran Khalid to Bopara, no run, overpitched and it's driven only as far as cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imran Khalid to ten Doeschate, 1 run, drifts one onto the pads and ten Doeschate tucks it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imran Khalid to ten Doeschate, no run, compensates with a fuller klength and ten Doeschate meets with with a defensive straight bat again]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imran Khalid to ten Doeschate, no run, drags one down for a warm-up delivery, ten Doeschate defends it solidly]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Imran Khalid, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to Bopara, 2 runs, on a length, Bopara kneels to sweep and collects a brace to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to ten Doeschate, 1 run, knee-high full toss, ten Doeschate shuffles across to get behind this ball on leg-stump and punches it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to ten Doeschate, no run, flat and full on middle and leg, Doeschate works it round the corner]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to Bopara, 1 run, ideal line and length to sweep and Bopara obliges with a single to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ryan ten Doeschate, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to Iftikhar Ahmed, <b>out</b> Caught by A Russell!! Dragged down and Iftikhar Ahmed pulls. Couldn't wood it as well as he would have liked, mistimed towards cow corner and Russell wheels to his right from long-on and snaffles it. <b>Iftikhar Ahmed c A Russell b Badree 8(14) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Badree to Iftikhar Ahmed, <b>THAT'S OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to Iftikhar Ahmed, no run, flat and quick within the stumps, Ahmed works it into the leg-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Iftikhar Ahmed, 1 run, splayed into the pads, Ahmed helps it with a clipped single to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Iftikhar Ahmed, no run, overpitched and Ahmed drills it straight back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Bopara, 1 run, short delivery and Bopara pulls it through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Iftikhar Ahmed, 1 run, good yorker. Ahmed jams his bat into the ground, ekes out an inside edge that rolls towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Bopara, 1 run, fullish ball screaming to be driven and Bopara obliges by placing it through cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Bopara, no run, short of length delivery armoured with an angle in, Bopara nudges it into the leg-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell [1.0-0-4-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to Iftikhar Ahmed, no run, fires it full and straight, Ahmed pats it back]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to Iftikhar Ahmed, no run, quick delivery banged in wide of off, Ahmed flashes the cut but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to Bopara, 1 run, fuller length delivery outside off, Bopara leans into a drive that goes as far as cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to Bopara, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four!</b> Spotted the width and went really hard on the cut. Got a thickish edge that runs away wide of the lone slipper who reaches out to his right one-handed but to no avail]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to Bopara, no run,]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Badree to Iftikhar Ahmed, 1 run, googly that's dragged down, Ahmed fails to read it and is rapped on the pads]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Samuel Badree, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Bopara, no run, shuffles inside his crease and Bopara follows him. Defended in front of gully with an open blade]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Bopara, no run, fullish and straight, Bopara shows the full face of the bat and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Bopara, no run, he has to be patient. Doesn't want to step in every Malik shoe. Length ball outside off and Bopara pats it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ravi Bopara, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Shoaib Malik, <b>out</b> Caught by Haddin!! And post captaincy, <b>Malik has been duck'd</b>. Goes for nought. Attempts the big slog across the line. The ball was on short of length, Malik makes room and swings his bat across. Gets a bottom edge and it travels at a quilt-comfortable height to Haddin behind. <b>Shoaib Malik c Haddin b Irfan 0(4)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Irfan to Shoaib Malik, <b>THAT'S OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Shoaib Malik, no run, that's a busy area at the moment. Another steered away single to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Iftikhar Ahmed, 1 run, width outside off and Ahmed guides it down to third man for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Irfan [2.0-1-18-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Shoaib Malik, no run, there's movement here. Scissors in from a fuller length and Malik ekes out an inside-edge onto his pad in defence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Shoaib Malik, no run, short of length delivery, Malik opens the face of the bat and blocks it behind point]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shoaib Malik, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Simmons, <b>out</b> Caught&Bowled!! What a horror! If wickets are to fall to these deliveries, I wouldn't mind turning my arm over. High, high full toss and Simmons decides to pat it back. Uppish and Russell protracts his hands a little to his right over his head and gobbles it up. <b>Simmons c and b A Russell 19(18) [4s-3 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A Russell to Simmons, <b>THAT'S OUT!!</b> Caught&Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Iftikhar Ahmed, leg byes, 1 run, another one. Fired onto the pads, Ahmed misses and is struck on the pads. Ball rolls away and the duo cross over]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Iftikhar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, short and this looked pretty. Stood tall and murdered it over mid-wicket. Sped away]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Russell to Simmons, leg byes, 1 run, quick and speared into the pads, Simmons misses and the ball rolls off the pads to give Simmons a leg bye]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Andre Russell, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kaushik</b>, who's at the ground, tells me that the stadium is only about 25% occupied. A certain downer after yesterday's full house. He even reasons out the poor attendance: the performance of these teams in the league stages and the lack of a showstopper in Afridi]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Iftikhar Ahmed, no run, another one past the outside edge. People who walked in expecting a boundary shower will be disappointed but I am not. Ahmed let out a tentative drive to this full ball and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Simmons, 1 run, some width outside off is digested away with a steered single to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Iftikhar Ahmed, leg byes, 1 run, loud, loud appeal but the impact was outside the leg-stump and it would have gone down too. Pacy delivery that raps him on the pad after Ahmed fails to work it away]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Iftikhar Ahmed, no run, this length ball holds its line outside off and whistles past Ahmed's bat. What a welcome!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Iftikhar Ahmed, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Wessels, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Here's the first wicket. With Simmons going hammer-and-tongs, Wessels had to try too. Goes for the mighty slog sweep but missed the ball completely! Ball sneaks through with the angle and took down leg-stump's throat. <b>Wessels b Sami 1(5)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sami to Wessels, <b>THAT'S OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Wessels, no run, that looked cramped. Wessels was expecting width and he gets a ball that seams back in. Wessels readjusts and tapely pats it into the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, finally this over makes up for all the run scarcity in the first over. Pitched up, Simmons mostly stays put and bullets the drive through covers]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Simmons, no run, full and straight, Simmons sanely pats it back to Irfan]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Simmons, <b>SIX</b>, this one's tonked! Audacious. Absolutely smoked. Comes dowm the track while making room and flat-bats it. With such brute force that it sails over long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, this one's off the middle. Short ball sitting up pretty, Simmons stands up, swivels and hammers the pull over mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Simmons, no run, this is way too wide. Simmons had his soles glued, arches to reach out to this full ball but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Simmons, <b>FOUR</b>, up and over! Short with a hint of width, Simmons protracts his arms and fierces the cut over point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Simmons, leg byes, 1 run, this one ducks in and a shuffling Simmons fails to make the bat-ball connection. The ball takes the pads and rolls into the off-side for Simmons to steal a bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Simmons, no run, full and straight, he pushes it to mid-off but there's no run available]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Simmons, no run, this perhaps stayed low. Simmons wanted to defend this length ball down the ground and manages a bottom-edge back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Wessels, 1 run, yes. Stop the press. There's a run scored. The nervous activation energy has been breached. Veering into the batsman who kneels and helps it with a sweep to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Wessels, no run, gets one to nip in from a length. Whoever thought about this pitch being in moribund needs to think again. Wessels was hurried into his on-side defence and gets hit high on the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Wessels, no run, fullish and Wessels drive-defends it to the cover fielder]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Sami, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Simmons, no run, short ball into Simmons who lifts his bat high and dead-bats the ball down the pitch]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Simmons, no run, and again! Make that two-in-two. Similar delivery, Simmons this time half-deliberately plays inside the line and lets this out-ducker pass away]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Simmons, no run, ah, nearly! This was a ripper. Angled in on short of length, pitches and jags away to beat Simmons's tentative poke]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Simmons, no run, this rips up from a good length and Simmons allows it to bound behind to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Simmons, no run, drags his length back, Simmons lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Irfan to Simmons, no run, on a good length outside off, Simmons bunts it with an open blade to point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Simmons and Wessels are at the crease. Simmons is on strike. Irfan will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Islamabad United</b> (Playing XI): Dwayne Smith, Sharjeel Khan, Khalid Latif, Asif Ali, Misbah-ul-Haq(c), Brad Haddin(w), Andre Russell, Mohammad Irfan, Samuel Badree, Imran Khalid, Mohammad Sami]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Karachi Kings</b> (Playing XI): Lendl Simmons, Riki Wessels(w), Shoaib Malik, Ravi Bopara(c), Ryan ten Doeschate, Iftikhar Ahmed, Imad Wasim, Mohammad Amir, Usama Mir, Sohail Khan, Mir Hamza]]></line><line><![CDATA[Captaincy is much like a doctorate degree; everyone yearns for a "Dr." prefix but few can survive through the MBBS toils. The game should begin or I will continue to hurl more such jokes/whatever at you. Five minutes to go..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Malik update</b>: He argues on air that he stepped down because of the team's performance and because he wanted to concentrate on his own game. He thinks someone else (Bopara eventually) can do the captaincy job better than him at this moment. Hmmm.]]></line><line><![CDATA[So, Misbah decides to chase. The dew, perhaps? A safer option and a luxury with the coin being your friend. Bopara, in stunning form, wouldn't mind a rein-free batting and anything around 150 should be competitive, given the tired Dubai strips and the nerve circus. <b>Russell, Khalid and Badree come in</b> and the big news is that <b>Saeed Ajmal has been left out</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Islamabad United have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Current scenario</b>: Quetta Gladiators are through to the final. Despite yesterday's defeat, Peshawar Zalmi will get another chance. They will fight it out with today's winner (Islamabad United or Karachi Kings) for the second finalist's berth. This new elimination-qualification system is radical; gives the league toppers due rewards and in a way, makes sure that the best two teams wrestle it out in the finale.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Karachi Kings, with six beatings in the tournament, haven't put up their best cricket cloak yet. Courtesy Lahore Qalanders' feats, they are now into the playoffs and will look to compensate and move over from the mid-tournament captaincy saga. Islamabad have been better overall and with Russell likely to be fit and available, they will fancy their chances. Misbah-ul-Haque has been cunning with his team and it will be interesting to see him in contrast to a captain who's as English as him in his tactics.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Hello and welcome to another potential classic. Quetta put on its 1-run sneakers and tip-toed ahead of Peshawar yesterday. Defending 133 and eventually 8 runs in the last over, Aizaz Cheema conceded a boundary before roaring back with two wickets to pull off a choking win. But for the teams, the venue and the hunger to win mirror yesterday. Malik's men, now Bopara's because of the former stepping down, will take on Misbah-ul-Haq's serene army in the second of the play-offs today.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Karachi Kings</b> (From): Nauman Anwar, Lendl Simmons, Shoaib Malik, Ravi Bopara(c), Ryan ten Doeschate, Riki Wessels(w), Imad Wasim, Sohail Tanvir, Mohammad Amir, Sohail Khan, Bilawal Bhatti, Iftikhar Ahmed, Saifullah Bangash, Shahzaib Hasan, Mir Hamza, Usama Mir, Owais Shah]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Islamabad United</b> (From): Sharjeel Khan, Dwayne Smith, Brad Haddin(w), Misbah-ul-Haq(c), Andre Russell, Khalid Latif, Imran Khalid, Ashar Zaidi, Azhar Mahmood, Mohammad Sami, Mohammad Irfan, Amad Butt, Samuel Badree, Kamran Ghulam, Saeed Ajmal, Babar Azam, Umar Amin, Rumman Raees, Hussain Talat, Umar Siddiq, Asif Ali]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>111</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>9</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Karachi Kings">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>599</playerid>
					<name>Lendl Simmons</name>
					<batsman-name>L Simmons</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Simmons</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>19</runs>
					<balls>18</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>A Russell</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7736</bowlerId>
						<fielder>A Russell</fielder>
						<fielderId>7736</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7987</playerid>
					<name>Riki Wessels</name>
					<batsman-name>Riki Wessels</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Wessels</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>M Sami</bowler>
					<bowlerId>31</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10799</playerid>
					<name>Iftikhar Ahmed</name>
					<batsman-name>Iftikhar Ahmed</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Iftikhar Ahmed</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>8</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Badree</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1609</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Andre Russell</fielder>
						<fielderId>7736</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>33</playerid>
					<name>Shoaib Malik</name>
					<batsman-name>S Malik</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shoaib Malik</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Irfan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7621</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Brad Haddin</fielder>
						<fielderId>159</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>571</playerid>
					<name>Ravi Bopara</name>
					<batsman-name>R Bopara</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bopara</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>37</runs>
					<balls>36</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Sami</bowler>
					<bowlerId>31</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Dwayne Smith</fielder>
						<fielderId>255</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>640</playerid>
					<name>Ryan ten Doeschate</name>
					<batsman-name>ten Doeschate</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>ten Doeschate</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>16</runs>
					<balls>23</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Sami</bowler>
					<bowlerId>31</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Brad Haddin</fielder>
						<fielderId>159</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10408</playerid>
					<name>Imad Wasim</name>
					<batsman-name>Imad Wasim</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Imad Wasim</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Sami</bowler>
					<bowlerId>31</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Asif Ali</fielder>
						<fielderId>9565</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1120</playerid>
					<name>Sohail Khan</name>
					<batsman-name>S Khan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sohail Khan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>7</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>A Russell</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7736</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Khalid Latif</fielder>
						<fielderId>860</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>11318</playerid>
					<name>Usama Mir</name>
					<batsman-name>Usama Mir</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Usama Mir</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Sami</bowler>
					<bowlerId>31</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Andre Russell</fielder>
						<fielderId>7736</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1917</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Amir</name>
					<batsman-name>M Amir</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Amir</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>5</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8366</playerid>
					<name>Mir Hamza</name>
					<batsman-name>Mir Hamza</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mir Hamza</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7987</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>20</runs>
				<overs>3.2</overs>
				<batsman>Riki Wessels</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Riki Wessels</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>599</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>28</runs>
				<overs>4.4</overs>
				<batsman>Lendl Simmons</batsman>
				<batsman-name>L Simmons</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>33</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>29</runs>
				<overs>5.3</overs>
				<batsman>Shoaib Malik</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Malik</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>10799</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>39</runs>
				<overs>8.2</overs>
				<batsman>Iftikhar Ahmed</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Iftikhar Ahmed</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>571</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>88</runs>
				<overs>16.3</overs>
				<batsman>Ravi Bopara</batsman>
				<batsman-name>R Bopara</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>640</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>89</runs>
				<overs>16.5</overs>
				<batsman>Ryan ten Doeschate</batsman>
				<batsman-name>ten Doeschate</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>10408</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>100</runs>
				<overs>18.2</overs>
				<batsman>Imad Wasim</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Imad Wasim</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>11318</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>100</runs>
				<overs>18.3</overs>
				<batsman>Usama Mir</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Usama Mir</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1120</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>111</runs>
				<overs>19.6</overs>
				<batsman>Sohail Khan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Khan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>1</byes>
			<wides>1</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>10</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>12</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Islamabad United">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7621</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Irfan</name>
					<bowler-name>Irfan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Irfan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>24</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>31</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Sami</name>
					<bowler-name>M Sami</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sami</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>8</runsoff>
					<wickets>5</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7736</playerid>
					<name>Andre Russell</name>
					<bowler-name>A Russell</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>A Russell</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>21</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1609</playerid>
					<name>Samuel Badree</name>
					<bowler-name>Badree</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Badree</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>22</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9561</playerid>
					<name>Imran Khalid</name>
					<bowler-name>Imran Khalid</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Imran Khalid</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>18</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<bowler-name>Dwayne Smith</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dwayne Smith</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>7</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9052</playerid>
					<name>Sharjeel Khan</name>
					<bowler-name>S Khan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sharjeel Khan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>860</playerid>
					<name>Khalid Latif</name>
					<bowler-name>K Latif</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Khalid Latif</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9565</playerid>
					<name>Asif Ali</name>
					<bowler-name>Asif Ali</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Asif Ali</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>274</playerid>
					<name>Misbah-ul-Haq</name>
					<bowler-name>Misbah</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Misbah</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>159</playerid>
					<name>Brad Haddin</name>
					<bowler-name>Haddin</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Haddin</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>115</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>1</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>14.2</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Islamabad United">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>255</playerid>
					<name>Dwayne Smith</name>
					<batsman-name>Dwayne Smith</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dwayne Smith</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>50</runs>
					<balls>48</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9052</playerid>
					<name>Sharjeel Khan</name>
					<batsman-name>S Khan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sharjeel Khan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>9</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>S Khan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1120</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Iftikhar Ahmed</fielder>
						<fielderId>10799</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>159</playerid>
					<name>Brad Haddin</name>
					<batsman-name>Haddin</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Haddin</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>52</runs>
					<balls>29</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>860</playerid>
					<name>Khalid Latif</name>
					<batsman-name>K Latif</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Khalid Latif</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9565</playerid>
					<name>Asif Ali</name>
					<batsman-name>Asif Ali</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Asif Ali</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>274</playerid>
					<name>Misbah-ul-Haq</name>
					<batsman-name>Misbah</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Misbah</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7736</playerid>
					<name>Andre Russell</name>
					<batsman-name>A Russell</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>A Russell</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7621</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Irfan</name>
					<batsman-name>Irfan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Irfan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1609</playerid>
					<name>Samuel Badree</name>
					<batsman-name>Badree</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Badree</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9561</playerid>
					<name>Imran Khalid</name>
					<batsman-name>Imran Khalid</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Imran Khalid</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>31</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Sami</name>
					<batsman-name>M Sami</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sami</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9052</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>18</runs>
				<overs>3.3</overs>
				<batsman>Sharjeel Khan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Khan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>1</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>3</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>4</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Karachi Kings">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1917</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Amir</name>
					<bowler-name>M Amir</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Amir</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>13</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1120</playerid>
					<name>Sohail Khan</name>
					<bowler-name>S Khan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sohail Khan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3.2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10408</playerid>
					<name>Imad Wasim</name>
					<bowler-name>Imad Wasim</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Imad Wasim</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>29</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>11318</playerid>
					<name>Usama Mir</name>
					<bowler-name>Usama Mir</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Usama Mir</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>20</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>571</playerid>
					<name>Ravi Bopara</name>
					<bowler-name>R Bopara</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bopara</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>14</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8366</playerid>
					<name>Mir Hamza</name>
					<bowler-name>Mir Hamza</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mir Hamza</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>11</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>599</playerid>
					<name>Lendl Simmons</name>
					<bowler-name>L Simmons</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Simmons</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7987</playerid>
					<name>Riki Wessels</name>
					<bowler-name>Riki Wessels</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Wessels</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>33</playerid>
					<name>Shoaib Malik</name>
					<bowler-name>S Malik</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shoaib Malik</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>640</playerid>
					<name>Ryan ten Doeschate</name>
					<bowler-name>ten Doeschate</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>ten Doeschate</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10799</playerid>
					<name>Iftikhar Ahmed</name>
					<bowler-name>Iftikhar Ahmed</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Iftikhar Ahmed</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



