<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14716" >
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>1st ODI</gameDesc>
		<series>Pakistan tour of Bangladesh, 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Bangladesh</home>
		<away>Pakistan</away>
		<teamsabbr>BAN vs PAK</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>BAN</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>PAK</awayabbr>
		<homeId>6</homeId>
		<awayId>3</awayId>
		<venue>Shere Bangla National Stadium, Dhaka</venue>
		<startdate>17 04 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>17 04 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Bangladesh</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Bangladesh won by 79 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Bangladesh</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>79</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Ruchira Palliyaguru</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Sharfuddoula</Name>
			<Country>Ban</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Nigel Llong</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Jeff Crowe</Name>
			<Country>NZ</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>08:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150417162314</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>Pak</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>Ban</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>250</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>10</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>45.2</batteamovers>
		<status>Bangladesh won by 79 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>8301</playerid>
			<name>Rahat Ali</name>
			<batsman-name>Rahat Ali</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Rahat Ali</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>1</runs>
			<balls-faced>1</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
			<batsman>
				<name />
				<runs />
				<balls-faced />
				<fours />
				<sixes />
			</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>544</playerid>
			<name>Shakib Al Hasan*</name>
			<bowler-name>Shakib</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Shakib</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>9.2</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>45</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1736</playerid>
			<name>Rubel Hossain</name>
			<bowler-name>Rubel</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Rubel</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>8</overs>
			<maidens>1</maidens>
			<runs>45</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>330</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>1053</playerid>
<name>Saeed Ajmal</name>
<player-runs>0</player-runs>
<player-balls>4</player-balls>
<runs>250</runs>
<wicket-nbr>10</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>544</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Shakib</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>6</wides>
			<noballs>1</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>9</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[2 2 1 . . 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 Wd 4 1 4 2 W <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 N . W . . W <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 W ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/BAN_PAK_2015/BAN_PAK_APR17/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[On behalf of <b>Mani</b> and my co-commentators, <b>Ramakrishnan</b> and <b>Pradeep</b>, this is <b>Sidhant Maheshwari</b>, signing off.]]></line><line><![CDATA[So, that brings us to the end of our coverage of this game. Bangladesh are 1-0 up in the series. Can they make it 2-0 on Sunday? Join us then to find out.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier in the day, Bangladesh posted their highest ODI total, thanks to brilliant hundreds from Tamim Iqbal and Mushfiqur Rahim. Their 178-run partnership for the third wicket was a delight to watch, with Rahim firing on all cylinders. In the end, a few good hits from Shakib and Sabbir helped Bangladesh post 329 on the board.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rizwan kept batting well from one end, dispatching the bad deliveries to the fence, while keeping out the good ones. However, he didn't get much support from the other end as wickets kept tumbling. In the end Pakistan were bowled out for 250, losing their <b>last 6 wickets for just 33 runs.</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bangladesh deserved this win. Even though Pakistan started off really well, putting together a 50-plus opening stand, Bangladesh picked up two wickets in quick succession to pull things back. Ali and Sohail then tried to consolidate, but Ali got out to Taskin in the 28th over. After that Rizwan and Sohail, both tried to up the ante, but Sohail too perished after reaching his fifty.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rahim:</b> 'I thought I was really lucky. I thought Tamim deserved it more than me (on winning the Man of the Match award). It is dedicated to my wife. The boys really did a great job. The preparation was really good. If someone fails, someone puts their hand up every time. This was a pressure match for us, but we are happy to win here. The bowlers did a great job as there was nothing for the bowlerson that pitch.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mushfiqur Rahim</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his <b>77-ball 106</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib:</b> 'I thought Tamim and Rahim batted really well. It was a good wicket to bat on, but we never thought that we can score that much. So credit goes to those two. We did well in the field too. All in all, it was a very good team performance. It was a great performance from the batting and bowling unit, it was really professional. Hopefully, we can keep playing like that. We now have the belief that we can win this series. They were hoping for a win and thanks to them for coming down here to support us. I just hope they support us when we don't perform that well too. ']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Azhar Ali:</b> 'We made some mistakes in the field. They played really well. We dropped some catches at the wrong time, but credit should go to the Bangladeshi batsmen. There are a few positives, especially Rizwan, who showed his class with the bat. We made some mistakes and hopefully, we can rectify them. As a bowling unit, we made some mistakes. We have only one day and we will try and fix it before the next game.']]></line><line><![CDATA[The players walk off the field. The Bangladeshis are delighted. They have beaten their opposition comprehensively today. <b>Bangaldesh have beaten Pakistan after 16 years</b>. This is <b>only their second win against Pakistan</b> in ODI history.]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Ajmal, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Ajmal has been given out lbw here. He reviews it and Hawk-Eye shows that the ball was hitting the stumps there. It was a flatter delivery on middle and leg, Ajmal looks to pull it through the on-side and misses. The ball hits the pad, the umpire raised his finger after the bowler appealed. Hawk-Eye showed that the ball was clipping the leg stump. The onfield decision stays and <b>Bangladesh win by 79 runs.</b> They go <b>1-0 up in the 3-match series</b>. <b>Ajmal lbw b Shakib 0(4)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shakib to Ajmal, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rahat Ali, 1 run, inside edges this flighted delivery towards square leg for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan [9.0-0-44-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rahat Ali, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Ajmal, <b>out</b> Junaid Khan Run Out!! Junaid has been run-out here. At least the umpire thinks so. It was a yorker outside off, Ajmal squeezes it out towards point and sets off, Junaid was out of his crease too. Junaid was looking to run back as Sabbin charges in from point, picks the ball and fires in a direct-hit at the non-striker's end. The third umpire took his time and decided that it is out as Junaid just about planted his bat when the bails had gone off. <b>Junaid Khan run out (S Rahman) 0(0)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rubel to Ajmal, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[The third umpire has been pressed into service for a run-out decision. Junaid probably put his bat inside the crease just in time to save himself there. Wait a minute! It looks closer than it appears. It is touch and go. He has been given out there and Junaid is not a happy man.]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Ajmal, no run,]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Ajmal, no run, bowls this very full and around off, Ajmal jams the drive out into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Junaid Khan, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rizwan, <b>out</b> Caught by Nasir Hossain!! Rizwan is gone and this will probably be the end of Pakistan's hopes of winning this game. He went down on his knee and went for the slog sweep on this occasion, gets a top-edge and Nasir Hossain runs to his right from deep square leg and takes a good catch. <b>Rizwan c Nasir Hossain b Rubel 67(58) [4s-8]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rubel to Rizwan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rizwan, no run, slower ball from Rubel, Rizwan goes across and tries to play the lap shot once again, the ball beats the bat and goes over the stumps as well. Good change of pace from Rubel]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rizwan, <b>no ball</b>, what was that? A beamer from Rubel that almost took Rizwan on its way, the batsman did well to get out of the way. The umpire gives an official warning for that as well. Rubel apologises to the batsman as it must have slipped out of his hand]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rizwan, <b>FOUR</b>, poor delivery from Rubel, it was a full toss well wide outside off, Rizwan drives it wide of mid-off and the ball rockets away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Saeed Ajmal, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Riaz, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Taskin has the last laugh as Riaz has been outfoxed here. It was a slower delivery from Taskin, Riaz backed away and went for the big slog, he was way too early into the shot and the ball beats his blade, crashes into the top of middle and leg stump. Taskin is jubilant after taking that wicket. <b>Riaz b Taskin Ahmed 8(12) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Taskin Ahmed to Riaz, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Riaz, 2 runs, slower delivery from Taskin, Riaz picks it up and over mid-wicket, the ball falls in no man's land and Riaz comes back for the second before the ball is hunted down]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Riaz, <b>FOUR</b>, full delivery just outside off, Riaz leans forward and goes for the expansive drive on the off-side, he gets an inside edge and the ball runs away to the fine leg fence, the fielder was inside the circle and had no chance of stopping that]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rizwan, 1 run, Taskin bowls this well outside off and Rizwan tries to be cheeky as he goes across and tries to play the lap sweep, he can't get it off the middle of the bat and the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rizwan, <b>FOUR</b>, low full toss on the stumps, Rizwan waits and smashes it over mid-wicket, the ball crashes into the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rizwan, <b>wide</b>, bumper from Taskin, Rizwan tries to hook, but can't connect. The umpire calls it a wide for height]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Riaz, 1 run, low full toss from Riaz, Riaz mistimes the drive to mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Taskin Ahmed [7.0-0-29-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Riaz, 1 run, punches this to the right of cover and sets off, the fielder runs to his right and doesn't pick the ball cleanly. Had he picked it cleanly, he could have fired the throw at the bowler's end as Riaz was struggling to make his ground. But he gets in as the throw never arrived]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Riaz, no run, it was the toe-crusher on leg stump, Riaz looks to clip it through the on-side and misses, the ball hits him right on the boot, the umpire raised his finger after giving it a though but <b>Hawk-Eye showed that the ball was going down</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riaz has been given out lbw. He decides to review it. Rubel's front foot foot is fine and the batsman didn't get any bat on that. Is the ball going down leg or is it hitting leg stump? Even if it's clipping, the onfield decision will stay. The Hawk-Eye is taking a lot of time for some reason. The Bangladeshi players wait and the decision is out. Hawk-Eye shows that the ball was going down leg and Riaz stays. Good review by him and Pakistan still have their review]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Riaz, no run, length delivery outside off, Riaz looks to drive and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rizwan, 1 run, guides this one to the right of third man, he was looking for the second there and was halfway down the track, but Riaz sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rizwan, 2 runs, Rizwan comes down the track and Rubel bangs it in short and outside off, he goes for the pull and gets a top-edge that goes high in the air, Sunny from mid-wicket runs to his right, puts in the dive, but the ball falls in short of him]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Rizwan, 2 runs, Rizwan goes down on one knee and sweeps this fullish delivery down towards fine leg, the batsmen take two before the ball is stopped after the deep backward square leg fielder runs to his right and stops the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Rizwan, 1 run, whips this flighted delivery down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Rizwan, no run, makes room and goes for a big slog sweep over the leg-side, but fails to lay bat on it. The ball hits him on the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Riaz, leg byes, 1 run, looks to tickle it fine, but fails to connect. The ball runs away fine off the pad and the batsmen run for a leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Riaz, no run, pushed through by Sunny, Riaz looks to work it towards the on-side and is hit on the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Rizwan, 1 run, Rizwan brings out the lap sweep, gets down on his knees and laps it very fine for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Rizwan, 2 runs, <b>fifty on debut for Rizwan!</b> A full toss on his pads, whipped away in front of straight mid-wicket for a couple of runs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Riaz, no run, tossed up outside off, Riaz leans forward and pushes it towards point, can't get the single away]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, 1 run, flatter on the stumps, Rizwan punches it towards deep mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Riaz, leg byes, 1 run, drifting in on the pads, Riaz was looking to work it through the on-side, he misses and the ball clips the pad and rolls away into the on-side, the batsmen sneak in a leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Riaz, no run, tossed up on off and middle, Riaz leans forward and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, 1 run, pushed through quicker on off and middle, Rizwan drops it in front of cover and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, no run, slower delivery outside off, Rizwan drives it towards point off the outside half of the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The batting powerplay yielded <b>35 runs</b> for Pakistan and they lost <b>2 wickets</b> in that period.]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Saad Nasim, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Nasim goes without even disturbing the scorers there. Sunny picks his second of the over and he punches the air in delight. It was the quicker one on the off stump, Nasim made room for the cut and the ball sneaks under his bat, crashes into the off stump. <b>Saad Nasim b A Sunny 0(4)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A Sunny to Saad Nasim, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Saad Nasim, no run, another dot and it was the arm ball drifting in, Nasim looks to drive and gets it off the inside half of the bat towards the on-side, mid-wicket runs across to his left and parries it towards mid-on, prevents the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Saad Nasim, no run, quicker and on middle and leg, Nasim drives it to the right of the bowler, who moves across to prevent the run]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Saad Nasim, no run, bowled quicker on off and middle, Nasim pushes at it off the front foot, gets an inside edge onto the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Saad Nasim, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Fawad Alam, <b>out</b> Caught by Soumya Sarkar!! Unlucky way to get out for Alam, but Sunny is delighted as he puts his dancing shoes on. Alam made room even before the ball was bowled and Sunny follows him, cramping him for room. Even though it was a full toss, Alam hits it straight to mid-on. Pakistan slip further and Bangladeshis are on top once again. <b>Fawad Alam c Soumya Sarkar b A Sunny 14(19) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A Sunny to Fawad Alam, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Rizwan, 1 run, fires this on middle and leg, Rizwan drives it down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Fawad Alam, 2 runs, floated up on middle, Alam goes slightly across and lofts it over mid-wicket, the fielder at long-on runs to his left, dives and parries the ball towards the fielder who was running to his right from deep mid-wicket, the batsmen can only manage two in the meantime]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Fawad Alam, no run, Shakib shortens his length after seeing Alam give the charge, Alam almost ended up yorking himself there and squeezes it out to the right of the bowler, can't get the single away]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, 1 run, quicker and on middle and leg, Rizwan jams it out to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Fawad Alam, 1 run, full toss on the pads, Alam hits it straight to mid-wicket and took off, Rizwan makes it easily at the striker's end as the fielder fired in the throw]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, 1 run, slows this one outside off, Rizwan pushes it towards cover-point, the batsmen pinch a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, <b>FOUR</b>, bowled fuller and on middle stump line, Rizwan had made his mind there as he goes down on one knee and slog sweeps it to the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Rizwan, 1 run, Rizwan pushes it down to mid-off for another single, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Fawad Alam, 1 run, Alam drives this fullish delivery to mid-off and sets off, the fielder runs in, picks the ball and fires in the throw at the non-striker's end. A direct-hit could have made things interesting and since the throw missed the stumps, Alam makes it in time]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Rizwan, 1 run, in the blockhole, Rizwan squeezes it out to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Rizwan, 2 runs, floated up outside off, Rizwan drives it wide of long-off and the batsmen come back for the second, the fielder fires in the throw at the bowler's end and had it been a little more accurate, <b>there was a chance of run-out</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Fawad Alam, 1 run, fuller and outside off, Alam drives it towards extra cover and sets off, the fielder has a shy at the bowler's end but Alam made his ground with ease there]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Fawad Alam, <b>FOUR</b>, to long on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Fawad Alam, <b>FOUR</b>, great shot from Alam, he comes down the track to this tossed up delivery on off and middle, he lofts it straight over the bowler's head and the ball crashes into the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Fawad Alam, 1 run, Alam goes across to this flighted delivery on off, he clips it towards mid-wicket and gets to the other end, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, 1 run, drifting on leg stump line, Rizwan nudges it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, no run, quicker through the air this time, Rizwan defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, <b>FOUR</b>, poor fielding from Taskin at short third man. It was bowled slightly short and wide outside off, Rizwan cuts it hard, Tasking was running to his right and overruns the ball, it runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, <b>FOUR</b>, drifting on the pads once again, Rizwan kneels down and slog sweeps it to the left of short fine leg, the ball runs away to the fence in no time, Shakib needs to get his line right]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, no run, bowls it down the leg-side, Rizwan goed down on one knee and sweeps it straight to short fine leg, he wanted the single there but Alam sends him back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan [6.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Rizwan, 1 run, comes down the track and takes this tossed up delivery on the full, driven down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Fawad Alam, 1 run, tossed up on middle and leg, clipped towards mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Fawad Alam, no run, flatter and outside off, Alam backs away and cuts it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Rizwan, 1 run, overpitching on middle, Rizwan drives it towards the bowler, who dives to his left, but makes a half stop. The batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away towards the mid-off region]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Fawad Alam, 1 run, goes across to this delivery pushed through with the angle from round the wicket on off, Alam pushes it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Rizwan, 1 run, full on middle, Rizwan pushes it uppishly past the non-striker for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Arafat Sunny [6.0-1-27-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>batting powerplay</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Rizwan, 1 run, Rizwan comes down the track and Mahmudullah drags his length back slightly. Almost beats Rizwan as well, but Rizwan gets a soft leading edge as he was looking to drive it down to long-on, the ball dribbles away to long-off and the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Rizwan, no run, in the blockhole this time, Rizwan digs it out to the right of the bowler, who runs across, dives and prevents the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Fawad Alam, 1 run, Mahmudullah bowls it flatter this time, Alam pulls it wide of long-on, but the fielder did well to prevent the batsmen from taking the second run there. Good effort in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Fawad Alam, no run, goes across this time to this flighted delivery on middle and clips it to the left of mid-wicket this time]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Fawad Alam, no run, pushed through on middle and leg, Alam pushes it to the right of mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mahmudullah [1.0-0-5-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Fawad Alam, 1 run, goes across this time and Taskin bowls it on the pads of the batsman. Not sure if the batsman got some bat on that as he was trying to glance it fine, but the ball rolls away towards fine leg off the pad, the batsmen cross over and Alam will keep the strike. May have got an inside edge on the pad there]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Fawad Alam, no run, back of a length delivery angled across off, Alam was probably trying to put the bowler off after backing away a touch, but Taskin did well to keep it just outside off. Alam punches it straight to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rizwan, 1 run, Taskin bowls it slightly wide outside off, Rizwan slaps the cut straight to the fielder at sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rizwan, no run, length delivery outside off, Rizwan puts his front foot forward and drives it towards short cover, who quickly moves across to his left and prevents the batsmen from taking any runs there]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rizwan, no run, full and just outside off, Rizwan comes forward and drills the drive back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rizwan, 2 runs, short and slightly wide outside off, Rizwan hops and cuts it to the left of backward point, who dives but can't stop the ball. The third man fielder runs to his right, stops the ball and the batsmen take two in the meantime]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Fawad Alam, no run, leans forward and defends this flighted delivery outside off]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Fawad Alam, no run, lbw appeal but the umpire is not interested! It was quicker and bowled around off, Alam was looking to clip it through the on-side after going across, he missed and the ball hit the pad, there was a huge appealm but the ball probably hit the pad outside the off stump line]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, 1 run, pushed through on middle stump line, Rizwan pushes it to the right of the bowler, who fielder after bending down and moving across to his right]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, no run, confusion in running, but no harm done in the end. It was floated up outside off, Rizwan pushes it to the right of cover-point, but the fielder was quick to run across to his right and prevents the single. Alam was out of his crease there, but makes it back in time]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, no run, quicker one on the stumps, Rizwan defends from the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, no run, floated up slightly wide outside off and gets it to spin away, Rizwan was on the front foot and was looking to drive, the extra bounce and turn takes the ball past the outside edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Fawad Alam, no run, angles this one away outside off, Alam defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Fawad Alam, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place for Alam]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sohail, <b>out</b> Caught by Mahmudullah!! Sohail departs after a well constructed fifty. Not a great time for the wicket to fall as Pakistan were looking to accelerate. It was banged in short and on middle stump line, Sohail goes for the pull after backing away and gets it high on the bat. Looks like the ball hurried onto him as he went for the pull, the ball was dropping in front of mid-on, who was charging forward and had to dive to complete the catch. Good effort from Mahmudullah to take that catch. <b>Sohail c Mahmudullah b Taskin Ahmed 51(64) [4s-4 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Taskin Ahmed to Sohail, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rizwan, 1 run, bowls this slightly wide outside off, Rizwan waits on the back foot, opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man to get off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rizwan, no run, short of a good length delivery just outside off, Rizwan hangs on the back foot and punches it to short cover, he set off for the single there but his partner sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rizwan, no run, short delivery outside off, Rizwan goes across and goes for the pull, the ball doesn't bounce much and goes past the bat, the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rizwan, no run, full delivery outside off, Rizwan drives but picks out short cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, no run, comes down the track and Shakib bowls it on his legs, Sohail squeezes it out towards short fine leg, he was looking for the single there, but it's not available]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, no run, clips this flighted delivery towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, 1 run, slower through the air and drifting in on off, Rizwan pushes at it off the front foot, the ball rolls away towards square leg off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, 1 run, comes down the track and drives this fullish delivery down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, no run, flatter and just outside off, Sohail backs away and looks to cut it, but the ball doesn't bounce as much as he expected and goes under his bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, 1 run, flatter and outside off, Rizwan goes back and punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan [4.0-0-19-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rizwan, 1 run, <b>in the air and safe!</b> It was a well directed short ball towards the batsman, who was hurried onto the pull. He goes for it and top-edged it high in the air, the bowler runs across towards the short mid-wicket region, but the ball falls in front of him. Rizwan is lucky to survive there as the ball landed in no man's land]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rizwan, no run, yorker on middle stump line, Rizwan squeezes out the drive to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sohail, 1 run, <b>Sohail gets to his fifty with this single</b>, it was a back of a length angling away outside off, Sohail waits inside the crease, opens the face of the bat and dabs it towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sohail, no run, bumper from Taskin, Sohail ducks under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rizwan, 1 run, full delivery outside off, it was slightly wide as well, Rizwan reaches to the pitch of the ball and drives it square of the wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sohail, 1 run, length delivery angled across off, Sohail opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Rizwan, 2 runs, fuller and on the stumps, Rizwan goes across and works it towards deep mid-wicket, deep square leg tidies up after running to his right and the batsmen take two in the meantime, <b>19 runs came off that over</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Rizwan, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>third consecutive boundary for Rizwan</b>, it was a length delivery on middle stump line, Rizwan clips it to the deep mid-wicket fence, deep square leg runs to his left but the ball beats him to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Rizwan, <b>FOUR</b>, back-to-back boundaries for Rizwan, it was short and slightly wide outside off, Rizwan cuts it hard, the fielder at backward point dives to his left but fails to get a hand on it. The ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Rizwan, <b>FOUR</b>, back of a length delivery outside off, Rizwan punches it off the back foot and gets it wide of mid-off, who dives to his left, but the ball beats him and crashes into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Sohail, 1 run, turns it towards mid-wicket and the batsmen cross over]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four!</b> That was mighty close to the keeper. It was full and outside off, Sohail gets lured into the drive and goes after it without much feet movement. The ball takes the outside edge and beats the keeper who was diving to his left, it was inches away from his gloves and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Abul Hasan [4.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rizwan, no run, full with a hint of shape back in from outside off, Rizwan leaves it for the keeper as the ball was never coming back enough to hit off]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rizwan, no run, full delivery outside off, Rizwan leans forward and drives it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place for the new man]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Rizwan, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Rizwan guides it down to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Rizwan, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Azhar Ali, <b>out</b> Caught by Rahim!! That's a big wicket. Captain Ali goes and Pakistan are three down now. It was a length delivery outside off, Ali tries to cut it very late there, he was cramped for room and also the length was not there for him to play that shot. He ends up edging it to the keeper, who takes a simple catch and throws the ball high in the air in delight. It's a big blow for Pakistan. This is also the <b>highest score by a Pakistani player on captaincy debut.</b> <b>Azhar Ali c Rahim b Taskin Ahmed 72(73) [4s-7]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Taskin Ahmed to Azhar Ali, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four!</b> It was a length ball outside off, Ali makes rooma and looks to go inside-out towards cover, the ball takes the outside edge and runs away to the right of the keeper and into the third man fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Azhar Ali, no run, back of a length delivery on the stumps, Ali comes down the track and slaps it straight towards short cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Taskin Ahmed [3.0-0-16-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Azhar Ali, 1 run, full and on leg, Sohail goes down on one knee and sweeps it hard to deep backward square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Sohail, 1 run, slower and loopy just outside off, Sohail waits inside the crease and turns it behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Sohail, no run, flatter and just outside off, Sohail stays back and punches it to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Azhar Ali, 1 run, Ali gives the charge this time and drives this fullish delivery on middle stump to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Sohail, 1 run, drifting on the pads, Ali clips it towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Azhar Ali, 1 run, flighted delivery on middle and leg from round the wicket, Ali drives it down to long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mahmudullah, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mahmudullah will chance his arm for the first time today]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, 1 run, Ali comes down the track and drives this tossed up delivery down to widish long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, 1 run, pushed through just outside off, Sohail goes deep in the crease and works it towards square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, <b>wide</b>, down the leg-side, Sohail leaves and the umpire exercises his arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, 1 run, bowls this slower and gets it to spin away around off, Ali pushes it towards backward point after opening the face of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, no run, flatter and just around off, Ali makes room and cuts it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, 1 run, on middle and leg, Sohail works it off his pads to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, no run, quicker and angling away on off, Sohail defends off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan [3.0-0-14-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Sohail, 1 run, short of length delivery on middle and leg, Sohail hops and tucks it away backward of square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, poor delivery from Hasan, it was a wide full toss outside off, Sohail goes after it and drives it past backward point, the ball hurries through the turf and crashes into the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Sohail, 2 runs, drifting on the pads this time, Sohail tucks it away behind square o the on-side, the fielder from deep square leg runs to his left and keeps the batsmen down to a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Sohail, no run, just short of a good length and angled across off, Sohail goes across and nudges it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Sohail, 2 runs, back of a length delivery outside off, Sohail guides it towards the squarish third man region, the batsmen take two before the third man fielder runs to his left and stops it]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Sohail, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Sohail pushes it to the right of the bowler and sets off, the bowler stretches across and stops the ball with his right hand. Sohail to rush back into his crease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sohail, 1 run, full and on the stumps, Sohail mistimes the punch past the bowler, mid-on moves to his right and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sohail, no run, another short delivery angling away outside off, Sohail goes for the big pull on the on-side, this time the extra bounce did him as the ball goes over his bat, Rahim applauds the effort ball from Rubel]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sohail, no run, bumper on the stumps, Sohail ducks under it and the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>delicate touch!</b> It was just short of a good length and angling away outside off, Sohail stays back, opens the face of the bat at the last moment and gets it to the left of Rahim, the ball runs away to the third man fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, 1 run, fuller delivery on off and middle, Ali works it to the right of mid-wicket, who dives to his right and makes half a stop, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away to his right]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, no run, indipper on off, Ali goes across and clips it to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Sohail, no run, Bangladesh have decided to take the review for a caught behind decision. The original decision is not out. The sound that caused the appeal there probably came as the bat hit the ground. Hasan's front foot is fine. The ball missed the bat there and it should be 'Not Out'. The umpire is taking his time and he decides in favour of the batsman. <b>Bangladesh lose their review!</b> Coming back to the ball, it was a yorker outside off, Sohail tries to squeeze it out and the ball goes past the outside edge, the sound the bowling team were appealing for came as the bat hit the ground. Sohail stays]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Sohail, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Sohail defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Azhar Ali, 1 run, opens the face of the bat and guides it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, <b>in the air but safe!</b> It was bowled slightly wide outside off, Ali makes slight room after giving the charge, he goes hard at it and ends up slicing it high. Luckily for him the ball falls in front of a backtracking backward point and third man also couldn't get around in time, the batsmen take a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Sohail, 1 run, back of a length delivery angled across off, Ali stays back and punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Azhar Ali, 1 run, goes across to this length delivery outside off, he works it to deep square leg for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sohail, no run, back of a length delivery angled across off, Sohail nudges it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sohail, no run, banged in short and on off, Sohail goes for the pull and doesn't time it well at all, Sohail pulls and luckily for him, the ball bounces in front of the mid-on fielder, who was running forward to try and take the catch there]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sohail, no run, another short delivery down the leg-side, the umpire through deems it a legal ball. Maybe, it was a wide as it was down the leg-side, but clearly the umpire doesn't think so]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sohail, no run, bumper from Rubel this time, Sohail leaves it for the keeper after ducking under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, 1 run, length delivery outside off, Ali leans forward and drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, short and slightly wide outside off, Ali cuts it in the gap between gully and backward point, the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Azhar Ali, 1 run, bowls this slightly wide outside off, Ali goes chasing after that and gets an outside edge that runs away towards third man, who fumbles a little, but the batsmen don't take the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Sohail, 1 run, back of a length delivery on middle and leg, Sohail nudges it down towards the short fine leg region for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Sohail, no run, shortish delivery outside off, Sohail chops it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Azhar Ali, 1 run, charges down the track to this back of a length delivery outside off, punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Sohail, 1 run, short and slightly wide outside off, Sohail opens the face of the bat and guides it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Azhar Ali, 1 run, short delivery just outside off, Ali rises with the bounce, gets on top of it and glides it down to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sohail, 2 runs, on the pads this time, Sohail flicks it behind square on the on-side, the batsmen take two before fine leg runs to his right and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, 1 run, <b>Ali reaches his fifty in his first ODI as captain</b>. It was angled in on off, Ali goes across and drops it in front of mid-on, the batsmen charge through for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, no run, short of length delivery on the stumps, Ali defends it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, no run, full delivery outside off, Ali drives it towards point and can't beat the fielder there]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sohail, 1 run, angling away outside off, Sohail waits on the back foot and guides it down to third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, 1 run, full delivery on the stumps, Ali drives it off the inside half of the bat to the right of mid-on, the single brings up the team <b>100</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rubel Hossain [3.0-1-18-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Azhar Ali, 1 run, back of a length delivery angling in on off, Sohail waits on it, opens the face of the bat and guides it towards the squarish third man region, the fielder from third man runs to his right and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Sohail, 1 run, slightly back of a length and outside off, Sohail waits on the back foot, opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Sohail, no run, short of length delivery on off, Sohail defends it off the back foot, he was looking for the single there but it's not there]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Azhar Ali, 1 run, comes down the track to this short of length delivery outside off, he punches it towards sweeper cover and gets off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Azhar Ali, no run, back of a length delivery angling in on off, Ali turns it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Abul Hasan to Sohail, 1 run, back of a length delivery angled across off, Sohail looks to fend it away after jumping up, the ball takes the shoulder of the bat and rolls away towards third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Abul Hasan, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, drags his length back slightly and bowls it on the middle stump line, Ali goes back in the crease and punches it to the deep extra cover fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sohail, 1 run, gives the charge once again and drives this tossed up delivery down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sohail, no run, steps out of the crease and defends this slowish delivery with his bat close to the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, 1 run, gives the charge this time and eases this fullish delivery down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, drifting in on middle and leg, Ali works it past mid-wicket and comes back for the second before the ball is hunted down]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, no run, knocks this delivery outside off towards point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, <b>SIX</b>, quicker through the air and bowls this one well short, Sohail backs away and pulls it hard, gets it over the deep mid-wicket fence for the first six of the innings]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, 1 run, slightly flatter outside off, Ali goes deep in the crease and cuts it square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, 1 run, turning in from outside off, Sohail works it towards mid-wicket with the turn]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, 1 run, Ali puts his front foot across, bends down and drags the sweep from outside off to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, 1 run, spinning in from just outside off, Sohail comes on the front foot and drives it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, 1 run, Sunny darts this in on the pads seeing Ali give the charge, Ali bunts it down to long-on and gets off strike]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, 3 runs, pushed through quicker, Sohail backs away slightly and punches it through extra cover off the back foot, the fielder from cover gives chase and saves a run for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sohail, 1 run, quicker and drifting in on middle, Sohail drives it down to long-on off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sohail, no run, comes down the track and drives this flighted delivery back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, 1 run, comes down the track and closes the face of the bat a little too early as he looks to drive it straight down the ground, the ball rolls away to long-off off the outside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sohail, 1 run, eases this fullish delivery down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, 1 run, slowish delivery outside off, Ali pushes it to the right of point after reaching it to the pitch of the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, no run, flatter and quicker on the stumps, Sohail punches it towards short mid-wicket, who moves to his right and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, no run, drifting on the pads, Sohail glances it to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, no run, flatter and just outside off, Sohail backs away slightly, opens the face of the bat and punches it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, no run, floated up on off, Sohail shuffles across and clips it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, no run, slower through the air and just outside off, Sohail goes across and drives it to mid-wicket off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, no run, quicker on off, Sohail stays back and defends it into the leg-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sohail, 1 run, goes across and works this past mid-wicket, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, Sohail gives the charge this time and lofts this slightly flatter delivery over mid-wicket, he didn't time it that well, but the ball had enough legs to reach the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sohail, no run, tossed up on off and middle, Sohail clips it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sohail, no run, <b>beaten!</b> It was bowled slightly slower and turns away as Sohail pushes at it, the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sohail, no run, flighted delivery on off, defended off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sohail, no run, <b>huge lbw appeal!</b> Sohail was pushing forward to this arm ball on off and middle, he luckily gets an inside edge onto the pad and that's what saved him. It would have been plumb out had that missed the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Nasir Hossain, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, flatter and outside off, Ali makes room and looks to cut it hard, gets an outside edge that runs away to the third man fence, short third man ran after it, but the ball wins the race]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, no run, flighted delivery on off, Ali drives it to mid-off after coming forward]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, 1 run, works this slower delivery outside off to deep square leg after going across]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, no run, drives this fullish delivery towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, no run, goes across and turns this into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Haris Sohail, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, <b>out</b> Hafeez Run Out!! Ali comes down the track and pushes this flighted delivery in front of mid-on, he sets off for the single and Hafeez was late to respond. Sarkar runs forward, throws the ball at the striker's end and Rahim does the rest. The throw was right on target and brought about Hafeez's downfall. <b>Hafeez run out (Soumya Sarkar/Rahim) 4(7) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[A Sunny to Azhar Ali, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[The third umpire has been pressed into service. Hafeez is the man in question and <b>he is short of his ground here</b>. The third umpire dives his verdict and Hafeez has to make his way back.]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Hafeez, <b>FOUR</b>, finally Hafeez gets off the mark with a boundary, it was bowled slower and fuller outside off, Hafeez comes down the track and caresses it to the right of cover, who gives chase but the ball wins the race]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Hafeez, no run, comes charging down but wasn't upto the pitch of the ball, he defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Hafeez, no run, comes charging down but wasn't upto the pitch of the ball, he defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Hafeez, no run, flatter and quicker on the stumps, Hafeez goes across slightly and punches it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Hafeez, no run, slower through the air and on off, Hafeez hangs back and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Hafeez, no run, flighted delivery outside off, Hafeez comes on the front foot and drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Ali comes down the track and drives it to the left of the bowler, who dives and makes a half stop, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away towards the mid-off region]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Hafeez, no run, Hafeez charges down the track and Sunny defends his length back a touch, defended into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Hafeez, no run, arm ball on leg, Hafeez misses the forward defensive and is hit on the pad, Sunny made half an appealm but the ball was snaking down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, 1 run, floated up well outside off, Ali advances and reaches out to drive it towards sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, no run, darted on off, Ali defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Hafeez, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sarfraz Ahmed, <b>out</b> Caught by Nasir Hossain!! Sarfraz perishes trying to play another slog sweep. It was a flighted delivery that was turning away around off, Sarfraz goes down on one knee and slog swept it in the air, Nasir from deep backward square leg runs to his left and takes a good catch. He covered a lot of distance there. It wasn't an easy catch and Nasir did really well to get there in time. <b>Sarfraz Ahmed c Nasir Hossain b A Sunny 24(31) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A Sunny to Sarfraz Ahmed, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, 1 run, floated up just outside off, Ali steps out of the crease and drives it down to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, 1 run, Shakib tosses this up outside off, Ali comes down the track and drives it to long-off after taking it on the full]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sarfraz Ahmed, 1 run, full toss on the pads, Sarfraz goes down on one knee, takes it on the full and sweeps it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, 1 run, floated up just outside off, Ali lofts it inside-out over extra coverr for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, no run, slightly fuller outside off, Ali drives it to the left of cover-point, who dives to his left and stops the ball, can't get the single away]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, no run, loopy delivery outside off, Ali goes for the expansive drive, but mistimes it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sarfraz Ahmed, 1 run, comes down the track, reaches to the pitch of the ball and eases it down to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, no run, flatter from Sunny, Ali punches it to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, no run, arm ball on middle stump line, Ali goes deep in the crease and cracks it hard to the left of cover-point, who moves across to his left and prevents the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sarfraz Ahmed, 1 run, goes down on one knee and sweeps this delivery on stumps to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, Sunny bowls this quicker on middle and leg as Sarfraz comes charging down, he can only nudge it towards short fine leg, can't get the single away]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, 1 run, to long on]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, 1 run, Ali comes down the track and clips this flighted delivery on off and middle past mid-wicket, the batsmen cross over for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, no run, arm ball on off, Ali goes back in the crease and pushes it into the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tossed up this time, Ali drives it wide of long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, no run, goes across this time and gets an inside edge on the forward push, the ball rolls away to short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sarfraz Ahmed, 1 run, Sarfraz comes down the track and works this fullish delivery to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, roundarmish delivery that turns away as Sarfraz looks to defend, the ball spins past the outside edge and strikes him on the back foot, Shakib appeals but it was probably missing off]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, 3 runs, drifting in on the pads, Ali flicks it past short fine leg, who gives chase, dives and pulls the ball back just in time to save a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, no run, quicker and on middle stump line, Ali drops it behindsquare off the inside half of the bat, the batsmen can't take a single as the fielder at square leg quickly moves to his left and stops it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two left-arm spinners will bowl in tandem now as Shakib replaces Taskin]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sarfraz Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, Sarfraz comes charging down and drives this full delivery past the non-striker, mid-on was inside the circle and he had no chance of stopping that as the ball was a little too far to his left]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, slider from Sunny on leg, Sarfraz misses the clip and is hit on the pad, the ball was going down leg though]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, full and on off, Sarfraz sweeps it fine, but short fine runs to his right and prevents the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, touch quicker and on off]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, touch quicker and on off, Sarfraz gets his bat down just in time to defend]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sarfraz Ahmed, 2 runs, Sarfraz puts his front foot across and sweeps this flighted delivery on off towards fine leg, comes back for the second as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tosses this one just outside off, Azhar comes down the track and pushes it past the bowler, who was diving to his left. The batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Arafat Sunny, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and a leg slip in place for him]]></line><line><![CDATA[Spin for the first time as Sunny replaces Rubel]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sarfraz Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>punched!</b> Super shot from Sarfraz as he hops to this back of a length delivery outside off, gets on top of the bounce and punches it in the gap between cover and backward point for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, full and angling in just outside off, Sarfraz comes forward and punches it back to the bowler, who bends down in his followthrough and stops the ball with his right hand]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, that's a great shot but straight to the fielder. It was just short of a good length and outside off, Sarfraz cuts it straight to the fielder at shortish point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, length that that holds its line outside off, Sarfraz looks to force it through the off-side, but doesn't get to the pitch of the ball. The ball goes past the outside edge this time]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, fuller in length and angles it in from outside off, Sarfraz punches it back to the bowler, who stops it with his left hand]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, very full outside off, Sarfraz leans forward and drives it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, short again and this time Ali dispatches it to the deep mid-wicket fence, this time Ali had enough time to rock back and he muscles the pull past mid-wicket, who was diving to his right but fails to stop the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, short and slightly wide outside off, Ali goes across and cracks it past the shortish point, the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sarfraz Ahmed, 1 run, short delivery that sits up nicely for Sarfraz to swivel as he pulls it along the ground to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, 1 run, fuller in length this time and outside off, Ali goes forward and drives, gets an outside edge that dribbles away to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sarfraz Ahmed, 1 run, bangs this one midway, but the ball doesn't rise as much as Rubel expected, Sarfraz goes on the back foot and tucks it away to square leg to get off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, 1 run, back of a length delivery on off, Ali pushes it down to mid-on and sets off for the single, he played that with soft hands and that's why the batsmen were able to easily complete the single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sarfraz Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, Sarfraz goes down on one knee and gets the slog sweep away after going across. It was a length ball from Taskin and Sarfraz dispatched it to the deep backward square leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, that's a good shot for no run! It was a length delivery outside off, Sarfraz leans forward and drives it hard, cover moves and slides to his left and fields the ball, prevents the single too]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, shuffles across his stumps and drives it uppishly past the non-striker, can't beat mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sarfraz Ahmed, <b>wide</b>, short delivery wide outside off, Sarfraz goes after it once again, but the ball bounces over the bat, called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, Sarfraz walks across his stumps again and looks to whip this fullish delivery through mid-wicket, he fails to connect and the ball hits the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Sarfraz hangs back and punches it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Azhar Ali, 1 run, short and slightly wide outside off, Ali goes chasing after it and slices the cut towards third man, gets off strike]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Slip has been moved to a leg slip position for Taskin]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, banged in short and at the batsman, Sarfraz goes for the pull, but the ball hurries onto him. He tries to roll his wrists on it, but mistimes it completely towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, bumper from Rubel this time, Sarfraz is happy to duck under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, goes across and clips this length delivery towards mid-wicket, who moves across to his right and prevents the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, 1 run, <b>uppish but safe!</b> It was full and wide outside off, Ali looks to drive, the ball flies off the outside edge and goes to the left of backward point, the batsmen take a single as third man tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, great shot from Azhar to pick his first boundary today, it was a length delivery shaping away outside off, Ali gets on top of the bounce and drives it to the sweeper cover fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sarfraz Ahmed, 1 run, back of a length delivery angling in on off, Sarfraz walks across and nudges it towards deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Azhar Ali, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Ali punches it straight to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Azhar Ali, no run, short delivery that surprises Azhar with the extra bounce, who fends it awkwardly into the off-side after taking his eyes off the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Azhar Ali, no run, length delivery shaping in outside off, Ali tries to force it through the on-side, gets an inside edge that rolls away towards the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Azhar Ali, <b>3 wides</b>, bowls this well down the leg-side, Rahim dives full length to his left and gets his left hand on it, makes a half stop, the ball rolls away towards fine leg and the batsmen take two more runs apart from the wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Azhar Ali, no run, Azhar Ali goes right across his off stump and tries to flick the ball towards square leg, there was a little extra bounce on this, he misses and the ball hits the pad. Tehre was an appeal, but the impact was outside off]]></line><line><![CDATA[Just a slip in place for Taskin]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sarfraz Ahmed, 1 run, Sarfraz goes across once again and looks to clip it through the on-side, the ball shapes away and takes the outside edge to third man, the batsmen cross over]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sarfraz Ahmed, 2 runs, Sarfraz walks across his stumps to this delivery angling in on off, he works it behind square on the on-side and comes back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Taskin Ahmed, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Taskin Ahmed will share the attack with Rubel]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, no run, short of length delivery angling in towards the batsman, who pulls it straight to mid-on, a <b>maiden</b> to start the proceedings]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, no run, overpitching outside off, Ali leans forward and drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, no run, overpitching outside off, Ali leans forward and drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Ali gets behind the line and defends it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, no run, length delivery shaping away outside off, it was too close to the tramline, but the umpire doesn't call it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, no run, almost a replay of the previous ball, Ali reached out once again, drives and picks out backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, no run, full delivery well outside off, Ali reaches out and drives it towards backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Azhar Ali and Sarfraz Ahmed are at the crease. Azhar Ali is on strike. Rubel will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players are out in the middle. Rubel will open the proceedings with the ball. There are two slips in place. Azhar Ali will take strike first up]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back. Bangladesh are in the driver's seat for now. It's not going to be easy for Pakistan to chase this down and if Bangladesh manage to take early wickets, they will put the Pakistani middle-order under a lot of pressure.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Wahab Riaz was the pick of the bowlers for the visitors as he picked up four wickets. Although Junaid Khan and Rahat Ali bowled decently, the returning Saeed Ajmal took a pasting and conceded 67 runs in his last 6 overs. Can Pakistan chase this down? We'll find out in a while.]]></line><line><![CDATA[So Bangladesh have finished with 329/6 - their highest score in ODIs. After opting to bat first, openers Tamim Iqbal and Soumya Sarkar got Bangladesh off to a good start before the latter was run-out. Mahmudullah, who had a wonderful World Cup, threw his wicket away early, but Tamim combined well with Mushfiqur Rahim and the duo thrashed the Pakistani bowlers to all corners as they registered their respective hundreds. They were also involved in a record 178-run stand - the highest for Bangladesh for any wicket in ODIs. Although both perished at the fag end of the innings, Shakib Al Hasan and Sabbir Rahman took the score past 300 with some fine hits.]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shakib, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Shakib almost in a funny manner reviews that. He knew that he was out, just signalled to the umpire and walked off the field. The Hawk-Eye comes in and it says impact in-line and crashing into the base of middle stump. Inswinging low full toss, Shakib walks across and tries to ramp it away to fine leg, but misses and is hit plumb in front. The extra ball gives Riaz his 4th wicket. <b>Shakib lbw b Riaz 31(27) [4s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riaz to Shakib, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shakib, <b>wide</b>, slower ball bouncer outside off stump, left alone. How is that a wide? It was inside the line!]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Nasir Hossain, 3 runs, full and outside off stump, Hossain squeezes it out to short third man, where Junaid Khan fumbles the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Nasir Hossain, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Rahman, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Riaz puts out a loud appeal. Was he not aware that the batsman was bowled? Full and on the leg stump from round the wicket, Rahman misses the reverse sweep and the ball hits the leg stump. <b>S Rahman b Riaz 15(7) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riaz to S Rahman, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shakib, <b>2 wides</b>, full down the leg-side, Shakib misses the flick and Rahman steal an extra run to get back on strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Rahman, 1 run, short ball from Riaz, Rahman mistimes the pull to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shakib, 1 run, Shakib swings across the line and gets an inside edge that rolls to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shakib, byes, <b>FOUR</b>, the keeper's made a mess of a fantastic inswinging yorker, Riaz followed Shakib as he backed away and cramped him for room, Shakib tried to dig it out but couldn't put bat on ball, but the ball fumbles to gift four runs to Bangladesh]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[48.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Shakib, 1 run, low full toss again, driven to extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Shakib, <b>FOUR</b>, low full toss down the leg-side, Shakib helps it on its way and beats fine leg. Timely blow from Shakib]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Shakib, no run, inswinging yorker, Shakib could only dig it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to S Rahman, 1 run, short and outside off stump, Rahman dabs it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to S Rahman, 2 runs, full and outside off stump, Rahman mistimes the loft and it rolls to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to S Rahman, <b>wide</b>, full and way outside off stump, Rahman fails to reach out and called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Shakib, 1 run, backs away and drives the full ball to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[47.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Rahman, <b>FOUR</b>, short ball on the stumps, Rahman pulls behind square on the on-side and the ball runs away through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Rahman, <b>SIX</b>, incredible shot. Full and way outside off stump, he's picked that up nicely and smashed it over long-on. Gee! That was a great connection as he had to reach out for the shot. Brings up the 300 for Bangladesh]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shakib, 1 run, good length delivery from Riaz, Shakib mistimes the slog to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Rahman, 1 run, short of length delivery on the stumps, Rahman turns it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sabbir Rahman, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Rahim, <b>out</b> Caught by Sarfraz Ahmed!! Full and just tailing away, Rahim stays leg-side of the ball and slogs, gets an outside edge and the keeper makes no mistake. The umpire checks for the no-ball but Riaz's foot was well behind the line. Rahim walks off to a good round of applause. End of an excellent knock from the right-hander. <b>Rahim c Sarfraz Ahmed b Riaz 106(77) [4s-13 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riaz to Rahim, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shakib, 1 run, short and outside off stump, Shakib steps out and looks to slap, but mistimes it to the man at sweeper, he looks for the second but Rahim sends him back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz [8.0-0-38-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, no run, Rahim tries to ramp this to the fine leg after getting across the stumps but misses and it almost shaves the off stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, no run, yorker outside off stump, Rahim tries to squeeze it out but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Shakib, 1 run, full and on the stumps, driven to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Shakib, <b>FOUR</b>, innovative shot from Shakib. Full toss on the stumps, Shakib goes to the off-side and scoops it over the man at 45 and it almost goes all the way]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, 1 run, flighted delivery just outside off stump, Rahim under-edges the sweep to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Shakib, 1 run, full and on the leg stump, Shakib drives it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Junaid Khan [8.0-0-36-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Shakib, 1 runs, moves across the stumps and flicks the full ball to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Rahim, 1 run, shortish and outside off stump, Rahim cuts it square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Rahim, no run, appeal for caught behind, but not given. Short and on the stumps, Rahim gets across the stumps and tries to scoop it to fine leg but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Shakib, 1 run, full and outside off stump, Shakib goes for the cover-drive, but gets an inside edge that rolls to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Shakib, no run, short and just outside off stump, Shakib goes for the pull but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Rahim, 1 run, Rahim was shaping up for the ball, but on seeing this slower ball go well outside off stump, he dabs it towards backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rahat Ali [9.0-0-52-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Shakib, no run, flatter and just outside off stump, Shakib sweeps it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Rahim, 1 run, on the leg stump, glanced to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, that's gone through and that's a <b>hundred off 69 balls</b> for Rahim. Again Ajmal fires it flat and outside off stump, Rahim waits for the ball and guides it very fine, short third man dives to his left but dives over the ball. Rahim takes his helmet off and has his hands aloft pointing towards the sky]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, flatter delivery outside off stump, Rahim guides it fine, beats backward point's dive and he moves on to 98]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Shakib, 1 run, steps out, but Ajmal follows him. Shakib mistimes the loft and chips it back over the bowler's head]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Shakib, no run, short and spinning away outside off stump, cut to backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shakib, 1 run, slower ball bouncer, Shakib toe-ends the pull to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shakib, <b>FOUR</b>, width on offer and Shakib doesn't miss out. Short and outside off stump, Shakib rocks back and cuts it fiercely through backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shakib, no run, back of a length from Riaz, Shakib tries to slog, misses, the ball goes past the leg stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shakib, 2 runs, short of length delivery outside off stump, Shakib cuts it to square third man, gets back for the second before the keeper takes the bails off]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shakib, <b>FOUR</b>, short of length delivery down the leg-side, Shakib fails to tickle it fine, the ball goes off the thigh pad and beats the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shakib, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, dabbed to backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Shakib, 1 run, flatter delivery on the stumps, Shakib flicks it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Rahim, 1 run, worked away to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Rahim, <b>SIX</b>, Ajmal is getting no respect from the Bangladeshi batsmen! Flighted delivery on the stumps, Rahim goes down on one knee and muscles the slog-sweep over deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Shakib, 1 run, on the off stump, pulled to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Rahim, 1 run, on the leg stump, Rahim tucks it away to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Rahim, <b>SIX</b>, full toss and that's a gift. Rahim waits for the ball and slogs it hard over the deep square leg fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Shakib, no run, short and wide outside off stump, Shakib cuts well, but backward point makes an excellent diving save to his right]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Rahim, 1 run, pulled away to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, <b>out</b> Caught by Rizwan!! Rizwan and Azhar Ali almost collided and dropped the catch. Tamim walks off to a standing ovation. Riaz bangs this slower ball very short, Tamim tries to manufacture some pace and flat-bat it over the infield, but completely mistimes the ball. Mid-off and extra-cover go for the catch, luckily for Pakistan, Rizwan took the catch just before Ali put his hands across his team-mate. End of a fine innings. <b>Tamim c Rizwan b Riaz 132(135) [4s-15 6s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riaz to Tamim, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, leg byes, 2 runs, low full toss following the batsman as he makes room, the ball rolls towards backward point, they take the run, the fielder has a shy and hits the stumps at the bowler's end, the ball ricochets away and they get an extra-run]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Rahim, 1 run, slower ball outside off stump, Rahim taps it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Rahim, no run, short slower ball, Rahim backs away and tries to cut but misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Rahim, <b>wide</b>, Rahim backs away and tries to scoop it to fine leg but it was way down the leg-side, a late call from the umpire for wide]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz [6.0-0-24-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, no run, fired in flat at 64.5mph, Tamim misses the flick and gets hit on the pad, but the impact was outside leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Rahim, 1 run, low full toss, flicked to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, 1 run, on the stumps, Tamim pulls it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, no run, advances and almost yorks himself up, but manages to drill it to extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, 2 runs, once again Tamim gives the charge to Ajmal, goes for the lofted drive, but slices it over extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Rahim, 1 run, short and spinning back in, Rahim backs away and cuts it to deep point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Saeed Ajmal [7.0-0-43-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Excellent <b>batting powerplay</b> for Bangladesh. They scored 55 runs in 5 overs and are looking very good for 300.]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Rahim, 1 run, short of length delivery on the leg stump, Rahim tucks it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, 1 run, full and outside off stump, Tamim toe-ends the drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Rahim, leg byes, 1 run, short of length delivery cramping Rahim for room, Rahim fails to defend, the ball rolls off the pad towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, a delightful drive from Rahim. Full and swinging away outside off stump, Rahim goes leg-side and drives it over cover to pick up four more]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, 1 run, again tailing back into the left-hander, Tamim drives it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, no run, good yorker from Rahat Ali first up, the inswing foxes Tamim on the clip and he gets hit on the pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, no run, yorker on the stumps, Rahim digs it out to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[This partnership, worth 161 runs so far, is the best stand for Bangladesh against Pakistan in ODIs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, 1 run, bit of shape back into the left-hander on the yorker, Tamim backs away and digs it out through cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, 1 run, low full toss on the stumps, Rahim drives it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, how did that go for four? He just seemed to check his shot as Junaid Khan foxed him with a slower ball outside off stump, Rahim checks the cut and it races away past mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, 1 run, looks for the yorker, but just misses it, slogged along the ground to wide long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, very full, Tamim mistimes the drive to extra-cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Junaid Khan [7.0-0-29-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bangladesh have scored <b>40 runs</b> in the first three overs of the powerplay.]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Rahim, no run, slower ball on the stumps, Rahim makes away and tries to dab it to third man, but the bounces extra and goes past the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Rahim, no run, yorker outside off stump, Rahim tries to squeezes it out but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, poor bowling. Length ball right in the slot, Rahim lofts it easily over mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, these two are just unstoppable at the moment. Short of a length delivery outside off stump, Rahim advances and lofts it over extra-cover. He gave himself a bit of room to free his arms and made great contact]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, <b>no ball</b>, 1 run, oh that's a high full toss and it's called a no-ball as it was above the waist. Tamim slogs it through square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, no run, nice inswinging yorker on the leg stump, Tamim digs it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Rahim, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off stump, dabbed to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rahat Ali [7.0-0-34-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Before this spell, Ajmal's figures read 4-0-7-0. But in the last two overs of this spell, he's conceded 32 runs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, 2 runs, again steps out and goes for the big hit, but this time Tamim slices it over extra-cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, <b>SIX</b>, wow! Flighted delivery on the leg stump, Tamim advances, gets to the pitch of the ball and muscles the loft all the way over wide long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, in the airrrrr and just past the outstretched arm of Rahat Ali at short third man. Tamim races down the track and looks for the inside-out hit, he slices it, but luckily got enough on it to clear the infield]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Rahim, 1 run, down the leg-side, Rahim tucks it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, 1 run, this time Ajmal fires it down the leg-side on seeing Tamim give the charge, the batsman nudges it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, this is a classy shot and it's played against a quality off-spinner. Flighted delivery just outside off stump, Tamim steps out, also gives himself a bit of room and lofts it inside-out over extra-cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, punched off the front foot and it's running away past the fielder. Good length delivery just outside off stump, Rahim places it to the left of mid-off. Great start to the powerplay for Bangladesh. They scored 11 runs off the first over]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Rahim, no run, short of length delivery outside off stump, Rahim defends it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, leg byes, 1 run, full and angling into the left-hander, Tamim misses the flick and gets hit on the pad but it was going down the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Rahim, 1 run, good length delivery on the off stump, Rahim gets an inside edge that rolls to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, 1 run, shortish slower ball, slogged to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, great start for Bangladesh! Full and outside off stump, Tamim backs away and slices the drive over backward point and that gets the crowd going]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>batting powerplay</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, 1 run, flighted delivery from Ajmal, Tamim slogs it wide of long-on. <b>14 runs off the over</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>fifth ODI hundred for Tamim</b>. He takes his gloves off and points five with his fingers to the crowd. Probably he was telling them that it was his fifth ton. Flatter delivery down the leg-side, Tamim glances it fine past short fine leg and it runs away for four. Tamim gets a tight hug from his partner Mushfiqur Rahim. He took 75 balls to complete his fifty, but he scored his next 50 runs off just 37 balls]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, no run, flighted delivery just outside off stump, Tamim defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, deft touch! Spinning away outside off stump, Tamim waits for the ball and guides it fine past the keeper and it races away to the third man fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Rahim, 1 run, gets across the stumps and tucks it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>fifty</b> off just 42 balls. Flighted delivery on the off stump, Rahim gets down on one knee and slog-sweeps it over mid-wicket. <b>22nd ODI fifty</b> for Rahim and he raises his bat to the crowd]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, no run, shortish and outside off stump, Tamim flashes hard and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, no run, back of a length outside off stump, Tamim looks to cut but misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, no run, short of length delivery jags back in, Tamim hops and looks work it on the on-side but gets beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>100 partnership</b> is up now. Slower delivery on the stumps, Tamim pulls it along the ground through backward square leg. He moves into the 90s]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Rahim, 1 run, on the leg stump, Rahim flick it away behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Rahim, no run, short of length delivery just outside off stump, Rahim defends it to point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz [4.0-0-9-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, no run, punched to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, no run, on the stumps, Tamim flicks it towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, no run, on the off stump, Tamim defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, no run, tossed up outside off stump, Tamim drives it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, clever shot. Fired down the leg side, Tamim paddle-sweeps it very fine past the keeper and it races away]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, no run, round the wicket, flighted delivery on the stumps, Tamim defends]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Saeed Ajmal [4.0-0-7-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, 1 run, low full toss outside off stump, driven straight to mid-off, Rahim is late to take off but they get the single in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, it's too short from Junaid Khan and he disappears. Tamim rocks back and pulls it over mid-wicket, no one in the deep and it runs away]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, 2 runs, pulled nicely by Tamim. Shortish and just outside off stump, Tamim plays it wide of long-on, Rahim races back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, 1 run, shortish slower ball, Rahim misimes the pull to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, 1 run, to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, 1 run, low full toss on the leg stump, Tamim flicks it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, 1 run, full and on the stumps, Rahim flicks it to square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Rahim, 1 run, low full toss on the leg stump, Rahim flicks it along the ground to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Rahim, no run, googly from Ali, surprises Rahim a bit as he backs away to cut and hits him on the glove]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Tamim, 1 run, on the leg stump, punched to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Rahim, 1 run, way outside off sttump, cut square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, excellent use of the feet and he's timed it beautifully as well. Flighted delivery outside off stump, Rahim steps out and plays an inside-out drive that beats long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Tamim, 1 run, low full toss down the leg-side, flicked along the ground to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, no run, Rahim checks the flick shot, it goes uppishly towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, 1 run, very full on the stumps, flicked wide of long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, Junaid Khan drops it short on seeing Tamim advance, Tamim looks to slap it over cover but mistimes it]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, 1 run, overpitched outside off stump, Rahim punches it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, 1 run, punched off the front foot to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, low full toss on the leg stump, flicked to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Junaid Khan [5.0-0-16-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Rahim, no run, just outside off stump, Rahim defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Rahim, no run, Rahim defends from the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Tamim, 1 run, tucked away to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Rahim, 1 run, he's mistimed it and must be an easy catch. Oh dear! <b>Junaid Khan drops a sitter</b>. How costly is that drop going to be? Flighted delivery on the stumps, Rahim goes for the slog-sweep but gets a top edge, mid-wicket moves to his right, he had it covered, but dropped it]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Rahim, 2 runs, short and outside off stump, cut to deep point for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Rahim, no run, spinning away outside off stump, Rahim mistimes the cut into the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[This partnership, worth 66 runs so far, has been very busy at the crease and is doing it nicely for Bangladesh.]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Tamim, <b>SIX</b>, and again! The crowd goes berserk. Full and in the slot, Tamim waits for the ball to spin back in and smashes it over the mid-wicket boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Tamim, <b>SIX</b>, nice hit! Flighted delivery just outside off stump, Tamim gets down on one knee and slog-sweeps it hard over the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Rahim, 1 run, short ball, tucked away through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Tamim, 1 run, picks this flighted delivery from outside off stump and slogs it wide of long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Rahim, 1 run, short and spinning away outside off stump, cut to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Rahim, 2 runs, on the leg stump, Rahim flicks it along the ground to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Rahim, 1 run, tossed up outside off stump, driven to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Tamim, 1 run, on the leg stump, Tamim flicks it along the ground through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Tamim, no run, another full toss, Tamim plays the reverse sweep but hits it straight to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Rahim, 1 run, waits for the ball to spin away and drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Tamim, 1 run, low full toss on the leg stump, Tamim drives it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Rahim, 1 run, shortish outside off stump, Rahim cuts it square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Azhar Ali, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Rahim, 1 run, Sohail drifts one flatter and well outside off, worked down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Rahim, no run, slower and just outside off, Rahim makes room and dabs it straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Tamim, 1 run, pushed through by Sohail, Tamim comes down the track and works it in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Rahim, 1 run, tossed up and on the stumps, driven down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, Rahim is looking very positive! This was tossed up and on the stumps, Rahim goes down on his knees and slog sweeps it over mid-wicket, there's no one in the deep, another boundary for Rahim]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Rahim, no run, flatter and on the stumps, Rahim backs away and cuts it straight to the fielder at point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Tamim, no run, slower and wider outside off, driven straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Tamim, <b>wide</b>, Nasim drifts this one well down leg-side, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Tamim, no run, quicker delivery from Nasim, Tamim goes back and gets an inside edge onto the chop]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Tamim, 2 runs, slightly short and just outside off, Tamim makes room and carves it square on the off-side, two fielders give chase and haul the ball back in, another brace for Tamim]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Rahim, 1 run, flighted delivery and on Rahim's pads, nudged in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, Nasim now drops one short and wide outside off, Rahim makes room and cracks it square on the off-side, beats the man in the deep for another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, this is poor bowling from Nasim, another juicy full-toss, Rahim punches it over extra cover, earns himself another boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Tamim, no run, another reverse sweep from Tamim, Sohail belts out an excited appeal as the ball hit the pads, but there was an inside edge before that]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Tamim, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Tamim pushes it towards short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, reverse sweep and four! Sohail was looking to fire this one outside off as Tamim set himself up for the reverse sweep, he does well to bisect the gap between short third man and backward point for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Rahim, 1 run, slower and on the stumps, worked down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Tamim, 1 run, <b>29th ODI fifty for Tamim</b>, it's been a responsible knock from the opener, flatter and just outside off, eased down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sohail to Rahim, 1 run, flatter and just outside off, Rahim makes room and cuts it square on the off-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Haris Sohail, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Rahim, 1 run, Nasim drifts one on Rahim's pads, worked behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Tamim, 1 run, pushed through by Saad Nasim, Tamim nudges it in front of square leg, Rahim calls for a quick single and Tamim rushes across to make his end]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Tamim, no run, flatter and on Tamim's pads, tucked away towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Rahim, 1 run, slower and just outside off, eased down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Tamim, 1 run, <b>dropped!</b> That was an absolute dolly for the bowler, it was a rubbish ball, full-toss from Nasim, chipped back at him, he isn't in a great position, the ball bursts through his fingers]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Rahim, 1 run, tossed up and on the stumps, worked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, no run, a proper bouncer from Rahat, Tamim drops his wrists and bends underneath, he looks for a wide, but there's nothing given]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, cheeky from Tamim, width on offer from Rahat, Tamim waits on it and delicately guides it through the vacant slip cordon for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Rahim, 1 run, the bouncer from Rahat, Rahim swivels across, rolls his wrists and pulls it in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Rahim, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Rahim prods across and defends it with an open face towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Rahim, no run, Rahat shortens his length and gets this one to angle across Rahim, defended towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, 1 run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, driven to the right of mid-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a dreadful delivery! A long hop from Nasim, Rahim rocks back and pulls it over mid-wicket for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Tamim, 1 run, Nasim drops one short and on Tamim's pads, nudged away behind square on the on-swide for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Rahim, 1 run, Saad Nasim gives this one more air, driven down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Rahim, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Rahim prods forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Rahim, no run, almost chopped on! Flatter and spinning away from off, Rahim pushed forward, the inside edge rolled past the leg-stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Tamim, 1 run, flighted delivery and just outside off, driven down towards long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mushfiqur Rahim, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Mahmudullah, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Cleaned up! Mahmudullah had a rush of blood last ball and he has now lost his middle stump! Change of pace from Rahat, the slower ball and on the middle-stump line, Mahmudullah made room outside leg and was looking to go inside out over extra cover, is done in by the lack of pace and the middle pole is knocked out. First wicket for Rahat. Pakistan continue to fightback. <b>Mahmudullah b Rahat Ali 5(18)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rahat Ali to Mahmudullah, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Mahmudullah, no run, aggression from Mahmudullah, backs away to a short ball and misses a wild hoick]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Mahmudullah, no run, short of a length and just outside off, dabbed straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, 1 run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Tamim charges down the track and drills it to the right of mid-off, Azhar dives and makes a half-stop, saves three runs for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, no run, short and just outside off, Tamim swivels across and pulls it straight to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, no run, on a good length and well outside off, dabbed to the right of backward point, he wanted a single but is sent back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Tamim, 1 run, flighted and spinning back into Tamim, eased past the bowler for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, that should break the shackles! This was tossed up wide by Nasim, Tamim gets a big stride forward and creams it through extra cover, the ball races away to the fence in a hurry]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Tamim, no run, flighted delivery and on off, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Tamim, no run, slower and spinning back into Tamim, nudged towards backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Tamim, 2 runs, tossed up and on off, Tamim comes down the track and drills it back over the bowler's head, gets it to the right of long-on and gets back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Tamim, no run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Saad Nasim to Tamim, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Tamim prods forward and blocks]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Saad Nasim, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Mahmudullah, no run, the bouncer from Rahat, Mahmudullah drops his wrists and sways away from the line]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Mahmudullah, no run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, driven straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, 1 run, on a good length and on the stumps, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Mahmudullah, 1 run, short of a length and on Mahmudullah's hips, tucked away past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, 1 run, back of a length and well outside off, steered away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, no run, the bouncer from Rahat, Tamim drops his wrists and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Mahmudullah, no run, Ajmal floats one on the middle stump line, nudged towards backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Mahmudullah, no run, this one's given more air, Mahmudullah prods across and defends it towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, 1 run, slower and just outside off, eased down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, no run, pushed through by Ajmal, Tamim went down on his knees as he looked to sweep and missed, looked like the ball was going on with the angle and would have been missing the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[Appeal for a LBW, Ajmal looked interested and Pakistan want a <b>review</b>. Well, the umpire says that it's a bit too late, the 15-second time limit has elasped]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, no run, flighted and on off, Tamim prods forward and nudges it towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Mahmudullah, 1 run, fraction shorter and just outside off, Mahmudullah makes room and cuts it square on the off-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, no run, fuller length delivery and in that channel outside off, Tamim leans forward and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, no run, the bumper from Rahat, Tamim drops his wrists and sways away from the line]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Mahmudullah, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, nudged behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Mahmudullah, no run, width on offer from Rahat, Mahmudullah cracks it straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Mahmudullah, no run, Rahat shortens his length on off, Mahmudullah pushes at that and gets a bottom edge that bounces over the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Mahmudullah, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, left alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rahat Ali [3.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, no run, pushed through quicker and on Tamim's pads, he looks to nudge it away towards the on-side and gets a bottom edge, the ball rolls away towards short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, no run, slower and on the stumps, Tamim goes down on his knees as he looks to sweep, gets a bottom edge towards short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, no run, flatter and on the stumps, Tamim goes back and nudges it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Mahmudullah, 1 run, this one is given more air by Ajmal, eased down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Mahmudullah, no run, slower and just outside off, Mahmudullah prods forward and turns it towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, 1 run, tossed up and on off, driven down towards long-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, 1 run, too straight from Riaz, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mahmudullah, 1 run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Mahmudullah leans into the drive and beats cover, there's a man in the deep, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mahmudullah, no run, that's a good short delivery from Riaz, angles this one across the right-hander, Mahmudullah was shaping up for the pull, drops his wrists and lets it go at the last moment]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mahmudullah, <b>wide</b>, Riaz sprays one way outside off, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mahmudullah, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Mahmudullah gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mahmudullah, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, <b>out</b> Soumya Sarkar Run Out!! Exceptional piece of fielding from Riaz, the crowd has been silenced. This was pitched up and held its line outside off, Tamim was cramped for room as he looked to dab it towards the off-side, gets an inside edge onto the pads and stops near the popping crease. Soumya Sarkar called for a quick single, Riaz is quick to react, runs across, picks up the ball and hits the stumps. Soumya Sarkar was struggling all along and has to walk back to the hut. <b>Soumya Sarkar run out (Riaz) 20(36) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riaz to Tamim, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Appeal for a <b>run-out</b>. Soumya Sarkar is the man in question. Riaz was celebrating. Replays suggest Soumya Sarkar is struggling. The third umpire is taking a long time on this. OUT is the call]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, no run, rush of blood from Tamim, shimmies down the track, makes room and swings at a length ball, misses by a long way]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Soumya Sarkar, no run, pushed through quicker and just outside off, Soumya Sarkar nudges it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Soumya Sarkar, no run, slower and on off, Soumya Sarkar goes back, opens the face of the bat and guides it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Soumya Sarkar, no run, pushed through by Ajmal, Soumya Sarkar goes back and whips it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, 1 run, slower and just outside off, Tamim gets an inside edge on the drive, the ball rolls away towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, no run, full and just outside leg, Tamim rolls his wrists and sweeps it straight to the fielder at short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, no run, tossed up and drifting outside off, Tamim lunges forward and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, dabbed away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, no run, tad fuller and angling back into the left-hander, Tamim closes the face of the bat and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, no run, back of a length and on the stumps, Tamim presses across and defends it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Tamim prods forward and defends it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, no run, short and wide from Riaz, Tamim throws his bat at that and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, no run, on a good length and just outside off, dabbed straight to the fielder at point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Soumya Sarkar, no run, slower and just outside off, Soumya Sarkar plays with an open face and guides it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Soumya Sarkar, no run, flighted and just outside off, Soumya Sarkar prods forward and defends it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, 1 run, tossed up and well outside leg, Tamim looks to sweep and gets a bottom edge past the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Tamim, no run, this was pushed through by Ajmal, Iqbal was looking to work it towards the on-side, was there an inside edge on that? Ajmal looked convinced, but they decide against a review. Replays suggest that the ball was just about clipping the leg-stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[Loud shout for LBW. Pakistan decide against a review]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, tossed up and on off, driven past the bowler for a single to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ajmal to Soumya Sarkar, no run, flighted delivery and on Soumya Sarkar's pads, he gets an inside edge as he looked to nudge it towards the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Saeed Ajmal, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Ajmal's introduced into the attack. This will be interesting..]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, no run, short of a length and holding its line outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, no run, back of a length and just outside off, dabbed with an open face and towards short point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, just short of Junaid at deep backward square leg! The bumper from Riaz, Sarkar swivelled across and pulled it behind square, just bounces in front of the onrushing fielder, he gets his body behind the line and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, no run, that's a wild hoick from Soumya Sarkar, the slower ball from Riaz, pitched up and on the leg-stump line, beats Soumya Sarkar's swing and goes past the leg-stump, by a whisker]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, no run, back of a length and angling into Soumya Sarkar, cramps him on the pull shot, picks out the man at mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, no run, short of a length and on the stumps, Soumya Sarkar backs away slightly and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Tamim closes the face of the bat as he defends it towards mid-wicket. There's a direct hit from the fielder as Soumya Sarkar was backing up, but he's well home]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, width on offer from Junaid, Soumya Sarkar was looking to use the pace on the ball and helps it over the infield, just about gets enough to clear the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, 1 run, Junaid bangs one short and on the stumps, Tamim swivels across, rolls his wrists and pulls it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, tad fuller and angling back into Tamim, driven straight to the fielder at mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, the slower bouncer from Junaid , the batsman was taken by surprise as he went for the pull and missed, the ball bounces through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, punched towards mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Soumya Sarkar plays with an open face and guides it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, no run, short and wide from Riaz, Soumya Sarkar cuts it straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, no run, short of a length and angling back into Soumya Sarkar, he wasn't in any position as he fended at that, took his eyes off the ball and the ball rolls towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, no run, appeal for LBW, but the height was an issue. Soumya Sarkar was shuffling across a long way and missed the flick, gets hit high on the pads, would have been sailing over the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, that's the best of the lot! Back of a length and just outside off, Sarkar leans into the cut and cracks it square on the off-side, the timing is superb and the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, no run, short and wide from Riaz, that was there to be smacked, Soumya Sarkar goes hard at it and mistimes it towards cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, Junaid slips in the slower ball, dabbed straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, fraction too short and just outside off, Tamim picked the length early, swivels across and pulls it in front of square on the on-side, beats the man in the deep for another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, punched back towards the bowler, he gets a hand and the ball rolls away towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[A man has been posted at leg-gully]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, 2 runs, too full and too straight from Junaid, ends up angling into Tamim's pads, worked away behind square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, Tamim gives the charge to a fuller length delivery, doesn't get hold of the drive and the ball rolls away towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, Tamim wasn't to the pitch of the ball and ends up pushing it towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, that's much better! Full and on Soumya Sarkar's pads, whipped away over mid-wicket for another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, that's slugged away by Soumya Sarkar, should break the shackles, short of a length and on the stumps, Soumya Sarkar heaves at it, gets it high on the bat but has enough to clear mid-on, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Soumya Sarkar, no run, Rahat shortens his length on off, Soumya Sarkar gets behind the line and pushes it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, 1 run, length ball and on Tamim's pads, worked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, Tamim makes room as he gives the charge, doesn't get hold of the shot and gets an inside edge towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, no run, this was pitched up and nipped back in slightly, Tamim was shuffling across on the flick, misses and is struck high on the knee-roll, the impact was on the leg-stump line and the ball would have missed the stumps]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Loud shout for LBW. Will Pakistan review? NO]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, no run, on a good length and slanting away from the left-hander, he pushes at that and gets an inside edge towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, <b>wide</b>, the bouncer from Junaid, but it went sailing over Soumya Sarkar's head, given as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, no run, length ball and on Soumya Sarkar's pads, tucked away towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[Junaid changes to round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Soumya Sarkar was playing from his crease and gets an inside edge towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, no run, Junaid shortens his length outside off, punched straight to short point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, no run, tad fuller and on the stumps, Soumya Sarkar presses forward and defends it with an open face towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, 1 run, on a good length and holding its line outside off, Tamim pushes at that and gets an inside edge towards square leg, off strike with a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Soumya Sarkar, no run, fraction fuller and on off, defended from the crease and towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Soumya Sarkar, no run, much better from Rahat, tad fuller and nipping away from off, Soumya Sarkar is slightly opened up as he defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, 1 run, too straight from Rahat, ends up drifting onto Tamim's pads, he gets inside the line and tucks it towards long leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, nicely played by Tamim, back of a length and well outside off, Tamim rides with the bounce and hits it up and over point, the ball races away to the fence in a jiffy]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, no run, on a good length and holding its line outside off, Tamim covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, tad fuller and just outside off, Soumya Sarkar plays with an open face and guides it down towards third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Tamim strides forward and pushes it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, fraction too full and well outside off, Tamim leans forward, presents the full face of the bat, punches it on the up and drives it past cover for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, short of a length and just outside off, punched straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, full and on the stumps, Tamim leans forward and gets an inside edge on the drive, the ball rolls away towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, Junaid keeps it full and just outside off, Tamim gets a big stride forward and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, driven back towards the bowler. Junaid throws it back at the stumps, but Tamim was alert enough to get back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, 1 run, tad fuller and just outside off, Tamim presses forward and gets an inside edge to the left of mid-on, calls for a quick single and gets it with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, first boundary off the Bangladesh innings! This was banged in short and just outside off, Tamim gets on top of the bounce and cracks it square past point for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Tamim, no run, pitched up and in thnat channel around the fifth stump, Tamim prods forward and blocks it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, short of a length and shaping away from outside off, dabbed away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Soumya Sarkar, no run, that's an absolute peach! On a good length and shaping away from outside off, draws Sarkar half-forward before opening him up, zips past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rahat Ali to Soumya Sarkar, 2 runs, that was tentative from Soumya Sarkar, short of a length and in that channel outside off, Sarkar brought his bat down with an angle, gets an inside edge that rolls away past the leg-stump]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rahat Ali, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Tamim leans forward and defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, on a good length and in that corridor outside off, Soumya Sarkar plays with an open face and guides it down towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, no run, appeal for a <b>caught behind</b>, but it wasn't a convincing one, this was pitched up and shaped away late, drew Soumya Sarkar forward and beat his outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, no run, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, Soumya Sarkar prods forward and defends it towards mid-off, the ball went off the inner half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, no run, Junaid keeps it full and in that channel outside off, Soumya Sarkar gets a good stride forward and punches it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, 1 run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, Tamim leans forward and drivs it square behind point for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tamim and Soumya Sarkar are at the crease. Tamim is on strike. Junaid Khan will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[We are set for the first ODI. Junaid Khan will open the bowling. Two slips in place..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pitch Report:</b> There's quite a lot of live grass. There should be good carry and bounce off the deck. The captains will be tempted to play more pacers. The batsmen should be watchful, runs will come as the innings progresses, the team winning the toss might opt to bowl first,' reckons <b>Athar Ali Khan</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangladesh</b> (Playing XI): Tamim Iqbal, Soumya Sarkar, Mahmudullah, Mushfiqur Rahim(w), Shakib Al Hasan(c), Nasir Hossain, Sabbir Rahman, Abul Hasan, Arafat Sunny, Rubel Hossain, Taskin Ahmed]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan</b> (Playing XI): Mohammad Hafeez, Azhar Ali(c), Haris Sohail, Saad Nasim, Fawad Alam, Sarfraz Ahmed(w), Mohammad Rizwan, Wahab Riaz, Junaid Khan, Saeed Ajmal, Rahat Ali]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangladesh have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Both teams have had their share of administrative wrangings and the series will provide them a much needed distraction from events which are out of their control. There's some early team news from the Pakistan camp. <b>Mohammad Rizwan</b>, the wicket-keeper batsman and <b>Saad Nasim</b>, the all-rounder, are set to make their ODI debuts for Pakistan.]]></line><line><![CDATA[On the other hand, hosts, Bangladesh are a confident unit. They put up their best ever performance in the World Cup scalping England before eventually losing to India in the quarter-final at the Melbourne Cricket Ground. Mashrafe Mortaza led an inspired show from the Tigers, but he will be missing today, serving his one-match ban for slow over-rate during the Q/F match against India.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>13:45 Local Time, 07:45 GMT, 13:15 IST:</b> It's the beginning of a new era in Pakistan cricket. Misbah-ul-Haq and Shahid Afridi announced their ODI retirements at the end of the 2015 Cricket World Cup. Saeed Ajmal, who missed the sport's biggest tournament after his action was found to be illegal, returns after having rectified his bowling action. Azhar Ali, who wasn't considered good enough to be a part of the 15-member WC squad has been named as the captain. Wicket-keeper batsman, Sarfraz Ahmed, will be his deputy. Also returning to the team is Mohammad Hafeez, who missed the World Cup with an injury.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/>If one looks at Bangladesh's record against Pakistan, it is abysmal. In 47 international matches spread across formats, Bangladesh have registered just one victory and it came in an ODI 16 years ago during the 1999 World Cup match in Northampton. They have lost 25 consecutive ODIs against them since that day. In the list of bogey teams, Pakistan's name is right on top for Bangladesh. However, in a fresh season, it is time for a new beginning.<br/><br/>It is a new era for Pakistan. With Misbah-ul-Haq retiring from ODIs after the end of the World Cup, the team will be led by Azhar Ali, who last played an ODI two years ago. During his time, Azhar has demonstrated a cool head and the tourists will be hoping for some stability in his leadership.<br/><br/>Already, players from both camps are having their say. Shakib Al Hasan said this series was the best opportunity for Bangladesh to register a win over Pakistan. In the opposition camp, allrounder Mohammad Hafeez pointed out that Pakistan have the resources but cautiously stated that Bangladesh are an improved team. On paper, Pakistan are favorites to continue the dominance but Bangladesh will be determined to snap this losing streak. The home team have already made the right start after a BCB XI defeated a full strength Pakistan team by one wicket during a warm-up match in Fatullah on Wednesday.<br/><br/><b>Venue:</b> Shere Bangla Stadium, Mirpur<br/><br/><b>Date:</b> April 17, 2015<br/><br/><b>Time:</b> 14:30 local<br/><br/><b>Team news:</b><br/><br/><b>Bangladesh</b><br/><br/>Shakib Al Hasan, who was playing for the Kolkata in IPL 8, will come back to lead the team in the first ODI after Mashrafe Moratza was ruled out due to a knee injury. The team will also see Rony Talukdar making his ODI debut. Talukdar was the most consistent performer in the Bangladesh domestic circuit last year when he scored 714 runs in the Dhaka Premier Division while he also made 777 runs in the National Cricket League games. He will partner Tamim Iqbal as Bangladesh search for stability at the top. The batting will once again revolve around the trio of Shakib, Mushfiqur Rahim and Mahmudullah, who became the first Bangladesh player to score consecutive centuries in the World Cup.<br/><br/>Probable XI<br/><br/>1 Tamim Iqbal, 2 Rony Talukdar, 3 Soumya Sarkar, 4 Mahmudullah, 5 Shakib Al Hasan (c), 6 Mushfiqur Rahim (wk), 7 Sabbir Rahman, 8 Nasir Hossain, 9 Rubel Hossain, 10 Abul Hasan, 11 Taskin Ahmed<br/><br/><b>Pakistan</b><br/><br/>The scoreline for Pakistan already reads 3-0. They have lost three players heading into the series. Sohaib Maqsood was ruled out due to a fractured wrist while Sohail Khan, who impressed in the 2015 World Cup, will miss the series due to a back injury. During the warm-up game in Fatullah, Yasir Shah sustained a hand injury which required stitches, thus ruling him out for the ODI series.<br/><br/>However, in addition to a new captain, Pakistan will also welcome back Junaid Khan, who missed the World Cup due to a knee injury and Saeed Ajmal, who will play his first international match after remodelling his action. The team will also see some fresh faces in 22-year-old Mohammad Rizwan, the back-up keeper to Sarfraz Ahmed and also 19-year-old Sami Aslam, who captained the Pakistan U-19 team in the 2014 World Cup. The presence of Junaid and Ajmal will be reassuring for a team that has struggled in bilateral series. In the last 13 ODIs, they have won just three games. Pakistan will aim to improve their record in bilateral ODIs in a new season.<br/><br/>Probable XI<br/><br/>1 Mohammad Hafeez, 2 Sami Aslam, 3 Haris Sohail, 4 Azhar Ali (c), 5 Sarfraz Ahmed (wk), 6 Asad Shafiq, 7 Saad Nasim, 8 Wahab Riaz, 9 Saeed Ajmal, 10 Junaid Khan, 11 Rahat Ali/Ehsan Adil<br/><br/><b>Quotes</b><br/><br/>"We break down mentally when we lose a practice match abroad. Pakistan might be having the same thought process, which will have some effect on the first game. We will try to play better cricket." - Bangladesh legspinner Sabbir Rahman fires a psychological salvo at Pakistan following a win by the BCB XI over them in Fatullah on Wednesday.<br/><br/>"It might look easy to beat them but they never been as easy. For the last 2-3 years, they have developed into a good team." - Pakistan allrounder Mohammad Hafeez has urged his team not to take Bangladesh lightly.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan</b> (From): Mohammad Hafeez, Azhar Ali(c), Haris Sohail, Saad Nasim, Fawad Alam, Sarfraz Ahmed(w), Asad Shafiq, Wahab Riaz, Junaid Khan, Saeed Ajmal, Rahat Ali, Sami Aslam, Mohammad Rizwan, Ehsan Adil]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangladesh</b> (From): Tamim Iqbal, Rony Talukdar, Soumya Sarkar, Mahmudullah, Shakib Al Hasan(c), Mushfiqur Rahim(w), Sabbir Rahman, Nasir Hossain, Arafat Sunny, Rubel Hossain, Taskin Ahmed, Abul Hasan, Mominul Haque]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>329</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>6</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>50</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Bangladesh">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>612</playerid>
					<name>Tamim Iqbal</name>
					<batsman-name>Tamim</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Tamim</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>132</runs>
					<balls>135</balls>
					<fours>15</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Riaz</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1051</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mohammad Rizwan</fielder>
						<fielderId>9468</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8233</playerid>
					<name>Soumya Sarkar</name>
					<batsman-name>Soumya Sarkar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Soumya Sarkar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>20</runs>
					<balls>36</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Wahab Riaz</fielder>
						<fielderId>1051</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1121</playerid>
					<name>Mahmudullah</name>
					<batsman-name>Mahmudullah</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mahmudullah</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>5</runs>
					<balls>18</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Rahat Ali</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8301</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>394</playerid>
					<name>Mushfiqur Rahim</name>
					<batsman-name>Rahim</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rahim</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>106</runs>
					<balls>77</balls>
					<fours>13</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Riaz</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1051</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sarfraz Ahmed</fielder>
						<fielderId>881</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>544</playerid>
					<name>Shakib Al Hasan</name>
					<batsman-name>Shakib</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shakib</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>31</runs>
					<balls>27</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Riaz</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1051</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8231</playerid>
					<name>Sabbir Rahman</name>
					<batsman-name>S Rahman</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Rahman</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>15</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Riaz</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1051</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8018</playerid>
					<name>Nasir Hossain</name>
					<batsman-name>Nasir Hossain</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nasir Hossain</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8332</playerid>
					<name>Abul Hasan</name>
					<batsman-name>Abul Hasan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Abul Hasan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8243</playerid>
					<name>Arafat Sunny</name>
					<batsman-name>A Sunny</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>A Sunny</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1736</playerid>
					<name>Rubel Hossain</name>
					<batsman-name>Rubel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rubel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8548</playerid>
					<name>Taskin Ahmed</name>
					<batsman-name>Taskin Ahmed</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Taskin Ahmed</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8233</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>48</runs>
				<overs>13.2</overs>
				<batsman>Soumya Sarkar</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Soumya Sarkar</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1121</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>67</runs>
				<overs>19.6</overs>
				<batsman>Mahmudullah</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mahmudullah</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>612</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>245</runs>
				<overs>41.4</overs>
				<batsman>Tamim Iqbal</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Tamim</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>394</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>295</runs>
				<overs>47.2</overs>
				<batsman>Mushfiqur Rahim</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rahim</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8231</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>325</runs>
				<overs>49.4</overs>
				<batsman>Sabbir Rahman</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Rahman</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>544</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>329</runs>
				<overs>49.6</overs>
				<batsman>Shakib Al Hasan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Shakib</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>4</byes>
			<wides>8</wides>
			<noballs>1</noballs>
			<legbyes>4</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>17</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Pakistan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7900</playerid>
					<name>Junaid Khan</name>
					<bowler-name>Junaid Khan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Junaid Khan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>53</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8301</playerid>
					<name>Rahat Ali</name>
					<bowler-name>Rahat Ali</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rahat Ali</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>56</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1051</playerid>
					<name>Wahab Riaz</name>
					<bowler-name>Riaz</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Riaz</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>59</runsoff>
					<wickets>4</wickets>
					<wides>5</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1053</playerid>
					<name>Saeed Ajmal</name>
					<bowler-name>Ajmal</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ajmal</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>74</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10094</playerid>
					<name>Saad Nasim</name>
					<bowler-name>Saad Nasim</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Saad Nasim</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>31</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8299</playerid>
					<name>Haris Sohail</name>
					<bowler-name>H Sohail</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sohail</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>31</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6633</playerid>
					<name>Azhar Ali</name>
					<bowler-name>Azhar Ali</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Azhar Ali</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>17</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>360</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Hafeez</name>
					<bowler-name>M Hafeez</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Hafeez</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>697</playerid>
					<name>Fawad Alam</name>
					<bowler-name>F Alam</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Fawad Alam</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>881</playerid>
					<name>Sarfraz Ahmed</name>
					<bowler-name>S Ahmed</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sarfraz Ahmed</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9468</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Rizwan</name>
					<bowler-name>M Rizwan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rizwan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>250</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>10</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>45.2</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Pakistan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>6633</playerid>
					<name>Azhar Ali</name>
					<batsman-name>Azhar Ali</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Azhar Ali</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>72</runs>
					<balls>73</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Taskin Ahmed</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8548</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mushfiqur Rahim</fielder>
						<fielderId>394</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>881</playerid>
					<name>Sarfraz Ahmed</name>
					<batsman-name>S Ahmed</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sarfraz Ahmed</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>24</runs>
					<balls>31</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>A Sunny</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8243</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Nasir Hossain</fielder>
						<fielderId>8018</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>360</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Hafeez</name>
					<batsman-name>M Hafeez</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Hafeez</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Soumya Sarkar</fielder>
						<fielderId>8233</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Mushfiqur Rahim</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>394</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8299</playerid>
					<name>Haris Sohail</name>
					<batsman-name>H Sohail</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sohail</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>51</runs>
					<balls>64</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Taskin Ahmed</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8548</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mahmudullah</fielder>
						<fielderId>1121</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9468</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Rizwan</name>
					<batsman-name>M Rizwan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rizwan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>67</runs>
					<balls>58</balls>
					<fours>8</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Rubel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1736</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Nasir Hossain</fielder>
						<fielderId>8018</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>697</playerid>
					<name>Fawad Alam</name>
					<batsman-name>F Alam</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Fawad Alam</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>14</runs>
					<balls>19</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>A Sunny</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8243</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Soumya Sarkar</fielder>
						<fielderId>8233</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10094</playerid>
					<name>Saad Nasim</name>
					<batsman-name>Saad Nasim</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Saad Nasim</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>A Sunny</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8243</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1051</playerid>
					<name>Wahab Riaz</name>
					<batsman-name>Riaz</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Riaz</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>8</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Taskin Ahmed</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8548</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1053</playerid>
					<name>Saeed Ajmal</name>
					<batsman-name>Ajmal</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ajmal</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Shakib</bowler>
					<bowlerId>544</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7900</playerid>
					<name>Junaid Khan</name>
					<batsman-name>Junaid Khan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Junaid Khan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sabbir Rahman</fielder>
						<fielderId>8231</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8301</playerid>
					<name>Rahat Ali</name>
					<batsman-name>Rahat Ali</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rahat Ali</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>881</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>53</runs>
				<overs>10.2</overs>
				<batsman>Sarfraz Ahmed</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Ahmed</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>360</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>59</runs>
				<overs>12.1</overs>
				<batsman>Mohammad Hafeez</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Hafeez</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6633</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>148</runs>
				<overs>27.3</overs>
				<batsman>Azhar Ali</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Azhar Ali</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8299</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>175</runs>
				<overs>31.5</overs>
				<batsman>Haris Sohail</batsman>
				<batsman-name>H Sohail</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>697</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>217</runs>
				<overs>39.2</overs>
				<batsman>Fawad Alam</batsman>
				<batsman-name>F Alam</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>10094</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>217</runs>
				<overs>39.6</overs>
				<batsman>Saad Nasim</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Saad Nasim</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1051</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>244</runs>
				<overs>43.6</overs>
				<batsman>Wahab Riaz</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Riaz</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9468</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>249</runs>
				<overs>44.3</overs>
				<batsman>Mohammad Rizwan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Rizwan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7900</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>249</runs>
				<overs>45</overs>
				<batsman>Junaid Khan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Junaid Khan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1053</playerid>
				<nbr>10</nbr>
				<runs>250</runs>
				<overs>45.2</overs>
				<batsman>Saeed Ajmal</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Ajmal</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>6</wides>
			<noballs>1</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>9</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Bangladesh">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1736</playerid>
					<name>Rubel Hossain</name>
					<bowler-name>Rubel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rubel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>45</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8548</playerid>
					<name>Taskin Ahmed</name>
					<bowler-name>Taskin Ahmed</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Taskin Ahmed</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>42</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>5</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8243</playerid>
					<name>Arafat Sunny</name>
					<bowler-name>A Sunny</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>A Sunny</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>47</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>544</playerid>
					<name>Shakib Al Hasan</name>
					<bowler-name>Shakib</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shakib</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9.2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>45</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8018</playerid>
					<name>Nasir Hossain</name>
					<bowler-name>Nasir Hossain</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nasir Hossain</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>20</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8332</playerid>
					<name>Abul Hasan</name>
					<bowler-name>Abul Hasan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Abul Hasan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>42</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1121</playerid>
					<name>Mahmudullah</name>
					<bowler-name>Mahmudullah</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mahmudullah</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>7</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>612</playerid>
					<name>Tamim Iqbal</name>
					<bowler-name>Tamim</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Tamim</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8233</playerid>
					<name>Soumya Sarkar</name>
					<bowler-name>Soumya Sarkar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Soumya Sarkar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>394</playerid>
					<name>Mushfiqur Rahim</name>
					<bowler-name>Rahim</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rahim</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8231</playerid>
					<name>Sabbir Rahman</name>
					<bowler-name>S Rahman</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Rahman</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



