<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14718" >
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>3rd ODI</gameDesc>
		<series>Pakistan tour of Bangladesh, 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Bangladesh</home>
		<away>Pakistan</away>
		<teamsabbr>BAN vs PAK</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>BAN</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>PAK</awayabbr>
		<homeId>6</homeId>
		<awayId>3</awayId>
		<venue>Shere Bangla National Stadium, Dhaka</venue>
		<startdate>22 04 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>22 04 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Pakistan</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Bangladesh won by 8 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Bangladesh</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>8</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries>Tamim Iqbal</manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Ruchira Palliyaguru</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Sharfuddoula</Name>
			<Country>Ban</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Nigel Llong</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Jeff Crowe</Name>
			<Country>NZ</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>08:30</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150422154810</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>Ban</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>Pak</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>251</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>2</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>39.3</batteamovers>
		<status>Bangladesh won by 8 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>394</playerid>
			<name>Mushfiqur Rahim*</name>
			<batsman-name>Rahim</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Rahim</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>49</runs>
			<balls-faced>43</balls-faced>
			<fours>6</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>8233</playerid>
			<name>Soumya Sarkar</name>
			<batsman-name>Soumya Sarkar</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Soumya Sarkar</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>127</runs>
			<balls-faced>110</balls-faced>
			<fours>13</fours>
			<sixes>6</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>7900</playerid>
			<name>Junaid Khan*</name>
			<bowler-name>Junaid Khan</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Junaid Khan</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>7.3</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>67</runs>
			<wickets>2</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1051</playerid>
			<name>Wahab Riaz</name>
			<bowler-name>Riaz</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Riaz</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>6</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>30</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>251</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>1121</playerid>
<name>Mahmudullah</name>
<player-runs>4</player-runs>
<player-balls>10</player-balls>
<runs>154</runs>
<wicket-nbr>2</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>7900</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Junaid Khan</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>4</wides>
			<noballs>2</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[1 1 . . 6 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 4 4 6 1 2 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 1 1 1 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. N4 2 4 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/BAN_PAK_2015/BAN_PAK_APR22/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[Whether they do so remains to be seen. It has been fun bringing you the game today. Do join us for all the action from the remainder of the series. There is IPL and a Test match going on - if you still want your cricket fix. Head over there. Until next time it's goodbye from all of us here. Remember to sleep tight! Sayonara!]]></line><line><![CDATA[For Pakistan this is a hard lesson for young Azhar Ali and Co. Granted a few seniors have left but losing a series 0-3 is not what they would've envisaged before the start of this tour. They have been comprehensively outplayed by hungrier opposition. The tour isn't over. There is still a T20 and a couple of Tests to follow. So Pakistan would be hoping to turn a corner there.]]></line><line><![CDATA[So after failing to win an ODI for close to 15 years and 320 days against Pakistan, Bangladesh have 'Banglawashed' Pakistan in the space of 6 days. And they have done it with style, passion, flair and gumption. Pakistan were thrashed in all the three games. The last two games Bangladesh chased 250 as if they had an appointment elsewhere. Terrific all-round performance by them as a team. They have completely annihilated the opposition.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Tamim:</b> 'Finally I'm enjoying my batting. That is the main thing. Thanks to the team and the coaching staff, they supported me when I wasn't doing well. Special thanks to Mushy and Mash - they were brilliant and were always talking to me and gave me confidence when I wasn't getting runs. We dominated the series. The boys showed their character and Bangladesh is ready to take another step. We always believe that we have the talent to play against the big boys and now is the time to show them']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Tamim Iqbal is the Man of the Series for his 312 runs in the series.</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Unfortunately he is speaking in Bangla and I have no clue. So can't bring you guys what he says. Sorry!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Soumya Sarkar is the Man of the Match for his stunning innings</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mortaza:</b> 'The way the boys are playing it is very pleasing for me and the team as well. The boys are performing every day which is good. Tamim has been brilliant whole tournament as was Soumya today. We have got the confidence and we delivered in the middle. Our main focus will be the T20 day after and then the Test match.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Azhar Ali:</b> 'I would like to congratulate the Bangladeshi team. Their team management needs applauding. They played good cricket. Our team played well in patches. But we didn't put it together. We need to come back well and play as a combined unit. A few senior players are missing. The youngsters have to stand up. We didn't do it this series. We need to put our hands up and perform as unit. In T20s and Tests we have some experienced guys and you will see an improved performance there.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rahim:</b> 'It is a great moment for Bangladesh cricket. We have whitewashed a few other teams but to whitewash Pakistan is a great achievement. Someone puts their hands up and does their job. My job is to bat as many overs as I can and score runs. I want to keep this going.']]></line><line><![CDATA[Another comprehensive win for Bangladesh. Chasing 251, openers Soumya Sarkar and Tamim Iqbal shared an excellent 145-run stand, before the latter was dismissed. Tamim completed his 29th ODI fifty and this is the first time in the series that he was dismissed before scoring a hundred. Although Mahmudullah went soon after, Sarkar carried on and completed his maiden ODI hundred. Mushfiqur Rahim then gave Sarkar good company and the duo took Bangladesh past the line to sweep the ODI series 3-0. Although Junaid Khan picked up two wickets, he was very expensive. Umar Gul wasn't impressive in his comeback game either. Mohammad Hafeez being cleared to bowl by the ICC came as big boost for Pakistan, but he could not give them a breakthrough, despite bowling an economical spell.]]></line><line><![CDATA[It is a carnival atmosphere at the Sher-e-Bangla tonight. The crowd are going mental. The players walk off and the Pakistanis wait to shake hands with their counterparts. Mortaza is all smiles. As are all the Bangladeshis. 'It is a magical moment' says Athar Ali Khan on air and I agree. Bangladesh may have reached the World Cup quarter-final but sweeping Pakistan 3-0 is perhaps their greatest achievement in ODIs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>Pakistan have been Banglawashed!</b> All over! Down leg, Rahim had to get bat on it and just did that, glancing it down to fine leg, beating short fine inside the ring. Rahim lets out a mighty roar after hitting the winning runs. He has his hands aloft in joy and hugs Soumya Sarkar]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, 2 runs, he tried but couldn't. Steps out and it is short, Rahim upper cuts wide of third man. Only a two as the fielder gets across and stops]]></line><line><![CDATA[Can Rahim finish it off on a high?]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, <b>no ball</b>, <b>FOUR</b>, did Rahim hear the no-ball call? It doesn't matter now as Rahim charges Junaid Khan and smashes it straight back over the bowler's head. Connected well and now it will be a <b>free-hit</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, no run, good length outside off, Rahim tries to run it down and is beaten. Was too close to be playing that shot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Junaid Khan [7.0-0-56-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Six singles off the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Rahim, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Rahim gets forward and drives to mid-off, takes the quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, Soumya Sarkar shuffles across outside off and wrists that short-arm pull to deep backward square leg, another single]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Rahim, 1 run, short of length, sliding across Rahim who runs it down with an open face to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, Riaz follows Soumya Sarkar with a pacy back of a length delivery on leg, the batsman makes room and dabs it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Rahim, 1 run, good length outside off, Rahim opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, short of length outside off, dabbed with an open face to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz [5.0-0-24-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Rahim, 2 runs, short of length outside off, dabbed down to third man. Babar has work to do and does so well, running around to his left and cutting it off. Saves two]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, on the pads, flicked to deep mid-wicket, sensible batting]]></line><line><![CDATA[A discussion about field placements as Umar Gul takes a breather]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, <b>SIX</b>, Soumya Sarkar is in overdrive now. He comes down the track and sends the length ball from Umar Gul soaring into the stands at deep mid-wicket. Soumya Sarkar gave it plenty and it carried way back. Umar Gul just stood there and grimaced. This is exceptional batting from the young Sarkar. He is toying with one of the best death bowlers in the world]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, now one bounce over the ropes and a four to deep mid-wicket. Slower short ball outside off, Soumya Sarkar was waiting on the back foot and hammered the pull beating two fielders on the leg-side boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, that has been rifled past the left-hand of Umar Gul. Full on the stumps, Soumya Sarkar shows the full face of the bat and drills it in the air over the bowler. That went away very quickly to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Rahim, 1 run, good length outside off, Rahim opens the face of the bat and steers to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Soumya Sarkar, no run, very optimistic from Babar, Soumya Sarkar is beaten on the sweep, the line is middle and leg and it hits the batsman high on the pad. The umpire rightly rules it not out]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Soumya Sarkar, <b>SIX</b>, all the fielders are in on the off-side, Soumya Sarkar goes over mid-off. Uses his feet and then whips the loft over the infield. Just about carries all the way. Soumya Sarkar and Rahim punch gloves. Soumya Sarkar has a big smile on his face]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Soumya Sarkar, no run, short down leg, Babar gets away, Soumya Sarkar pulls straight to the fielder at short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Soumya Sarkar, no run, turning in, clipped straight to the fielder at mid-wicket. Was in the air, but fell short]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, 1 run, allows the length ball to turn across him and then nudges it off the back foot wide of mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, Soumya Sarkar uses his feet and drags the loft to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, <b>straight in and straight out.</b> That is a sitter and Junaid has dropped it at deep mid-wicket. Short on the stumps, Soumya Sarkar pulls and Junaid after getting both hands shells it. Nothing going right for Pakistan]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, no run, was that dropped? Need a replay. Soumya Sarkar missed a hook to a very short delivery and Rizwan fumbled after leaping. Cannot glove that and the umpire signals one short ball for the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, no run, pitched up on off, Soumya Sarkar drills that hard towards Rahim and looks like it has deflected off Rahim's bat, that spoils all timing and rolls to mid-off. Soumya Sarkar hit that really well]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Rahim, 1 run, good length outside off, steered down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Rahim, no run, short of length on off, Rahim defends solidly to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[This is now batting powerplay time]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, the runs keep flowing. Short and wide outside off, Rahim cuts in the air and wide of backward point's left. Third man can't get across in time]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Umar Gul [5.0-0-29-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Soumya Sarkar, no run, tossed up outside off, Soumya Sarkar attempts a reverse sweep and is hit on the right bicep]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, 3 runs, turn and bounce for Babar, produces the outside edge but it falls in front of Hafeez at first slip and runs through his hands. They take three. Lovely delivery from Babar, angled in and spun away after pitching, opened Rahim up completely]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, 2 runs, turn and bounce for Babar, Rahim handles it well, steering it wide of slip for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, that has been given as runs. Drifting down leg, Rahim looked like he had missed it. Deflected off the thigh pad I suppose and races away to the fence. Umpire gives it as runs though]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Rahim gets forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, no run, tossed up outside off, Rahim defends with an open face to backward point, they don't risk the single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Soumya Sarkar, <b>SIX</b>, Soumya Sarkar is all smiles as he brings up his <b>maiden ODI ton.</b> Dragged down short from Azhar Ali, a gift and Soumya Sarkar latches on. Rocks back and pulls over deep mid-wicket. Had to clear the fielder and did so. Knew as soon as he hit it that it was his moment. Swings the bat wildly in celebration. Takes the helmet off and has a word with Rahim]]></line><line><![CDATA[Slip added now]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Soumya Sarkar, no run, another googly and Soumya Sarkar doesn't read it well, gets forward to defend and the extra bounce beats the forward defence. Lovely delivery but no edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Soumya Sarkar, no run, tentative from Soumya Sarkar that time, googly from Azhar Ali, keeps a bit low, Soumya Sarkar turns to leg and gets an inside edge onto the pads. That could've gone anywhere]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Rahim, 1 run, low full toss on the stumps, Rahim digs it out to mid-on, quick single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Rahim, no run, bit of turn for Azhar Ali, Rahim defends cautiously to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azhar Ali to Rahim, no run, tossed up outside off, Rahim gets forward and defends to point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Azhar Ali, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Rahim gets forward to defend and gets a thick inside edge to short fine leg, takes the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, flat outside off, punched off the back foot to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Soumya Sarkar, no run, waits for the ball to turn in and then nudges it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, 1 run, well tossed up on the stumps, Rahim gets forward and drives to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, Rahim uses his feet and smashes the drive to deep extra cover, hit all along the ground and hits the gap]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, no run, flatter and outside off, Rahim defends off the back foot wide of silly point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[That will be <b>drinks.</b> Soumya Sarkar has batted brilliantly and it will only take a miracle from Pakistan to pull this game out of the hat. Bangladesh have all the momentum and the crowd behind them and look unstoppable in this series.]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, no run, dug in short and Soumya Sarkar half ducks to let it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, no run, slower delivery on off, Soumya Sarkar gets forward and looks to drive hard, mistimed to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, Soumya Sarkar is taking on every bowler and is putting them to the sword. On a back of a length on off, he is quick to rock back and muscles the pull over mid-wicket. Moves to 94]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Rahim, 1 run, good length on off, Rahim opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[Just a slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Rahim, no run, short of length on off, defended from the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, short outside off, Soumya Sarkar ramps and ensures he keeps it down in front of the fielder, doesn't carry to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz [4.0-0-18-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, no run, short and wide outside off, turning away, cut straight to the fielder at point. Missed out there]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, no run, pushed through on off, Rahim in defending gets a thick inside edge onto the pads. Babar felt that he nearly got through there]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, no run, flatter on middle and leg, Rahim defends and defends late]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, 2 runs, Babar almost gets Rahim. The keeper going over cover and just about clears a leaping Saad Nasim. Mistimed and Rahim got lucky as the fielder running back didn't get a finger on it]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Rahim defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, no run, tossed up outside off, Rahim drives in the air but falls short of cover. Not too wide of short cover as well]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, take that Junaid Khan says Soumya Sarkar. Charges the bowler and hits it over his head. Much more of a clean strike that and a couple of bounces before it races away to the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, Soumya Sarkar swings over mid-on and gets a boundary. On a length and outside off, Soumya Sarkar wants to finish it off quickly. That was cross-batted but got enough elevation to clear mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, 1 run, good length outside off, Rahim gets forward and dabs to cover, wide of the fielder and single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, <b>FOUR</b>, that has raced away to third man, good length outside off, Rahim opens the face of the bat and steers very late past the lone slip, raced across the turf, third man ran across and didn't dive]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, angled in on the stumps, flicked wide of mid-on for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, 1 run, good length on middle, Rahim closes the face of the bat and tucks it through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, 1 run, flighted delivery outside off, Rahim gets forward and drives to long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, no run, fired in quicker, Rahim lunges out to defend to off]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, no run, and again, flatter on the stumps, Rahim defends off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, no run, Rahim wants to come forward but isn't allowed to do so by Babar, defended with an open face to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, no run, tossed up outside off, Rahim gets forward and drives to the right of short cover, bit of confusion between the batsmen but they don't risk the quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Three men around the bat for Rahim]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Rahim, no run, flatter and turns away, Rahim handles that off the back foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Rahim, 1 run, back of a length on the hips, tucked away to deep backward square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mushfiqur Rahim, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Mahmudullah, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Good comeback by Junaid Khan. He bowls Mahmudullah out. Pitched up on off, went through the shot of Mahmudullah who was aiming for a drive on the rise. The ball sneaks between bat and pad to hit the top of off. Junaid Khan exults. <b>Mahmudullah b Junaid Khan 4(10) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Junaid Khan to Mahmudullah, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Mahmudullah, <b>FOUR</b>, Mahmudullah puts away the free-hit to the deep mid-wicket fence. Very full on the stumps, Mahmudullah cleared his front leg and then hoicked it over mid-wicket. One bounce and over the ropes. Sweetly struck]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Free-hit.</b> Junaid Khan round the wicket to Mahmudullah]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, <b>no ball</b>, 1 run, Junaid Khan oversteps and Soumya Sarkar plays a fine drive on the rise to sweeper cover, single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, 2 runs, short of length outside off, Soumya Sarkar stands tall and cracks it square of the wicket, for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[Fawad Alam helps out Soumya Sarkar with his bat grip]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, no run, Rizwan is appealing for everything, even when he knows there is no edge. Soumya Sarkar using his feet and missing a swipe to a length ball, the ball flies over the stumps. Daylight between bat and ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, no run, shortish on the stumps, Soumya Sarkar rocks back and pulls but mid-wicket goes to his left to field. That was mistimed as well]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Mahmudullah, no run, loud shout for lbw but the height would've been an issue there. The slider from Babar, Mahmudullah misses the forward defence and is hit on the back leg, bouncing over. The umpire shakes his head and Pakistan don't have any reviews left]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Mahmudullah, no run, sliding down leg, Mahmudullah flicks and misses. There are three men close-in now, with a silly point added to the fray]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Mahmudullah, no run, that has hit the bat splice and fallen in the vacant silly point region. Extra bounce for Babar as Mahmudullah pushed forward to defend]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Mahmudullah, no run, very full on middle and leg, Mahmudullah eases it back to Babar]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Mahmudullah, no run, that keeps a bit low, Mahmudullah handles it well and keeps it out]]></line><line><![CDATA[Slip and a short leg. Now round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Soumya Sarkar slog sweeps hard to deep mid-wicket, hit hard and the fielder did well to get across to that]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Mahmudullah, no run, that has pitched outside leg and can't be given out lbw. Raps Mahmudullah on the thigh pad. Height would've been a factor as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Mahmudullah, no run, that is a fine delivery from Junaid Khan, pushes this good length delivery across Mahmudullah who stayed in the crease and flirted out. Nearly feathered it through]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Mahmudullah, no run, short of length on off, Mahmudullah wrists it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mahmudullah, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Nips back in and beats Tamim's attempted dab to third man. Was too close to be playing that and Tamim pays for his cheekiness. It struck him in line and the original decision will stand. Hitting the stumps as the replays showed. <b>Tamim lbw b Junaid Khan 64(76) [4s-8 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Junaid Khan to Tamim, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Tamim has been given out lbw. But he is reviewing it. Looks out at first glance. Pad first and impact seems to be in line as well. Umpire's call and Pakistan have got their first wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, this back of a length delivery hurries onto Soumya Sarkar and his pull eludes mid-wicket running back. Falls in no-man's land. Soumya Sarkar completely mistimed that]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, very poor from Junaid Khan and Soumya Sarkar puts him away. Short and down leg, sat up to be hit and Soumya Sarkar pulls hard to the deep backward square leg fence. It didn't bounce high to trouble Sarkar]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Tamim, no run, flighted outside off, Tamim dabs it in front of cover, wants a quick single, Soumya Sarkar isn't interested]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Tamim, no run, tossed up outside off, Tamim gets forward and wrists it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, whatever Soumya Sarkar can do, Tamim says he can emulate him. He does just that with a reverse sweep, gloving it wide of the short third fielder, Gul gave chase but he was beaten to the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Tamim, 2 runs, Tamim takes it from outside off and paddles it fine to fine leg, for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, Soumya Sarkar uses his feet and wrists it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, Soumya Sarkar shows off his wide array of strokes. Sees the tossed up delivery outside off and reverse sweeps wide of backward point. Played all along the ground and gets it in the gap. Superbly executed]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, short of length on off, no room to work with for Tamim who dabs to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, tries to repeat the blow and almost holes out. Length delivery on the stumps, Soumya Sarkar went for a cross-batted slog and got enough to clear mid-on running back. Soumya Sarkar got lucky there]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, <b>SIX</b>, Soumya Sarkar is making the crowd go mad with his daredevilry batting. Charges Junaid Khan and then slogs the pacer over long-on. More of a pre-meditated hit that but Soumya Sarkar emerged victor]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, 1 run, good length outside off, Tamim comes down the track and slashes hard, the ball flies away to third man, Tamim's body twisted in all directions as he gave it his all]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, good length on off, Tamim gets forward and defends solidly to cover. What do we have here? Pakistan reckon that it was pad first and review for an lbw. It wasn't a big appeal as well from Pakistan. Impact - umpire's call and Tamim will stay. Pakistan waste a review. That is sheer desperation as Pakistan look for an elusive breakthrough]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, short of length on the stumps, Tamim brings the bat down late and defends to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Junaid Khan [3.0-0-19-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Tamim, 1 run, pushed to the right of the bowler for a quick single, Tamim and Soumya Sarkar harrying the Pakistanis]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Tamim, no run, turned to short leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Tamim, no run, tossed up on the stumps, Tamim gets forward and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, now Tamim is looking to entertain. Skips out and slices the lofted hit over mid-off. Got it over the man and it's an easy boundary. He is making batting look easy at the moment]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Tamim, no run, shortish on the stumps, punched off the back foot to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>50 for Tamim. After two tons in the series.</b> Spinning down leg, Tamim got a feather on the sweep and gets it fine, runs away to the fence. The crowd clear their throats]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, 1 run, comes down the track and lofts on the bounce to long-off, wanted to go over cover but hit it straighter]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, no run, looks for a drop and run to short cover, but Soumya Sarkar isn't interested, sends his partner back, the fielder was to the ball quickly]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, <b>SIX</b>, now Tamim gives Hafeez the treatment. Comes down and hits it inside out over cover. Got to the pitch and timed it really well, all the way over the ropes. Tamim moves to 47 with that meaty blow]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, flighted outside off, Soumya Sarkar gets forward and eases it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, <b>SIX</b>, Soumya Sarkar breaks the shackles with a big hit. Charges Hafeez and swings across the line over deep mid-wicket. Went miles back as Soumya Sarkar connected really well with the shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, no run, flatter and Soumya Sarkar defends off the back foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Tamim, no run, <b>definite dropped catch.</b> Tamim lunging out to flick and getting an inside edge, it looped to short leg who leapt and couldn't hold on, despite getting both hands. The fielder tried his best but the ball eluded him. Pakistan needed that]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, Soumya Sarkar uses his feet and clips with the turn to fine leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Soumya Sarkar, no run, flatter and on the stumps, Soumya Sarkar defends off the back foot to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[Slip and a short leg in]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Tamim, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Tamim kneels down and sweeps softly to fine leg, controlled shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Tamim, no run, turn and bounce for Babar, Tamim stretches out to defend and is hit on the body]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Tamim, no run, the ball spins and turns in, Tamim shoulders arms and allows to hit him on the body. Runs away to fine leg, they take the single but rightly the umpire signals dead ball for the batsman didn't play a shot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, 1 run, flighted delivery outside off, driven off the front foot to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, no run, flatter on off, Tamim gets forward and blocks it back down the track]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Soumya Sarkar gets forward and drives to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, no run, uses his feet and flicks, gets an inside edge onto the pads, the ball rolls to mid-wicket, sent back by Tamim and Soumya Sarkar makes it in time, beating the direct hit]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, no run, flatter outside off, cut straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, 1 run, Tamim comes down the track and makes room to go inside out, but finds long-off, just a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Tamim, 1 run, turned to the right of the backward square leg, quick single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Tamim, no run, turning in, Tamim clips it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, that is put away. Takes it on the full and reverse sweeps it past the diving point, to the left of the man and once he beat the fielder it was a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, 50 for Soumya Sarkar. He turns this flighted delivery wide of mid-wicket for a quick single. A raise of the bat after reaching the landmark]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Soumya Sarkar, no run, Babar dragged the length back as he saw the batsman advancing, Soumya Sarkar defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[Just a slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Babar to Soumya Sarkar, no run, tossed up outside off, Soumya Sarkar gets forward and wrists it to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Zulfiqar Babar, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, no run, another false stroke, Tamim looking to flick and gets a leading edge that goes to ground, to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, no run, Tamim comes down the track and gets an inside edge onto the pads. Hafeez appealed for an lbw but Tamim got bat on the shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, no run, gets his front foot across and flicks the flighted delivery to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, punched down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, no run, slider on the leg stump, Sarkar gets an inside edge onto pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, no run, was that <b>dropped</b>? Hafeez is not happy. Oh yes! That was an outside edge. Flighted delivery on the off stump, Sarkar looks to defend off the front foot, gets an edge but the keeper spills the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Hafeez [5.0-1-19-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> will be taken. Bangladesh are coasting and are well on their way. Pakistan need wickets and quickly. Bad news - the wicket isn't helping them at all. The batsmen look very confident out there]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, that nips back in and has Soumya Sarkar in some trouble, but he gently nudges it to square leg, and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, 1 run, down leg, clipped to fine leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, no run, back of a length on the stumps, Tamim gets right behind the line and defends solidly]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, no run, that hit the bat splice as Tamim pushed forward. Extra bounce off a good length and Tamim defends to the mid-wicket fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, angling in down leg, clipped to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, 1 run, short of length outside off, Tamim dabs it close to his body and gets it to square third man, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, 1 run, full on the stumps, flicked to deep square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, 2 runs, Tamim is on the front foot, then waits for it and steers the good length delivery square of the wicket for a couple, good aggressive running]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, now a false stroke as Soumya Sarkar looks for a cover drive, the thick inside edge runs away to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, no run, uppish and just to the right of Junaid Khan in his followthrough. Soumya Sarkar showing the full face and driving, Junaid Khan went for it but it was too far wide of him]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, no run, pitched up on the stumps, driven with a full face to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, no run, no edge on the pull and Rizwan once again goes up for a caught behind appeal. The umpire shakes his head though. Soumya Sarkar into the shot early and missed]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, short of length down leg, clipped to fine leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, no run, Riaz follows Soumya Sarkar who was making room, short of length on the stumps, defended to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, no run, good length outside off, Soumya Sarkar went for a big shot over cover and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, no run, short of length on off, Soumya Sarkar stays beside the line of the ball and punches to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[Tamim then points out the fallen towel to the Pakistanis]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, 1 run, Riaz loses his towel which was tucked behind his back as he runs in, that doesn't distract Tamim who guides a back of a length delivery outside off to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, no run, short of length on the stumps, clipped straight to the fielder at mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, no run, Soumya Sarkar has played well so far but that is a bad shot. Tries a pre-meditated heave to a good length delivery outside off and misses. Wasn't far from the off stump, Junaid Khan grimaces]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, 1 run, short of length outside off, dabbed down to third man, it was close to his body but Tamim played it well]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pakistan badly need a wicket to get back into this game. Maybe a couple will do nicely at the moment]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, fullish on the stumps, flicked in the air but wide of mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, 1 run, good length angled in, Tamim closes the face of the bat and tucks it through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, pitched up outside off, now Soumya Sarkar stands tall and drives to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, that is a magnificent shot. On a good length and outside off, Soumya Sarkar plays a tremendous front foot slash, all along the ground and beats point to his right. No chance for third man to his left. That sped along the turf very quickly]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, back of a length outside off, Soumya Sarkar opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man, takes the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, no run, did it take a feather? Rizwan leaping up and collecting, certainly thought so. Short and climbing outside off, Soumya Sarkar tried the upper dab and didn't connect. Rizwan made a good take and thought the batsman got something on it. They had a chat but decided against the review. Replays showed nothing]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, no run, pacy back of a length delivery on middle and leg, follows Soumya Sarkar who was making room, the batsman gets an inside edge onto the pads on the flick]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, <b>wide</b>, short and down leg, Soumya Sarkar pulls and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, 1 run, back of a length on the hips, nudged to deep backward square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, no run, short of length on the stumps, turned to mid-wicket, sends Soumya Sarkar back]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, cracking cut shot. Fraction short outside off, Tamim got on top of the bounce and slashed it up and over point. Almost went all the way, one bounce over the ropes. That time Tamim relied on timing and played a crisp stroke]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[On a slow wicket Tamim is trying to hit the ball too hard and that is spoiling all his timing]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, no run, short of length outside off, punched to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, 1 run, Tamim once again mishits as he uses his feet and tries to blast Junaid Khan through cover. Gets a single wide of mid-off though]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, poor delivery and Tamim won't miss out. Full toss on the stumps, flicked away behind square, beats deep backward square running across. Raced across the turf]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, Umar Gul does well at mid-on to dive to his right and save three runs. Soumya Sarkar this time skipping out and hitting to the right of mid-off. Gul's effort was praiseworthy as he dived full length]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, 1 run, good length outside off, Tamim wrists it through mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Junaid Khan to Tamim, no run, Tamim charges Junaid Khan first ball and it hits the toe end of the opener's bat. Tamim went too hard at it and that spoiled all timing]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Junaid Khan, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, 1 run, back of a length outside off, Tamim punches sweetly off the back foot to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, shortish slower delivery, Soumya Sarkar waits for it and pulls to fine leg, in a controlled manner]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, leg byes, 1 run, drifting down leg, Tamim looks to flick and misses, runs off the thigh pad and they take a leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, on a length and outside off, Soumya Sarkar stands tall and gets forward to drive with an open face to deep backward point, just a single though]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Tamim, 1 run, short of length on the stumps, clipped away to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, short of length on the stumps, Soumya Sarkar stays beside the line of the ball and punches it to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Tamim, no run, Tamim steps out and looks to deposit Umar Gul out of the park but the wide length ball catches the inside edge and rolls back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, Tamim controlled that really well. Off-speed delivery from Umar Gul, on the stumps, Tamim half-pulled it to the right of short fine and got it wide of the fielder, once it beat the fielder, it was a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Tamim, no run, slower delivery on the stumps, Tamim steers it to the right of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, length on middle, Soumya Sarkar wrists it with plenty of bottom hand to deep mid-wicket, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, no run, short of length on off, punched well but cover fields]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Tamim, 1 run, short of length on the stumps, Tamim closes the face of the bat and tucks it through mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, <b>SIX</b>, that is a clean strike. Very full from Hafeez and Soumya Sarkar got under that nicely. Lifted it flat and over the ropes at long-on. Went all the way]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, no run, Soumya Sarkar wants a quick single but Tamim sends him back in time, Soumya opens the face of the bat and taps it to cover-point, wants a run but the fielder was in quickly]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, no run, well tossed up on the stumps, Soumya Sarkar presses it back down the track]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Soumya Sarkar defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, no run, tossed up on the stumps, Soumya Sarkar gets forward and drives to the left of short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, Hafeez smiles and he knows that was a poor stroke. Soumya Sarkar used his feet and heaved, but got a thick inside edge through square leg, the ball has enough legs to reach the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Tamim, no run, that is a good delivery from Umar Gul and he beats the bat. Angled across Tamim on a good length and going away with the angle, Tamim pushes out and nearly nicks off to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, slower delivery on the pads, turned through mid-wicket for a comfortable single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Tamim, 1 run, short of length on the stumps, Tamim closes the face of the bat and tucks it to deep square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Tamim, no run, Tamim has a huge smile on his face after charging Umar Gul and missed a slog to leg. That was a wild mow and Tamim didn't connect. Umar Gul wasn't impressed with that and had a few words to say]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, a <b>direct hit</b> from Azhar Ali at mid-off and Soumya Sarkar would've been <b>walking back</b>. But he misses despite having all three stumps to aim at. Driven without any timing to the left of mid-off and Soumya Sarkar set off. Didn't dive and was lucky that the throw missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, <b>wide</b>, that is a harsh call. Wide length delivery outside off, Soumya Sarkar missed the square drive off the front foot and got beaten. Was inside the tramline but the umpire stretches his arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, no run, short of length on the stumps, Soumya Sarkar gets forward to punch and gets an inside edge to short fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, no run, well flighted and on the stumps, Tamim gets forward and presses it back to Hafeez]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, no run, slower and outside off, Tamim gets forward and pushes it to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, no run, sliding on from round the wicket, on middle, Tamim punches to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, no run, Tamim uses his feet and drags it to mid-on, got too close to the pitch of it]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, no run, flighted outside off, driven back to Hafeez]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Soumya Sarkar gets forward and drives to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Tamim, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, too short from Gul, bangs it halfway down the pitch, Tamim swivels across and pulls it over mid-wicket, a couple of bounces and over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Tamim, no run, on a length and on the stumps, stayed a tad low as well, Tamim was shuffling across and just about gets his bat down in time]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Tamim, no run, pitched up and in that channel outside off, Tamim prods half-forward and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Tamim, no run, Gul keeps it full and in that channel outside off, Tamim is happy to let it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Tamim, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away, Tamim covers the line and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Tamim, no run, on a good length and shaping away from outside off, left alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, no run, the slider from Hafeez, came back after pitching, Sarkar gets a bottom edge on the drive, <b>maiden over from Hafeez </b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, no run, more flight from Hafeez, comes back with the angle and cramps Sarkar for space, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, no run, Hafeez drifts one on off, Sarkar gets half-forward and blocks it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, no run, slower and on off, Sarkar watches it all along and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, no run, floated on off, Sarkar presses forward and drives it back at the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, no run, Hafeez gives this one plenty of air, punched straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, on a good length and well outside off, punched to the right of mid-off where Azhar Ali makes a tumbling stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, no run, much better from Gul, shortens his length and gets this one to nip across the left-hander, he was lured into poking at that and is beaten on the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Sarkar presents the full face of the bat and punches it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Sarkar goes for an ambitious drive, mistimes the drive towards short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, this is even better! Fraction too short from Gul, Sarkar swivels across, uses his bottom hand to good effect and pulls it wide of mid-wicket for consecutive boundaries]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, that's nicely played by Sarkar, picked up the length early, gets underneath the delivery and hoicks it over mid-wicket for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, no run, pushed through quicker by Hafeez as Tamim came down the track, he prods forward and defends it off his pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, flighted delivery and just outside off, eased down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, 1 run, this one is drifted onto Tamim's pads, turned to the left of mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, no run, slower and just outside off, Tamim goes back and defends it with an open face]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, no run, Iqbal shimmies down the track to a well flighted delivery and drives it back at the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and a leg-slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Iqbal lunges forward and blocks]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Sarkar gets half-forward and pushes it towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[The second slip had moved across to short cover prior to the last short of length]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, no run, tad fuller and shaping away from outside off, Sarkar leans forward and drives it straight to the man at short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, no run, short of a length and on Sarkar's hips, tucked away straight to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, <b>wide</b>, Gul loses his radar once again, slips this one well down leg-side, Sarkar looks to flick and misses, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Sarkar presses forward and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, <b>wide</b>, Gul is struggling to get his line right, slips this one well down leg-side, given as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, no run, on a good length and just outside off, punched straight to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Umar Gul to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>inside edge and four</b>, Sarkar gets lucky, this was tad fuller and held its line outside off, drew Sarkar into the drive, the inside edge is found and the ball races away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Umar Gul, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, no run, spinning away outside off stump, Tamim defends off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, 1 run, fullish and on the leg stump, Sarkar glances it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, no run, on the leg stump, Sarkar gets an inside edge that rolls towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, no run, on the off stump, Sarkar defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Soumya Sarkar, <b>FOUR</b>, he's used the pace on the ball and that's a fine little dab for four. Well played Soumya Sarkar, he's off the mark first ball. Flatter delivery outside off stump, Sarkar guides it past the man at slip to the third man boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Tamim, 1 run, tossed up outside off stump, Tamim leans forward and drives it wide of long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tamim and Soumya Sarkar are at the crease. Tamim is on strike. Hafeez will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Slip, leg slip and silly-point in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back. The Pakistani team is in a huddle. Hafeez has the new ball in his hand. His action was cleared yesterday and straightaway he's into action.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Don't go too far. Do stay tuned for we will be back in a jiffy]]></line><line><![CDATA[The openers put on 91 and gave a solid platform. It was built on by Azhar Ali and Haris Sohail and the captain promptly got his maiden ODI ton. At that stage it looked like Pakistan will get 300 minimum. But the fall of Azhar Ali's wicket changed the complexion. Good captaincy by Mashrafe though for he kept attacking and backed his bowlers with aggressive fields. All the bowlers chipped in. We saw Tamim come out all guns blazing in the last ODI. Will we see the same today? Find out pretty soon when Bangladesh walk out to chase.]]></line><line><![CDATA[So Pakistan have collapsed to 250 all out. They were 202/2 and going strong when Azhar Ali reached his hundred. But his wicket has sparked a meltdown of the innings. The last eight wickets going for 47 runs in 10.3 overs. Inexplicable really. Now Pakistan have a task on their hand to avert the <b>'Banglawash'</b> as Athar Ali Khan puts it. The bowling wasn't out of the ordinary nor was the pitch playing tricks. Poor shots and lack of common sense from the middle-order has seen Pakistan waste all the good work done in the first 38 overs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Junaid Khan, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Cleaned up. Junaid Khan attempts the reverse sweep to a ball on middle and misses. It was quicker and Junaid Khan didn't connect. Very ambitious stroke attempted and the ball crashes into middle and leg. Sunny does a little jig. <b>Junaid Khan b A Sunny 4(6)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A Sunny to Junaid Khan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Babar, 1 run, shortish on the stumps, Babar rocks back and flat-bats it wide of cover. Just a single to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Babar, no run, Babar took a step out and missed the slog, was out of his crease but dragged it back before Rahim whipped the bails off]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire called for a stumping check. Has Babar got his foot back in? Looks like it. He has made it]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Junaid Khan, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Junaid Khan fetches the sweep and drags it to deep square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Junaid Khan, no run, fired in and Junaid Khan pushes it back to Sunny]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Junaid Khan, 2 runs, tossed up on the stumps, Junaid Khan slogs it away wide of long-on for a couple]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[47.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Babar, no run, full outside off, Babar drives and picks out cover. Hit well but straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Junaid Khan, 1 run, full toss on the stumps, Junaid Khan jabs it awkwardly wide of mid-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip being brought in now]]></line><line><![CDATA[It is very well possible that Bangladesh could bowl Pakistan out]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Junaid Khan, no run, short and outside off, Junaid Khan cuts and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Junaid Khan, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Saad Nasim, <b>out</b> Caught by Taskin Ahmed!! Pakistan continue to lose the plot. Nothing but a straight full delivery on the stumps, Saad Nasim lofts and picks out mid-off. Taskin bends down and snaffles an easy catch. Nasim needed to hit it over the man but couldn't get the elevation. <b>Saad Nasim c Taskin Ahmed b Rubel 22(24) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rubel to Saad Nasim, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Saad Nasim, no run, pitched up on the stumps, Saad Nasim makes room and drives hard but picks out cover at the edge of the circle]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Saad Nasim, no run, slower delivery on the stumps, Saad Nasim defends to the left of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Babar, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, pushed back to Sunny]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Saad Nasim, 1 run, makes room and drives to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Zulfiqar Babar, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Umar Gul, <b>out</b> Umar Gul Run Out!! Horror running from Umar Gul. He pushed it to the left of cover and set off, then stopped for some strange reason. That gave Shakib time to turn around and fire a throw to Sunny who did the rest. Umar Gul wasn't even in the picture. Yet another waste of a wicket. <b>Umar Gul run out (Shakib/A Sunny) 0(2)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A Sunny to Umar Gul, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Umar Gul, no run, fraction short outside off, cut straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Saad Nasim, 1 run, Saad Nasim uses his feet and punches it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Saad Nasim, no run, fired in on the stumps, Saad Nasim nudges it to the right of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Arafat Sunny [8.0-0-37-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Umar Gul, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Riaz, <b>out</b> Caught by Mortaza!! Caught at cover. Pitched up outside off, Riaz lofted it straight to the fielder. Simple catch. <b>Riaz c Mortaza b Rubel 7(8) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Rubel to Riaz, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Riaz, no run, full and down leg, Riaz flicks and misses, going down]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Riaz, <b>FOUR</b>, Soumya Sarkar tails to prevent the boundary despite a dive. It was pulled hard and to the left of deep mid-wicket, Sarkar ran and dived but just got a hand on it, the ball then rolled into the ropes. That was a good effort but the timing on the shot meant Sarkar's effort went in vain]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Saad Nasim, 1 run, just short of a good length and outside off, Nasim opens the face of the bat and pushes it towards backward point from inside the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Riaz, 1 run, yorker from Rubel, Riaz squeezes it out towards square leg and the batsmen take a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Riaz, no run, full delivery angling in on leg stump, Riaz fails to clip it into the on-side, there was a <b>loud lbw appeal</b> as the ball rapped him on the pad, but it was going down leg for sure]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rubel Hossain [4.0-0-36-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Saad Nasim, no run, well tossed up outside off, Saad Nasim leans forward to block]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Riaz, 1 run, flighted delivery outside off, Riaz gets forward and drives to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Riaz, no run, flat on the stumps, punched to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Saad Nasim, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Saad Nasim went for a big slog and inside-edged it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Saad Nasim, no run, more flight and on off, Saad Nasim hangs back and dabs to short third, looks for the quick single, but not there]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Saad Nasim, <b>FOUR</b>, that is a poor delivery from Shakib, way too short on the stumps, Saad Nasim rocks back and pulls to deep mid-wicket, hit in the gap and bisected the two men on the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Saad Nasim, 1 run, slower delivery outside off, Saad Nasim gets forward and drives wide of cover, mid-off moves to his left to keep it to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Saad Nasim, <b>FOUR</b>, that was smashed. Waited for the short delivery and pulled it down, deep mid-wicket diving got a hand but the power on the shot meant that he couldn't stop it cleanly. Trickles away into the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Riaz, 1 run, full outside off, Riaz opens the face of the bat and square drives to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Saad Nasim, 1 run, good length outside off, Saad Nasim opens the face of the bat and cuts hard to third man, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Saad Nasim, no run, dug in short outside off, Saad Nasim lifts his bat high up in the air and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Fawad Alam, <b>out</b> Caught by Nasir Hossain!! Good running catch. Ugly innings from Fawad Alam comes to an end. He never looked settled, this shot to get out is a horrid swipe across the line, the head falls away, the balance is all over the place, the body is contorting in different directions, he connected alright but Nasir running to his left from deep square pulled off a fine catch. Tumbled after taking it. <b>Fawad Alam c Nasir Hossain b Mortaza 4(9)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Mortaza to Fawad Alam, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Saad Nasim, no run, sliding on, Saad Nasim hangs back and pats it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Saad Nasim, no run, again softly tapped to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Saad Nasim, no run, more air from Shakib, Saad Nasim opens the face of the bat and pushes it to point, Fawad Alam sends Saad Nasim back]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Saad Nasim, no run, lots of flight on the stumps, defended back down the track]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Saad Nasim, <b>FOUR</b>, Saad Nasim comes down the track and then connects with the loft. To the pitch and straight back over the bowler's head. Trickles away into the straight boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Saad Nasim, 2 runs, tossed up on off, Saad Nasim lofts inside out between extra cover and long off, for a couple]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Fawad Alam, no run, Fawad Alam nearly lobs a return catch to Mortaza and then the bowler attempts to throw down the stumps, misses and a few words exchanged between Fawad Alam and Mortaza. Chipped uppishly by Fawad Alam to a slower delivery and it didn't carry]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Fawad Alam, no run, Mortaza bowls the slower delivery on the stumps, Fawad Alam is shuffling all across, dabs to point, sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Fawad Alam, <b>wide</b>, Mortaza digs it in short, beats Fawad Alam charging on the pull, called wide for height, Mortaza doesn't like the call]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Saad Nasim, 1 run, did that <b>carry</b> to point? Mortaza applauds the effort from his fielder. Overpitched outside off, Nasim gets forward and opens the face of the bat to slice the square drive, can't keep it down and need a replay to check whether it carried or not]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Fawad Alam, 1 run, yorker length on off, Fawad Alam digs it out wide of short cover running across and another risky run taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Saad Nasim, 1 run, shortish outside off, Saad Nasim cuts uppishly but safely to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Fawad Alam, 1 run, direct hit would've been interesting. Dabbed to point and a hurried single, the fielder came in and under-armed at the striker's end and missed. <b>Out with the direct hit</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Saad Nasim, no run, lots of air on that, pushed back towards Shakib who lets that run to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Saad Nasim, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, <b>out</b> Caught&Bowled!! Lobbed straight back. Tossed up outside off, stopped on Rizwan's shot, who played it early and chipped a dolly back to the bowler. Shakib catches and then breaks out into a beaming smile. Pakistan stumbling in the death overs. <b>Rizwan c and b Shakib 4(6)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shakib to Rizwan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught&Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, no run, this one is on middle and leg, straightened too, Rizwan gets a thick edge to point, sent back by Fawad Alam]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Fawad Alam, 1 run, well tossed up outside off, Fawad Alam stays back and works it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Fawad Alam, no run, flighted delivery outside off, Fawad Alam uses his feet and taps it back to Shakib]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, 1 run, tossed up outside off, pushed off the front foot to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[A slip in place for Shakib]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Fawad Alam, no run, Fawad Alam is almost running at the bowler, Mortaza bowls a cutter outside off, dabbed to point. This time Shakib fields and there is no quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rizwan, 1 run, dug in short at no real pace, Rizwan pulls hard but picks out deep mid-wicket, needed to hit the gap there]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Fawad Alam, 1 run, short of length on the stumps, dabbed to point, they take on Shakib and complete a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Fawad Alam, <b>wide</b>, dug in short as he saw Fawad Alam coming down the wicket. Way too short and wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Rizwan, 1 run, almost another. Too close to cut and Rizwan nearly drags it on. The inside edge trickles away to the left of him and he races across to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Fawad Alam, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Sohail, <b>out</b> Caught by Rahim!! Ugly swipe and the top edge goes straight up. Rahim settles under it. Sohail knelt down to heave the slower delivery, but got a big top edge. Both the well-set batsmen are gone and Bangladesh have struck twice in quick succession. <b>Sohail c Rahim b Mortaza 53(58) [4s-1 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mortaza to Sohail, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Sohail, 2 runs, slower delivery on the stumps, Sohail comes down the track and makes room to go over cover for a couple]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, leg byes, 1 run, direct hit from Rahim but Rizwan was well in. They don't even go upstairs. Sohail came down and got a thin inside edge onto the pads, to the left of the keeper who ran and then threw down the stumps, wasn't quick enough to beat Rizwan. Given as leg byes]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chants of 'Shakib, Shakib' at the venue]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Rizwan, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Rizwan gets forward and eases it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Rizwan, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, <b>out</b> Bowled!! 100 and out. Azhar Ali tries to be cheeky and misses the late dab. The ball straightened and hit the top of off after going past the shot. Azhar Ali walks off bat raised to applause from the crowd. <b>Azhar Ali b Shakib 101(112) [4s-10]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shakib to Azhar Ali, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, 1 run, very full on the stumps, Sohail steps out and jams it out to long-on. That is <b>fifty</b> for Sohail]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, no run, flat again, punched back to Shakib]]></line><line><![CDATA[Looks like Azhar Ali has sprained a muscle while celebrating. The physio is out and working on the right arm of Azhar Ali. A slight delay]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, no run, flat outside off, punched back to Shakib]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan [6.0-0-18-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, look at Azhar Ali! He is jumping in joy and punching the air in delight. He does the Sajda too. Gets to his <b>maiden ODI ton</b> with a clip through mid-wicket. Shuffled across and got it in the gap for a couple. After he completed the second, began the celebrations. Gets a hug from Sohail as well. The pressure has been on Azhar Ali but that hasn't affected his batting]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, no run, pitched up outside off, Azhar Ali gets forward and plays a nice drive but well-stopped at short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[Azhar Ali on 99 and on strike. Sohail has a word with his skipper]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Sohail, 1 run, short of length on the stumps, Sohail shuffles across and punches to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, 1 run, slower delivery outside off, pushed to long-on, Azhar Ali moves to 99]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Sohail, 1 run, good length outside off, Sohail dabs off the front foot to point, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Sohail, no run, Mortaza beats Sohail on the cut with a slower delivery, the ball goes past the edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, 1 run, fired in on the stumps, clipped to the right of short mid-wicket, sliding stop but can't prevent the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, 2 runs, on the pads, turning in, clipped to deep square leg, for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, <b>SIX</b>, just over Mahmudullah running back and leaping at long-on. Sohail used his feet and lofted it over the ropes. He must have felt that he had holed out when he hit it, but got away with it]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, no run, tossed up outside off, Sohail mistimes the sweep straight to Shakib at backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, 1 run, very full on the stumps, dug out to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, short on the stumps, Azhar Ali rocks back and punches to the right of long-on for a couple]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Mortaza is unhappy with something. He is having a chat with the umpire. Not sure what the fuss is all about]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Sohail, no run, back of a length outside off, punched back to Mortaza]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, 1 run, short of length on the stumps, Azhar Ali gets forward and whips it to the left of short fine who fields]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, no run, Azhar Ali once again skips out, but this time misses the clip to leg, is hit above the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Sohail, 1 run, slower delivery on the pads, clipped off the front foot to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, 1 run, short of length outside off, Azhar Ali is outside his crease and tucks it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Sohail, 1 run, slower delivery outside off, Sohail works it through mid-wicket. There is a fumble from the fielder running in, but they are happy with the single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mashrafe Mortaza [5.0-0-17-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> being taken again. Pakistan are all set for the final assault. Azhar Ali is inching his way to his first ODI ton with Sohail giving company. Powerplay will follow after drinks. Let's see what sort of a score can Pakistan get]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, no run, flatter on off, pushed to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, no run, Azhar Ali uses his feet and drives it back to Sunny, a slight fumble but the bowler recovers in time]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, 1 run, Sohail makes room and Sunny follows him, clipped to deep square leg, Azhar Ali sends Sohail back this time for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, no run, tossed up on the stumps, Sohail uses his feet and pushes it back to Sunny. He fires it back at the stumps, hits direct and it has been referred to the third umpire. Again a waste of time as Sohail plants his foot back in]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, no run, this one turns in and beats Sohail's attempt to clip, hits him on the thigh pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, 2 runs, now Sohail takes two with a soft tuck to deep square leg. Was down the wicket which helped him get a start]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Arafat Sunny [6.0-0-22-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Sohail, 1 run, angled in on middle, worked away to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Azhar Ali gets forward and clips with the turn to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, that is good running from Azhar Ali, he skips out and clips to deep mid-wicket, takes on the fielder and makes it back with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Sohail, 1 run, low full toss and Sohail takes it on the full, stepping out and driving to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Sohail, no run, tossed up and outside off, stops on Sohail who defends it back to Mahmudullah]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Sohail, no run, fraction short outside off, Sohail hangs back and late-cuts, finds backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, that is a rubbish delivery and Azhar Ali moves into the nineties with a super cut. Off-speed short ball outside off, Azhar Ali latches onto the cut and delays the shot to beat sweeper cover to his left]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sohail, 1 run, short on the stumps, Sohail swivels on the pull and plays it to deep mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, 1 run, good length outside off, Azhar Ali opens the face of the bat and steers to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sohail, 1 run, on the bounce to third man. Sohail charges Rubel and slashes at a back of a length delivery, the thick edge is found but doesn't carry]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sohail, no run, dug in short by Rubel, Sohail ducks under that. Called one short ball for the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, 1 run, short of length outside off, dabbed down to third man, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Mortaza has a word with Rubel]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Azhar Ali closes the face of the bat and glances it to deep backward square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, Nasir does well to save two with a run and then dive to his right at deep backward square leg. Swept hard by Azhar Ali and he must have felt he got a boundary when he hit it]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Sohail, 1 run, slightly short outside off, punched to sweeper cover, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Sohail, no run, again turns away, Sohail punches once more to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Sohail, no run, turns away, Sohail punches to short cover off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mahmudullah to Sohail, no run, Mahmudullah does well to run across and stick a boot in to his left, stops the single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mahmudullah, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, no run, slower delivery outside off, Azhar Ali shuffles across and pushes it to mid-on. Doesn't take the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sohail, 1 run, good length outside off, Sohail opens the face of the bat and steers to square third man, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, 1 run, length outside off, Azhar Ali opens the face of the bat and cuts to third man, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, a front foot cut and Azhar Ali gets another nice boundary. It wasn't too short but Azhar Ali latched on, timing the shot past the diving point, beating the fielder to his left. Third man couldn't get across]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sohail, 1 run, short of length on the stumps, nudged to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, Rubel comes back and starts off with a half-volley outside off, Sohail gets forward and drives superbly through cover. Leant into the shot and timed it all along the ground. Brilliant threading of the gap too on the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rubel Hossain [2.0-0-17-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Rahman to Sohail, 1 run, Sohail now uses his feet and punches it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Rahman to Azhar Ali, 1 run, steps out and punches it to long- on]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Rahman to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, Azhar Ali goes over cover. Makes room and then lifts the tossed up delivery on the stumps into the gap at deep cover. The ball trickles away into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Rahman to Azhar Ali, no run, that is a leading edge as Azhar Ali comes down the track, but it is a soft one and the ball dies on its way to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Rahman to Sohail, 1 run, tossed up from round the wicket, Sohail gets forward and drives to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Rahman to Sohail, no run, Sohail comes down the track and drills it hard back at Rahman who fields]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, no run, that stopped on Azhar Ali and turned away too, he jabs it awkwardly back to Shakib]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, no run, fired in on middle and leg, Azhar Ali defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, 1 run, skips out and drives to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Azhar Ali comes down the track and just about pushes it to long-on, didn't reach the pitch of it but managed a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, 1 run, shortish on the stumps, Sohail goes on the back foot to whip to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, 1 run, sliding down leg, clipped to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Rahman to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Azhar Ali comes down the track and makes room to drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Rahman to Azhar Ali, no run, Azhar Ali misses out. Short and wide outside off, Azhar Ali cuts and picks out point]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Rahman to Sohail, 1 run, pushed through, Sohail gets forward and drives to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Rahman to Azhar Ali, 1 run, Azhar Ali uses his feet and drives to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Rahman to Sohail, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Sohail gets forward and drives to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Rahman to Sohail, <b>SIX</b>, just over the leaping deep mid-wicket. Full toss from Rahman first up, Sohail heaves it and clears the fielder peddling back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sabbir Rahman, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, no run, tossed up and turning away, Azhar Ali opens the face of the bat to steer to the left of point]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, no run, shortish outside off, Azhar Ali rocks back and finds Sabbir at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, 1 run, takes a step out and wrists it through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, clipped to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, no run, Sohail skips out and gently nudges it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Azhar Ali uses his feet and eases it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Azhar Ali gets forward and clips to deep mid-wicket, keeps the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, deft touch from Azhar Ali. Saw the shortish length outside off, Azhar Ali rocked back and opens the face of the bat to glide it down to third man, nicely done]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sohail, 1 run, Sohail gets forward and pushes it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, 1 run, spinning down leg, clipped to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, no run, shout for lbw but Azhar Ali got outside the line off as he missed the sweep]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, again Azhar Ali takes a calculated risk and it comes off. Skips out and goes over mid-off. Knew that the fielder was in and ensured he cleared him, which he did]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Azhar Ali sweeps in the air, one hand comes off the bat handle and he gets it down to deep backward square]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, 1 run, this time gets it to the right of square leg and gets a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, no run, on the middle and leg line, worked to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, no run, stays back and nudges to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, 2 runs, clipped through mid-wicket for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, no run, Sohail makes room and Shakib follows him with a tossed up that turns in, is hit on the pads outside leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sohail, 1 run, Sohail skips out and wrists it to long-on, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sohail, no run, pushed through, punched to the left of Nasir Hossain]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sohail, no run, Sohail uses his feet and then defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, 1 run, flighted delivery outside off, Azhar Ali kneels down and sweeps hard to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, no run, Azhar Ali shuffles across and clips to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sohail, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Sohail gets forward and drives to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Nasir Hossain [5.0-0-23-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, no run, slower and Azhar Ali punches to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, 1 run, angled in, clipped to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, 1 run, short and wide outside off, cut hard to sweeper cover, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, no run, that stopped on Azhar Ali who defends it awkwardly back down the track. It was in the air but stopped well in front of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, no run, Azhar Ali opens the face of the bat and dabs it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Sohail, 1 run, flat from over the wicket, Sohail punches it off the back foot to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, no run, stays back and push-drives to cover, the fielder moves to his left and dives]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, no run, uses his feet and tries to nudge it away, gets a thick inside edge onto the pads as he isn't to the pitch]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, no run, slides on with the arm, Azhar Ali gets forward to defend and gets a thick inside edge to short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sohail, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Sohail uses his feet and drives to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Haris Sohail, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Hafeez, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Once again Sunny gets Hafeez. This is poor batting from the experienced Hafeez. He charges Sunny and tries to swing to leg, the arm-ball from Sunny and it beats the swipe before falling on the stumps. That looked very ungainly from Hafeez. Another failure for him. <b>Hafeez b A Sunny 4(15)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A Sunny to Hafeez, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, 3 runs, flatter and down leg, Azhar Ali clips it through mid-wicket, the fielder in the deep runs to his left and pulls it back, saving a run for his side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Hafeez, 2 runs, fraction short outside off, Hafeez rocks back and cuts to deep backward point, two it is]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Hafeez, no run, tossed up on off, Hafeez stretches forward and presses it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Hafeez, no run, now charges Shakib and has to adjust as it is fired outside off, he dabs it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Hafeez, no run, how did that miss off? Even Hafeez has a smile on his face. Drifted in, brought Hafeez forward, then pitched, turned and bounced away over off stump. The bounce saved Hafeez there. Brilliant delivery from Shakib]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Hafeez, no run, comes down the track and defends to the right of short cover. Hafeez wanted the quick single, sent back by Azhar Ali and he made it by stretching out and dragging his bat in, beating the direct hit]]></line><line><![CDATA[Has Hafeez got himself run out? A direct hit from short cover but Hafeez has made it back. Dragged his bat in]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, 1 run, Azhar Ali gets <b>fifty</b> with a tuck through mid-wicket for a single. No real celebrations]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Hafeez, no run, Sunny fired that in seeing Hafeez advance, defended back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, 1 run, makes room and drives inside out to long-off, is now on 49]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, Azhar Ali has hit that hard and over cover. Danced down and got to the pitch before getting it in the gap, punches gloves with Hafeez after playing that]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Hafeez, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Hafeez gets forward and opens the face of the bat to push it wide of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Hafeez, no run, flighted delivery on off, Hafeez gets forward and presses it back to Sunny]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Hafeez, no run, short and turning away, Hafeez rocks back to cut and mistimes it to point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Arafat Sunny [4.0-0-12-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[If there was anything it was only glove in that Sami Aslam dismissal]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Hafeez, 1 run, flat on the stumps, Hafeez rocks back and punches to deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Hafeez, no run, angling in, Hafeez gets forward and defends to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Hafeez, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Hafeez presses it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Hafeez, no run, Hafeez uses his feet and pushes it to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Hafeez, no run, tossed up on middle and leg, Hafeez gets forward and defends it back to Shakib]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place for Hafeez]]></line><line><![CDATA[Did Sami Aslam not know there was DRS in place. Replays show that it may have missed everything. A huge puff of dust when that ball landed]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shakib to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Azhar Ali gets forward and eases it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shakib Al Hasan, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Hafeez, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, <b>out</b> Caught by Rahim!! Nasir Hossain gets the breakthrough. That turned and bounced and looks like a feather, if there is one. Tough to be dead sure with no HotSpot and Snicko. It pitched outside off and gripped, brought Sami Aslam forward and then turned away to take the tiniest of nicks, off the handle to the keeper. Good take by Rahim too and Nasir Hossain pumps his fist in celebration. Given out immediately by the umpire and Sami Aslam didn't review. <b>Sami Aslam c Rahim b Nasir Hossain 45(50) [4s-7]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, no run, that bounced from a length, Sami Aslam goes on the back foot to defend in front of point, no chance of a quick single and is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, 1 run, very full on the stumps, driven to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, no run, flatter on middle and leg, clipped straight to the fielder at backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, no run, Nasir Hossain shortens the length on the stumps, Azhar Ali using his feet punches it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, no run, tossed up on the stumps, Azhar Ali gets forward and drives it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[That will be <b>drinks.</b> Pakistan have eschewed risks and played sensibly to get to 90/0 in the first 17 overs. The young Sami Aslam has looked quite impressive on debut. The platform is set for a 300 score. Can Pakistan continue to build on the start?]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, 1 run, fired in and Azhar Ali using his feet clips it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, no run, flighted delivery outside off, Azhar Ali went too hard at the cover drive, mistimed it completely]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sami Aslam, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Sami Aslam gets forward and drives to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Azhar Ali sweeps to deep square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sami Aslam, 1 run, uses his feet and drives along the ground to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sami Aslam, no run, that kept low outside off, Sami Aslam bends down and defends it back to Sunny]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, 1 run, softly dabbed to point, for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Azhar Ali pre-meditates the paddle, is lucky to have got some glove over Rahim]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, 1 run, quicker outside off, Sami Aslam opens the face of the bat and steers it to the left of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, no run, flat on the stumps, punched back to Nasir Hossain]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, 1 run, dragged down, Azhar Ali steps out, adjusts to punch it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Sami Aslam gets forward and drives wide of mid-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, no run, shortish and Azhar Ali mistimes the cut off the back foot to short cover. Is disappointed for not getting more on the shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sami Aslam, 1 run, Sami Aslam is early into the flick, gets a thick leading edge but nowhere close to long-on. So gets away with that]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, 1 run, Azhar Ali skips out and drives to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sami Aslam, 1 run, flat on the middle and leg, clipped off the back foot to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Azhar Ali uses his feet and drives to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sami Aslam, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Sami Aslam uses his feet and wrists it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, 1 run, uses his feet and chips in the air, but played softly so it won't carry to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, <b>FOUR</b>, intentional and Sami Aslam gets a boundary. Sees the flight outside off, goes over cover. Inside-out, long-off running to his right can't get across in time]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, 1 run, regulation off-break, Azhar Ali comes down the track and clips it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, 1 run, Sami Aslam uses his feet and chips it over the bowler, for a single to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, no run, flat again, on the stumps, punched back to Nasir Hossain]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, no run, flatter and on the stumps, clipped to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, no run, this one stays a bit low and also turns a bit, Azhar Ali hangs back and taps to the covers]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, no run, Sunny almost gets through Azhar Ali's defences, it was angled in and Azhar Ali missed the clip, brushed the pad and went inches wide of off. That was very close]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sami Aslam, 1 run, full on the stumps, Sami Aslam gets forward and clips in the air but in the gap to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sami Aslam, no run, tossed up outside off, Sami Aslam uses his feet and defends to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, 1 run, fraction short outside off, Azhar Ali rocks back and cuts square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, no run, tossed up on the stumps, driven to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Arafat Sunny [1.0-0-1-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, no run, straightens outside off, Sami Aslam taps it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, no run, flatter on the stumps, punched to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, no run, tossed up outside off, Sami Aslam gets forward and pats it to point, no chance of a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, no run, no room to dab late as the ball follows Sami Aslam, he plays it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, 1 run, flatter outside off, Azhar Ali taps it square of the wicket, for an easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, no run, tossed up outside off, driven back to Nasir Hossain who flicks it back at the stumps at the non-striker's end. Sami Aslam was well in and a waste of time in going for the third ump. Nasir Hossain forced the umpire to refer it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Nasir Hossain [1.0-0-9-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, 1 run, short of length on the stumps, clipped to fine leg, with a roll of the wrists]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sami Aslam, 1 run, fraction short outside off, Sami Aslam rocks back and pulls to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sami Aslam, no run, slower delivery on the stumps, Sami Aslam presses forward and blocks to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sami Aslam, <b>wide</b>, short and down leg, Sami Aslam pulls and misses. Called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, 1 run, shortish outside off, Azhar Ali cuts to deep backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely timing from Azhar Ali. Drifting on middle and leg, Azhar Ali whipped it wide of both mid-wicket and mid-on, who barely moved as they watched the ball run away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, no run, full and on the stumps, hint of nip back in, Azhar Ali clips it to mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rubel Hossain [1.0-0-9-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sami Aslam, no run, fired down leg, Sami Aslam sweeps and misses. The ball seemed to have missed the glove after the batsman completed the sweep. Not out for lbw as well as it had pitched outside leg. So Bangladesh lose their only review. Good catch by Tamim, going back and diving acrobatically to take it at leg gully. All that came to nothing as the on-field call stood]]></line><line><![CDATA[What has happened here? Yes, Bangladesh are reviewing it. Tamim with an acrobatic catch at leg gully. Not out the call from the umpire. Tamim impresses upon Rahim to take the review and they do. Has it taken the glove? Need another angle to see properly. After Sami Aslam completed the sweep, did it brush the glove on the way through to Tamim? Very difficult to give it out from that replay. No HotSpot or Snicko here. They are checking for the lbw as well. <b>Pitched outside leg. Bangladesh waste a review.</b> Sami Aslam stays]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sami Aslam, no run, tossed up on the stumps, Sami Aslam prefers to defend off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Sami Aslam, no run, highly optimistic from both Sunny and Rahim. Went up for an lbw appeal when the ball hit the glove of Sami Aslam who was sweeping]]></line><line><![CDATA[Same field for Sami Aslam too]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Azhar Ali kneels down and sweeps hard to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and a leg gully for Sunny]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, no run, tossed up outside off, Azhar Ali drives to point now]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Sunny to Azhar Ali, no run, short and wide outside off, turned away, Azhar Ali aborts the cut and gently plays it to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Arafat Sunny, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, 1 run, walks out and then shuffles across to clip through square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, second time in two overs that Azhar Ali has timed the cut past the short point fielder. This time the fielder didn't even get a hand to it diving across. That was crisply played by the Pakistani batsman]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, no run, back of a length outside off, Azhar Ali takes a step forward and punches it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Sami Aslam, 1 run, another off-speed delivery on the hips, nudhed to deep backward square leg, Sami Aslam wanted two, sent back by Azhar Ali]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Sami Aslam, no run, slower delivery on off, Sami Aslam gets forward and defends to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, 1 run, Azhar Ali looks to punch that good length delivery outside off through cover, but the inside half of the bat is found and it dribbles to mid-on. They take a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sami Aslam, no run, Rubel pulls his length back and bowls it on off, Sami Aslam with a shuffle defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Sami Aslam, <b>FOUR</b>, overpitched and Rubel pays the price. Sami Aslam kneels down and on a bent knee smashes the cover drive and no-one moved]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, 1 run, good length outside off, Azhar Ali opens the face of the bat and guides it to third man, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, short and wide outside off, Azhar Ali hammers the cut hard into the ground, short cover diving to his left gets a hand, takes some pace off the shot but still it goes to the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, no run, another nice looking shot and no runs. Azhar Ali times the back foot punch but finds backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[That Nasir Hossain experiment lasted just one over]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Rubel to Azhar Ali, no run, back of a length outside off, Azhar Ali stays back and punches straight to the fielder at short cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rubel Hossain, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, 1 run, short of length outside off, pushed in front of mid-off for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, no run, good length outside off, around the fourth stump line, Azhar Ali chops it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Sami Aslam, 1 run, short and down leg, was there for the taking, Sami Aslam though pulls straight to the fielder at fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Sami Aslam, no run, on the middle and leg stump line, Sami Aslam defends to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, 1 run, on the hips, Azhar Ali shuffles across and clips to deep backward square leg, Azhar Ali wanted two but Shakib was quick to get to the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[No slips now for Mortaza]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, no run, good length outside off, Azhar Ali takes a step out and defends to short cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, no run, flighted delivery outside off, Sami Aslam gets forward and pushes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, no run, tossed up on off, Sami Aslam gets forward and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, <b>FOUR</b>, this is superb batting. Quicker ball outside off, Sami Aslam hangs back and chops down on it, the ball runs wide of backward point and the outfield does the rest. Consecutive boundaries]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Sami Aslam, <b>FOUR</b>, dragged down short outside off, Sami Aslam rocks back and pulls it down beating mid-on who gave chase. Fourth four for Sami Aslam]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and a leg gully for Sami Aslam. Nasir Hossain from round the wicket now]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, 1 run, Azhar Ali comes down the track and then flicks to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and a leg slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Nasir Hossain to Azhar Ali, no run, Azhar Ali clips uppishly in the air, but doesn't carry to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Nasir Hossain, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Sami Aslam, no run, short of length on the stumps, Sami Aslam shuffles across and defends it back to Mortaza]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, 1 run, slower delivery outside off, Azhar Ali opens the face of the bat and dabs it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, no run, punched off the front foot but Mahmudullah at short cover dives to his right and makes a sharp stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, no run, good length on off, Azhar Ali defends with an open face to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, no run, length on the stumps, Azhar Ali gets forward and pushes it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[The slip needs to come up a few paces on this slow wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, no run, <b>edged and just short</b> of the widish slip. Mortaza induced the outside edge as Azhar Ali came forward to drive, luckily for him the edge didn't carry]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sami Aslam, <b>FOUR</b>, delightful drive this. Sami Aslam looks to be a compact player, from what one has seen so far. He gets forward and then laces the length delivery wide of mid-off, to the right of the fielder. That's three boundaries in the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sami Aslam, <b>FOUR</b>, Taskin Ahmed seems to be not learning. He digs it in short, but the ball rises near his head and Sami Aslam still hooks it away, controlling the shot with a roll of the wrists. Kept it down and the ball raced away to the deep backward square leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sami Aslam, no run, on the leg stump line, Sami Aslam nudges to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sami Aslam, no run, pitched up outside off, Sami Aslam gets forward and opens the face of the bat on the drive, point runs to his left and dives to keep it to a dot]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sami Aslam, <b>wide</b>, now bowls it well outside leg, Rahim dives to his right to collect. Saved some runs with that effort]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sami Aslam, <b>FOUR</b>, can't bowl short on this wicket. Sami Aslam was quick to rock back and pulls to the deep backward square leg fence. Shifted his weight and swivelled on the shot to get it to the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sami Aslam, no run, short of length outside off, Sami Aslam hangs to defend and the inside edge is found, the ball gets lodged inside the right pad. Aslam takes the ball out from there and throws it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, no run, slower delivery outside off, dabbed to the left of backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Sami Aslam, 1 run, another quick single taken and Mortaza is already unhappy. Shows off his displeasure at the fielder, it was nudged to square leg, Sami Aslam looked at Azhar Ali who hared across to the other end and made it easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, 1 run, length outside off, Azhar Ali gets forward and pushes it softly in front of mid-on, takes the quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Sami Aslam, 1 run, looked like a cutter, off-speed delivery, sits up for Sami Aslam to cut and he hits it in the air, wide of backward point to his right]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Sami Aslam, no run, on a length and on the stumps, Sami Aslam shuffles across and clips it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Sami Aslam, no run, pitched up outside off, Sami Aslam gets forward and defends to short cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, fabulous cut shot. On a back of a length outside off, Azhar Ali flashed the cut wide of the diving backward point, third man had little ground to cover to his right but the ball beat him to the fence. He should've dived but didn't]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, angling in, Azhar Ali wrists it wide of mid-on for a couple of runs. Timed well and wide of the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Azhar Ali, no run, short of length outside off, Azhar Ali stands tall and punches it well but straight to the fielder at short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[It looks quite cloudy at the moment. The forecast is for rain later in the day]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Azhar Ali, no run, short of length outside off, punched back to Taskin Ahmed]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sami Aslam is just 19]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Sami Aslam, 1 run, down leg, Sami Aslam gets his frist runs in international cricket, clipped to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Azhar Ali, 1 run, on the hips, nipped back in, Azhar Ali tucks it to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Taskin Ahmed to Azhar Ali, <b>wide</b>, that's a wayward delivery, way too wide of off, wide called]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Taskin Ahmed, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, 1 run, short of length outside off, Azhar Ali steers it to third man, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, on a length and outside off, Azhar Ali gets forward and drives on the rise, wide of cover, that's the first runs of the game. A couple it is]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, no run, pitched up outside off, Azhar Ali gets forward and drives to mid-off, the batsman wants a single but the fielder is there]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, no run, on a length and outside off, Azhar Ali shuffles across a bit and clips it straight to the fielder at mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[Some movement behind the bowler's arm and Mortaza is sorting it out. A slight delay]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, no run, back of a length outside off, little shortish, Azhar Ali mistimed the cut to cover. Went too hard at it]]></line><line><![CDATA[Just a lone slip for Mortaza]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mortaza to Azhar Ali, no run, short of length outside off, punched back to Mortaza]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Azhar Ali and Sami Aslam are at the crease. Azhar Ali is on strike. Mortaza will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mortaza:</b> "We would've looked to bat first. But last game we bowled brilliantly. Boys are looking forward to this game. We are not looking forward to 3-0 but hope to play well like the last two games, the result will come. No changes."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Azhar Ali:</b> "We are going to bat first. It looks quite slow and it might not come onto the bat. We will look to get runs on the board. We have to improve big time in every aspect of the game. Everyone know that and we will look to correct that today. Sarfraz is resting and we have three changes. Sami Aslam is making his debut. It is a big challenge for me and the whole team is behind me and supporting me."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pitch report:</b> A different pitch today. But quite similar to the one that were used for the first two ODIs. A bit of cracks but still a good batting pitch.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangladesh</b> (Playing XI): Tamim Iqbal, Soumya Sarkar, Mahmudullah, Mushfiqur Rahim(w), Shakib Al Hasan, Sabbir Rahman, Nasir Hossain, Mashrafe Mortaza(c), Arafat Sunny, Taskin Ahmed, Rubel Hossain]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan</b> (Playing XI): Azhar Ali(c), Mohammad Hafeez, Haris Sohail, Fawad Alam, Mohammad Rizwan(w), Saad Nasim, Sami Aslam, Wahab Riaz, Umar Gul, Junaid Khan, Zulfiqar Babar]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pakistan have made <b>three changes</b> to the team that lost the last game. Out go Rahat Ali, Sarfraz Ahmed and Saeed Ajmal. In come Umar Gul, Zulfiqar Babar and there is a <b>debut for Sami Aslam. Bangladesh are unchanged.</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Toss and teams coming up in a short while. Do stay tuned...]]></line><line><![CDATA[The form of Tamim Iqbal for Bangladesh has been a huge plus. He has notched up consecutive hundreds in the series and will be trying to become the first Bangladeshi to make three in a row today. He clinically dismantled the Pakistani attack in the last game, taking on the opening bowlers with calculated hitting. His onslaught set the platform for an easy win. For Pakistan Umar Gul has been drafted in as a replacement for Ehsan Adil. He should get a look in today and it will be interesting to see how he goes.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pakistan are undergoing a transition phase after the World Cup. For this series they are without Misbah and Afridi - who have retired from ODIs. They have a new captain in Azhar Ali who is yet to find his bearings. So the losses in the first two games isn't a huge shock considering how Bangladesh have been playing ever since the World Cup. The injuries to players like Sohaib Maqsood, Sohail Khan, Yasir Shah and Ehsan Adil hasn't helped the side too.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shakib said before the series began that they will be favorites. A lot of them laughed at that statement. After two matches and with the series sealed in favor of his side, it is Shakib who is doing all the laughing. Pakistan have been outplayed in both games as the hosts won their first ever ODI series. A warm welcome to the final game of this series as Bangladesh attempt a rare shot at a whitewash.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan</b> (From): Azhar Ali(c), Sarfraz Ahmed(w), Mohammad Hafeez, Haris Sohail, Fawad Alam, Mohammad Rizwan, Saad Nasim, Wahab Riaz, Umar Gul, Saeed Ajmal, Junaid Khan, Rahat Ali, Sami Aslam, Asad Shafiq, Zulfiqar Babar]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bangladesh</b> (From): Tamim Iqbal, Soumya Sarkar, Mahmudullah, Mushfiqur Rahim(w), Shakib Al Hasan, Sabbir Rahman, Nasir Hossain, Mashrafe Mortaza(c), Arafat Sunny, Rubel Hossain, Taskin Ahmed, Mominul Haque, Abul Hasan, Rony Talukdar]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>250</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>10</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>49</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Pakistan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>6633</playerid>
					<name>Azhar Ali</name>
					<batsman-name>Azhar Ali</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Azhar Ali</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>101</runs>
					<balls>112</balls>
					<fours>10</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Shakib</bowler>
					<bowlerId>544</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8370</playerid>
					<name>Sami Aslam</name>
					<batsman-name>Sami Aslam</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sami Aslam</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>45</runs>
					<balls>50</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Nasir Hossain</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8018</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mushfiqur Rahim</fielder>
						<fielderId>394</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>360</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Hafeez</name>
					<batsman-name>M Hafeez</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Hafeez</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>15</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>A Sunny</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8243</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8299</playerid>
					<name>Haris Sohail</name>
					<batsman-name>H Sohail</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sohail</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>52</runs>
					<balls>58</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mortaza</bowler>
					<bowlerId>323</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mushfiqur Rahim</fielder>
						<fielderId>394</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9468</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Rizwan</name>
					<batsman-name>M Rizwan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rizwan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Shakib</bowler>
					<bowlerId>544</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Shakib</fielder>
						<fielderId>544</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>697</playerid>
					<name>Fawad Alam</name>
					<batsman-name>F Alam</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Fawad Alam</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mortaza</bowler>
					<bowlerId>323</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Nasir Hossain</fielder>
						<fielderId>8018</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10094</playerid>
					<name>Saad Nasim</name>
					<batsman-name>Saad Nasim</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Saad Nasim</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>22</runs>
					<balls>24</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Rubel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1736</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Taskin Ahmed</fielder>
						<fielderId>8548</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1051</playerid>
					<name>Wahab Riaz</name>
					<batsman-name>Riaz</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Riaz</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>7</runs>
					<balls>8</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Rubel</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1736</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mashrafe Mortaza</fielder>
						<fielderId>323</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>504</playerid>
					<name>Umar Gul</name>
					<batsman-name>U Gul</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Umar Gul</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Shakib Al Hasan</fielder>
						<fielderId>544</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Arafat Sunny</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>8243</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8991</playerid>
					<name>Zulfiqar Babar</name>
					<batsman-name>Z Babar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Babar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7900</playerid>
					<name>Junaid Khan</name>
					<batsman-name>Junaid Khan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Junaid Khan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>A Sunny</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8243</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8370</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>91</runs>
				<overs>17.6</overs>
				<batsman>Sami Aslam</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Sami Aslam</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>360</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>105</runs>
				<overs>21.2</overs>
				<batsman>Mohammad Hafeez</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Hafeez</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6633</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>203</runs>
				<overs>38.4</overs>
				<batsman>Azhar Ali</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Azhar Ali</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8299</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>207</runs>
				<overs>39.2</overs>
				<batsman>Haris Sohail</batsman>
				<batsman-name>H Sohail</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9468</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>213</runs>
				<overs>40.5</overs>
				<batsman>Mohammad Rizwan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Rizwan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>697</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>224</runs>
				<overs>43.1</overs>
				<batsman>Fawad Alam</batsman>
				<batsman-name>F Alam</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1051</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>243</runs>
				<overs>45.6</overs>
				<batsman>Wahab Riaz</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Riaz</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>504</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>244</runs>
				<overs>46.4</overs>
				<batsman>Umar Gul</batsman>
				<batsman-name>U Gul</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>10094</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>245</runs>
				<overs>47.3</overs>
				<batsman>Saad Nasim</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Saad Nasim</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7900</playerid>
				<nbr>10</nbr>
				<runs>250</runs>
				<overs>48.6</overs>
				<batsman>Junaid Khan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Junaid Khan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>5</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>6</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Bangladesh">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>323</playerid>
					<name>Mashrafe Mortaza</name>
					<bowler-name>Mortaza</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mortaza</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>44</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8548</playerid>
					<name>Taskin Ahmed</name>
					<bowler-name>Taskin Ahmed</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Taskin Ahmed</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>22</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8018</playerid>
					<name>Nasir Hossain</name>
					<bowler-name>Nasir Hossain</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nasir Hossain</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>37</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1736</playerid>
					<name>Rubel Hossain</name>
					<bowler-name>Rubel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rubel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>6</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>43</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8243</playerid>
					<name>Arafat Sunny</name>
					<bowler-name>A Sunny</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>A Sunny</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>43</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>544</playerid>
					<name>Shakib Al Hasan</name>
					<bowler-name>Shakib</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shakib</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>34</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8231</playerid>
					<name>Sabbir Rahman</name>
					<bowler-name>S Rahman</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Rahman</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>17</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1121</playerid>
					<name>Mahmudullah</name>
					<bowler-name>Mahmudullah</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mahmudullah</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>9</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>612</playerid>
					<name>Tamim Iqbal</name>
					<bowler-name>Tamim</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Tamim</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8233</playerid>
					<name>Soumya Sarkar</name>
					<bowler-name>Soumya Sarkar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Soumya Sarkar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>394</playerid>
					<name>Mushfiqur Rahim</name>
					<bowler-name>Rahim</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rahim</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>251</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>2</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>39.3</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Bangladesh">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>612</playerid>
					<name>Tamim Iqbal</name>
					<batsman-name>Tamim</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Tamim</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>64</runs>
					<balls>76</balls>
					<fours>8</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Junaid Khan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7900</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8233</playerid>
					<name>Soumya Sarkar</name>
					<batsman-name>Soumya Sarkar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Soumya Sarkar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>127</runs>
					<balls>110</balls>
					<fours>13</fours>
					<sixes>6</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1121</playerid>
					<name>Mahmudullah</name>
					<batsman-name>Mahmudullah</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mahmudullah</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Junaid Khan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7900</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>394</playerid>
					<name>Mushfiqur Rahim</name>
					<batsman-name>Rahim</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rahim</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>49</runs>
					<balls>43</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>544</playerid>
					<name>Shakib Al Hasan</name>
					<batsman-name>Shakib</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shakib</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8231</playerid>
					<name>Sabbir Rahman</name>
					<batsman-name>S Rahman</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Rahman</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8018</playerid>
					<name>Nasir Hossain</name>
					<batsman-name>Nasir Hossain</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nasir Hossain</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>323</playerid>
					<name>Mashrafe Mortaza</name>
					<batsman-name>Mortaza</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mortaza</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8243</playerid>
					<name>Arafat Sunny</name>
					<batsman-name>A Sunny</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>A Sunny</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8548</playerid>
					<name>Taskin Ahmed</name>
					<batsman-name>Taskin Ahmed</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Taskin Ahmed</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1736</playerid>
					<name>Rubel Hossain</name>
					<batsman-name>Rubel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rubel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>612</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>145</runs>
				<overs>25.3</overs>
				<batsman>Tamim Iqbal</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Tamim</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1121</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>154</runs>
				<overs>27.5</overs>
				<batsman>Mahmudullah</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mahmudullah</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>4</wides>
			<noballs>2</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Pakistan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>360</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Hafeez</name>
					<bowler-name>M Hafeez</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Hafeez</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>37</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>504</playerid>
					<name>Umar Gul</name>
					<bowler-name>U Gul</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Umar Gul</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>53</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1051</playerid>
					<name>Wahab Riaz</name>
					<bowler-name>Riaz</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Riaz</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>6</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>30</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7900</playerid>
					<name>Junaid Khan</name>
					<bowler-name>Junaid Khan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Junaid Khan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7.3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>67</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>2</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8991</playerid>
					<name>Zulfiqar Babar</name>
					<bowler-name>Z Babar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Babar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>56</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6633</playerid>
					<name>Azhar Ali</name>
					<bowler-name>Azhar Ali</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Azhar Ali</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>7</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8370</playerid>
					<name>Sami Aslam</name>
					<bowler-name>Sami Aslam</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sami Aslam</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8299</playerid>
					<name>Haris Sohail</name>
					<bowler-name>H Sohail</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sohail</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>697</playerid>
					<name>Fawad Alam</name>
					<bowler-name>F Alam</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Fawad Alam</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9468</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Rizwan</name>
					<bowler-name>M Rizwan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rizwan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10094</playerid>
					<name>Saad Nasim</name>
					<bowler-name>Saad Nasim</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Saad Nasim</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



