<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14762" >
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>1st ODI</gameDesc>
		<series>Zimbabwe tour of Pakistan, 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Pakistan</home>
		<away>Zimbabwe</away>
		<teamsabbr>PAK vs ZIM</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>PAK</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>ZIM</awayabbr>
		<homeId>3</homeId>
		<awayId>12</awayId>
		<venue>Gaddafi Stadium, Lahore</venue>
		<startdate>26 05 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>26 05 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Pakistan</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Pakistan won by 41 runs</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Pakistan</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns>41</wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets></wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Aleem Dar</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Russell Tiffin</Name>
			<Country>Zim</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Ahmed Shahab</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Azhar Khan</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>11:00</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150526192451</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>Zim</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>Pak</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>334</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>5</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>50</batteamovers>
		<status>Pakistan won by 41 runs</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>9352</playerid>
			<name>Richmond Mutumbami*</name>
			<batsman-name>Mutumbami</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Mutumbami</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>21</runs>
			<balls-faced>19</balls-faced>
			<fours>3</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>181</playerid>
			<name>Prosper Utseya</name>
			<batsman-name>P Utseya</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Utseya</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>21</runs>
			<balls-faced>18</balls-faced>
			<fours>3</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1051</playerid>
			<name>Wahab Riaz*</name>
			<bowler-name>Riaz</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Riaz</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>10</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>47</runs>
			<wickets>3</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>1052</playerid>
			<name>Anwar Ali</name>
			<bowler-name>A Ali</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Anwar Ali</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>10</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>81</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>376</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>170</playerid>
<name>Elton Chigumbura</name>
<player-runs>117</player-runs>
<player-balls>95</player-balls>
<runs>293</runs>
<wicket-nbr>5</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>1051</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Riaz</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>5</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[. 1 . 4 . Wd . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 1 . 1 2 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 4 . 1 . Wd . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 . 1 4 1 2 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_PAK_ZIM/PAK_ZIM_MAY26/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[That brings an end to the proceedings. The second ODI is coming up on Friday. Do join us for that game. Until then, this is <b>Akshay Maanay</b> signing off on behalf of <b>Krishna</b> and my co-commentators <b>Pradeep</b>, <b>Sidhant Maheshwari</b> and <b>Raju.</b> Goodnight and Cya!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Azhar Ali:</b> "It was an outstanding effort from the batsmen. Hafeez gave us a good start. Haris (Soahil) and Malik continued the good work. The wickets are very good and it is tough for the bowlers. We have to adapt to the conditions and not give away many runs. I have been working hard on my batting. I try to go out and play fearless cricket and set an example for the team. We need to have the right balance between caution and aggression."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Malik:</b> "I needed it. I was asked to bat at No. 5, but Waqar (Younis) and Mushtaq (Ahmed) came to me and told me to go at No. 4. So, that push helped me play well. I have been performing well in the domestic tournament, I have got a nice flow going on. Before I got selected, I have been playing Leagues all round the world, I want to play as an allrounder. I want to bowl and have been working hard on it. I am still in that learning process and hope I keep learning. I am honored to get this award. I would like to thank the people who backed me and those who didn't as well."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shoaib Malik</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his 76-ball 112 and one wicket.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chigumbura:</b> "I thought we applied ourselves well. But the last 7 overs didn't go our way to get the score. I am delighted with my knock, hopefully can get more in the next game. I thought we started well with the ball, but didn't execute the yorkers at the death. It was still a good wicket to bat on, it was important to score as many runs as possible."]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sean Williams looked scratchy during his brief stay at the crease and he fell after top-edging one to the keeper off Riaz. Chigumbura took a toll on Mohammad Sami as he smacked the Pakistani veteran for 22 runs in an over which included 3 sixes and a four. Chigumbura finally got out to a pacy full delivery from Wahab Riaz as he was forced to slog every ball while trying to reduce the required run rate. It was too difficult for the rest of the batsmen with the Pakistani bowlers keeping it tight towards the end. Zimbabwe had a day to forget barring the fact that they registered their highest ODI score (334/5) against a Test playing nation today.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Zimbabwe got off to a steady start as the openers played sensibly in the mandatory powerplay. Even though they lost both the openers in the space of five overs, Masakadza and skipper Chigumbura steadied the ship with a 124-run stand for the third wicket. Just when the partnership was looking dangerous, Masakadza threw his wicket away in quest of some quick runs. Chigumbura stayed on and ensured that he clobbered the freebies as he went on to register his maiden ODI ton.]]></line><line><![CDATA[It has been a happy outing for the hosts as they registered a comprehensive victory against Zimbabwe. Pakistan won the toss and elected to bat on a pitch which was flat and hard. Pakistan openers provided a great start which helped set a platform for the batsmen to follow. Shoaib Malik played a magnificent knock on his comeback as he registered his first century in six years. Pakistan managed to post a mammoth total as all the top four batters scored in excess of 75 runs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Utseya, 2 runs, <b>Pakistan win by 41 runs.</b> Another off-speed delivery outside off, Utseya leans forward and caresses the drive wide of long-off, the fielder runs to his left and tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Mutumbami, 1 run, yorker on off, Mutumbami brings his bat down and squeezes it to the vacant mid-wicket region]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Mutumbami, <b>FOUR</b>, slower ball outside off, Mutumbami shuffles across, opens the bat face and steers it past the diving short third man fielder, the fast outfield takes care of the rest]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Utseya, 1 run, good length ball on off, Utseya knocks it to cover and picks up a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Utseya, no run, yorker on the stumps, Utseya digs it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Utseya, <b>FOUR</b>, boundary to start the final over, width on offer, Utseya throws his bat at that, slices it between backward point and short third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[48.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, no run, bouncer to end his spell. Mutumbami sinks under it and allows the ball to sail through to Sarfraz. Riaz finishes with figures: <b>10-0-47-3</b>. Another terrific effort from him on a flat track]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, <b>wide</b>, Riaz will have to reload, slips in the slower ball down leg, wide signalled by umpire Tiffin]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, no run, drags the length back, Mutumbami taps it to backward point, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Utseya, 1 run, gives the charge to Riaz, who bowls it short, doesn't rise much, pulled to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Utseya, no run, back of a length around off, Utseya guides it to backward point, wanted the run but is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Utseya, <b>FOUR</b>, short ball aimed at the batsman, Utseya gets inside the line and goes for the pull, the ball takes the glove and flies to the left of the keeper, fine leg was square and he had no chance of stopping that]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, 1 run, shortish and outside off, Mutumbami rides the bounce and cuts to square third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[47.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Mutumbami, 1 run, low full toss on off, Mutumbami whips it down to long-on and retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Mutumbami, 2 runs, drops the slower ball short, Mutumbami pulls to deep mid-wicket, had enough time to come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Utseya, 1 run, yorker length on the stumps, Utseya squeezes it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Utseya, no run, change of pace, it was in the slot, Utseya was looking to send it into orbit, fails to make the required connection]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Mutumbami, 1 run, fuller and just outside off, Mutumbami chips it on the bounce to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Utseya, 1 run, slower ball outside off, Utseya mistimes the drive towards cover, easy single taken]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Anwar Ali [8.0-0-63-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, no run, short and on leg-stump, Mutumbami ducks under it and evades it comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[Back over the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, <b>wide</b>, that must have slipped out of his hands, high full toss well wide of off, Mutumbami can't reach it, Sarfraz Ahmed doesn't glove it as well, but the duo don't risk a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, no run, low full toss around off, Mutumbami drives and picks out mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, <b>FOUR</b>, Sami continues to have a horror day. Full toss outside off, Mutumbami goes hard at it, the ball takes the outside edge and rolls down to third man, Sami allows it to go through his legs. He fetches the ball back and shakes his head]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, no run, shortish and outside off, Mutumbami slaps it straight to extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Utseya, 1 run, too straight, on middle and leg, Utseya works it square of the wicket on the leg-side, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Utseya, no run, angled across off, Utseya drives and misses, just too good for the batsman]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[45.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Mutumbami, no run, fullish and outside off, Mutumbami drives but this time finds the fielder at extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Mutumbami, <b>FOUR</b>, fabulous shot! That brings up the <b>300</b> as well. Pitched up just outside off, Mutumbami leans forward and creams it wide of mid-off, the timing was excellent as the ball raced away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Utseya, 1 run, on a length just outside off, Utseya goes for the on-the-up drive, drags it to mid-on off the inner part of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Utseya, no run, too full and on the stumps, almost a yorker, Utseya digs it out towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Utseya, <b>FOUR</b>, Sami continues to leak runs. Short and not much venom on this delivery, Utseya swivels and pulls it behind square, split fine leg and deep backward square to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Utseya, no run, short and rising on the batsman, Utseya defends off his gloves to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Utseya, 1 run, shortens the length and gets it to holds its line, Utseya is squared up as the outside edge goes wide of the slip fielder and down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[A wide slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Utseya, no run, slanted across the right-hander, Utseya has a slash and fails to make contact]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Prosper Utseya, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Cleaned up! A top innings from Chigumbura comes to an end. He takes the hopes of a Zimbabwe win along with him. Riaz is delighted. Good length ball, Chigumbura backs away and wanted to force it through the off-side, is beaten by the pace and the off-stump goes for a walk. <b>Chigumbura b Riaz 117(95) [4s-10 6s-4]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riaz to Chigumbura, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, 1 run, direct hit and <b>Chigumbura would have been in trouble.</b> Back of a length around off, Mutumbami taps it towards backward point, calls for a sharp run, Chigumbura responds and was short if the fielder had hit the bulls-eye]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, no run, short and angled across the right hander, Mutumbami looks to glide it to third man, but is undone by the extra bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, no run, back of a length on middle and leg, Mutumbami gets inside the line and doesn't connect with the flick, wears it on the thigh pad, the ball dribbles to the on-side, wanted a single but is sent back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, <b>SIX</b>, third six of the over and Sami gives away <b>22 runs.</b> This is unbelievable hitting. Short delivery, Chigumbura sits back and waits for it, pulls it over deep square leg, the fielder near the rope was a mere spectator]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, <b>FOUR</b>, this is tremendous batting, Sami goes full, targets the stumps, Chigumbura drills it straight down the ground, long-on had no chance of stopping that, plenty of power behind that shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, <b>SIX</b>, another massive six. This is some shot by the Zimbabwean skipper. Length delivery right in the slot, Chigumbura moves away to the leg-side and smashes it over wide long-on for the second six of the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, no run, off-speed bumper, Chigumbura looks to ramp it over the keeper, can't make the required connection]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, no run, slower short ball, Chigumbura is early into the pull, misses it by a distance]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, <b>SIX</b>, what a moment! Chigumbura registers his <b>maiden ODI hundred.</b> He gets there in style. Raises his bat and takes his helmet. Soaks in the applause from the crowd and his team-mates. Coming to the ball, short and plenty of width on offer, Chigumbura cuts it up and over backward point, had enough legs to go the distance]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Sami [5.0-0-32-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, no run, back of a length just outside off, Mutumbami stays back and knocks it down the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, 2 runs, short and just outside off, Mutumbami rides the bounce and cuts square of the wicket, the sweeper runs to his left and tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, 1 run, takes the pace off the ball, Chigumbura steers it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, no run, back of a length around off, Chigumbura mistimes the punch to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, <b>FOUR</b>, edged and four. It was a ripper from Riaz, short and rising steeply, Chigumbura was hanging back trying to defend, the ball takes the shoulder and flies wide of the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Richmond Mutumbami, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sean Williams, <b>out</b> Caught by Sarfraz Ahmed!! Riaz once again provides the breakthrough for Pakistan. And it is the short delivery that gives him yet another wicket. Williams goes for the pull, top-edges it high in the air and to the right of the keeper, Sarfraz Ahmed called for it and took it easily. <b>Sean Williams c Sarfraz Ahmed b Riaz 36(28) [4s-5]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Riaz to Sean Williams, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz [6.0-0-25-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chigumbura, <b>FOUR</b>, banged in halfway down the wicket, Chigumbura was expecting it, rocks back and muscles the pull towards deep mid-wicket, it just bounced before the ad cushions. Hafeez near the rope signalled four, but umpire Dar still went upstairs, just to be sure]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, 1 run, too straight, on leg-stump, Williams whips it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chigumbura, 1 run, short delivery right at the batsman, Chigumbura tucks it awkwardly to mid-wicket, thinks about the second but settles with one as Anwar Ali tidies up himself]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chigumbura, no run, another slower short ball outside off, Chigumbura goes for the upper cut, fails to connect with it]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, 1 run, change of pace, Williams backs away and forces it to mid-off, quick single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, <b>wide</b>, slower short ball down leg, Williams has nothing to do with it, wide given for line]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, <b>FOUR</b>, Anwar Ali has been extremely unlucky today. Excellent yorker, Williams squirts it off the outer half of the bat to third man, the fielder was inside the ring and was very square]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, <b>SIX</b>, that's a monstrous hit from the Zimbabwean skipper. Takes a couple of steps down the wicket for this flighted delivery, gets underneath it and sends it soaring over long-on for a maximum. That went a long way into the crowd]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, no run, shimmies down the wicket, gets to the pitch and drives to the right of the bowler, Malik puts his hand out and makes a fine stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, no run, stays round the wicket for Chigumbura, slows this up on leg-stump, Chigumbura misses the sweep and is struck on the kneeroll]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, 1 run, fired into the blockhole, Williams squeezes the drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, no run, down the track and plays the big hit, ekes out an inside edge onto the pad, the ball towards the keeper and Williams had to rush back]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! Malik starts from round the wicket, tosses it up on off and middle, Williams kneels down and sweeps it over square leg, ball bounces a couple of times before reaching the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shoaib Malik [3.0-0-22-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The batting powerplay yielded 40 runs. Zimbabwe need 136 runs in the last 10 overs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, 1 run, too full and on the stumps, Williams whips it to mid-wicket, takes on Azhar Ali and makes it with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, no run, fullish and close to off, Chigumbura stays leg-side of the ball and slices the drive to backward point, straight to the fielder, hence no single available]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chigumbura, 1 run, Chigumbura is cramped for room with the back of a length delivery, defends awkwardly to the on-side, gets across to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chigumbura, 2 runs, slower ball that is dragged short, Chigumbura pulls between deep mid-wicket and long-on, picks up two before the ball is hunted down]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, 1 run, fuller and around off, Williams push-drives to mid-off, calls for a quick single and gets a good response from Chigumbura]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, 2 runs, pitched up outside off, Williams drives it to deep extra cover, the sweeper had some ground to cover, that allows the batsmen to come back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, <b>FOUR</b>, pitched up and in the slot, Chigumbura plants his front foot and drives it handsomely to the deep extra cover fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riaz goes round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, no run, short and wide of off, Chigumbura goes for a wild pull, misses it by a long way]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, no run, bumper right into the helmet grill, Chigumbura was hurried on the pull and misses, he wears it on the helmet grill and he is lucky that it didn't harm him]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, <b>FOUR</b>, short and angling away from the right hander, Chigumbura hangs back and cuts it uppishly square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, 2 runs, on a good length into middle and leg, Chigumbura swivels across and miscues the pull to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sean Williams, 1 run, short delivery just outside off, this was slower as well, Williams yet again gets a top-edge on the pull and the ball rolls to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, 1 run, full delivery on the pads, Williams works it to deep mid-wicket and scampers for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, <b>FOUR</b>, short ball just outside off, Williams top-edges the pull and the ball rolls towards the third man fence, lucky boundary for Williams]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, no run, full delivery just outside off, Williams drives it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chigumbura, leg byes, 1 run, bumper just outside off, Chigumbura was looking to pull, he misses it by a long way, ball hits the shoulder and rolls to keeper who gets a bad bounce and concedes an extra]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, 1 run, back of a length delivery outside off, Williams mistimes the pull to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, <b>FOUR</b>, poor first ball from Anwar Ali, back of a length on middle and leg, Williams sits back and helps it on its way behind square on the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Anwar Ali [5.0-0-34-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, no run, slower ball bouncer outside off, Chigumbura lets it go through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sean Williams, 1 run, slower delivery outside off, Williams cuts it to square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, 1 run, <b>dropped</b>, that's a dolly to Azam at deep square leg, another short delivery at the batsman, Chigumbura connects with pull and the ball goes straight to Azam who attempts a reverse cup, fails to hang onto it]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, no run, short delivery angling away from the right hander, Chigumbura plays the pull a day late and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sean Williams, 1 run, short of length delivery just outside off, Williams guides it uppishly towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, 1 run, back of a length delivery around the hip, Chigumbura tucks it off the back foot towards square leg and gets an easy single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz [4.0-0-10-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Sean Williams, <b>FOUR</b>, finally, Williams gets the boundary he was looking for. Straying onto leg-stump, Williams bends his knee, plays the sweep/pull over backward square, the fielder jumps but the ball eludes him]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Sean Williams, no run, touch short and just outside off, Williams makes room and mistimes the cut to extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, 1 run, down the wicket to meet the pitch of the ball, whipped on the bounce to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, no run, flighted close to off, Chigumbura push-drives to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Sean Williams, 1 run, Williams comes down the track, wrists it wide of long-on, wanted two but decides against it]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, 1 run, starts from round the wicket, tossed up around off, Chigumbura drives to mid-off, the fielder dives to his right and makes a half stop]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>batting powerplay</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, 1 run, once more on the leg-stump, Chigumbura works it in front of square and collects a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, 1 run, floated up outside off, Williams drags the loft to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, 1 run, slower and on leg-stump, Chigumbura nudges it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, <b>FOUR</b>, bad delivery and Chigumbura latches onto it. Half tracker outside off, Chigumbura backs away and slaps it in front of square, wide of long-off and picks up four more]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, no run, goes round the wicket, angles it across off, punched to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, 1 run, Williams gives the charge to Malik, gets to the pitch and drills to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, no run, sliding onto the pads, Chigumbura glances and finds short fine, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Sean Williams, 1 run, eases the flighted delivery down to long-on, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Sean Williams, no run, flatter and on leg-stump, Williams fails to connect with the flick, the ball gets stuck between his legs]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Sean Williams, no run, takes a step out and mistimes the punch to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Sean Williams, no run, quicker and on off, Williams pushes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, Chigumbura works it behind square on the leg-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, 1 run, drifting on the pads, Chigumbura works it away to deep backward square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sean Williams, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for a <b>drinks</b> break]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to H Masakadza, <b>out</b> Caught by Azam!! Malik gets the big wicket of Masakadza. This was bowled quicker on the pads and Masakadza wanted to hit it over the deep mid-wicket fence, he gets the elevation on the hoick as he comes down the track but doesn't get the distance. Azam from deep mid-wicket runs forward and takes a simple catch. Masakadza walks back disappointed. <b>H Masakadza c Azam b Shoaib Malik 73(73) [4s-4 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shoaib Malik to H Masakadza, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to H Masakadza, no run, tossed up on off, Masakadza defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to H Masakadza, <b>SIX</b>, that's been <b>smashed!</b> It was a freebie from Malik, full toss down the leg-side, Masakadza kneels down and slog sweeps it over the deep backward square leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, 1 run, sweeps this quicker one to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, 2 runs, comes down the track and converts it into a full toss, he hoicks it over mid-wicket but doesn't get the desired elevation or the distance. Luckily for him, the ball falls just short of the fielder charging in from deep mid-wicket, gets back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, 1 run, <b>dropped!</b> This was bowled on middle and leg stump line, Chigumbura goes slightly across and hoicks it straight towards mid-wicket, where Shafiq gets both hands on the ball, but he somehow can't hold on. The ball escapes to the deep and the batsmen take a single. That was hit hard by Chig and went fast to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, no run, pushes this delivery on middle stump line to the right of the bowler, who quickly moves across and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, no run, quicker and on the pads, Chigumbura can't tuck it away into the on-side and wears it on the pad, it was going down leg though]]></line><line><![CDATA[Goes back over the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, 1 run, kneels down and sweeps this quicker delivery straight to the man at deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, <b>SIX</b>, <b>that's been tonked!</b> This was flighted on middle stump line, Masakadza steps out of the crease and launches it over the deep mid-wicket fence for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, 1 run, Chigu gets to his <b>19th ODI fifty</b> with this single, it was flatter and on the stumps, Chigumbura punches it down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, 1 run, drifting on the pads, worked away through backward square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, no run, <b>in the air and just short!</b> This was tossed up on the stumps from round the wicket, Chigumbura looks to work it away into the on-side, closes the bat face a little too early and gets a leading edge, the ball was in the air for sometime but falls just short of the fielder at cover, who was charging in towards the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to H Masakadza, 1 run, on middle and leg stump line, Masakadza knocks it through mid-on and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, 1 run, punches this quicker delivery on off down to long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to H Masakadza, 1 run, employs the reverse sweep but fails to connect with it properly, the ball rolls away towards the short third man region and the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to H Masakadza, no run, flatter around off, Masakadza bunts it towards extra cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shoaib Malik, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, no run, straighter one outside off, Chigumbura was playing for the turn there as he pushed at it, the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, 1 run, on middle and leg, Masakadza chips it to the right of mid-wicket, who can't reach it. The batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, no run, comes down the track and converts this full delivery into a full toss, drills it back to the bowler, who jumps and parries it towards mid-wicket with his right hand]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, 1 run, once again bowls this one on the pads, Chigumbura works it through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, 1 run, <b>100-run partnership</b> comes up with this single, drifting on middle and leg, Masakadza flicks it through square leg and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, no run, works this flighted delivery on middle stump line towards mid-wicket, who dives to his right and prevents the single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, 1 run, Sami drags his length back outside off, Masakadza stays on the back foot and guides it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, no run, Sami errs in line yet again, short of length and sliding down leg, Masakadza was looking to help it on its way, can't beat the diving short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, 1 run, on a length and slinging into middle and leg, Chigumbura tucks it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, <b>FOUR</b>, three in three for Zimbabwe, this was full and just outside off, Chigumbura drives off the front foot and beats the diving mid-off, into the extra cover fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, <b>FOUR</b>, short and wide again, Chigumbura stays on the back foot and cuts it to the deep backward point fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, <b>FOUR</b>, poor delivery first up from Sami, delivers it short and wide, Chigumbura cuts it uppishly over point and gets a four]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Sami [4.0-0-18-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, <b>FOUR</b>, that's been nicely played. It was floated up, Masakadza kneels down and employs the reverse sweep, sends it through backward point and the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, 1 run, drifting on the pads this time, Chigumbura flicks it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, 1 run, slightly flatter this time around, Masakadza bunts it down to long-off and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, 1 run, drives this flighted delivery down to long-off for another run]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, 1 run, <b>uppish and safe!</b> Masakadza gets to his <b>27th ODI fifty</b> with this single. It was tossed up outside off, Masakadza drives it in the air through the vacant mid-off region for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, no run, punches this flatter delivery off the inside half of the bat towards mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, 1 run, puts his front foot forward and drags this fuller delivery down to long-on off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chigumbura, 1 run, googly from Yasir on off, Chigumbura drives it to the left of the bowler, who dives but can't reach the ball. The batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, 1 run, eases this flighted delivery down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, no run, shortish and outside off, Masakadza goes deep in the crease and cuts, picks out backward point to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, no run, looks to drive, gets an inside edge onto the pad and the ball rolls away to the left of the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, no run, flatter and around off, Masakadza punches it to the left of the bowler, who dives full length and makes a good stop]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, no run, quicker and on leg, Chigumbura kneels down and sweeps, hits it straight to the fielder at short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, no run, turning in on leg from middle stump line, Chigumbura makes room and pushes it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, 1 run, leans forward and drives this tossed up delivery to the left of long-on, he was looking for the second there but it's not available]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, 1 run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Chigumbura bunts it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, no run, this was the straighter one from Hafeez, Chigumbura was expecting the ball to turn as he pushed at it, the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, no run, flatter and on the stumps, Chigumbura punches it to the right of the bowler, who fields]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chigumbura, 1 run, quicker outside off, Chigumbura goes on the back foot and punches it to the left of cover, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, 1 run, drifting in on middle and leg, Chigumbura hangs back and works it through mid-wicket for another run]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chigumbura, 1 run, flatter outside off, Chigumbura goes on the back foot and punches it to sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chigumbura, no run, comes down the track and takes this tossed up delivery on the full, driven straight to the man at extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, 1 run, floated up on middle, Masakadza puts his front foot forward and drives it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, no run, quicker and fuller just outside off, Masakadza drills it back to the bowler, who jumps high and stops the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, 1 run, quicker and on off, Masakadza bunts it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, 2 runs, goes down on one knee and sweeps it past a diving short fine leg, the fielder from deep backward square leg runs to his right and stops the ball, the batsmen take two in the meantime]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, <b>wide</b>, down the leg-side, Masakadza was looking to help it fine, can't connect and the umpire signals a wide as the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, 1 run, kneels down and sweeps this flighted delivery straight to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, no run, tossed up outside off, driven to extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, 2 runs, another one that's slightly shorter in length and turning away outside off, Chigumbura was looking to work it through the on-side, gets an outside dge that runs away down towards third man, the batsmen run for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, no run, flatter on off, Chigumbura punches it to the left of mid-wicket, can't get the single away]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chigumbura, 1 run, shortish outside off, Chigumbura mistimes the cut towards backward point, the batsmen hare across for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, 1 run, flatter on the stumps, Masakadza punches it through mid-wicket and gets to the other end with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chigumbura, 1 run, quicker on the stumps, Chigumbura nudges it through mid-wicket, the bowler goes after the ball and the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chigumbura, 2 runs, floated up outside off, Chigumbura drives it through extra cover, sweeper runs to his right to stop the ball and the batsmen take two in the meantime]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, 1 run, flatter and on off, Masakadza flat-bats it hard back to the bowler, who jumps up and gets a hand on it, the ball rolls away behind him and the batsmen take a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, no run, tossed up around off, Masakadza leans forward and drives it to extra cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, 1 run, eases this down to long-on after going across to this tossed up delivery on off]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, no run, flatter on off, Chigumbura punches it to the right of the bowler, mid-wicket runs to his left and prevents the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, 1 run, floated up on off and middle, Masakadza goes across and eases it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, 1 run, flighted delivery on off, Masakadza comes forward and wristily works it towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, 2 runs, kneels down to this slower delivery on middle stump line, Masakadza laps it towards fine leg and gets back for the second. Hafeez thought that it hit the pad first and was appealing for an lbw, but the umpire was not amused]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chigumbura, 1 run, flatter and turning in on off, Chigumbura punches it down to long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Hafeez, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, no run, <b>almost sneaked through!</b> That was flatter and quicker on the stumps, Masakadza wanted to flat-bat it hard, but didn't judge the pace of the ball. Luckily for him, he got an inside edge onto the pad and the ball rolled away past the off stump]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chigumbura, 1 run, tossed up and spinning away just outside off, Chigumbura comes on the front foot, reaches to the pitch of the ball and drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chigumbura, 2 runs, googly on leg, Masakadza hangs back and works it through mid-wicket, gets back for the second with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, 1 run, once again bowls it quicker on off, Masakadza knocks it to sweeper cover and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chigumbura, 1 run, bowled slightly quicker and fuller on off, Masakadza leans forward and drives it wide of long-off, he was looking for the second there but the fielder was quickly onto the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, 1 run, flighted delivery on off, Masakadza comes forward and drives it to the left of the bowler, who dives across but fails to stop it. The batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to H Masakadza, 3 runs, back of a length delivery swaying into middle and leg, Masakadza flicks it to deep mid wicket, the ball almost reached the fence, Haris Sohail makes a diving stop and saves a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to H Masakadza, <b>FOUR</b>, slow, short and wide and gets the treatment, Masakadza stays on the back foot and cuts it square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Chigumbura, 1 run, change of pace outside off, Chigumbura mistimes the slog as the ball rolls towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Chigumbura, no run, slower delivery just outside off, Chigumbura walks across slightly and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to H Masakadza, 1 run, off-cutter just outside off, Masakadza guides it to third man off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Chigumbura, 1 run, on a good length and outside off, Chigumbura sits back and cuts it in front of square on the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, <b>FOUR</b>, googly from Yasir Shah and Masakadza picks it quickly, he goes deep in the crease and pulls it magnificently to the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chigumbura, 1 run, turning away from outside off, Chigumbura hangs back and punches it through extra cover for a single, the batsmen almost collided with each other while crossing over, but did well to avoid it in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, 1 run, slows this one outside off, Masakadza knocks it to sweeper cover and crosses over for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chigumbura, 1 run, flatter and quicker outside off, Chigumbura punches it to sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chigumbura, <b>FOUR</b>, this time Chigu gets the desired result. This was tossed up outside off, Chigumbura lofts it over extra cover and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chigumbura, no run, googly on leg, Chigumbura comes down the track and looks to go big on the off-side, he misses and the ball hits him on the pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Chigumbura, 1 run, slower delivery just outside off, Chigumbura punches it to deep extra cover and hustles for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Chigumbura, no run, short of length delivery outside off, Chigumbura cuts and picks point fielder to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Chigumbura, no run, slower delivery outside off, the off-cutter, Chigumbura was looking to drive, misses by a long way]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to H Masakadza, 1 run, back of a length delivery outside off, Masakadza comes down the track and slaps it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to H Masakadza, no run, slower and just outside off, Masakadza prods forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to H Masakadza, 2 runs, on a length swaying into the pads, Masakadza flicks it to deep backward square leg and steals a couple]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, 1 run, Yasir drags his length back and Masakadza rocks back, he pulls it past the bowler, who dives but fails to stop the ball, the batsmen cross over as the ball dribbles away to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chigumbura, 1 run, googly on the pads, Masakadza fails to work it away into the on-side, the batsmen sneak in a single as the ball rolls away into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, 1 run, floated up on middle stump line, Masakadza bunts it down to long-on and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, no run, touch quicker and fuller on off, Masakadza drives it straight to short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chigumbura, 1 run, drifting on middle and leg, Chigumbura eases it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, 1 run, flatter and on off, Masakadza goes back and punches it down to long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yasir Shah, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to H Masakadza, 1 run, Azam pulls his length back and delivers it on middle and leg, Masakadza waits on the back foot and knocks to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to H Masakadza, 2 runs, short and wide of off, Masakadza stays back and cuts it behind square on the off-side, gets a couple with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to H Masakadza, no run, length delivery on middle and leg, Masakadza works it straight to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Chigumbura, 1 run, back of a length delivery sliding into middle and leg, Chigumbura swivels across and mistimes the pull towards short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Chigumbura, no run, on a length and just outside off, Chigumbura blocks it off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Chigumbura, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Chigumbura punches it straight to short cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Chigumbura gets a thick inside edge as he was looking to defend off the front foot, ball hares across to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, no run, bumper on the stumps, Chigumbura sways away from the line and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[Short leg in place now]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, 1 run, short of length delivery swaying on middle and leg, Masakadza was looking to fend, ball takes the glove and rolls towards fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, no run, back of a length delivery on the body line, Masakadza pulls and picks mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, no run, back of a length just outside off, defended back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, no run, on a good length and angling away from the right hander, Masakadza was looking to defend, misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to H Masakadza, 1 run, length delivery on middle and off, Masakadza was looking to scoop it over the keeper, misses and gets a thin outside edge as the ball rolls to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to H Masakadza, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a gift from the bowler, short of length and had enough time for Masakadza to pull over mid-wicket, ball races into the fence in a hurry]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Chigumbura, 1 run, length delivery on middle and leg, Chigumbura pushes it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Chigumbura, no run, that's a <b>ripper from Azam</b>, Chigumbura had no idea about it, on a good length and gets it to straighten, Chigumbura was pressing forward to defend, he misses and the ball hits in line with the off and middle, that looked very close but the umpire says 'Not Out']]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to H Masakadza, 1 run, full delivery on the pads, Masakadza works it wide of mid-on and gets a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to H Masakadza, no run, on a good length and just outside off, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Elton Chigumbura, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sibanda, <b>out</b> Caught&Bowled!! Riaz gets a deserved reward! This was banged in short and just outside off, Sibanda was beaten for pace, there was no room to play the pull as well. He was in no position, ends up getting a top-edge and Riaz holds onto the return catch. Zimbabwe have lost both openers now. Once again Sibanda fals after getting a start. <b>Sibanda c and b Riaz 23(36) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riaz to Sibanda, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught&Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, worked wide of cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, no run, loud shout for a <b>caught behind</b>, Riaz was pumped up, so was Sarfraz Ahmed, but the finger stays down. This was banged in short and angled across the right-hander, Masakadza went for the pull, looked like the ball grazed the top-edge on its way to the keeper. Everyone was convinced, but the umpire wasn't. There's no DRS in this series]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sibanda, leg byes, 1 run, short of a length and angling onto Masakadza's pads, he looks to work it behind square and is struck high on the pads, the ball rolls past the lone slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, 1 run, short of a length and on Masakadza's hips, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, no run, back of a length and just outside off, punched towards mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Sibanda, 2 runs, width on offer from Azam, Sibanda comes down the track and slashes it behind square on the off-side, he wants a second run and Masakadza has to hurry at the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Sibanda, no run, on a good length and well outside off, steered straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Sibanda, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, Sibanda prods across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Sibanda, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Sibanda comes down the track and drives it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Sibanda, no run, on a good length and in the channel around off, defended towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Sibanda, <b>wide</b>, Azam slips one well down the leg-side, called as a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to H Masakadza, 1 run, on a good length and well outside off, steered away towards third man for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Hammad Azam, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, 1 run, short and on Masakadza's hips, he wasn't in control as he looked to pull, gets it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, no run, on a good length and shaping away from outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, no run, short of a length and angling into Masakadza, worked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Masakadza stays behind the line and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sibanda, 1 run, another short ball from Riaz, Sibanda was beaten on pace, is cramped for room and gets a bottom edge towards the on-side, scampers across for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sibanda, no run, short of a length and holding its line outside off, Sibanda looks to cut and misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to H Masakadza, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Masakadza gets a big stride forward and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to H Masakadza, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Masakadza gets a good stride forward in defence]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hamilton Masakadza, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, <b>out</b> Caught by Hafeez!! That's a soft dismissal for Raza! He is very disappointed as he trudges back to the hut, it was an innocuous delivery on his pads, Raza was looking to flick, played a bit too early, gets it high on the bat and chips it towards mid-wicket. Hafeez moves across to his left and holds onto the simple chance. Zimbabwe have lost their first wicket. <b>S Raza c Hafeez b Anwar Ali 36(31) [4s-4 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Anwar Ali to S Raza, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, <b>FOUR</b>, that's sloppy from Riaz at third man, on a good length and holding its line outside off, Raza pushes at that and gets a thick edge towards third man. Riaz slides and stops the ball, but the ball rolled onto the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, no run, length ball on the stumps, turned towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, 2 runs, back of a length and just outside off, Raza waits on it, plays with an open face and guides it square behind point for a couple of runs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, 1 run, short of a length and angling across the right-hander, he was looking to pull and gets a bottom edge behind square on the on-side, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sibanda, 1 run, back of a length and in that channel outside off, dabbed away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sibanda, no run, lovely length from Riaz, shortens his length and gets this one to nip away from outside off, Sibanda nearly followed it, lucky not to have edged it]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, 1 run, short of a length and on Raza's hips, he tucks it in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sibanda, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, steered away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sibanda, no run, short of a length and on Sibanda's pads, he was beaten for pace as he looked to work it towards the on-side, the ball rolls away towards the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Sibanda dabs it with soft hands, calls for a quick single as the ball rolls slowly towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, 1 run, fuller length delivery and on Raza's pads, worked past mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four</b>, Raza runs down the track to a length delivery and throws his bat at that, gets a thick edge past the lone slip, the ball races away to the fence in a hurry]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, <b>FOUR</b>, tad fuller and on the stumps, Raza was shufling across on the flick, gets a soft leading edge back past the non-striker, the ball has enough power to race away to the straight boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, no run, Anwar Ali slips in the slower ball outside off, Raza covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, no run, on a good length and well outside off, punched firmly but straight to cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, 1 run, another short ball from Sami, Raza swivels across and pulls it in front of square on the on-side, just a single to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, <b>SIX</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, fraction too short and well outside off, Raza is quick to rock back and pulls it high and over wide mid-wicket, the first six of the chase]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, no run, on a good length and in that channnel outside off, defended off the backfoot towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, 1 run, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, steered away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, fuller length delivery and angling away from outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, on a good length and a hint of shape away from outside off, Sibanda is prodded into playing at that, beaten on the outside edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, 1 run, back of a length and just outside off, Sibanda plays with an open face and runs it down towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, short of a length and well outside off, punched off the backfoot and towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, on a good length and in that corridor outside off, Sibanda plays inside the line and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, fuller length delivery and in that channel outside off, Sibanda covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, lovely channel from Anwar Ali, keeps it full, drags Sibanda into the drive, a hint of shape away from outside off and the ball whizzes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, on a good length and on the off-stump line, driven back towards the bowler with a straight bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, 1 run, fuller length delivery and angling onto Sibanda's pads, worked to the right of mid-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, 1 run, too straight from Sami, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Sibanda plays with an open face and runs it behind square on the off-side. Yasir makes a half-stop but can't save the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, 1 run, back of a length and in that channel outside off, steered away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, no run, fuller length delivery and a hint of late shape away from middle, Raza was early into the flick, closed the face of the bat and gets a soft leading edge back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, tad overpitched and in that channel outside off, Raza leans forward, meets the ball on top of the bounce and caresses it past cover-point for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, 1 run, tad fuller and well outside off, punched off the backfoot to the right of backward point, Yasir dives and deflects it towards cover-point, saved three runs for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, no run, on a length and just outside off, Raza waits on it and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, 2 runs, back of a length and in that channel around off, Raza goes back and works it in front of square on the on-side, he wants a second run and gets it with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, no run, short of a length and just outside off, punched towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, no run, pitched up and in that channel outside off, kept a tad low as well, Raza bends down and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, 2 runs, short of a length and angling into Raza, he was looking to pull and gets a bottom edge behind square on the on-side, back for the second run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Sibanda prods across and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Sibanda plays close to his body and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, 1 run, width on offer from Sami, Raza plays away from his body and gets a thick outside edge towards third man, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, no run, Sami shortens his length outside off, Raza prods across and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, no run, on a good length and in that corridor outside off, defended off the backfoot towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, no run, lovely line from Sami, pitched on a good length and gets it to leave the batsman. Raza went nowhere as he poked at that, beaten on the outside edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Sibanda stays behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, <b>FOUR</b>, Sibanda gets lucky again! This was a tad fuller and held its line outside off, Sibanda was looking to drive, gets an inside edge that races away past the leg-stump, another fortious boundary for Sibanda]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Sibanda gets half-forward and defends it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lucky and four</b>, short of a length and angling back into Sibanda, he was late on the pull, gets a bottom edge and the ball races away past the leg-stump and into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Sibanda gets behind the line and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, Anwar Ali starts off with a wide half-volley, Sibanda leans forward, presents the full face of the bat and drills it through extra cover for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Anwar Ali, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, no run, on a good length and a hint of late away swing, Raza is slightly squared up but manages to defend it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, no run, the bouncer from Sami, Raza watches it all along and ducks underneath it]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, no run, back of a length and in that channel around off, Raza gets behind the line and defends it with soft hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, 1 run, tad too straight from Sami, ends up drifting onto Sibanda's pads, nudged to the right of mid-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, Sami shortens his length and gets it to hold its line outside off, Sibanda covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Sibanda gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sibanda and S Raza are at the crease. Sibanda is on strike. Sami will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. Two slips in place for Sami]]></line><line><![CDATA[Here are some <b>highlights</b> of Pakistan's innings:]]></line><line><![CDATA[This is the <b>second time</b> where all the top four Pakistani batters have scored in excess of 50 runs. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shoaib Malik's 70-ball century is also the <b>second fastest century at Lahore</b>. ]]></line><line><![CDATA[375/3 is also the <b>highest team total at Lahore</b> in ODIs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[It will be a huge task for the visitors to chase this down. However, they showed some fight in the T20s. It will be interesting to see how the chase goes. Stay tuned for Zimbabwe's response in a short while.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pakistan skipper, Azhar Ali, departed after scoring 79 while Hafeez was bowled by Utseya. Malik and Sohail spent ample time in the middle to get used to the conditions. Once they were set, they smashed the Zimbabwean bowlers all over the park. Shoaib Malik reached his 8th century and played some delightful strokes during his brilliant knock. It took 6 years and 31 innings for the veteran to reach his 8th ton. Haris Sohail also played a superb knock as he gave good support to Malik. As a result, Pakistan posted a mammoth total and ensured that they are in the driver's seat to win this game.]]></line><line><![CDATA[After 6 long years, ODIs have made a return to Pakistan and they couldn't have asked for a better start to proceedings. Pakistan opted to bat and they made full use of the conditions. The openers got them off to the best of starts as Hafeez and Azhar Ali put on a 170-run stand for the first wicket. Although the opening duo played cautiously for the first eight overs, they shifted gears later on as they kept punishing the hapless Zimbabwean pacers. Zimbabwe's bowlers kept bowling poor lengths and paid the price for doing so.]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, <b>out</b> Caught by H Masakadza!! Malik falls off the last ball of the innings. The umpires check for the front foot, but it's fine. This was very full just outside off, Malik looks to carve it over backward point, but can't get the elevation. He ends up hitting it straight to the man at cover-point. Nonetheless, it was a great knock from Malik on his comeback in the ODI team. <b>Shoaib Malik c H Masakadza b Panyangara 112(76) [4s-12 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, 1 run, in the blockhole, Sohail jams out the drive to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, <b>dropped!</b> <b>200 of the partnership</b> comes up with this single as well. It was a low full toss from Panyangara, Malik slices it towards cover-point, who jumps and gets his right hand on the ball, but can't hold onto it]]></line><line><![CDATA[This is now <b>Pakistan's second highest total in ODIs</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, 1 run, yorker length delivery outside off, Sohail digs it out towards cover-point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, full and slightly wide outside off, Malik reaches out and squeezes out the drive to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, 1 run, almost a yorker just outside off, Sohail jams out the drive to long-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tinashe Panyangara [9.0-0-70-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a poor effort from the fielder at long-on, it was full and on the stumps, Malik slogs it down towards long-on, the ball bounces just in front of the fielder, who allows the ball to go through the fence. He should have tried for the catch and if not even that, he should have tried getting his body behind the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, no run, slower short ball angling in towards the batsman, Malik looks to pull but fails to lay bat on it]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a <b>great shot</b>. It was a full delivery just outside off, Malik lofts it over a leaping mid-off and collects four]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sohail, 1 run, mistimes the loft of this fuller ball, long-off runs forward to try and take it, but it falls well short of him]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, 3 runs, Malik gets to his <b>8th ODI ton</b>, he is delighted, while the crowd and his team-mates and support staff are up on their feet, applauding his effort. He removes his helmet and waves his bat to the crowd. Coming back to the ball, it was a slower ball outside off, Malik goes across and nudges it through square leg, comes back for the second easily. The fielder fires the throw at the non-striker's end, but the fielder fails to collect it cleanly behind the stumps, allowing an extra run on the overthrow]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, 2 runs, full and wide outside off, Malik drives it square of the wicket, sprints back for the second and is on <b>99</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[47.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, full on the stumps, Malik drives it to the left of mid-off, who dives to his left and stops the ball. The batsmen take a quick single and Malik will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, <b>FOUR</b>, full and around off, Malik makes room, gets under the ball and lofts it over mid-off and extra cover, collects four as there was no one in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, 2 runs, on a good length and on the stumps, Malik goes for a big slog, doesn't get the desired elevation and the ball falls in front of the fielder at long-on, who was running forward to his right to try and take it, the batsmen take a couple in the meantime]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, 1 run, makes room and jams out this overpitched delivery back onto his pad, the batsmen sneak in a single as the ball rolls away into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, 2 runs, Sohail backs away and Vitori follows him with a fuller one, clipped through mid-wicket for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, in the blockhole just outside off, Malik jams out the drive towards extra cover for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, slogs hard but picks out deep mid-wicket, he will keep the strike as the batsmen crossed over for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sohail, 1 run, slower full ball angling in on the stumps, Sohail swings hard at it, loses control of the bat as it falls to his left, he ends up slicing it high, the fielder at cover-point runs to his left, slides but fails to reach it in time, the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sohail, 2 runs, low full toss well outside off, Sohail drives it through extra cover, sweeper runs to his left and stops the ball, the batsmen take two in that time]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, yorker length delivery just outside off, Malik jams it out past the bowler, who gets a hand as he dives to his left, he can't stop it cleanly and the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, no run, low full toss outside off, Malik reaches out and jams it hard on the turf, the ball bounces up for the bowler, who leaps to his left and palms the ball to his left, doesn't allow the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sohail, 1 run, low full toss wide outside off, Sohail drives it to the left of point, who dives and stops the ball, the batsmen take a single in the meantime]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Mpofu [8.0-0-50-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, leg byes, 1 run, angling in on the pads, Sohail fails to tickle it fine, the ball rolls away into the on-side off the pad, the batsmen sneak in a leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, 2 runs, Sohail backs away and Vitori bowls a yorker on his legs, Sohail squeezes it out through mid-on, good running ensures that they come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Vitori, this was a high full toss at the batsman, Sohail was backing away and swings hard at it, sends it over square leg and the ball runs away to the fence. The umpire deems it to be a legal ball as he thinks it was just below the waist height]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, <b>SIX</b>, that's been <b>clobbered!</b> Sohail backs away and Vitori follows him with a fuller one, Sohail lofts it over the long-on fence with sheer ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, good ball from Vitori, this was bowled on a yorker length slightly wide outside off, Malik reaches out and squeezes it out towards mid-off, the batsmen pinch a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, no run, full and on the stumps, Malik drills the drive straight to mid-off, can't get the single away]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brian Vitori [8.0-1-53-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, Sohail has finished this over very strongly, brings up the <b>150-run partnership</b> as well, he gives the charge to this delivery on leg stump line, takes it on the full and whips it through mid-wicket, the fielder in the deep runs to his right but the ball was too far away from his reach]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, <b>SIX</b>, slower ball from Panyangara and Sohail had all the time in the world to transfer his weight on the back foot, Sohail pulls it up and over deep mid-wicket for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, Sohail goes leg-side to this fuller delivery and lofts it it in the gap between mid-off and extra cover, the ball hurries across the turf and crashes into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, no run, yorker length ball outside off, Sohail jams it out back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, bowls this one almost on a yorker length just outside off, Malik drives it straight to point, the batsmen cross over for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, 1 run, overpitched outside off, Sohail squeezes out the drive to sweeper cover for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tinashe Panyangara [8.0-0-54-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sohail, 1 run, low full toss outside off, Sohail slashes hard, the fielder at backward point dives full length to his left, stops the ball and saves some runs for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sohail, 2 runs, Sohail gets to his <b>6th ODI fifty</b> with this single, he goes across to his back of a length delivery just outside off, pushes it through the gap between mid-wicket and mid-on, good running ensures they come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sohail, 2 runs, low full toss outside off, Sohail drives it through extra cover, the sweeper runs to his left and tidies up in the deep, the batsmen come back for the second easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, angled across off stump line, Malik mistimes the slog towards mid-wicket and gets off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sohail, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Sohail leans forward and drives it to sweeper cover, gets to the other end with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Comes round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, full and slightly wide outside off, Malik reaches out for it and drives it to sweeper cover, the fielder misfields but the batsmen decide against coming back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Mpofu [7.0-0-42-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, low full toss well outside off, Malik moves across, opens the face of the bat late and guides to the right of short third man, who dives and stops the ball, the batsmen take a single in the meantime]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, <b>SIX</b>, on a length and on the stumps, Malik goes for a mighty heave, swings hard and sends it soaring over the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, <b>FOUR</b>, full delivery just outside off, Malik clears his front leg and slogs across the line, the fielder at long-on runs to his right but the ball escapes to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, 1 run, just short of a good length and just outside off, Sohail punches it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, Malik backs away slightly and Vitori follows him with a low full toss, he looks to help it down the ground, gets an inside edge onto the pad, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, 1 run, full delivery on middle and leg, Sohail clips it to deep mid-wicket and gets to the other end]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brian Vitori [7.0-1-39-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Sohail, 1 run, goes across and clips this through mid-wicket, gets across for a single and will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, gives the charge and ends up yorking himself, Malik jams it out to long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shoaib Malik, 2 runs, Williams drags his length back and Malik rocks back, he pulls it wide of long-on, the fielder in the deep runs to his right, dives and stops the ball. The batsmen take a couple in the meantime]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shoaib Malik, no run, comes down the track and drives this straight to extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[Changes to round the wicket now]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shoaib Malik, <b>FOUR</b>, Malik makes room and lofts this tossed up delivery inside-out over cover, there was no one in the deep and the ball rolls away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Sohail, 1 run, drifting on middle and leg, Sohail walks across and works it to deep mid-wicket for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sean Williams [4.0-0-33-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, 1 run, full toss on the pads, clipped through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, 2 runs, on the pads this time, Sohail works it behind square on the on-side, a misfield inside the circle allows the batsmen to come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, <b>no ball</b>, 2 runs, 100 of the partnership comes up with this couple, this was the back-of-the-hand slower ball full toss from Panyangara, he bowls it at the shoulder height, Sohail pulls it wide of long-on and comes back for the second. Called a no-ball for height]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, no run, low full toss outside off, Sohail must be feeling that he missed out on a freebie, he sliced it straight to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, full delivery outside off, Malik drives it towards cover-point, who dives to his left and misfields, allows the batsmen to take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Panyangara, ends up bowling a full toss while trying to bowl the yorker, Malik drives it wide of mid-off and collects four]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, <b>FOUR</b>, in the blockhole and it goes for four. This was bowled on a yorker length and on the stumps, Malik backs away and looks to drive it inside-out, gets a thick outside edge and it runs away to the third man fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>41 runs came in the batting powerplay</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, Malik takes a step and converts this full ball into a full toss, he had to reach out as the line was wide of off, he manages to drive it to sweeper cover and picks a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, 1 run, full and on the pads yet again, but this time Sohail finds the fielder at fine leg as he clipped it]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Sohail stays on the front foot and drives it straight to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, he connects it fine this time, full and on the pads, Sohail middles the flick as the ball hares across to the fine leg fence in a flash]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, 2 runs, fuller delivery on the stumps, Sohail works it wide of long-on and steals a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, no run, tad fuller and angling into the pads, Sohail clips, picks square leg to perfection]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brian Vitori [6.0-1-31-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, <b>FOUR</b>, full and in the slot, Malik stays rooted and slogs it to deep mid-wicket, the ball raced away in a hurry]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, <b>FOUR</b>, top-edge and four, that's Malik's <b>first fifty in 31 innings</b>, short and just outside off, Malik top-edges the pull to the fine leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, 1 run, full toss on the stumps, Sohail knocks it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, no run, short and wide of off, Sohail was shaping for the heave, decides against it at the last moment as he defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, full and on the pads, Malik clips to mid-wicket where the fielder dives and saves some runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, no run, short of length delivery around middle and off, Malik was looking to work it into the on-side but ends up pushing it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Malik hops across and clips it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sohail, 1 run, low full toss just outside off, Sohail whips it towards deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, short and wide of off, Malik stands tall and pulls it to deep mid-wicket, didn't connect with it that well]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, 2 runs, short and wide, Malik hangs back and late-cuts it square of the wicket, gets a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, no run, fullish delivery outside off, Malik mistimes the drive back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sohail, 1 run, full delivery angling into the left hander, Sohail works it wide of long-on and scampers for a run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, no run, Panyangara splays this one short and down leg, Malik was late on the pull, misses it by a long way]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, 2 runs, back of a length delivery wide of off, Malik turns it to mid-wicket and steals a couple, good running from both the batsmen]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, 1 run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Sohail knocks it to long-on, gets a single with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, on a good length and around middle and off, Malik works it to mid-wicket off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, <b>FOUR</b>, errs in line yet again, short and angling into the pads, Malik jumps inside the crease and clips it to backward square leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, <b>FOUR</b>, poor line this from Panyangara, bowls this on a length and on the pads, Malik moves across and helps it to fine leg fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tinashe Panyangara [5.0-0-17-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, Mpofu drops this one short and wide, Malik had enough time to pull it to deep mid-wicket, easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sohail, 1 run, back of a length delivery angling into the left hander, Sohail turns it to mid-wicket and hustles for a single, bowler hunts it down and restricts the batsmen from stealing the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, tad fuller just outside off, Malik works it to mid-wicket and gets a single with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sohail, 1 run, slightly fuller outside off, Sohail pushes it in front of point and steals an easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, back of a length delivery outside off, Malik hangs back and cuts it to point, Raza fumbles and allows the duo to sneak a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, no run, tad fuller just outside off, Malik walks across and blocks it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Mpofu [5.0-0-31-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>batting powerplay</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Sohail, no run, slower and around off, Sohail leans forward and wrists it to mid-wicket, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, full and fired onto the pads, flicked away to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Sohail, 1 run, pulls the length back, Sohail comes down the track and punches to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Sohail, no run, kneels down and takes it on the full, sweeps and finds the man at short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, flighted on middle and leg, Malik nudges it to mid-wicket, quick single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Shoaib Malik, <b>FOUR</b>, slightly short and Malik pounces onto it, makes a bit of room and cuts it through cover-point, no protecting the sweeper cover fence as the ball raced away]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Shoaib Malik, 3 runs, floated up and turning into the batsman, Malik leans forward and whips it through the on-side, places it between deep mid-wicket and long-on, Masakadza runs to his right from long-on, dives and saves a run for the team. Utseya finishes his spell, his figures read: <b>10-0-63-2</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Sohail, 1 run, fraction short and outside off, Sohail backs away and cuts square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, calculated shot! Tossed up around off, Sohail advances down the wicket, gets to the pitch and lofts it handsomely over mid-off, he saw the fielder inside the ring and took advantage of it]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Sohail, no run, slows this up considerably, Sohail comes half forward and bunts it to the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, tossed up just outside off, Malik drives to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Sohail, 1 run, flighted on off, Sohail leans forward and wrists it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Sohail, 1 run, that must have slipped out, high full toss, Sohail was surprised, manages it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, punched down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Shoaib Malik, <b>SIX</b>, muscled! He got it nowhere close to the middle, but got enough power behind it to clear the rope. Flighted delivery, Malik comes down the track, doesn't get to the pitch but still goes through with the loft, gets it over long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Shoaib Malik, no run, flighted around off, Malik works it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Sohail, 1 run, Sohail gives the charge, Raza drags the length back, punched down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Sohail, 2 runs, not all that short, Sohail uses the depth of the crease, makes a bit of room and cuts it behind point, good aggressive running allows them to come back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Shoaib Malik, no run, quicker and on off, Malik knocks it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Sohail, 1 run, fullish and on the pads, Sohail works it square on the leg-side, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, drops it halfway down the wicket, Sohail had ample time to go back and slap it in front of square on the off-side, no chance for the sweeper cover to stop that]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, fraction short and on the stumps, Malik rocks back and pulls to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Shoaib Malik, no run, flatter and on off, Malik goes back and works it to straightish mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Shoaib Malik, no run, tossed up on off, Malik drills it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Sohail, no run, once more Sohail uses his feet, doesn't get to the pitch and knocks it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, quicker and on leg-stump, Malik nudges it behind square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Sohail, 1 run, floated up on the stumps, Sohail skips out of the crease, yorks himself but manages to squeeze it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Sohail, no run, slightly short and just outside off, Sohail punches it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Sohail, no run, flighted around off, Sohail comes down the track and pushes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, flatter and on the pads, Malik goes back and flicks it to deep square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sikandar Raza [2.0-0-22-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, slower and on off, Malik whips it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Sohail, 1 run, angling into the pads, Sohail works it with the angle to the left of mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, fuller and on the stumps, Malik drives down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Shoaib Malik, no run, flatter and on the stumps, Malik punches to the right of the bowler, Utseya gets across quickly]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Shoaib Malik, no run, quicker and outside off, Malik tries to use the pace and guide it to third man, misses and the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Sohail, 1 run, starts round the wicket, slants it into the batsman, Sohail wrists it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, no run, fullish and just outside off, Malik stands still and punches it straight to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, no run, fuller delivery around middle and off, Malik gets across and knocks it to wide of mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sohail, 1 run, tad fuller and angling into the pads, Sohail clips it to mid-wicket and scampers for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, back of a length delivery outside off, Malik sits back and steers it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sohail, 1 run, fuller delivery just outside off, Sohail gets an edge on the drive as the ball rolls to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sohail, no run, length delivery angling into the left hander, Sohail pushes at it tentatively and is beaten]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sohail, <b>wide</b>, full and way wide of off, another run added to the extras]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Sohail, 1 run, tossed up on off, Sohail gets forward and eases it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, slanting into the pads, Malik helps it along the way square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Shoaib Malik, no run, pushed through just outside off, punched straight to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Sohail, 1 run, flatter and on off, Sohail punches down the ground to long-on and opens his account]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Sohail, no run, goes round the wicket, angled into the pads, Sohail turns it gently towards short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and short leg in place...]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Haris Sohail, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Utseya gets his second in as many overs. Hafeez is livid with himself, swipes the bat in anger over the stumps. This was fuller and on the stumps, Hafeez shuffles across, kneels down and misses the sweep, the ball sneaks up behind him and crashes into middle and leg stump. Pakistan have lost both their openers now, just what Zimbabwe required. <b>Hafeez b Utseya 86(83) [4s-8 6s-4]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Utseya to Hafeez, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, no run, full delivery outside off, Malik prods forward and blocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Hafeez, 1 run, short and wide, Hafeez cuts it to sweeper cover and picks up an easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Hafeez, no run, full delivery angling into the pads, Hafeez turns it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, 3 runs, length delivery and had enough width, Malik lunges forward and drives it to sweeper cover, gets three with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, no run, good length ball on middle and off, Malik walks across slightly and misses on the defensive stroke, gets hit on the thigh pad, too high for an lbw appeal]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, no run, full delivery just outside off, Malik presses forward and blocks]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Mpofu [3.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shoaib Malik, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Azhar Ali, <b>out</b> Caught by Panyangara!! A fine innings from the Pakistani skipper comes to an end. Zimbabwe needed that wicket badly. Flighted on middle, Ali kneels down and goes for the sweep, he gets a top-edge that flies towards long leg, Panyangara moved to his left and reverse cupped it. <b>Azhar Ali c Panyangara b Utseya 79(76) [4s-9 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Utseya to Azhar Ali, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, 1 run, swept away to deep backward square leg, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, <b>FOUR</b>, this is just rubbish. Rank long hop around off, Hafeez bends his knee and plays the pull/sweep in front of square on the leg-side, two men in the deep and he bisected them to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Azhar Ali, 1 run, turning down leg, Ali helps it along the way to long leg with a sweep]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Azhar Ali, no run, tossed up around off, Ali comes down the track and pushes it to straightish mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, fraction short and outside off, Ali had all the time in the world to pick his spot and dispatch it, makes a bit of room and cuts through cover-point, no one in the deep and four more]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Hafeez, no run, touch short and around off, Hafeez makes room and cuts to backward point, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Hafeez, no run, pushed through on leg-stump, Hafeez leans forward and turns it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Hafeez, no run, round the wicket, sees the batsman skip out and drags the length back, knocked to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Hafeez, <b>SIX</b>, this is even better. Raza keeps tossing it up and Hafeez keeps sending it out of the ground, advances down the wicket and lofts it handsomely over long-on for the second six of the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Hafeez, <b>SIX</b>, top shot! Hafeez is turning it on here. Shimmies down to this flighted delivery, gets underneath it and smacks it over long-on for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Azhar Ali, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, Ali works it towards mid-wicket, the fielder dives to his left and can't stop it, single taken to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, no run, was there an edge? With the way Mutumbami reacted it certainly seemed like it. Flighted on the stumps, Hafeez misses the reverse paddle, the ball goes past his leg-stump. Mutumbami doesn't collect cleanly on the first attempt, tries to do so on the second, but fails again. I don't think there was an edge on that]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Azhar Ali, 1 run, floated up close to off, Ali eases it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, 1 run, bit more on this one, Hafeez comes down the track, drives it to deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, no run, tossed up on off, Hafeez defends off the front foot to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, no run, Hafeez steps out of the crease, gets to the pitch and drills back to the bowler, Utseya makes a half stop which is enough to prevent the run]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Azhar Ali, 1 run, quicker and on off, Ali drives it along the ground to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Hafeez, no run, drops it short and outside off, Hafeez cuts and picks out cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Azhar Ali, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, Ali knocks it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Azhar Ali, no run, slower and just outside off, Ali mistimes the punch towards extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Azhar Ali, <b>SIX</b>, massive! Brilliant footwork from Ali. Flighted around off, Ali dances down the wicket, meets the pitch of the ball and sends it sailing over deep mid-wicket with a beautiful loft]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Hafeez, 1 run, trifle short and on the stumps, Hafeez backs away and cuts square on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Azhar Ali, 1 run, starts from round the wicket, tosses it up around off, driven away to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sikandar Raza, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Azhar Ali, 1 run, pushed through around off, Ali bunts it to long-off and retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, 1 run, tossed up on off, Hafeez goes down on his knee and sweeps to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Azhar Ali, 1 run, flighted on off and middle, Ali leans forward and milks it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, 1 run, drifting into the pads, Hafeez nudges it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, <b>FOUR</b>, poor bowling from Utseya, half tracker outside off, Hafeez goes back and cuts it past cover-point, there was no sweeper cover and Hafeez picks up consecutive fours]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, <b>FOUR</b>, superb shot! The timing and placement was fantastic from Hafeez. Quicker, fuller and around off, Hafeez presses forward and pushes it through extra cover, it was a mere push and the ball raced away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, 1 run, drops it short and on the stumps, Hafeez pulls behind square leg, only a single as the deep backward square fielder tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, no run, slower and on off, Hafeez drops it to the off-side, he was looking for the single, but is sent back, good call from Ali as the fielder got to the ball quickly]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! Williams errs in line, floats it up outside leg, Hafeez kneels down, rolls his wrists and sweeps it past the diving short fine leg fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, flighted on middle and leg, Ali leans forward and works it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, 1 run, flatter and on the pads, Hafeez nurdles it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, 2 runs, Williams starts from over the wicket, tossed up on middle, Hafeez goes down on one knee, top-edges the sweep wide of short fine leg, Vitori gives chase and makes a mess of it. He allows Hafeez to come back for the second and reach his <b>fifty</b>, 24th in ODIs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sean Williams [3.0-0-24-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, 1 run, slower through the air, Hafeez kneels down and sweeps it to long leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Azhar Ali, 1 run, flatter and around off, punched down to long-off, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, 1 run, Hafeez gets forward and nudges it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Azhar Ali, 1 run, pushed through on the stumps, Ali wrists it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Azhar Ali, <b>SIX</b>, in the air and parried over the rope. Flighted just outside off, Ali skips out of the crease and miscues the loft to long-off, Mpofu was standing just before the rope, he tries to take it over his head, but ends up palming it over the rope. <b>He should have taken it</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, 1 run, tossed up around off, Hafeez reverse paddles it to third man, the fielder from short third gives chase and keeps it to a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, no run, short and on the stumps, Azhar mistimes the punch back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, 1 run, tad fuller and just outside off, Hafeez knocks it to long-on and gets a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, 1 run, short of a length delivery on middle, Ali punches it to long-on and gets an easy single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, no run, short and wide of off, Azhar was shaping for the cut, misses by a long way]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket comes Vitori]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, 1 run, short of length delivery on the pads, Hafeez tucks it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, <b>FOUR</b>, full and on the stumps, Hafeez gave the charge and lifts it over the bowler and straight to the long-on fence, that also brings up the <b>100-run partnership</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, 1 run, drags the length back, Hafeez goes back and eases it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, no run, flatter and around off, Hafeez backs away and punches it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, no run, fraction short and outside off, Hafeez cuts to cover-point, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, no run, flighted around off, Hafeez knocks it to cover off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, no run, quicker and around off, Hafeez waits for and misses out on the late cut, it was too close to the body]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Azhar Ali, 1 run, pushed through just outside off, Ali punches it to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, 1 run, good knock from the skipper, that's his <b>6th fifty</b> and first in Pakistan, this was full and just outside, Ali drives it off the front foot, cover dives to his left and half stops the ball, that allows the duo to sneak a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, no run, full delivery angling into the pads, Ali works it straight to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, no run, full and outside off, almost a yorker, Azhar was looking to dig that out, misses by a long way]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, no run, length delivery on middle and leg, Azhar nudges it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, short and outside off, Azhar cuts it square of the wicket, the ball raced away in a flash]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, no run, Vitori comes round the wicket and angles it into the right hander, Azhar drives it along the ground, picks out extra cover who was diving to his right to stop the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brian Vitori [4.0-1-19-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Azhar Ali, 1 run, another half-tracker from Utseya, pulled away without any timing towards deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Azhar Ali, no run, pushed through flatter and quicker, Azhar was looking to cut and missed, was very close to the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Azhar Ali, byes, <b>FOUR</b>, this is poor bowling from Utseya, spotted that Azhar was looking to play the reverse sweep, fires it short and well down leg-side, Azhar aborts his shot and lets it go, no chance for the keeper. Umpire Dar signals it as byes]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Azhar Ali, no run, pushed through by Utseya, driven back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Azhar Ali, no run, tossed up and just outside off, driven straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Hafeez, 1 run, flatter and well outside off, Hafeez goes down on his knees and laps it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Prosper Utseya, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, 1 run, Williams gives this one more air, Hafeez comes down the track and works it past cover-point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Williams, dropped this one short and wide outside off, Hafeez made room, uses the width and cracks it square past point. The man in the deep is very square, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Hafeez presses forward and drives it straight to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, slower and spinning away from outside off, eased square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, 1 run, pushed through flatter and on Hafeez's pads, swept away behind square on the on-side, a single to deep backward square]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, <b>SIX</b>, nice use of the feet from Hafeez, comes down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and lofts it high and over long-on for a maximum]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, short and down leg, Ali comes down the track and pulls it to the fine leg fence, one bounce and over the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, full and sliding on middle and leg, Azhar gives the charge and flicks it to the deep mid wicket fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Azhar Ali, no run, short and wide of off, Azhar dabs it to left of Williams at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Azhar Ali, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Azhar defends it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Azhar Ali, no run, slower and short and wide outside off, Azhar was looking to play and decides against it at the last moment]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Azhar Ali, <b>wide</b>, fuller and sliding down leg, Azhar comes down the track, looks to clip and misses, signalled wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Hafeez, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Hafeez stays on the back foot and guides it to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, no run, flighted delivery and on the stumps, Azhar prods forward and tucks it in front of mid-wicket, the fielder gets across quickly and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, 1 run, <b>uppish and safe</b>, this was tossed up and on the stumps, Hafeez went down on his knees as he looked to sweep, is done in by the extra bounce, gets a thick top-edge over square leg, the man in the deep has a long way forward, the ball drops in no man's land]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, slower and on the stumps, worked past the diving short mid-wicket fielder, just a single to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, 1 run, flatter and on Hafeez's pads, nudged behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, pushed through by Williams, Azhar comes down the track and works it towards long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, no run, flighted delivery on the off-stump line, Azhar comes down the track and blocks]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Hafeez, no run, fuller and just outside off, Hafeez walks across and turns it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Hafeez, no run, on a good length and outside off, Hafeez hangs back and dabs it straight to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Azhar Ali, 1 run, short of length delivery wide of off, Azhar cuts it square of the wicket and gets a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Azhar Ali, no run, length delivery on the stumps, Azhar presses across and blocks it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Hafeez, 1 run, good length delivery just outside off, Hafeez guides it to third man and gets a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Hafeez, no run, length delivery on off and middle, Hafeez defends it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, no run, pushed through by Williams, Azhar presses forward and drives it straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, 1 run, flighted and on off, Hafeez stays back and punches it towards long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, no run, nicely bowled by Williams, slows down the pace and gets it to grip across Hafeez, he comes down the track and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, <b>FOUR</b>, Williams drops one short and well outside off, Hafeez makes room, waits on the ball and chops it behind square on the off-side for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, slower and on off, Azhar comes down the track and works it towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, 1 run, tossed up and on off, Hafeez comes down the track and drives it towards long-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sean Williams, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, that's an ugly slog from Azhar, charges down the track, doesn't get to the pitch of the ball and ends up splicing it over mid-on, just got enough to clear the man rushing back]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Azhar Ali, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Azhar was looking to work it towards the on-side, closed the face of the bat and gets a soft leading edge towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Azhar Ali, no run, on a good length and well outside off, Azhar leans forward and defends it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Azhar Ali, no run, fuller length delivery and on Azhar's pads, whipped away straight to the fielder at short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, nicely played by Azhar, Mpofu slipped in the slower ball, Azhar was prodding forward, opens the face of the bat at the last moment and steers it through the slip cordon, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, Mpofu drops his length as Azhar came down the track, he adjusts and cracks it past point, no need to run for those]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Azhar Ali, <b>wide</b>, short of a good length and angling down on Azhar's pads, he looks to flick and misses, called as a wide]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Mpofu, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Hafeez, no run, on a good length and well outside off, Hafeez plays with an open face and dabs it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Hafeez, no run, change of pace from Panyangara, slips in the slower ball, Hafeez lunges forward and defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Hafeez, no run, on a good length and just outside off, punched towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Hafeez, no run, short of a good length and just outside off, Hafeez gets half-forward and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Hafeez, <b>SIX</b>, this is even better! Pitched up and angling back into Hafeez, he gets a good stride forward, gets inside the line and helps it over square leg, the ball soars over the ropes for the first six of the match]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Hafeez, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, on a good length and just outside off, Hafeez gets a big stride forward and lofts it high and over mid-on, one bounce and over the ropes]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, that should ease some pressure! Wide half-volley from Vitori, Azhar leans forward and slashes it over cover-point, a couple of bounces and over the ropes]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, no run, tad fuller and on off, Azhar drives it back towards the bowler. Vitori doesn't stop it cleanly, Azhar wants a run and is sent back by his partner]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, no run, rush of blood from Azhar, charges down the track to one that was slanting across him, has a big swish and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, 1 run, Vitori shortens his length on off, Hafeez checked his shot at the last moment, pushes it in front of mid-off and scampers through for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, tad fuller and in that corridor outside off, Hafeez gets a big stride forward and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Hafeez gets a big stride forward and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Azhar lunges forward and defends it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Azhar shuffles across and nudges it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Azhar prods across and drives it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, signs of aggression from Azhar, he picked up the slower ball early, takes a step forward and mows it high and over square leg, a couple of bounces and over the ropes for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, fraction too straight from Panyangara, Azhar works it straight to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Azhar shuffles across and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, pitched up and just outside off, Hafeez prods forward and defends it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, 1 run, on a good length and slanting across the right-hander, steered away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, that's the first boundary of the innings! Hint of width from Vitori, the angle was going across Azhar, he leans forward, plays it on the up and gets it past cover, the ball races away to the fence in a hurry]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, 1 run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, driven in front of mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, 3 runs, nicely played by Azhar, on a good length and just outside off, he shuffles across and whips it with a straight bat, gets it in the gap between mid-on and mid-wicket, runs hard and gets back for the third run]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, no run, pitched up and in that channel around off, Azhar presses across and defends it towards mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Hafeez, no run, back of a length and in that corridor outside off, Hafeez stays behind the line and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Hafeez, no run, pitched up and just outside off, Hafeez leans half-forward and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Hafeez, no run, back of a length and in that channel outside off, Hafeez stands tall ande defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Hafeez, no run, Panyangara keeps it on a good length and in that corridor outside off, Hafeez presses forward defensively]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Hafeez, no run, on a good length and angling onto Hafeez's pads, turned towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, 1 run, Azhar shimmies down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and drives it to the left of mid-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping across the right-hander, he gets a big stride forward, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, on a length and just outside off, Hafeez stays behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, short of a length and on Hafeez's pads, tucked towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, tad fuller and on off, Hafeez closes the face of the bat and defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, on a good length and well outside off, Hafeez gets a big stride forward and drives it straight to the fielder at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, tad fuller and slanting across Hafeez, he presses forward and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, fuller length delivery and on the off-stump channel, driven firmly but straight to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, tad fuller and shaping back into the right-hander, Azhar went a long way across on the defensive push and is struck high on the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, short of a good length and just outside off, Azhar stays behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, on a good length and well outside off, Azhar leans forward and pushes it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, Azhar closes the face of the bat and defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Hafeez, 1 run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, Hafeez presses forward and plays with soft hands, calls for a quick single as the ball rolls away in front of cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, extra bounce for Vitori, draws Azhar into the drive and beats him on the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, that's nicely played by Azhar, moved a long way across to a well pitched up delivery that was slanting across the right-hander, works it through mid-wicket and comes back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, back of a length and on the stumps, Azhar shuffles across and nudges it in front of square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, 1 run, back of a length and angling across Hafeez, he was slightly late in prodding forward, the extra bounce surprised him, ends up jabbing it behind square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, Hafeez gets a big stride forward, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, on a good length and shaping across the right-hander, he covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brian Vitori, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, fuller length delivery and in that channel outside off, Azhar is happy to let it go through]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Azhar presses across, closes the face of the bat and drives it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[A short cover is in place now]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Hafeez, 1 run, Hafeez is off and running, Panyangara shortens his length outside off, Hafeez takes a step down the track and prods it in front of cover, calls for a quick single. Azhar Ali is quick to respond and beats the direct hit from the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Hafeez, no run, Panyangara shortens his length outside off, Hafeez prods across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Hafeez, no run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, Hafeez isn't tempted by the width as he lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place for Panyangara]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Hafeez, no run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, Hafeez covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Hafeez and Azhar Ali are at the crease. Hafeez is on strike. Panyangara will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players are out in the middle.. Chigumbura leads the Zimbabwe team huddle. All set for the first ODI in Pakistan after 24th February, 2009.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pitch Report:</b> 'There is a little bit of grass, but it's straw coloured, shouldn't worry the batsmen one bit. Win the toss and bat first. There's plenty of runs on this surface,' reckons <b>Rameez Raja</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Zimbabwe</b> (Playing XI): Hamilton Masakadza, Sikandar Raza, Vusi Sibanda, Sean Williams, Craig Ervine, Richmond Mutumbami(w), Elton Chigumbura(c), Prosper Utseya, Brian Vitori, Chris Mpofu, Tinashe Panyangara]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan</b> (Playing XI): Mohammad Hafeez, Azhar Ali(c), Haris Sohail, Shoaib Malik, Asad Shafiq, Sarfraz Ahmed(w), Hammad Azam, Anwar Ali, Wahab Riaz, Mohammad Sami, Yasir Shah]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[While the series is historic and significant from different perspectives, it's also important for the hosts to complete a 3-0 whitewash over the tourists. Pakistan are ranked nine at the moment in the ICC ODI rankings and desperately need points to finish amongst the top eight - to have a chance to play in the 2017 edition of the Champions Trophy. The cut-off date for that tourney is September 30th and Pakistan have just one more series after this (against Sri Lanka) to secure enough points needed for qualification.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pakistan are playing an ODI for the first time at home since 24th January, 2009. It has been more than six years that the Pakistan crowd has seen 50-over action on home soil. Lahore was the last home ODI venue for Pakistan, against Sri Lanka. The players have longed for home comfort and it's that stadium once again which welcomes back its heroes. Pakistan eased past Zimbabwe in the T20I series, but there's more at stake in the three match ODI series. Hello, and a warm welcome to one and all for the first ODI between Pakistan and Zimbabwe in Lahore.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Zimbabwe</b> (From): Hamilton Masakadza, Vusi Sibanda, Sikandar Raza, Sean Williams, Craig Ervine, Elton Chigumbura(c), Charles Coventry(w), Tinashe Panyangara, Chris Mpofu, Brian Vitori, Tawanda Mupariwa, Chamu Chibhabha, Graeme Cremer, Roy Kaia, Richmond Mutumbami, Prosper Utseya]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan</b> (From): Ahmed Shehzad, Azhar Ali(c), Mohammad Hafeez, Haris Sohail, Shoaib Malik, Sarfraz Ahmed(w), Mohammad Rizwan, Wahab Riaz, Yasir Shah, Mohammad Sami, Junaid Khan, Asad Shafiq, Imad Wasim, Anwar Ali, Hammad Azam, Babar Azam]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>375</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>3</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>50</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Pakistan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>360</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Hafeez</name>
					<batsman-name>M Hafeez</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Hafeez</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>86</runs>
					<balls>83</balls>
					<fours>8</fours>
					<sixes>4</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>P Utseya</bowler>
					<bowlerId>181</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6633</playerid>
					<name>Azhar Ali</name>
					<batsman-name>Azhar Ali</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Azhar Ali</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>79</runs>
					<balls>76</balls>
					<fours>9</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>P Utseya</bowler>
					<bowlerId>181</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Tinashe Panyangara</fielder>
						<fielderId>3465</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>33</playerid>
					<name>Shoaib Malik</name>
					<batsman-name>S Malik</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shoaib Malik</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>112</runs>
					<balls>76</balls>
					<fours>12</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Panyangara</bowler>
					<bowlerId>3465</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Hamilton Masakadza</fielder>
						<fielderId>425</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8299</playerid>
					<name>Haris Sohail</name>
					<batsman-name>H Sohail</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sohail</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>89</runs>
					<balls>66</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6481</playerid>
					<name>Asad Shafiq</name>
					<batsman-name>Shafiq</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shafiq</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>881</playerid>
					<name>Sarfraz Ahmed</name>
					<batsman-name>S Ahmed</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sarfraz Ahmed</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6272</playerid>
					<name>Hammad Azam</name>
					<batsman-name>H Azam</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Azam</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1052</playerid>
					<name>Anwar Ali</name>
					<batsman-name>A Ali</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Anwar Ali</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1051</playerid>
					<name>Wahab Riaz</name>
					<batsman-name>Riaz</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Riaz</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>31</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Sami</name>
					<batsman-name>M Sami</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sami</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8064</playerid>
					<name>Yasir Shah</name>
					<batsman-name>Yasir Shah</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Yasir Shah</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6633</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>170</runs>
				<overs>25.6</overs>
				<batsman>Azhar Ali</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Azhar Ali</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>360</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>174</runs>
				<overs>27.1</overs>
				<batsman>Mohammad Hafeez</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Hafeez</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>33</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>375</runs>
				<overs>49.6</overs>
				<batsman>Shoaib Malik</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Malik</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>4</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>1</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>9</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Zimbabwe">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>3465</playerid>
					<name>Tinashe Panyangara</name>
					<bowler-name>Panyangara</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Panyangara</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>75</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8020</playerid>
					<name>Brian Vitori</name>
					<bowler-name>Vitori</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Vitori</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>77</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>428</playerid>
					<name>Chris Mpofu</name>
					<bowler-name>Mpofu</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mpofu</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>70</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>441</playerid>
					<name>Sean Williams</name>
					<bowler-name>Sean Williams</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sean Williams</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>42</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>181</playerid>
					<name>Prosper Utseya</name>
					<bowler-name>P Utseya</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Utseya</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>63</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9354</playerid>
					<name>Sikandar Raza</name>
					<bowler-name>S Raza</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Raza</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>43</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>425</playerid>
					<name>Hamilton Masakadza</name>
					<bowler-name>H Masakadza</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>H Masakadza</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>179</playerid>
					<name>Vusi Sibanda</name>
					<bowler-name>Sibanda</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sibanda</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6334</playerid>
					<name>Craig Ervine</name>
					<bowler-name>C Ervine</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>C Ervine</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9352</playerid>
					<name>Richmond Mutumbami</name>
					<bowler-name>Mutumbami</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mutumbami</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>170</playerid>
					<name>Elton Chigumbura</name>
					<bowler-name>Chigumbura</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chigumbura</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>334</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>5</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>50</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Zimbabwe">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>179</playerid>
					<name>Vusi Sibanda</name>
					<batsman-name>Sibanda</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sibanda</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>23</runs>
					<balls>36</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Riaz</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1051</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Riaz</fielder>
						<fielderId>1051</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9354</playerid>
					<name>Sikandar Raza</name>
					<batsman-name>S Raza</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Raza</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>36</runs>
					<balls>31</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>A Ali</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1052</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mohammad Hafeez</fielder>
						<fielderId>360</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>425</playerid>
					<name>Hamilton Masakadza</name>
					<batsman-name>H Masakadza</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>H Masakadza</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>73</runs>
					<balls>73</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>S Malik</bowler>
					<bowlerId>33</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Hammad Azam</fielder>
						<fielderId>6272</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>170</playerid>
					<name>Elton Chigumbura</name>
					<batsman-name>Chigumbura</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chigumbura</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>117</runs>
					<balls>95</balls>
					<fours>10</fours>
					<sixes>4</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Riaz</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1051</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>441</playerid>
					<name>Sean Williams</name>
					<batsman-name>Sean Williams</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sean Williams</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>36</runs>
					<balls>28</balls>
					<fours>5</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Riaz</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1051</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sarfraz Ahmed</fielder>
						<fielderId>881</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9352</playerid>
					<name>Richmond Mutumbami</name>
					<batsman-name>Mutumbami</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mutumbami</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>21</runs>
					<balls>19</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>181</playerid>
					<name>Prosper Utseya</name>
					<batsman-name>P Utseya</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Utseya</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>21</runs>
					<balls>18</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6334</playerid>
					<name>Craig Ervine</name>
					<batsman-name>C Ervine</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>C Ervine</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8020</playerid>
					<name>Brian Vitori</name>
					<batsman-name>Vitori</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Vitori</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>428</playerid>
					<name>Chris Mpofu</name>
					<batsman-name>Mpofu</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mpofu</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3465</playerid>
					<name>Tinashe Panyangara</name>
					<batsman-name>Panyangara</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Panyangara</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9354</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>56</runs>
				<overs>9.4</overs>
				<batsman>Sikandar Raza</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Raza</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>179</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>65</runs>
				<overs>12.6</overs>
				<batsman>Vusi Sibanda</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Sibanda</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>425</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>189</runs>
				<overs>32.5</overs>
				<batsman>Hamilton Masakadza</batsman>
				<batsman-name>H Masakadza</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>441</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>263</runs>
				<overs>42.1</overs>
				<batsman>Sean Williams</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Sean Williams</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>170</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>293</runs>
				<overs>44.4</overs>
				<batsman>Elton Chigumbura</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Chigumbura</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>5</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Pakistan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>31</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Sami</name>
					<bowler-name>M Sami</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sami</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>63</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1052</playerid>
					<name>Anwar Ali</name>
					<bowler-name>A Ali</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Anwar Ali</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>81</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1051</playerid>
					<name>Wahab Riaz</name>
					<bowler-name>Riaz</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Riaz</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>47</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6272</playerid>
					<name>Hammad Azam</name>
					<bowler-name>H Azam</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Azam</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>5</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>29</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8064</playerid>
					<name>Yasir Shah</name>
					<bowler-name>Yasir Shah</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Yasir Shah</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>6</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>360</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Hafeez</name>
					<bowler-name>M Hafeez</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Hafeez</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>44</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>33</playerid>
					<name>Shoaib Malik</name>
					<bowler-name>S Malik</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shoaib Malik</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>33</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6633</playerid>
					<name>Azhar Ali</name>
					<bowler-name>Azhar Ali</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Azhar Ali</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8299</playerid>
					<name>Haris Sohail</name>
					<bowler-name>H Sohail</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sohail</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6481</playerid>
					<name>Asad Shafiq</name>
					<bowler-name>Shafiq</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shafiq</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>881</playerid>
					<name>Sarfraz Ahmed</name>
					<bowler-name>S Ahmed</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sarfraz Ahmed</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



