<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14760" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>1st T20I</gameDesc>
		<series>Zimbabwe tour of Pakistan, 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Pakistan</home>
		<away>Zimbabwe</away>
		<teamsabbr>PAK vs ZIM</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>PAK</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>ZIM</awayabbr>
		<homeId>3</homeId>
		<awayId>12</awayId>
		<venue>Gaddafi Stadium, Lahore</venue>
		<startdate>22 05 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>22 05 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Zimbabwe</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Pakistan won by 5 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Pakistan</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>5</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Ahsan Raza</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Shozab Raza</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Ahmed Shahab</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Azhar Khan</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>14:00</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150522172035</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>Pak</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>Zim</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>173</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>5</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>19.3</batteamovers>
		<status>Pakistan won by 5 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>142</playerid>
			<name>Shahid Afridi*</name>
			<batsman-name>Afridi</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Afridi</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>4</runs>
			<balls-faced>1</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>881</playerid>
			<name>Sarfraz Ahmed</name>
			<batsman-name>S Ahmed</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Sarfraz Ahmed</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>3</runs>
			<balls-faced>4</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>3465</playerid>
			<name>Tinashe Panyangara*</name>
			<bowler-name>Panyangara</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Panyangara</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>2.3</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>28</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>428</playerid>
			<name>Chris Mpofu</name>
			<bowler-name>Mpofu</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Mpofu</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>3</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>32</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>173</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>33</playerid>
<name>Shoaib Malik</name>
<player-runs>7</player-runs>
<player-balls>14</player-balls>
<runs>169</runs>
<wicket-nbr>5</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>3465</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Panyangara</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>0</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>5</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>5</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[. . L1 . W 4 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. . 1 . W . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 2 . 1 . 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>2 W 4 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_PAK_ZIM/PAK_ZIM_MAY22/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[That's all we have for you from this game. The second T20I will be played on Sunday. Don't forget to join us then. This is <b>Sidhant Maheshwari</b> and <b>Mahesh</b> signing off. See you!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pakistan will be extremely happy to have won this game, but surely they should have finished the game off much earlier. But, as they say, all's well that ends well. Now, they'll be looking forward to their next encounter and will be hoping to make it 2-0. Earlier, Zimbabwe posted 172 on the board, all thanks to the fifty from their captain Chigumbura and the initial onslaught by Hamilton Masakadza.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Even though Pakistan were cruising towards the total when the openers were out, their middle-order batsmen failed to get going out in the centre. Hafeez hit two lusty blows, but got out soon after. Malik's stay at the crease was a disappointing one as he failed to middle the ball on most occasions. In the end when Pakistan needed 4 runs from 4 balls, it was Afridi, who finished things off with a cracking hit.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pakistan started off in brilliant fashion, with Mukhtar Ahmed showing his class. He smashed the Zimbabwean bowlers all over the park during his knock of 83. Ahmed Shehzad was a little slow to get off the blocks but got into the groove soon after. Their 142-run opening partnership was a treat for the eyes, but Shehzad's fall after reaching his fifty soon triggered a mini-collapse.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players walk off the field after exchanging handshakes. Afridi has won his first game at home as captain. The crowd cheers the players on as they make their way back to the hut.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Afridi, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>Pakistan win on their return to home</b>. They take a <b>1-0 lead</b> in the series. Afridi was holding nothing back as he smashes this low full toss straight down the ground, 4 runs were needed and he provides them without much fuss]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shahid Afridi, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>4 needed from 4 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Malik departs after a miserable stay at the crease. Can Zimbabwe pull off a miraculous victory here? Boom-Boom walks out to the centre. It was almost a yorker from Panyangara, Malik looks to force it hard through the off-side, the ball sneaks under his bat and crashes into the middle stump. <b>Shoaib Malik b Panyangara 7(14)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, 2 runs, full delivery on the stumps, Malik clips it wide of long-on, the batsmen come back for the second before the fielder gets around]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tinashe Panyangara [2.0-0-22-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>6 needed from 6 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, Mpofu bowls a low full toss in trying to bowl the yorker, he gets an inside edge onto the pad and the ball rolls away towards gully. The bowler was appealing for an lbw, but the umpire was not interested]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, no run, what was that from Malik? He goes for a wild slog off this shortish delivery outside off, gets it off the toe-end of the bat and the ball rolls towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sarfraz Ahmed, 1 run, good length delivery just outside off, Sarfraz pushes at it, gets an inside edge onto the pad, the ball dribbles away in front of the keeper and the batsmen take a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, down the leg-side, the umpire doesn't call it a wide, maybe it brushed the pad on its way to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Sarfraz Ahmed, 2 runs, walks across his stumps, gets an inside edge on the clip, the ball rolls away behind square on the on-side, the batsmen take two before the keeper gets to the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, just short of a good length and angling in on top of off, Malik waits inside the crease and cuts it late towards third man, gets to the other end with a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Mpofu [2.0-0-27-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pakistan need <b>11 runs from 12 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, on a length and just outside off, Sarfraz leans forward and drives it straight to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sarfraz Ahmed, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to U Akmal, <b>out</b> Caught by Sibanda!! Pakistan are losing unnecessary wickets right at the end. Do we have a twist in the tale? It was a length delivery on middle stump line, Akmal looks to work it away but closes the bat face a little too early. He gets a leading edge, Sibanda at short cover jumps up and takes an easy catch. <b>U Akmal c Sibanda b Vitori 4(3) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Vitori to U Akmal, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to U Akmal, no run, back of a length delivery on the stumps, Akmal jumps in the crease and drops his wrists on it]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, bowls this one slightly wide outside off, Malik waits for it inside the crease and cuts it late to third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, no run, good length ball outside off, Malik pushes it to the right of extra cover, who moves across and prevents the run]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, no run, length delivery angled across off, Malik push-drives it down to mid-off, can't get a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brian Vitori [3.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to U Akmal, <b>FOUR</b>, that's not where you bowl to the new man at the crease. It was way too short and Akmal latches onto it in a flash, he pulls it through mid-wicket and gets off the mark with a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Umar Akmal, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Hafeez, <b>out</b> Caught by Charles Coventry!! Cremer gets his first wicket of the match. It was not a wicket-taking delivery at all, but Zimbabwe wouldn't mind it one bit. It was short outside off and spins away further, Hafeez looks to cut, but can only manage an outside edge. The keeper takes a good catch behind the stumps. <b>Hafeez c Charles Coventry b Cremer 12(11) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Cremer to Hafeez, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Hafeez, no run, pushed through just outside off, leans forward and bunts this towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, Malik gives the charge this time to this flatter delivery, he looks to defend with his bat close to the pad, the ball rolls away towards cover-point off the outside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shoaib Malik, no run, defends this quicker one to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shoaib Malik, no run, pushes this flighted delivery into the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, no run, goes for the sweep this time, but fails to connect because of the extra bounce, the ball rolls away to short third man off the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, no run, opens the face of the bat and guides this flatter delivery down to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, pushed through just outside off, Malik bunts it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, 1 run, goes down on one knee and sweeps it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, <b>SIX</b>, a maximum to follow the boundary. This was another flighted delivery from Williams, Hafeez gives the charge and tonks it over the long-on fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, <b>FOUR</b>, tossed up down the leg-side, Hafeez kneels down and sweeps it hard, sends it to the fine leg fence in no time]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shoaib Malik, no run, leans forward and pushes it towards point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shoaib Malik, no run, flighted delivery just outside off, Malik presses forward and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shoaib Malik, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>out</b> Caught by Mutumbami!! Mukhtar's brilliant innings comes to an end. He has done his job though. This was tossed up on middle and leg, Mukhtar gives the charge and went through with the loft. He was a little too close to the ball, gets it off the inside half of the bat and hence couldn't quite hit it that well, Mutumbami at long-on takes another simple catch. <b>Mukhtar Ahmed c Mutumbami b Cremer 83(45) [4s-12 6s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Cremer to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Hafeez, 1 run, turning away from around off, Hafeez goes deep in the crease and turns it through square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, drags his length back even further, Mukhtar rocks back and pulls it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, Mukhtar backs away and Cremer follows him with a quicker one, Mukhtar mistimes it to the right of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Graeme Cremer [2.0-0-21-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, no run, kneels down and sweeps this full delivery on leg stump line to short fine leg, four dots in a row from Zimbabwe]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, no run, that almost sneaked through, this was a flatter delivery on middle stump line, Hafeez looks to flick but misses it, the ball goes off the pad and drops to his right, could have well crashed into the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Hafeez, no run, slower through the air and on the stumps, Hafeez lunges forward in defence]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Hafeez, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>out</b> Caught by Mutumbami!! Finally, Zimbabwe get a wicket. Shehzad backs away even before the ball is bowled and Williams drops it flatter and slightly wide outside off, he cuts it in the air but didn't get it off the middle of the bat, hits it straight to Mutumbami at backward point, who snaffles it easily. <b>Ahmed Shehzad c Mutumbami b Sean Williams 55(39) [4s-6 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sean Williams to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Ahmed Shehzad, 2 runs, works this flighted delivery through mid-wicket, calls for the second and makes it easily in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, Shehzad premeditates and looks to lap this one fine, can only manage to drag it back on his body. Smiles after playing that shot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sean Williams [2.0-0-19-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, banged in short and at the batsman, who swivels on the pull but fails to lay bat on it]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>SIX</b>, this is just great batting from Mukhtar, it was just short of a good length and outside off, wasn't that bad a ball, but Mukhtar picks the length quickly, gets under it and lofts it straight down the ground. Didn't time it that well, but the ball had enough to clear the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a great shot the pierce the field. It was bowled short and wide outside off, Mukhtar had enough room on offer to go back and he cuts it in the gap between cover and extra cover, the ball runs away to the fence in a jiffy]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, short of length delivery just outside off, Mukhtar punches it down to mid-off and takes the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, gives more width on offer outside off this time around, Mukhtar mistimes the cut towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, Shehzad was standing across his off stump even before the ball was delivered, he tucks this back of a length delivery through mid-wicket and the batsmen cross over]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Mpofu [1.0-0-16-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, on a length and just outside off, Shehzad drives it down to mid-off and sets off, the fielder fires the throw at the non-striker's end, but Shehzad was quick to make his ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>FOUR</b>, Shehzad reaches his <b>4th T20I fifty</b> with a boundary, bit too straight from Vitori as he bowls this one on the pads, Shehzad tickles it fine and there was no stopping that ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, bumper from Vitori this time around, Shehzad sways away from the line and leaves it for the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, just short of a good length and just outside off, Shehzad goes across and nudges it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, once again he angles this one slightly wide outside off, Mukhtar leans forward and drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, full delivery well outside off, Mukhtar drives it to the left of the fielder at cover, who dives and saves some runs for his team]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brian Vitori [2.0-0-17-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a good blow from Shehzad. It was full and right in the slot, Shehzad mows it down the ground, long-off didn't have a lot of distance to run to his right, but the ball beat him quite comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, once again gives the charge and lofts this to the left of long-off, the fielder runs to his left and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>SIX</b>, <b>that's hammered!</b> It was floated just outside off, Mukhtar comes down the track and smashes it way over the long-on boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, Shehzad goes leg-side to this flighted delivery outside off, drives it hard but picks out sweeper in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, on the pads this time, Mukhtar nudges it to the left of short fine leg and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, quicker delivery angled across off, Shehzad drives it through the cover region for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, that's hit hard and it reaches the fence in no time. This was floated up outside off, Mukhtar lofts it inside-out over cover, the fielder at sweeper runs to his right but he had no chance of stopping the ball from reaching the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, steps out of the crease and drives this flighted delivery down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Ahmed Shehzad, 2 runs, this was tossed up outside off, Shehzad plays a controlled chip over extra cover, gets two before the fielder gets around in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Ahmed Shehzad, 2 runs, comes down the track and was looking to loft it down the ground, the ball goes square of the wicket off the outside half of the bat, the batsmen take two before it is hunted down]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, <b>100 of the partnership</b> comes up in the 10th over, this was flatter and just outside off, Mukhtar punches it through cover and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, floated up outside off, Shehzad eases it down to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, goes down on one knee and sweeps this flighted delivery on middle and leg to deep backward square leg, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>FOUR</b>, this is brilliant batting, Shehzad makes room before the ball is even delivered, he cuts it through backward point and it races away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, shortish and on the stumps, Mukhtar goes on the back foot and pulls it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, Shehzad kneels down and goes for the big slog sweep, drags it to deep backward square leg off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, touch quicker and turning in on middle stump line, Mukhtar hangs on the back foot and punches it uppishly to the right of the bowler, gets a single down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, flatter and on leg stump line, Shehzad premeditates and reverse sweeps it to the left of backward point, takes the single on offer]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sikandar Raza, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, works this delivery on middle and leg through mid-wicket, he was looking for the second but it's not there]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Ahmed Shehzad, 2 runs, once again Cremer drops it short outside off, Shehzad cuts it past backward point, comes back for the second easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Shehzad pushes it back to the bowler off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, drifting on the pads, Mukhtar goes deep in the crease and bunts it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, shortish outside off, Mukhtar cuts it straight to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>SIX</b>, <b>maiden T20I fifty for Mukhtar and what a way to get it</b>, This was tossed up just outside off, Mukhtar lofts it up and over long-off to reach the landmark. His team-mates too are up to applaud the effort]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Graeme Cremer, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>deft touch!</b> It was bowled slower through the air and turns away slightly just outside off, Shehzad waits inside the crease, opens the face of the bat and guides it very fine, the fielder tries to haul the ball back in just before the rope but the ball wins the race]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, goes on the back foot to this slower delivery just outside off, Mukhtar bunts it square of the wicket for another single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, Williams bowls this quicker, Shehzad leans forward and punches this down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, touch fuller and on off, Shehzad pushes it a little uppishly back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, works this delivery on leg stump line through backward square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, flatter on the stumps, Shehzad mistimes the cut through point, gets to the other end with a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[The mandatory powerplay is over and Pakistan have cruised to 71/0.]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, almost a yorker from Panyangara, Mukhtar jams it out into the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, short delivery angling down the leg-side, Mukhtar waits for it to arrive and smashes the pull to the fine leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, drop-and-run single, Shehzad calmly pushes this delivery in the channel outside off in front of cover and sets off, completes the single with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>what a shot!</b> this was full and on the stumps, Shehzad clears his front leg and whips it over mid-wicket, one bounce and over the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, fuller outside off, Mukhtar drives it to the left of the bowler, where extra cover runs to his right, dives but fails to stop the ball, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, slower ball yorker on the stumps, Shehzad squeezes it out to the left of mid-wicket, who dives across but can't stop the ball cleanly, the batsmen take a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tinashe Panyangara [1.0-0-11-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, goes across to this flighted delivery on middle and leg, Mukhtar clips it to backward square leg, can't get the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, floated up on the stumps, Shehzad whips it through mid-wicket and gets to the other end with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, in the blockhole this time, Shehzad squeezes it out onto the pad off the inside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>SIX</b>, even better from Shehzad, this was flighted on middle stump line, Shehzad once again gives the charge and lofts it through the line, this time the ball carries the distance]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>50 of the partnership comes up</b> with that boundary, he comes down the track and lofts it over mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, flatter outside off, Shehzad mistimes the cut towards cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sean Williams, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, a <b>hat-trick of boundaries</b> for Mukhtar, this was short and at the batsman, he goes for the pull, doesn't connect too well but gets it fine and to the left of the keeper, races away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, that bottom hand definitely packs some power. This was full and on the stumps, Mukhtar drills it it to the left of mid-on, who had no chance of stopping that. The ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, Mukhtar is looking in exceptional touch, this one was banged in short. Mukhtar rocks back and muscles the pull through mid-wicket, runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, length ball on off, Mukhtar pushes it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, slower length ball angling away outside off, Mukhtar goes hard at that, but the lack of pace beats his blade]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, fuller in length, Shehzad comes forward and drills it back towards the bowler, who bends down in his followthrough and takes some pace off the ball, parries it towards mid-on and the batsmen take a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, fourth successive four for Mukhtar, this one was angled in on middle and leg, Mukhtar picks it over mid-wicket, the ball hurries across the turf and crashes into the fence. <b>21 runs came off the over</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>third consecutive boundary</b> for Mukhtar, once again he drifts onto the pads, Mukhtar flicks it away backward of square leg for another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, not the way you want to make a comeback in international cricket, Mpofu bangs this one short, Ahmed swivels and pulls it behind square on the on-side, the ball runs away in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, short and wide outside off, Ahmed waits on the back foot and cuts it hard, gets it over short third man and the ball bounces once before crossing the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Ahmed Shehzad, leg byes, 1 run, once again on leg stump line, Shehzad fails to connect with the flick, the ball rolls away towards square leg off the pad, the batsmen sneak in a leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Ahmed Shehzad, leg byes, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball first up, it was on the pads this time, Shehzad looks to glance it fine, he fails to connect and the ball runs away to the right of short fine leg off the thigh pad, the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Mpofu, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, short of length delivery just outside off, Mukhtar opens the face of the bat and pushes it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Mukhtar Ahmed, 2 runs, once again Vitori bowls this on the pads, Mukhtar clips it through mid-wicket, good running ensures that they come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, on a length and angled across off, Mukhtar looks to heave it away without any feet movement, the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place for Vitori]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, full and on middle stump line, Shehzad goes across and flicks it to deep mid-wicket, gets a single to get off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, angling away outside off, Shehzad shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, back of a length delivery on the stumps, Mukhtar nudges it towards mid-wicket and the batsmen take a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brian Vitori, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, touch fuller and outside off, Mukhtar drives it down to mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, slower ball on leg stump line, Mukhtar fails to work it into the leg-side and wears it on the pad, there was an appeal but the ball was snaking down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, second boundary of the over for Mukhtar, it was full and on middle stump line, Ahmed lifts it over mid-on and there was no stopping that ball, Mukhtar reaches the double digits]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Mukhtar Ahmed, 2 runs, length delivery outside off, Mukhtar mistimes the loft but just about gets it over mid-off, who gives chase and keeps the batsmen down to a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Mukhtar pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a great way to start the innings, this was angled in on the pads, Mukhtar flicks it to the fine leg fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mukhtar Ahmed and Ahmed Shehzad are at the crease. Mukhtar Ahmed is on strike. Panyangara will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back. The players are out in the centre. Here we go then...]]></line><line><![CDATA[Apart from Anwar Ali and Shoaib Malik, the rest of the Pakistani bowlers were expensive. Sami finished with 3 wickets, while Riaz picked two. It was their fielding that probably allowed Zimbabwe to post such a total. Two missed stumping chances, a couple of dropped catches and a few misfields allowed the Zimbabwean batsmen to give something to their bowlers to bowl at.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Zimbabwe have managed to put on a competitive total on the board. It all started with a 50-plus opening stand, with Masakadza going hard at the bowlers first up. Sibanda fell to Sami in  the 7th over, while Masakadza too followed him back to the hut off the very next ball. Coventry hit three cracking boundaries before an umpiring error saw him lose his wicket. Captain Chigumbura though played some extraordinary shots, getting his 2nd T20I fifty during the process. Williams and Raza played second fiddle to their captain, helping Zimbabwe post 172 on the bard.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, 1 run, cracks the cut to the right of point, who moves across quickly and keeps the batsmen down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Cremer, 1 run, <b>dropped!</b> That's a shameful drop from Riaz. It was a short delivery from Riaz, Cremer goes for the pull and gets a top-edge, Riaz calls for the catch as it was to his right, tries to reverse-cup it, but ends up spilling the sitter]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, 1 run, slower ball and touch fuller on leg stump line, Mutumbami works it away to fine leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Cremer, 1 run, clips this back of a length delivery on the pads to deep square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Graeme Cremer, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Long-off comes inside the circle and fine leg goes out. Riaz comes back over the wicket.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Riaz finally gets his man. This was angled in on the stumps from round the wicket, Chigumbura clears his front leg and lines up for the slog. He misses the ball completely and the ball crashes into the middle stump. <b>Chigumbura b Riaz 54(35) [4s-8 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riaz to Chigumbura, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riaz comes round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, 1 run, back of a length delivery around off, Mutumbami drops it in front of cover off the back foot, crossed over for a single to get Chigu back on strike]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Mutumbami, 1 run, he gets a single off the last ball, on a length and outside off, he leans forward, opens the face of the bat and steers it towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Mutumbami, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Mutumbami wafts his bat at that with laden feet, fails to connect once again]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Mutumbami, no run, bumper outside off, Mutumbami jumps in the crease and looks to cut it late, can't connect with it and the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, 1 run, yorker length delivery outside off, Chigumbura jams it out square of the wicket, wantd the second run but it's not there]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, <b>SIX</b>, <b>Chigu brings up his 2nd T20I fifty in style</b>. What a cracking shot! This was a full toss on the pads, Chigumbura plays the pick-up shot and sends it soaring over the long leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, no run, full and slightly wide outside off, it was just inside the tramline as Chigu went after it, he fails to connect and the umpire deems it a legal ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, 1 run, opens the face of the bat and guides this length delivery down to third man to keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, <b>FOUR</b>, third consecutive boundary for Chigu, it was angling away just outside off, Chigumbura lofts it inside-out over extra cover, sweeper runs to his right but he was never reaching the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, <b>FOUR</b>, this time Chigu rocks back and pulls this short delivery from Riaz, it crashes into the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, <b>FOUR</b>, poor effort from the fielder at sweeper cover, it was short and wide outside off, Chigumbura cuts it past a diving backward point, sweeper runs to his left, he was lazy to bend down properly and the ball escapes through]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, leg byes, 1 run, back of a length delivery on the pads, Mutumbami fails to glance it fine, the ball rolls away to fine leg off the thigh pad, the batsmen take a leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, 1 run, leans forward and loft-drives this fuller delivery outside off, the ball goes on the bounce to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, <b>wide</b>, this was very quick from Riaz but it was down the leg-side, Chigumbura fails to tickle it fine and once again, the umpire exercises his arms]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chigumbura, <b>wide</b>, that's a poor ball first up, way wide outside off and Chigumbura had nothing to do with it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz [2.0-0-17-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Richmond Mutumbami, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, <b>out</b> Caught by Ahmed Shehzad!! Raza falters after hitting two good shots this over. This was a full toss from Sami, Raza looks to help it down over the long-on fence but doesn't get the desired distance on that. Shehzad from long-on runs to his left and takes a good catch. <b>S Raza c Ahmed Shehzad b Sami 17(13) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sami to S Raza, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>that's been smashed!</b> It was full and just outside off, Raza drills the loft over extra cover, long-off runs after it but fails to connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, <b>wide</b>, Raza gives himself room and Sami bowls a yorker wide outside off, Raza chases it but fails to lay bat on it, the umpire calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, <b>SIX</b>, I think I spoke too soon. This one was banged in short and at the batsman, who clears his front leg, lines up for the pull and muscles it over the cow corner fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, 1 run, super first three balls from Sami, another yorker length delivery around off, Chigumbura jams it hard and gets it down to long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, no run, another good ball from Sami, right in the blockhole just outside off, Chigumbura jams it out and fails to get a single on this occasion]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, 1 run, yorker just outside off, Raza squeezes it out to point and the batsmen take a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Sami [2.0-0-15-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hat-trick ball</b> coming up]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Chigumbura, no run, full once again from Bhatti, Chigumbura drills the drive straight to mid-off, can't even get the single away. <b>15 runs</b> came off that over]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Chigumbura, <b>FOUR</b>, back-to-back boundaries for Chigu, this was bowled in the blockhole, Chigumbura jams it out off the inside half of the bat, the ball runs away to the fine leg fence, the fielder at deep backward square leg had no chance of stopping that running to his right]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Chigumbura, <b>FOUR</b>, full delivery outside off, Chigumbura waits inside the crease and carves it over backward point, the ball crashes into the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Chigumbura, <b>no ball</b>, slower bumper outside off, Chigumbura looks to ramp it down towards third man but fails to connect, the umpire gives it a no-ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to S Raza, 1 run, back of a length delivery on the stumps, Raza looks to force it through the off-side, gets it high on the bat. The ball goes uppishly through the cover region and the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Chigumbura, 1 run, full toss outside off, Chigumbura pushes at that, gets an outside edge that runs away to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Chigumbura, <b>FOUR</b>, slower short ball from Bhatti, Chigumbura goes for the pull, he gets a top-edge and the ball runs away to the right of fine leg, the fielder runs across, puts in the dive but the ball beats him to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Bilawal Bhatti [2.0-0-22-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, 1 run, punches this flatter delivery down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to S Raza, 1 run, nurdles this flighted delivery through backward square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, 1 run, <b>dropped!</b> It was a very tough chance though. Chigumbura comes down the track and whips this fullish delivery towards mid-wicket, where Umar Akmal dives to his left, gets a hand, but can't hold on. He saved some runs though]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to S Raza, 1 run, works this through mid-wicket and crosses over for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, leg byes, 1 run, bowls this one slower and on the pads, Chigumbura fails to connect with the flick, the ball rolls away towards short third man off the pad, Raza calls him for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to S Raza, 1 run, floated up just outside off, Raza drives it through the covers, he was looking for the second there but it's not available]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, 1 run, short of length delivery on the stumps, Raza punches it down to long-on and will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chigumbura, 1 run, Ali drops this short, Chigumbura rocks back and pulls it to deep backward square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chigumbura, <b>FOUR</b>, that's beautifully driven, it was full and outside off, Chigumbura leans forward and drives it in the gap between short extra cover and mid-off, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, 1 run, almost drags it back on the stumps, it was a back of a length delivery on the stumps, Raza pushes at it off the back foot, gets an inside edge that goes past the leg stump and rolls away to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, no run, goes across to this length delivery and clips it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chigumbura, 1 run, banged in short and at the batsamn, Chigumbura checks his pull and plays it awkwardly, it falls in no man's land in the mid-wicket region, takes a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Anwar Ali [2.0-0-10-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to S Raza, no run, shortish and outside off, Raza backs away and cuts it late, can't beat the man at short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to S Raza, no run, defends this flatter delivery on the stumps into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sikandar Raza, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, <b>out</b> Caught by Riaz!! That's the wicket Pakistan wanted, a timely breakthrough for the home side. Williams went for the sweep this time after kneeling down, he gets a top-edge and Riaz at short fine leg takes the easiest of catches. <b>Sean Williams c Riaz b Shoaib Malik 16(15) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, 1 run, drags his length back this time, Chigumbura pulls it backward of square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, 1 run, Williams gives the charge and Malik fires it at him, Williams chips it over cover and gets the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, 1 run, guides this flatter delivery through backward point, gets to the other end with a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sean Williams, no run, <b>another stumping missed!</b> It was the googly from Afridi and Williams completely misses it, Sarfraz misses it as well and his captain won't be happy with that effort at all]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sean Williams, 2 runs, gives the charge and punches this flatter delivery wide of long-on, comes back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Chigumbura, 1 run, opens the face of the bat and guides it towards cover-point, he sets off for a single, the fielder fires a direct-hit at the non-striker's end, but the batsman was well in]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sean Williams, 1 run, clears his front leg and whips this fuller delivery to deep mid-wicket, only a single on this occasion]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sean Williams, 2 runs, tossed up on the stumps, Williams clips it through mid-wicket, the batsmen take two before the fielder can get around from the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sean Williams, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>what a shot!</b> Williams bends down and reverse sweeps this flighted delivery to the deep backward point fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, no run, <b>stumping chance missed!</b> It was bowled slower and Chigumbura gives the charge as he looks to whack it away, he fails to connect as the ball turns in and misses the inside edge, the keeper too can't collect cleanly and Chigu survives]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, no run, arm ball on the pads, Chigumbura looks to help it down fine but fails to connect, Chigumbura is hit on the pad, there was an appeal but no umpire can give that out]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, 1 run, kneels down and sweeps this flighted delivery to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, 2 runs, Williams advances down the track and lofts it over extra cover, the batsmen take two before the fielder from sweeper runs to his left and stops it]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, 1 run, flatter and on the pads, Chigumbura tucks it away behind square on the on-side, this time he gets the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chigumbura, no run, looks to glance this fine, but fails to connect. The ball rolls away to short fine leg off the pad, can't get the single away]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shoaib Malik, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sean Williams, no run, looks to work this through the on-side, gets an inside edge onto the pad and the ball rolls away back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Chigumbura, 1 run, opens the face of the bat and pushes this flighted delivery towards point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Chigumbura, no run, that's a great ball from Afridi, it was the googly just outside off, Chigumbura looks to force it through the off-side but the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Chigumbura, <b>FOUR</b>, that's great timing from Afridi, it was short and slightly wide outside off, Chigumbura cuts it past backward point, the sweeper runs to his left but the ball beats him to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sean Williams, 1 run, googly just outside off, Williams drives it through extra cover and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Chigumbura, 1 run, floated up outside off, Chigumbura looks to go big on the off-side, gets an inside edge that rolls away behind square on the on-side, the batsmen take a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sean Williams, 2 runs, another short delivery outside off, Williams rides the bounce and guides it past slip and to the right of third man, good running ensures that they come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sean Williams, no run, short and slightly wide outside off, Williams goes for the pull but fails to connect, the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sean Williams, no run, back of a length delivery on top of off, Williams gets on top of the bounce and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sean Williams, no run, short of length delivery around off, Williams hops and defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sean Williams, <b>wide</b>, down the leg-side, called a wide by the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sean Williams, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Charles Coventry, <b>out</b> Caught by Sarfraz Ahmed!! Coventry is not at all happy with that call. It was banged in short and at the batsman, Coventry was taking evasive action as he tries to fend it away. Sarfraz takes it down the leg-side and the umpire immediately raises his finger. Coventry is stunned as he didn't get it off his bat, but the Pakistanis are delighted. <b>Charles Coventry c Sarfraz Ahmed b Riaz 14(7) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riaz to Charles Coventry, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Charles Coventry, <b>FOUR</b>, that's poor fielding in the deep. It was shortish and wide outside off, Coventry flat-bats it over cover, the fielder from sweeper cover runs to his right and overruns the ball, the ball might have turned away from him as well. Riaz is not happy with that effort]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz [1.0-0-10-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Charles Coventry, 1 run, floated up on the stumps, Coventry eases it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Charles Coventry, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>back-to-back boundaries</b> for Coventry, it was tossed up outside off, Coventry loft-drives it inside-out over extra cover and the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Charles Coventry, <b>FOUR</b>, kneels down and paddles this flighted delivery on the stumps very fine, the ball runs away to the fence in a jiffy]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Chigumbura, 1 run, driven down to long-off to get off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Charles Coventry, 1 run, floated up around off, Coventry opens the face of the bat and guides it towards short third man, the fielder quickly fires the ball at the striker's end. The batsman was in though]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Charles Coventry, no run, in the blockhole this time, Coventry squeezes it out towards point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Elton Chigumbura, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shahid Afridi, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, <b>out</b> Bowled!! 2 in 2 balls for Sami. He is jubilant after getting the dangerous Masakadza out. It was just short of a good length and outside off, Masakadza looks to force it into the off-side off the back foot, gets an inside edge that crashes into the stumps. The umpire once again checks for Sami's front foot, but he is fine. Pakistan are suddenly pumped up and these two wickets have got the crowd going. Sami is on a <b>hat-trick</b>. <b>H Masakadza b Sami 43(27) [4s-6 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sami to H Masakadza, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Charles Coventry, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, <b>out</b> Caught by Sarfraz Ahmed!! Finally, Pakistan get the all important breakthrough. The umpires check for Sami's front foot, it looks close but the bowler should get the benefit of doubt. The umpire gives his confirmation and Sibanda is sent on his way back. It was short and outside off, Sibanda goes for the pull but gets a top-edge, the keeper runs back, calls for the catch and takes it comfortably in the end. <b>Sibanda c Sarfraz Ahmed b Sami 13(15) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sami to Sibanda, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, 2 runs, whips this delivery angling in on middle and leg through mid-wicket, collects two before the ball is hunted down in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, 1 run, touch fuller and on the stumps, Masakadza drives it straight down the ground for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, no run, comes on the front foot and punches this good length delivery to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, 1 run, full delivery just outside off, Sibanda drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Sami [1.0-0-11-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Sibanda, 1 run, <b>run-out chance missed!</b> It was on a length and just outside off, Sibanda drops it in front of short extra cover and sets off, the fielder quickly runs across and fires it at the non-striker's end, he missed. Had he hit the stumps directly, Sibanda would have been out by a long margin]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Sibanda, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot!</b> It was a wide delivery outside off, Sibanda stays on the back foot and cuts it to the left of backward point, who dives and fails to stop, the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to H Masakadza, 1 run, turns this one towards mid-wicket and sets off for a single, the fielder runs forward, picks the ball and fires a direct-hit at the non-striker's end. Masakadza was not very quick with the running but makes it before the throw arrived]]></line><line><![CDATA[The third umpire has been pressed into service to check a run-out decision. Masakadza just about makes his ground in time. It should be <b>not out</b> and the big screen displays the same.]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Sibanda, 1 run, full just outside off, Sibanda leans forward and drives it to the left of short extra cover, who dives to his right and parries the ball towards mid-off, the batsmen take a single in the meantime]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to H Masakadza, 1 run, on the pads once again, Masakadza clips it straight to deep backward square leg, gets a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to H Masakadza, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a great shot. Bhatti drifts one onto the pads, Masakadza flicks it to the left of short fine leg, there's no one in the deep and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, 1 run, back of a length delivery outside off, Masakadza opens the face of the bat and guides it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, <b>FOUR</b>, that's neatly played. It was a slower ball that was bowled full outside off, Masakadza waits for it, opens the face of the bat and slices it to the right of the keeper, who dives but it goes in vain as the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, FOUR, just short of a good length and on the stumps, Masakadza waits for it and whips it through mid-wicket, Hafeez runs to his left in the deep, puts in the deep and tries to stop the ball. The third umpire checks whether some part of his body was touching the rope, but he is happy with Hafeez's effort]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, <b>wide</b>, bowls this one down the leg-side, Masakadza fails to tickle it fine and it's been called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, no run, banged in short and at the batsman, Masakadza rises with the bounce but mistimes the pull towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, no run, Masakadza goes down and looks to lap it over short fine leg, the ball gets big on him, he misses and the ball crashes into his helmet, rolls away to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, no run, short of length delivery on the stumps, Masakadza blocks it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to H Masakadza, 1 run, shortish and slightly wide outside off, Masakadza cuts it late and uppishly, just about clears the fielders backtracking from short third man and backward point, the ball just about clears them and Masakadza will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to H Masakadza, <b>SIX</b>, that's the first six of the night, Masakadza rocks back and muscles the pull over mid-wicket, the ball carries the distance and Masakadza collects his first maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Sibanda, 1 run, punches this fullish delivery towards mid-off and sets off for a single, Sibanda collides with the bowler as Afridi fires the throw at the non-striker's, he misses but the batsman crashes right into him. Thankfully, everyone is fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to H Masakadza, 1 run, another misfield and this time it's Ahmed Shehzad at backward point, who allows the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Sibanda, 1 run, punches this short of length delivery down to mid-on and takes on Riaz's arm, who fumbles and allows the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Sibanda, no run, looks to work it away into the on-side, closes the bat a face a little too early, gets a leading edge that rolls away back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Bilawal Bhatti, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to H Masakadza, <b>FOUR</b>, another slower one around off, Masakadza goes hard at it, the ball runs away to the left of short fine leg off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to H Masakadza, no run, gives the charge and almost ends up yorking himself, did well in the end to squeeze it out into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to H Masakadza, <b>FOUR</b>, Masakadza goes across to this length delivery around off, he laps this slower ball to the right of short fine leg, who had no chance of cutting it off, the ball runs away in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, 1 run, banged in short and just outside off, Sibanda goes for the pull, doesn't get it off the middle, the ball goes to the right of mid-wicket, who dives and stops the ball, can't prevent the single though]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, bowls this one in the channel outside off, Sibanda pushes it towards cover, says no for the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to H Masakadza, leg byes, 1 run, on a length and angled on the pads, Masakadza looks to hoick it over mid-wicket but can't connect, the batsmen sneak in a leg bye as the ball rolls away into the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, 1 run, opens the face of the bat and dabs it to left of third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, 1 run, on a good length and outside off, Sibanda was in two minds whether to leave it or not, he was a little late to leave and the ball catches the bat and rolls away to third man, Sibanda gets off the mark with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, extra bounce on this delivery well outside off, Sibanda chases it and looks to cut, the extra bounce takes it past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, 1 run, punches this to the left of mid-on and set off, Riaz runs to his left, picks the ball and fires the throw at the non-striker's end. It would have been very close had he hit the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, <b>FOUR</b>, mistimed and it still goes for a boundary, it was another back of a length delivery just outside off, Masakadza goes for the loft, gets it high on the bat, the ball clears mid-on easily though and crashes into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, <b>FOUR</b>, Sami's first ball has been dispatched to the fence, it was short and there was enough width on offer for Masakadza, who rocks back and cuts it square of the wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Sami will share the attack with Anwar Ali. There is a slip in place for him as well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Sami, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, just short of a good length and around off, Sibanda once again gets behind the line and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, bowls this close to the channel around off, Sibanda defends off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to H Masakadza, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off, Masakadza goes slightly across and punches it down to mid-on, he set off for a quick single, the fielder fires a quick throw at the non-striker's end and it would have been interesting had he found the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to H Masakadza, no run, touch fuller and outside off, Masakadza leans forward and drives it to the right of mid-off, where Afridi slides and stops the ball, the crowd gives a loud cheer as Afridi fields the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to H Masakadza, no run, just short of a good length and just outside off, Masakadza gets behind the line and blocks it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to H Masakadza, no run, full and angling in on the pads, Masakadza fails to work it away into the on-side and wears it on the pad, the ball was snaking down leg though]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>H Masakadza and Sibanda are at the crease. H Masakadza is on strike. Anwar Ali will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players are out in the middle. Anwar Ali will start the proceedings with the ball. There is a slip in place. Masakadza will take strike first up...]]></line><line><![CDATA[players in the Pakistan XI are playing an international game in Pakistan for the first time. Mohammad Sami too is making an international comeback after a gap of 3 years.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Afridi:</b> 'We are going with three fast bowlers, our cominations are good. Hopefully, we can restrict them to a reasonable total. It's a great feeling not only for me, for my team and for my nation. I can't tell you in words how great a feeling it is. I am ready. We are going through a rebuilding process and hopefully, everyone can do their job well.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chigumbura:</b> 'We are going to bat first. It might slow down in the second innings. We want to put up a good score to defend. It's time to focus on the game and the process. Hopefully, we will get it right today. It feels great, there's a great crowd. Hopefully, they will support us as well.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pitch Report:</b> 'This is the first ever T20I at this ground. It looks like a belter, there are a few cracks but it looks really good for batting. The spinners might get something from the cracks, but the fast bowlers will find it tough to get going here.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Zimbabwe</b> (Playing XI): Vusi Sibanda, Sikandar Raza, Charles Coventry(w), Sean Williams, Hamilton Masakadza, Richmond Mutumbami, Elton Chigumbura(c), Tinashe Panyangara, Graeme Cremer, Chris Mpofu, Brian Vitori]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan</b> (Playing XI): Mohammad Hafeez, Ahmed Shehzad, Umar Akmal, Shahid Afridi(c), Shoaib Malik, Sarfraz Ahmed(w), Anwar Ali, Bilawal Bhatti, Mohammad Sami, Mukhtar Ahmed, Wahab Riaz]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Zimbabwe have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Finally, the Pakistan national team is coming home, much to the delight of the cricket crazy audience, who have waited for this moment for a long time. Zimbabwean team too have been welcomed with great zeal by fans all over Pakistan. Since international cricket is returning to Pakistan after such a long time, the stadium will be packed to its capacity. Expect the fans to go nuts when their team walks out to the centre.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pakistan will be hoping to turn their fortunes around after their dismal show against the Bangladeshi Tigers, against who they failed to win even a single game in the ODI series as well as the lone T20I. Their only win on the tour came in the final Test match, giving them the series 1-0. They will be hoping to put up an improved show in the shorter formats this time around.]]></line><line><![CDATA[There were some doubts regarding Zimbabwe's participation a little more than a week back, especially after the Zimbabwean government advised their cricket board against touring Pakistan. However, with assurances from the Pakistan Cricket Board, the tour will go ahead as planned. Both teams will first play 2 T20Is before playing 3 ODIs at the same venue.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>2271 days</b>, that's the time period after which Pakistan are finally playing a game at home. After the attack on the Sri Lankan team bus on March 3, 2009, cricket finally is making a return to Pakistan after a gap of more than 6 years. Yes, they are playing only against Zimbabwe, but the successful staging of the series could go a long way in bringing the game back to Pakistan on a consistent basis.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/>Yes, it has been a long time coming. Yes, it is only Zimbabwe. But, the first T20I between Pakistan and Zimbabwe in Lahore is going to garner tons of attention on Friday. The fixture is Pakistan's first on home soil since 2009, when militants launched a gun attack on Sri Lanka's team bus in Lahore, killing eight police and civilians and leaving seven players wounded. <br/><br/>Thousands of police and paramilitaries have been deployed and helicopters will be buzzing over Gaddafi Stadium, which has been turned into a fortress. Roads around the stadium will be closed and shops and restaurants have been shuttered for the duration of the series. Jammers are in use to cut out radio signals, hampering wifi at the stadium, and fans will have to go through metal detectors at three security checkpoints, raising the prospect of hours of queuing. Zimbabwe have been under tight wraps since their arrival early on Tuesday, when they were whisked from the airport to their hotel watched by thousands of security personnel.<br/><br/><b>Pakistan</b><br/><br/>Pakistan are on the back of two recent dismal outings. Their World Cup campaign wasn't really a complete disaster, but they would still have hoped to perform much better than the quarter-final finish. Their subsequent tour to Bangladesh was a bitter pill to swallow as they were blanked by the home team. Now, against Zimbabwe and playing at home, the Shahid Afridi-led side will hope to get back to winning ways. <br/><br/>Out of Pakistan's fifteen-man team, only six have played an international game in Pakistan. Despite that, the home side go in as comfortable favourites. Umar Akmal returns to the team following a string of consistent scores in the domestic T20 competition and he should be one of Pakistan's key players. The side are also heavily stacked in the all-rounders department with the likes of Afridi, Mohd Hafeez and Shoaib Malik available for the home side. <br/><br/>On the bowling front, too, Pakistan are well served with Wahab Riaz, Mohd Sami, who last played for Pakistan in 2012, and Bilawal Bhatti shouldering the responsibility.<br/><br/>Squad: Shahid Afridi (capt), Sarfraz Ahmed (vc), Ahmed Shehzad, Mohammad Hafeez, Mukhtar Ahmed, Nauman Anwar, Shoaib Malik, Umar Akmal, Mohammad Rizwan, Anwar Ali, Hammad Azam, Imad Wasim, Bilawal Bhatti, Wahab Riaz, Mohammad Sami.<br/><br/><b>Zimbabwe</b><br/><br/>No one will know what exactly to expect in Lahore. And as far as Zimbabwe are concerned, no one will know what to expect from them, too. <br/><br/>The team has undergone a plethora of changes and as many as six players have been recalled into the T20 squad. Vusi Sibanda, Brian Vitori, Charles Coventry, Chris Mpofu, Richmond Mutumbami and Graeme Cremer have been handed calls for the Pakistan tour, and they will fervently hope that they can overcome the loss created by Brendon Taylor's retirement from the national side. Zimbabwe also have called up the 23-year-old all-rounder, Roy Kaia and he will make his debut if given the chance. <br/><br/>Squad: Elton Chigumbura (capt), Sikandar Raza, Chamu Chibhabha, Charles Coventry, Graeme Cremer, Craig Ervine, Roy Kaia, Hamilton Masakadza, Christopher Mpofu, Tawanda Mupariwa, Richmond Mutumbami, Tinashe Panyangara, Vusi Sibanda, Prosper Utseya, Brian Vitori, Sean Williams.<br/><br/><b>Stats:</b> Zimbabwe have lost all their five previous T20 encounters against Pakistan.<br/><br/><b>Quotes:</b> <br/><br/>Unfortunately, many of us Pakistani cricketers have never been able to play in our own conditions which is really tough. I know the people of Pakistan are really looking forward to the return of international cricket to Pakistan and so are the players. I can't wait to hopefully walk out in front of the Lahore crowd if I am selected: Umar Akmal<br/><br/>Yes, it's obviously something new for us. But we know why it is like this and players are not worried because Pakistan have done this for us, to be secure and safe. For us the main thing is to play good cricket and I don't think it will affect us: Elton Chigumbura ]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Zimbabwe</b> (From): Hamilton Masakadza, Sikandar Raza, Chamu Chibhabha, Sean Williams, Craig Ervine, Elton Chigumbura(c), Richmond Mutumbami(w), Tinashe Panyangara, Tawanda Mupariwa, Vusi Sibanda, Brian Vitori, Prosper Utseya, Chris Mpofu, Roy Kaia, Graeme Cremer, Charles Coventry]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan</b> (From): Ahmed Shehzad, Mukhtar Ahmed, Mohammad Hafeez, Umar Akmal, Shoaib Malik, Sarfraz Ahmed(w), Mohammad Rizwan, Shahid Afridi(c), Wahab Riaz, Bilawal Bhatti, Mohammad Sami, Imad Wasim, Anwar Ali, Hammad Azam, Nauman Anwar]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>172</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>6</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Zimbabwe">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>425</playerid>
					<name>Hamilton Masakadza</name>
					<batsman-name>H Masakadza</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>H Masakadza</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>43</runs>
					<balls>27</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>M Sami</bowler>
					<bowlerId>31</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>179</playerid>
					<name>Vusi Sibanda</name>
					<batsman-name>Sibanda</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sibanda</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>13</runs>
					<balls>15</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Sami</bowler>
					<bowlerId>31</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sarfraz Ahmed</fielder>
						<fielderId>881</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3460</playerid>
					<name>Charles Coventry</name>
					<batsman-name>C Coventry</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Charles Coventry</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>14</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Riaz</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1051</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sarfraz Ahmed</fielder>
						<fielderId>881</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>170</playerid>
					<name>Elton Chigumbura</name>
					<batsman-name>Chigumbura</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chigumbura</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>54</runs>
					<balls>35</balls>
					<fours>8</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Riaz</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1051</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>441</playerid>
					<name>Sean Williams</name>
					<batsman-name>Sean Williams</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sean Williams</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>16</runs>
					<balls>15</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>S Malik</bowler>
					<bowlerId>33</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Wahab Riaz</fielder>
						<fielderId>1051</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9354</playerid>
					<name>Sikandar Raza</name>
					<batsman-name>S Raza</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Raza</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>17</runs>
					<balls>13</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Sami</bowler>
					<bowlerId>31</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ahmed Shehzad</fielder>
						<fielderId>1787</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9352</playerid>
					<name>Richmond Mutumbami</name>
					<batsman-name>Mutumbami</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mutumbami</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>278</playerid>
					<name>Graeme Cremer</name>
					<batsman-name>Cremer</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Cremer</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>2</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3465</playerid>
					<name>Tinashe Panyangara</name>
					<batsman-name>Panyangara</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Panyangara</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>428</playerid>
					<name>Chris Mpofu</name>
					<batsman-name>Mpofu</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mpofu</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8020</playerid>
					<name>Brian Vitori</name>
					<batsman-name>Vitori</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Vitori</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>179</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>58</runs>
				<overs>6.5</overs>
				<batsman>Vusi Sibanda</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Sibanda</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>425</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>58</runs>
				<overs>6.6</overs>
				<batsman>Hamilton Masakadza</batsman>
				<batsman-name>H Masakadza</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>3460</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>73</runs>
				<overs>8.2</overs>
				<batsman>Charles Coventry</batsman>
				<batsman-name>C Coventry</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>441</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>100</runs>
				<overs>12.4</overs>
				<batsman>Sean Williams</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Sean Williams</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9354</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>142</runs>
				<overs>16.6</overs>
				<batsman>Sikandar Raza</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Raza</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>170</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>168</runs>
				<overs>19.2</overs>
				<batsman>Elton Chigumbura</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Chigumbura</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>5</wides>
			<noballs>1</noballs>
			<legbyes>3</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>9</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Pakistan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1052</playerid>
					<name>Anwar Ali</name>
					<bowler-name>A Ali</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Anwar Ali</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>18</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>31</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Sami</name>
					<bowler-name>M Sami</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sami</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8582</playerid>
					<name>Bilawal Bhatti</name>
					<bowler-name>B Bhatti</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bhatti</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>37</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1051</playerid>
					<name>Wahab Riaz</name>
					<bowler-name>Riaz</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Riaz</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>38</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>4</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>142</playerid>
					<name>Shahid Afridi</name>
					<bowler-name>Afridi</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Afridi</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>28</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>33</playerid>
					<name>Shoaib Malik</name>
					<bowler-name>S Malik</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shoaib Malik</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>12</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>360</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Hafeez</name>
					<bowler-name>M Hafeez</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Hafeez</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1787</playerid>
					<name>Ahmed Shehzad</name>
					<bowler-name>Ahmed Shehzad</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ahmed Shehzad</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1992</playerid>
					<name>Umar Akmal</name>
					<bowler-name>U Akmal</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>U Akmal</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>881</playerid>
					<name>Sarfraz Ahmed</name>
					<bowler-name>S Ahmed</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sarfraz Ahmed</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10383</playerid>
					<name>Mukhtar Ahmed</name>
					<bowler-name>Mukhtar Ahmed</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mukhtar Ahmed</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>173</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>5</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>19.3</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Pakistan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>10383</playerid>
					<name>Mukhtar Ahmed</name>
					<batsman-name>Mukhtar Ahmed</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mukhtar Ahmed</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>83</runs>
					<balls>45</balls>
					<fours>12</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Cremer</bowler>
					<bowlerId>278</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Richmond Mutumbami</fielder>
						<fielderId>9352</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1787</playerid>
					<name>Ahmed Shehzad</name>
					<batsman-name>Ahmed Shehzad</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ahmed Shehzad</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>55</runs>
					<balls>39</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Sean Williams</bowler>
					<bowlerId>441</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Richmond Mutumbami</fielder>
						<fielderId>9352</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>360</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Hafeez</name>
					<batsman-name>M Hafeez</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Hafeez</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>12</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Cremer</bowler>
					<bowlerId>278</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Charles Coventry</fielder>
						<fielderId>3460</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>33</playerid>
					<name>Shoaib Malik</name>
					<batsman-name>S Malik</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shoaib Malik</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>7</runs>
					<balls>14</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Panyangara</bowler>
					<bowlerId>3465</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1992</playerid>
					<name>Umar Akmal</name>
					<batsman-name>U Akmal</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>U Akmal</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Vitori</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8020</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Vusi Sibanda</fielder>
						<fielderId>179</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>881</playerid>
					<name>Sarfraz Ahmed</name>
					<batsman-name>S Ahmed</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sarfraz Ahmed</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>3</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>142</playerid>
					<name>Shahid Afridi</name>
					<batsman-name>Afridi</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Afridi</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1052</playerid>
					<name>Anwar Ali</name>
					<batsman-name>A Ali</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Anwar Ali</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8582</playerid>
					<name>Bilawal Bhatti</name>
					<batsman-name>B Bhatti</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bhatti</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1051</playerid>
					<name>Wahab Riaz</name>
					<batsman-name>Riaz</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Riaz</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>31</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Sami</name>
					<batsman-name>M Sami</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sami</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1787</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>142</runs>
				<overs>13.3</overs>
				<batsman>Ahmed Shehzad</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Ahmed Shehzad</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>10383</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>144</runs>
				<overs>14.4</overs>
				<batsman>Mukhtar Ahmed</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mukhtar Ahmed</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>360</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>157</runs>
				<overs>16.5</overs>
				<batsman>Mohammad Hafeez</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Hafeez</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1992</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>162</runs>
				<overs>17.5</overs>
				<batsman>Umar Akmal</batsman>
				<batsman-name>U Akmal</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>33</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>169</runs>
				<overs>19.2</overs>
				<batsman>Shoaib Malik</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Malik</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>0</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>5</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>5</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Zimbabwe">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>3465</playerid>
					<name>Tinashe Panyangara</name>
					<bowler-name>Panyangara</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Panyangara</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2.3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>28</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8020</playerid>
					<name>Brian Vitori</name>
					<bowler-name>Vitori</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Vitori</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>24</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>428</playerid>
					<name>Chris Mpofu</name>
					<bowler-name>Mpofu</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mpofu</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>32</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>441</playerid>
					<name>Sean Williams</name>
					<bowler-name>Sean Williams</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sean Williams</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>33</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>278</playerid>
					<name>Graeme Cremer</name>
					<bowler-name>Cremer</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Cremer</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>28</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9354</playerid>
					<name>Sikandar Raza</name>
					<bowler-name>S Raza</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Raza</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>23</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>179</playerid>
					<name>Vusi Sibanda</name>
					<bowler-name>Sibanda</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sibanda</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3460</playerid>
					<name>Charles Coventry</name>
					<bowler-name>C Coventry</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Charles Coventry</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>425</playerid>
					<name>Hamilton Masakadza</name>
					<bowler-name>H Masakadza</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>H Masakadza</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9352</playerid>
					<name>Richmond Mutumbami</name>
					<bowler-name>Mutumbami</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mutumbami</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>170</playerid>
					<name>Elton Chigumbura</name>
					<bowler-name>Chigumbura</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chigumbura</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



