<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14763" >
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>2nd ODI</gameDesc>
		<series>Zimbabwe tour of Pakistan, 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Pakistan</home>
		<away>Zimbabwe</away>
		<teamsabbr>PAK vs ZIM</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>PAK</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>ZIM</awayabbr>
		<homeId>3</homeId>
		<awayId>12</awayId>
		<venue>Gaddafi Stadium, Lahore</venue>
		<startdate>29 05 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>29 05 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Pakistan</winner>
			<decision>Fielding</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Pakistan won by 6 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Pakistan</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>6</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries></manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Shozab Raza</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Russell Tiffin</Name>
			<Country>Zim</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Ahmed Shahab</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Azhar Khan</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>11:00</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150529184744</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>Pak</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>Zim</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>269</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>4</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>47.2</batteamovers>
		<status>Pakistan won by 6 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>8299</playerid>
			<name>Haris Sohail*</name>
			<batsman-name>H Sohail</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Sohail</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>52</runs>
			<balls-faced>49</balls-faced>
			<fours>6</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>33</playerid>
			<name>Shoaib Malik</name>
			<batsman-name>S Malik</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Shoaib Malik</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>36</runs>
			<balls-faced>20</balls-faced>
			<fours>4</fours>
			<sixes>1</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>3465</playerid>
			<name>Tinashe Panyangara*</name>
			<bowler-name>Panyangara</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Panyangara</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>8.2</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>42</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>8020</playerid>
			<name>Brian Vitori</name>
			<bowler-name>Vitori</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Vitori</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>8</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>52</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>269</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>6633</playerid>
<name>Azhar Ali</name>
<player-runs>102</player-runs>
<player-balls>104</player-balls>
<runs>209</runs>
<wicket-nbr>4</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>175</bowlerid>
<bowlername>T Mupariwa</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>1</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>3</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[1 2 1 6 1 2 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 . 2 1 . 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 4 1 1 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 2 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_PAK_ZIM/PAK_ZIM_MAY29/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[This is <b>Sidhant Maheshwari</b>, signing off on behalf of <b>Sriram</b> and my co-commentators, <b>Akshay Maanay</b> and <b>Pradeep</b>. Take care folks!]]></line><line><![CDATA[That brings us to the end of our coverage from this game. Both these sides will meet each other for one final time in this series on Sunday. Don't forget to join us then.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Azhar Ali:</b> I think it was a great performance by the team. Obviously, you as a captain want to do well for the team. In both the series, my performances have been good. The seniors have taught me that you can only play your natural game to the best of your ability, that's the only thing you can do, as it is in your hands. The result though is not in your hands. I wanted to mould myself according to how the game has changed. Hopefully, I can continue with this form even longer. The boys did extremely well to contain the opposition to 268. Everyone is working hard and we will keep trying harder. Thanks to the crowd as well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Azhar Ali spoke in Urdu. We have translated it for you.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Azhar Ali</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his <b>104-ball 102</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Masakadza:</b> 'The guys really tried hard today. Raza and Chamu (Chibhabha) played really well, but we didn't get enough runs on the board. I thought the wicket was a little drier today, but we were 20-30 runs short. We need to play every game with the same kind of importance. We don't play that many games. The guys need to come out and play well in the final game.']]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, Zimbabwe posted 268/7 in their 50 overs, riding on Raza's century and Chibhabha's 99. Although on a flat batting track, it was never going to be enough and Pakistan comprehensively defeated their opponents.]]></line><line><![CDATA[He was given good support by Asad Shafiq and the duo put on 85 runs for the third wicket. After Shafiq's departure, captain Ali was given good support by Haris Sohail. Ali though departed soon after getting to his second ODI ton. He also became the <b>first Pakistani skipper</b> to score a <b>ton</b> in a <b>successful run-chase.</b> Shoaib Malik walked out and hit some lusty blows towards the end, helping Pakistan chase the total down in the 48th over. Sohail too got to his fifty before the match got over.]]></line><line><![CDATA[With Hafeez injuring his leg while fielding, Sarfraz Ahmed was asked to open the innings with Azhar Ali. Both batsmen started off well, with Pakistan making steady progress in the first few overs before Sarfraz missed out on a sweep and was caught plumb in front. Hafeez then walked out but failed to get going as he fell for a 24-ball 15. Azhar Ali though continued to hold one end and played some superb shots throughout.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The players walk off the field after exchanging handshakes with each other. The Pakistani players and the support staff too walk out to shake hands with their counterparts.]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, 2 runs, that's it! <b>Pakistan take an unassailable 2-0 lead in the series!</b> This was on a good length and outside off, Sohail opens the face of the bat and runs it fine past the keeper, third man runs to his right, slides and stops the ball. The batsmen come back for the second and <b>Pakistan win by 6 wickets</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>Sohail gets to his 7th ODI fifty</b> with this boundary. It was full outside off from Panyangara, Sohail comes down the track and lofts it over extra cover, the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, 1 run, full and angling in on the pads, Sohail gets an inside edge onto the pad, the ball rolls away down to third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, Malik waits for this full ball to arrive and lofts it over extra cover, there was an easy two available but there was confusion between the two batsmen and they decide against it]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, 1 run, yorker length ball on the stumps, Sohail gets his bat down in time and jams it out to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, length ball just outside off, Malik looks to whip it hard, he gets an inside edge onto the pad, the ball rolls away into the off-side and the batsmen take a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, <b>FOUR</b>, this time Vitori offers width outside off, Malik slaps it through extra cover, sweeper runs to his right but the ball beats him to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, <b>FOUR</b>, Malik is in no mood to hold back today! This was a slower ball pitched up just outside off, Malik was expecting that and lifts it over mid-off with ease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brian Vitori [7.0-0-40-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan need 19 from 24 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, yorker length delivery on the stumps, Malik jams out the drive to long-on, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, no run, nudges this delivery angling in on off and middle towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, 1 run, comes down the track and wanted to play a big shot over the leg-side, his bottom hand comes off the bat as he connects with the ball, he gets a top edge that falls in no man's land in front of the third man region, the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, 2 runs, touch fuller and outside off, Sohail slices the loft over extra cover, sweeper tidies up in the deep and the batsmen take two]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Sohail defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, banged in short and at the batsman, Malik helps it down to fine leg and gets to the other end]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sohail, 2 runs, slower ball angled across off, Sohail comes down the track and pushes it past backward point, gets back for the second with ease as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, another slower ball just outside off, Malik comes across and works it past the non-striker, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Shoaib Malik, <b>SIX</b>, <b>that's hammered!</b> It was the slower ball outside off, Malik reads it quickly, gets forward and lofts it magnificently over extra cover. The ball clears the boundary rope as well and Malik moves into the twenties]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sohail, 1 run, nudges this length ball on middle and leg through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sohail, 2 runs, that's delicate from Sohail, this was a good length ball outside off, Sohail waits for it, opens the face of the bat late and runs it down towards third man, who runs to his right and fields, the batsmen take two in the meantime]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, just short of a good length and outside off, Malik goes hard at it, the ball rolls away to deep mid-wicket off the inside half of the bat. The batsmen were looking for the second but it's not there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tawanda Mupariwa [6.0-0-35-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan need 36 from 36 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, no run, slower ball angling away outside off, Sohail chases it and looks to crack it hard on the off-side, can't lay bat on it though and the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Sohail hangs back and punches it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, no run, Sohail backs away and Panyangara bowls it slightly wide outside off, he leaves it for the keeper in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, no run, length delivery on off, Sohail turns it to short fine leg, can't get the single away]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, leg byes, 1 run, angling in on the pads, Malik fails to get bat on the nudge, the ball rolls away into the on-side off the pad, the batsmen sneak in a quick leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Shoaib Malik, <b>FOUR</b>, on a good length and just outside off, Malik waits for the ball to arrive, opens the face of the bat at the last moment and gets it fine past the keeper, third man was slightly squarer, he runs to his left, puts in the dive but can only parry the ball over the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tinashe Panyangara [6.0-0-27-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Cremer finishes his spell. His figures: <b>10-0-52-2</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, slightly short and turning in on middle, Sohail backs away and cuts it past a diving cover-point, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Sohail, no run, touch quicker and on the stumps, Sohail goes back and nudges it towards mid-wicket, can't beat the fielder there]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, slower through the air and turning away outside off, Malik goes on the back foot and works it through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Sohail, 1 run, comes down the track and eases this fullish delivery down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Sohail, no run, floated up on off, Sohail plays it with the turn towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, short and outside off, Malik cuts it to deep cover, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Graeme Cremer [9.0-0-45-2] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, <b>in the air and safe!</b> It was the slower ball well wide outside off, Malik was looking to guide it late towards third man and hits it in the air, but it was to the left of backward point and not in his reach, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, 1 run, slightly back of a length just outside off, Sohail punches it down to long-off and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, no run, slower ball angling in on leg, Sohail fails to nudge it through the on-side and wears it on the pad, there was half an appeal from the bowler, but it was always going down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, opens the face of the bat to this back of a length delivery outside off and guides it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a great shot. Short and wide outside off, Malik hangs back and cuts it to the left of backward point, it crashes into the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shoaib Malik, 2 runs, on a good length and outside off, Malik comes forward and pushes it towards cover, sets off for a quick single. The fielder quickly runs forward and fires a throw at the non-striker's end, there was no one backing up and the batsmen take an extra run on the overthrow]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, just short of a good length and on the stumps, Malik punches it down to long-on, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sohail, 1 run, slower ball on the pads, Sohail works it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sohail, no run, on a good length and outside off, Sohail tries to play it very late as he opens the face of the bat to try and run it down towards third man, the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sohail, no run, angling away outside off, Sohail reaches out and looks to force it through the off-side, gets an inside edge that rolls away to his right]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, short and wide outside off once again, Malik cuts it to the right of backward point, sweeper gets across in the deep, the batsmen were in two minds whether to go through for the second run or not and in the end, they decide against it]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shoaib Malik, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Azhar Ali, <b>out</b> Caught by Sean Williams!! Azhar Ali has hit a poor ball straight to the fielder. Zimbabwe though won't mind it one bit. This was bowled short and well wide outside off, Ali hangs back and cuts it hard in the air, Williams at backward point takes an easy catch to his right. Ali walks off to a big applause. <b>Azhar Ali c Sean Williams b Mupariwa 102(104) [4s-8]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Mupariwa to Azhar Ali, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Tawanda Mupariwa [5.0-0-32-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The keeper is upto the stumps for Mupariwa]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a great shot from Sohail, he lofts this good length delivery straight through the line and poses for the photographers afterwards. Good shot to end the <b>batting powerplay that yielded 35/0</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, 1 run, gives this one more width outside off, Ali slaps it to the left of backward point, who dives and stops the ball, can't prevent the single though. This is <b>Azhar Ali's highest score in ODIs</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, 1 run, short of length delivery angling in on off and middle, Sohail punches it down to long-on and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Sohail gets on top of the bounce and punches it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, 1 run, on the pads this time, Sohail works it straight to short fine and the batsmen cross over for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sohail, 1 run, on a length and just outside off, Sohail drives it wide of mid-off, who runs across to his right, slides and keeps the batsmen down to a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brian Vitori [5.0-0-23-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, <b>Ali gets to his 2nd ODI hundred!</b> He takes his helmet off, waves his bat to his team-mates and the crowd. Everyone in the Pakistani dressing room is also up on their feet, applauding the effort from their captain. Coming back to the ball, it was drifting down leg, Ali tickles it to the right of short fine. The batsmen take two before the fielder chases it down]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Sohail, 1 run, comes down the track and Williams bowls a full toss on off, Sohail helps it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Ali goes across and turns it through square leg for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Sohail, 1 run, eases this one down to long-on and gets to the other end with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, touch quicker on the pads, Ali works it away through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, loopy delivery from Williams, Ali steps out, takes it on the full and drives it wide of long-on, good running ensures that they come back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, no run, back of a length delivery angled across off, Sohail opens the face of the bat at the last moment, can't beat the man at backward point, who dives to his right and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, no run, shortish and slightly wide outside off, Sohail cuts it straight to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, once again Sohail gives the charge, doesn't try to overhit it and times the inside-out loft beautifully over extra cover and mid-off, runs away to the fence in a jiffy]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Sohail opens the bat face and looks to run it down to third man, can't beat the man at short third]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, no run, angling away outside off, Sohail opens the face of the bat and bunts it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, no run, length delivery on off, Sohail comes forward and pushes it towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Sohail, 1 run, darted on the pads, Sohail comes across and works it away through backward square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot!</b> He comes down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and lofts it over mid-off, the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, flatter and on the pads, Ali fails to tickle it fine, the ball rolls away off the pad to short fine. The umpire didn't spot that and gave it as runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Sohail, 1 run, comes down the track and almost yorks himself, ends up squeezing out towards long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, flatter and on middle, Ali stays back and nudges it through mid-wicket, gets to the other end with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, full and on leg stump line, Ali works it through mid-wicket, calls for the second and makes it with ease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sean Williams [8.0-0-35-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, no run, on a good length and angled across off, Sohail tries to work it away into the on-side, gets a leading edge that falls short and to the left of the fielder running forward from extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, 2 runs, shortish and slightly wide outside off, Sohail cuts it to deep backward point, comes back for the second with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, 1 run, <b>that would have been close!</b> This was full and on off, Ali presses forward and drives it to mid-off, he sets off for a single and the fielder quickly runs forward, picks the ball and fires the throw at the non-striker's end, it would have been very tight had he hit the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, on a length and outside off, Ali comes forward and pushes it towards extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sohail, 1 run, on a good length and around off, Sohail opens the face of the bat and guides it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, 1 run, full delivery angling in on off and middle, Ali drives it down to long-on and gets to the other end]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tinashe Panyangara [4.0-0-18-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>batting powerplay</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Azhar Ali, 1 run, drifts onto the pads once again, worked away through square leg, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Azhar Ali, no run, clips this fullish delivery on the pads to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Sohail, 1 run, shortish outside off, Sohail rocks back and mistimes the pull, the ball goes on the bounce to the fielder at long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Azhar Ali, 1 run, pushed through quicker and just outside off, Ali punches it uppishly past the non-striker, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Azhar Ali, no run, flatter and on off, Ali punches it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, poor ball first up from Raza as it was down leg, Ali works it away behind square on the on-side and comes back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sikandar Raza, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, 1 run, drifts onto the pads, Ali works it in front of square on the leg-side, keeps strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, fraction short and outside off, Ali cuts and gets a thick edge, short third gives chase and keeps it down to a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Ali comes down the track and misses the nudge, is struck on the pad, no appeal for lbw as he was a long way down]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, drops it short, Ali rocks back and pulls, places it between deep mid-wicket and long-on, easy two]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Sohail, 1 run, too full and on the stumps, Sohail drives it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Sohail, no run, tossed up on off, Sohail tries to work it on the leg-side, jams it onto the pad, the ball rolls behind his legs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, no run, pushes it back to the bowler off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, second boundary of the over and it is a good shot. Ali skips out of the crease, takes it on the full and whips it past the diving mid-wicket fielder, long-on can't chase it down]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, no run, flatter and around off, Ali punches it straight to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Sohail, 1 run, Sohail comes down the track, wrists it down to long-on and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Sohail, no run, works it with the turn to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Sohail, <b>FOUR</b>, trifle short and outside off, Sohail slices the cut towards backward point, the fielder dives over the ball and allows it to run past him. A very poor effort that]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Sohail, 1 run, turning into the pads, Sohail stays back and nurdles to backward square, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Sohail, no run, floated up close to off, Sohail presses forward and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Haris Sohail, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, <b>out</b> Caught by S Raza!! Cremer has his second of the night. It was beautifully bowled. A big wicket for Zimbabwe as the partnership was growing and setting a platform. Flighted on off, Shafiq comes down the track, closes the bat face as he tried to work it to the on-side, the leading edge lobs towards cover, Raza runs forward, dives and clings on. <b>Shafiq c S Raza b Cremer 39(59) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Cremer to Shafiq, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, no run, slower and a bit of turn, Shafiq closes the bat face, the soft leading edge rolls back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, 1 run, nice loopy delivery, Ali drives it along the ground to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, 1 run, Shafiq gives the charge, works it between deep mid-wicket and long-on, wanted two but settles with one]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Graeme Cremer [7.0-0-36-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, 1 run, now Shafiq shimmies down, gets too close to the ball, mistimes the whip to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, once more gives the charge, goes for a wild slog towards cow corner, gets it off the inner part to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, no run, Ali skips out of the crease, gets to the pitch and drives it back to Williams]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, 1 run, flighted just outside off, Shafiq drives to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, no run, slower and around off, Shafiq presses it in front of cover after coming forward]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, no run, arm-ball that skids on, keeps low as well, Shafiq manages to bring the bat down and jam it to the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;H Masakadza to Shafiq, leg byes, 1 run, drifts onto the pads, Shafiq can't connect with the glance, the ball brushes the pad and rolls to short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;H Masakadza to Shafiq, 2 runs, Shafiq charges Masakadza, converts it into a fuller length delivery, drives to mid-off, Mupariwa lets it go through his legs, that is poor from him. Gave away an easy two]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;H Masakadza to Azhar Ali, 1 run, too straight, on middle and leg, Ali flicks it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;H Masakadza to Shafiq, 1 run, wicket-to-wicket stuff from Masakadza, Shafiq knocks it past the diving mid-wicket fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;H Masakadza to Shafiq, no run, pitched up on off, Shafiq drives, the fielder from mid-wicket intercepts and prevents the run]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;H Masakadza to Azhar Ali, 1 run, fuller and on off, Ali drives it along the ground to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Hamilton Masakadza, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, no run, fires it on the stumps, Shafiq is beaten by the pace, brings the bat down just in time and gets an inside edge, the ball deflects off the pad to short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, fraction short and on the stumps, Ali pulls to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, no run, full toss around off, Ali drives and finds cover, he should have done better with the freebie]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, 1 run, shortens the length on the stumps, Shafiq nudges it to the unmanned mid-wicket region]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, arm-ball around off, Ali drives and the ball squirts off the inside edge behind square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, no run, Ali comes down the track, Williams pulls the length back, defended to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Azhar Ali, 1 run, back of a length on off, Ali shuffles across, nudges it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, fullish and outside off, Ali decides to free his arms, lofts it over mid-off, Masakadza runs behind the ball, dives and pulls it back in, the third umpire had to check that, he confirms that Masakadza was in touch with the ad cushions]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Azhar Ali, no run, flicked straight to the man at mid-wicket, can't get the single away]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Azhar Ali, no run, pitched up around off, Ali closes the bat face and drives, it goes off the outer half to the bowler, Mupariwa stops it in his followthrough]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Shafiq, 1 run, on a length just outside off, Shafiq drives on-the-up to deep extra cover, for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Shafiq, no run, fuller and just outside off, Shafiq goes for the drive, gets a thickish inside edge to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, 1 run, slower through the air and on off, Shafiq wrists it to long-on and retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, no run, blocked off the back foot to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, <b>FOUR</b>, lovely shot! A much needed four for Pakistan. Flighted on off, Shafiq is quick to race down the track, whips it over mid-wicket, no one protecting the fence as the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, no run, slightly short and outside off, Shafiq cuts and picks out short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, no run, tossed up around off, Shafiq leans forward and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, flighted on the stumps, worked to the right of mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sean Williams [4.0-0-14-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Azhar Ali, 1 run, change of pace, bit of extra bounce on this occasion, Ali was looking to force it off the back foot, held back and knocked it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Shafiq, 3 runs, Shafiq advances, gets underneath the length delivery and lifts it over mid-on, couldn't connect it properly but enough to clear the fielder, Chibhabha gives chase, slides and hauls it in, saved a run for the team]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Shafiq, no run, another off-speed delivery, Shafiq punches it straight to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Azhar Ali, 1 run, slower ball outside off, Ali stretches forward and drives off the outside half to square third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Shafiq, 1 run, fullish and outside off, Shafiq drives to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Azhar Ali, 1 run, on a length just outside off, Ali presses it to long-on after coming forward]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tawanda Mupariwa [3.0-0-19-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, 1 run, nice loopy delivery, Ali goes hard on the drive, away from the body as well, the ball takes the inside half and rolls to the vacant mid-wicket region]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, 1 run, flighted on the stumps, Shafiq comes down the track and pushes it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, 1 run, touch short and outside off, Ali goes back and eases it once more past Masakadza, who lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, poor effort from the stand-in skipper. Too full and just outside off, Ali squeezes it towards backward point, Masakadza goes with one hand and dives over the ball, the batsmen hare back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, no run, floated up just outside off, Ali reaches out and pushes it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, no run, floated up on off, Ali drives inside out, picks out cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, another tight single taken, Ali taps it to the left of cover and takes off, Shafiq was in a bit of trouble but dives to make his ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, 1 run, again, slight hesitation, turned to the right of mid-wicket, Shafiq called ror a run and Ali was late to set off, but they get it easily in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, no run, flighted around off, Shafiq presses forward and blocks to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, Ali eases it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, 1 run, punched off the back foot to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, no run, miscommunication between the two men. But no harm done. Shafiq comes down the track and works it to the right of the bowler, the short mid-wicket intercepts and fires a wayward throw at the striker's end. Shafiq was halfway down the wicket before Ali sent him back, Shafiq had to dive to make his ground. A better throw would have made things interesting]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, 1 run, slower, but the length is tad short, allows the batsman to go back and cut square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, 1 run, <b>dropped!</b> Chibhabha has put one down. That would have been a huge wicket. Half tracker outside off, Ali goes back and slaps it to cover, Chibhabha dives to his left and fails to hang on. The ball rolls away towards sweeper cover. That should have been taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, 1 run, Shafiq uses his feet to meet the pitch of the ball, works it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, no run, gives this bit more air, Shafiq lunges forward in defence]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tossed up on off, Ali wrists it along the ground to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, 1 run, floated up on off, Shafiq runs down the wicket, takes it on the full and drags it to deep mid-wicket, it came off the inner part of the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, 1 run, flatter and outside off, Shafiq goes back and punches it to deep cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, pushed through, Ali advances and nurdles it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, 1 run, drags the length short and outside off, Shafiq cuts to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, no run, slower and around off, Shafiq comes down the track and knocks it to the on-side, he was not to the pitch of the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, no run, stifled appeal for lbw, Shafiq can't connect with the nudge, wears it on the pad, the ball was sliding down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, arm-ball on off, Ali stays rooted to the crease, pushes away from the body, the ball squirts off the inside edge to backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, no run, floated up on off, Shafiq presses forward and defends to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, 2 runs, drops it short and outside off, Shafiq slaps it in front of square on the off-side, Ali calls for two and Shafiq responds]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, 1 run, Azhar Ali brings up his <b>7th ODI fifty</b>. It is also his 4th as captain. Flatter and on the stumps, Ali turns it to deep mid-wicket and reaches the landmark]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, no run, flighted outside off, Ali gets on top of the bounce and dabs it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, 1 run, uses his feet now, gets to the pitch and works it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, 2 runs, slightly short and outside off, Shafiq goes deep in the crease and cuts to deep backward point, another brace added to the total]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, 1 run, not all that short, Shafiq goes right back and pulls, just eludes the mid-wicket fielder, long-on tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, no run, short and outside off, Shafiq cuts towards backward point, the fielder dives to his left and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, no run, slower through the air, Shafiq opens the bat face and guides it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, no run, jumps out of the crease, yorks himself and squeezes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, bowled with the round-arm action, flatter and on the pads, nudged away to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, 1 run, trifle short and outside off, Shafiq cuts square of the wicket, for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, nice floaty delivery outside off, Ali opens the bat face and square drives it through cover-point, easy two taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, nice friendly full toss on off, Ali stays leg-side of the ball and drives, cover dives in vain and he split sweeper cover and long-off to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, 1 run, fraction short, Shafiq pulls to deep mid-wicket, picks out the fielder there]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, 2 runs, Shafiq comes down the track, takes it on the full and whips it square on the leg-side, the fielder from deep mid-wicket runs to his right and tidies up]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, 1 run, slower and on off, Ali rolls his wrists and nudges it to mid-wicket, no one there and single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, no run, tossed up on off, Ali drives and picks out cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, no run, flatter and close to off, Shafiq mistimes the punch towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, no run, tossed up around off, Shafiq presses forward and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, no run, cramps the batsman for room, Shafiq can't get the pull away, picks out short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, Ali advances and Williams drags the length back, knocked to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Shafiq, 1 run, turning away outside off, Shafiq punches to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Azhar Ali, 1 run, short and outside off, Ali goes for cut, the thick outside edge goes to short third man, Masakadza makes a slight fumble, but the duo don't risk the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sean Williams, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, no run, flighted delivery and on off, Shafiq presses forward defensively]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, no run, fraction short and well outside off, Shafiq makes room and cuts it straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, 1 run, pushed through by Cremer, worked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, tossed up and spinning away from outside off, Azhar makes room and cuts it square past point, gets back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, punched down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, driven to the left of the bowler. Cremer dives and pushes it away towards cover, Shafiq wanted a run and is sent back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, short of a length and on Azhar's hips, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shafiq, 1 run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Shafiq closes the face of the bat and drives it to the right of mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Shafiq, no run, on a good length and shaping away from the right-handetr, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, 1 run, back of a length and on Azhar's pads, nudged away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, no run, on a length and just outside off, sliced straight to the fielder at cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, 2 runs, fuller length delivery and angling across Azhar, he gets a big stride forward and drives it past extra cover, Sibanda gets across from the deep, puts in the slide and saves a couple of runs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tossed up and spinning away from outside off, Azhar makes room and cuts it towards deep cover for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, 1 run, Cremer drops one short and well outside off, Shafiq makes room and cuts it square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shafiq, no run, tossed up and on off, Shafiq prods forward in defence]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Asad Shafiq, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip is in place for Shafiq]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Hafeez, <b>out</b> Caught by Charles Coventry!! That's a sharp catch from Coventry at wide long-off. This was nicely tossed up by Cremer, gets it to drift across the right-hander, Hafeez came down the track, he was looking to go inside out over extra cover, hits it a lot straighter than he wanted, Coventry runs across to his left at long-off and holds onto a sharp catch. Celebrations in the Zimbabwe camp, Pakistan lose their second wicket. <b>Hafeez c Charles Coventry b Cremer 15(24) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Cremer to Hafeez, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, 1 run, Cremer drifts one onto Azhar's pads as he came down the track, worked towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Hafeez, 1 run, Cremer floats one on off, eased down towards long-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, 1 run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, punched towards mid-off for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, short of a length and shaping away from outside off, eased straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Hafeez stands tall and pushes it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, driven back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, driven back at the stumps at the non-striker's end, the ball deflects away wide of mid-off, Azhar hares across for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, 1 run, tad fuller and slanting across the right-hander, eased square on the off-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, no run, slower and spinning away from outside off, Azhar was pressing forward on the push, gets a thick edge towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Hafeez, 1 run, this one is flighted outside off, eased down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Hafeez, no run, tossed up and wider outside off, Hafeez lunges forward defensively]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Hafeez, no run, Cremer loops one outside off, Hafeez gets a big stride forward and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Hafeez, no run, this one is given more air on off, Hafeez presses forward and defends it solidly]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Azhar Ali, 1 run, Cremer drops one short and on the stumps, pulled away towards long-on for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Graeme Cremer, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, poor ball from Vitori, can't bowl short at his pace, Hafeez swivels across, rolls his wrists and pulls it behind square on the on-side for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, 1 run, tad fuller and well outside off, Azhar leans forward and drives it past cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, 1 run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, driven square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, short of a length and just outside off, punched towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, 1 run, Vitori keeps it full and on the stumps, Azhar looks to flick and gets an inside edge towards long leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, no run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, driven towards mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chibhabha to Hafeez, no run, pitched up and well outside off, driven straight to the fielder at short extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chibhabha to Hafeez, no run, Chibhabha shortens his length as Hafeez came down the track, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chibhabha to Hafeez, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Hafeez closes the face of the bat and drives it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chibhabha to Hafeez, <b>FOUR</b>, gorgeous from Hafeez, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, Hafeez leans forward, presents the full face of the bat and eases it past mid-on for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chibhabha to Azhar Ali, 1 run, fraction too straight from Chibhabha, worked past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chibhabha to Azhar Ali, no run, tad fuller and on Azhar's pads, clipped towards mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, defended with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, 1 run, short of a length and on Azhar's pads, nudged towards wide mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, worked to the right of mid-on, the fielder tumbles and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, Vitori keeps it full and gets it to slant across the right-hander, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Hafeez, no run, on a good length and just outside off, defended towards mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chibhabha to Azhar Ali, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Azhar presses across and tucks it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chibhabha to Hafeez, 1 run, short of a length and angling into Hafeez's pads, worked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Hafeez, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chibhabha to Sarfraz Ahmed, <b>out</b> Lbw!! Sarfraz doesn't look happy but he has to go, it's a slow walk back to the hut. Chibhabha kept it very full and on the stumps, Sarfraz was a long way down the pitch, went for the sweep and missed. The ball struck him on the back leg, the impact was around middle and it would have crashed into the stumps. <b>Sarfraz Ahmed lbw b Chibhabha 22(28) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chibhabha to Sarfraz Ahmed, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chibhabha to Sarfraz Ahmed, 2 runs, on a good length and on Sarfraz's pads, whipped away in front of square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chibhabha to Sarfraz Ahmed, 2 runs, too straight from Chibhabha, Sarfraz presses across and works it in front of square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chibhabha to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, appeal for LBW, but the ball was slipping down leg, Sarfraz fell across as he went for the flick, gets struck low on the pads, the impact was in front of leg-stump and would have gone down]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chamu Chibhabha, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Azhar drives it uppishly and just wide of the fielder at short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Vitori, drops it short and on the stumps, Azhar swivels across, rolls his wrists and pulls it in front of square on the on-side for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Azhar Ali, no run, Vitori keeps it short and just outside off, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sarfraz Ahmed, 1 run, short of a length and on the stumps, Sarfraz shuffles across a long way and flicks it towards long leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Sarfraz watches it all along and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, on a good length and angling across the right-hander, defended towards cover-point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brian Vitori, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball from Panyangara, dropped it short and well outside off, pulled away over mid-wicket for a boundary, that ruins the over for Panyangara]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sarfraz Ahmed, 1 run, Panyangara keeps it full and well outside off, Sarfraz gets well forward and clips it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, defended towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, fuller length delivery and on off, driven towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, Panyangara shortens his length outside off, Sarfraz waits on it and defends it with soft hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sarfraz Ahmed, 2 runs, short of a length and on Sarfraz's pads, whipped away behind square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Azhar leans forward and drills it past cover, the ball races away to the fence in a hurry]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sarfraz Ahmed, 1 run, length ball on the pads, worked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, full toss from Mupariwa, clipped straight to the fielder at mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sarfraz Ahmed, 2 runs, short of a length and well outside off, Sarfraz waits on it, opens the face of the bat at the last moment and steers it very fine, gets back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, punched straight to the fielder at mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sarfraz Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, powerfully played by Sarfraz, this was full and just outside off, Sarfraz got down on his knees, rolls his wrists and sweeps it behind square on the on-side for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, that's an ugly hoick from Azhar, he ran down the track, Panyangara slipped in the slower ball, mistimed pull towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, on a good length and well outside off, driven towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, fuller length delivery and in that corridor outside off, driven towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, hint of width on offer from Panyangara, Azhar leans into the drive, finds the gap past point and the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, extra bounce for Panyangara, mistimed drive back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sarfraz Ahmed, 1 run, too straight from Panyangara, worked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Azhar Ali, no run, Mupariwa pitches it up and in that channel outside off, defended with an angled bat towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sarfraz Ahmed, 1 run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Sarfraz leans forward and drives it towards mid-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, fuller length delivery and on Sarfraz's pads, he looks to flick and misses, the ball rolls away towards short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sarfraz Ahmed, 2 runs, on a length and well outside off, Sarfraz leans into the drive, the fielder at mid-off gets across and makes a half stop, concedes another run]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, tad fuller and on off, Sarfraz presses across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Azhar Ali, 1 run, Mupariwa drifts one onto Azhar's pads, he looks to flick and gets an inside edge onto the pads, the ball rolls away behind square on the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Sarfraz leans forward and defends it to the right of cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, 1 run, too straight from Panyangara, worked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, pitched up and just outside off, Azhar leans forward and drives it to the right of short extra cover, the fielder tumbles and prevents a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, Panyangara keeps it full and just outside off, Azhar presses across and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, tad fuller and on the stumps, driven towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, Azhar shuffles across and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, <b>wide</b>, the bouncer from Panyangara, but it's way too short and well down the leg side, called as a wide]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sarfraz Ahmed, 2 runs, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Sarfraz leans forward, plays with an open face and guides it square behind point for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Sarfraz prods half-forward and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Azhar Ali, 1 run, too straight from Mupariwa, ends up drifting onto Azhar's pads, worked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sarfraz Ahmed, 1 run, fuller length delivery and in that corridor outside off, Sarfraz pushes forward and gets an inside edge behind square on the on-side, just a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Sarfraz gets well forward and defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mupariwa to Sarfraz Ahmed, no run, on a good length and on the off-stump line, defended with a straight bat towards mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tawanda Mupariwa, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and a gully in place for Mupariwa. The keeper is up to the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, tad too full and on Azhar's pads, he was moving across in the crease, takes a shimmy down the track and whips it past mid-wicket for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, on a length and a hint of shape away from off, Azhar prods across and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, Azhar pushes away from his body and gets an inside edge back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, on a good length and in that channel outside off, Azhar shuffles across and drives it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[Two slips in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, short of a length and angling back into Azhar, he takes a step down the track, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Panyangara to Azhar Ali, no run, beaten! On a good length and a hint of shape back into Azhar, he went nowhere as he pushed forward, beaten on the inside edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Azhar Ali and Sarfraz Ahmed are at the crease. Azhar Ali is on strike. Panyangara will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. Sarfaraz Ahmed is opening with Azhar Ali. Hafeez sprained his leg while attempting to catch a six off Sikandar Raza..]]></line><line><![CDATA[Yasir Shah was the pick of the Pakistani bowlers. He picked up two wickets and conceded only 40 runs in his 10 overs. Riaz was a bit wayward at the start of the innings, but came back well at the end. The Pakistani batsmen have a task on their hands. It is a good batting surface and they should fancy their chances of winning the series today. Join us back in a short while for the run-chase.....]]></line><line><![CDATA[Zimbabwe's innings was a tale of two knocks. First, Chibhabha batted freely and scored a well composed 99. He was very unlucky not to have scored a maiden hundred. Even though Sibanda was not fluent, Chibhabha kept going at the other end. The vistiors lost few quick wickets at the middle stage and that is when Raza came to the crease. He took his time to get going, but once he did, he carted the bowlers all round the park. At the start of the last over, he was on 96 and he managed to reach the landmark unlike Chibhabha. It was his second ODI ton and it has helped Zimbabwe post a decent total.]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Panyangara, no run, another change of pace from Anwar Ali, Panyangara is early into the shot, can't make the desired connection. The duo don't risk a bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Panyangara, <b>FOUR</b>, bad delivery, Anwar Ali bowls a full toss on leg-stump, Panyangara tickles it fine and beats the dive from Sarfraz Ahmed. Fine leg was inside the ring and he too had no chance]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, 1 run, Raza registers his <b>2nd ODI ton.</b> The crowd also appreciate the knock. They are up on their feet applauding the effort. Raza takes his helmet off and soaks in the applause. The whole Zimbabwe team were on their feet. He waves his bat towards them as well. Another off-speed delivery, Raza nurdles it to deep square leg and reaches the milestone]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, 2 runs, slower short ball, Raza waits for it, rolls his wrists on top of the ball and pulls to deep mid-wicket, called for two and sprints back to make his ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Panyangara, leg byes, 1 run, too straight, on middle and leg, Panyangara gets inside the line and misses the glance, the ball rolls off the thigh pad to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, 1 run, Anwar Ali bowls the slower short ball, Raza advances and flat-bats it to extra cover, he was deceived for pace and checked his shot, it lobbed towards extra cover, Shafiq dived forward, but the ball dropped in front of him. Raza survives]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Anwar Ali [8.0-0-47-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Panyangara, no run, full toss just outside off, Panyangara doesn't get any wood on that. It was a freebie and Panyangara missed out]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, 1 run, fuller and just outside off, Raza drives to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Tinashe Panyangara, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Cremer, <b>out</b> Caught by (sub)Ahmed Shehzad!! Cremer goes trying to up the ante. It was the slower one on off, Cremer backs away to the leg-side, he wanted to go inside out, doesn't get the elevation, picks out the fielder at extra cover. The umpire wanted to check for the no-ball, the front foot is fine. <b>Cremer c (sub)Ahmed Shehzad b Riaz 2(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riaz to Cremer, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Cremer, no run, wide yorker, the line is outside off, Cremer can't lay bat on ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, 1 run, too full and close to off, Raza squeezes it to extra cover, quick single taken]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, no run, yorker on off, Raza jams it back down the wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[47.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, 1 run, too full and outside off, Raza opens the bat face, guides it to the left of the backward point, he retains strike with that]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, no run, fullish and around off, Raza drives to extra cover, picks out the fielder and doesn't risk the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, <b>SIX</b>, once more Sami is leaking runs. He drops it short and on the stumps, Raza goes right back, pulls it to deep mid-wicket, Hafeez was interested for a while, but it went over him with ease. Raza moves into the 90s]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, 2 runs, slower ball outside off, Raza slices it over backward point, third man runs to his right and fires a throw at the striker's end, Sarfraz Ahmed doesn't collect the ball and Raza makes it in. Had the keeper collected, that would have been close]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, <b>FOUR</b>, Raza is helped by a freebie this time. Full toss following the batsman, Raza backs away slightly and lofts it over extra cover, he just wanted to clear the fielder, he did and picked up four more]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, <b>FOUR</b>, Sami misses the yorker, dishes out a full delivery. In fact, Raza made good use of the crease, went right back and got underneath it, tonked it over mid-off. Good start to the over]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Cremer, 2 runs, fullish and around off, Cremer closes the bat face as he looks to flick, the ball takes the leading edge and rolls wide of third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Graeme Cremer, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Charles Coventry, <b>out</b> Caught by Sarfraz Ahmed!! Riaz strikes for the first time today. It was fast, full and on the stumps, Coventry moves away to the leg-side, went for the drive, the outside edge settles nicely into Sarfraz's gloves. <b>Charles Coventry c Sarfraz Ahmed b Riaz 10(8) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Riaz to Charles Coventry, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, 1 run, low full toss just outside off, Raza drives and the thick outside edge runs down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Charles Coventry, 1 run, fullish and close to off, Coventry makes room and slices it square of the wicket, sweeper runs to his left and mops up]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Charles Coventry, <b>SIX</b>, hammered! Banged in halfway down the wicket, Coventry was expecting that, transfers his weight onto the back foot, pulls it over deep mid-wicket for a maximum. That was hit with utter disdain]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Charles Coventry, no run, angled across off, Coventry makes room and goes for the booming drive, fails to make contact. The ball misses the off-pole by a few inches]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[45.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, no run, well directed yorker, right on the stumps, Raza digs it out to the off-side, he wanted the run but is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Charles Coventry, 1 run, low full toss around off, Coventry couldn't do much about that, jams it off the inside edge onto the pad, the ball rolls to the off-side, Raza calls for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, 1 run, follows the batsman with a full delivery, Raza drives it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, <b>FOUR</b>, exceptional shot. Sami misses the yorker, it was just inches away, Raza backs away to the leg-side, opens the bat face, slices it up and over short third man. He made good connection as the ball raced away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Charles Coventry, 1 run, fuller and just outside off, Coventry drags the drive to long-on, the bat turned and hence no timing on that]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, 1 run, yorker on off, Raza bends down, opens the bat face and squeezes it to short third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Sami [7.0-1-28-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Charles Coventry, no run, another slower ball bouncer, the third of the over, Coventry ducks and evades it comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, 3 runs, another off-speed delivery, Raza was waiting for it, goes deep in the crease, opens the bat face and runs it behind point, third man was inside the ring and the batsmen come back for the third. Malik and Yasir do the tidying up]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, no run, goes back over the wicket, slips in the slower bumper, Raza sinks under it and lets it go through Sarfraz Ahmed]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, <b>SIX</b>, length delivery and Raza dispatches it into the crowd. It was on off and middle, Raza clears his front leg and hoicks it over deep mid-wicket, that sounded great once the ball made contact with the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Free-hit</b> coming up]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, <b>no ball</b>, would you believe it? Riaz oversteps and bowls a short and wide delivery, Raza slaps it straight to backward point, Yasir Shah hangs onto a good catch. He was almost celebrating before he saw the umpire signal a no-ball.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, <b>wide</b>, slower short ball goes wrong, Raza ducks under it, the umpire doesn't like the height on that, signals it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Charles Coventry, 1 run, short delivery rising on the batsman, Coventry gets on top of the bounce and glides it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, 1 run, starts with a slower delivery, Raza guides it to the left of backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz [7.0-0-30-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Charles Coventry, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Mutumbami, <b>out</b> Caught by Shafiq!! This might be a blessing in disguise for Zimbabwe. Mutumbami was having a tough time in the middle. He finally departs. Slower ball, on short of length, Mutumbami shimmies down the wicket, is deceived by the lack of pace, the flat-batted hit goes straight to extra cover. <b>Mutumbami c Shafiq b Anwar Ali 7(26)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Anwar Ali to Mutumbami, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Mutumbami, no run, on a length close to off, Mutumbami goes for the drive, he connects but not off the middle, goes back to the bowler, who fields in his followthrough]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Mutumbami, no run, Mutumbami wants to break the shackles, but just doesn't seem to get it right, gives the charge to Anwar Ali, goes for a mighty drive, fails to connect and the ball beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, 1 run, fuller and on off, Raza pushes it to mid-off and hares across for a sharp run]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, <b>FOUR</b>, Raza is turning it on. But he is being helped by Anwar Ali, full toss on middle and leg, Raza crouches low and whips it behind square leg to collect back-to-back boundaries]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, <b>FOUR</b>, bad delivery and deserved the treatment. Slower delivery that is dropped short, Raza makes room, advances and flat-bats it over mid-off, the ball had enough to reach the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Mutumbami, no run, flatter and goes straight, Mutumbami looks to force it off the back foot, misses and the ball beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Mutumbami, no run, comes forward and works it to mid-wicket, Mutumbami is struggling to get the singles away]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to S Raza, 1 run, again, very full on middle and leg, Raza gets an inside edge on the sweep, ball rolls towards short fine]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to S Raza, no run, knocks it towards cover-point, takes off for a single, but Mutumbami sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to S Raza, no run, pushes this to cover, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to S Raza, 2 runs, Raza brings up his <b>fifty</b>. Raises his bat and acknowledges the cheers from the crowd. Too full and on the stumps, Raza somehow manages to get the sweep away to long leg, pushed Mutumbami for the second and made it easily, a better throw would have had him in trouble]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Mutumbami, no run, off-cutter outside off, Mutumbami punches and finds cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Mutumbami, no run, takes the pace off the ball, Mutumbami is too early into the shot, the ball gently beats the inside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, 1 run, short and width on offer, Raza slaps it straight to sweeper cover, went on the bounce to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, <b>FOUR</b>, poor delivery, Anwar Ali went for the yorker, missed it completely, full toss on the stumps, Raza shuffles across, gets inside the line and helps it along the way to the deep backward square leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Mutumbami, leg byes, 1 run, nips back in from short of length, Mutumbami can't connect with the flick, is rapped above the kneeroll, no appeal for lbw as the ball was going over]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, 1 run, starts with an off-speed delivery, Raza stays back and punches to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Anwar Ali [6.0-0-32-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Mutumbami, no run, flighted delivery just outside off, Mutumbami pushes it to cover-point, picks out the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Mutumbami, no run, slower through the air, Mutumbami works it softly to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Mutumbami, 2 runs, top effort. Floated up on off, Mutumbami goes down on one knee, sweeps hard behind square leg, Azam at long leg, runs to his left, dives and stops the ball. Saved a certain couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Mutumbami, no run, punched back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Mutumbami, no run, goes straight on, Mutumbami plays for the turn, closes the bat face early, the leading edge lobs up and goes wide of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to S Raza, 1 run, Hafeez starts from over the wicket, tossed up on off, Raza kneels down and sweeps to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Hafeez [4.0-0-27-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The batting powerplay yielded 31 runs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, 1 run, slanted across the right-hander, Raza opens the bat face and steers to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, no run, bumper on the stumps, Raza ducks underneath it, that was well directed from Riaz and Raza handled it nicely]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, no run, takes the pace off the ball, Raza has a slash and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, <b>FOUR</b>, short and just outside off, Raza clears his front leg, heaves it to deep mid-wicket, got it off the toe-end and had enough for the ball to reach the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, 1 run, short of length and on the hips, nurdled away square of the wicket on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, 1 run, back of a length on off, Raza wrists it in front of mid-on, takes off for a quick single, makes it in comfortably and the throw was at the striker's end. Even Mutumbami had made the crease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, 1 run, drags the slower one short, Raza gets inside the line and nudges to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, <b>FOUR</b>, cracking shot! On a length just outside off, Raza drives on-the-up and through the line, pierced it through the packed off-side field, the ball sped away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, no run, short of length close to off, Raza stays leg-side of the ball and punches to backward point, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Mutumbami, 1 run, good save from Sohail, back of a length around off, Mutumbami punches it towards cover-point, Sohail dives to his left and stops the ball, saved a couple there]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Mutumbami, no run, keeps it a tad short and outside off, Mutumbami stands tall and crashes it straight to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to S Raza, 1 run, back of a length on off, Raza eases it off the back foot to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Anwar Ali [5.0-0-25-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, no run, on a length just outside off, Mutumbami has a slash at that and fails to connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, 1 run, back of a length on the stumps, Raza goes back and flicks it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, no run, short delivery angled across the batsman, Raza arches back and gets away from the line of the delivery]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to S Raza, no run, good length ball on off, it holds its line a bit, Raza is opened up as he defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, 1 run, too straight, on off and middle, Mutumbami gets inside the line and tucks it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Mutumbami, no run, fuller and just outside off, Mutumbami pushes it off the toe-end to point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz [5.0-0-21-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Mutumbami, leg byes, 1 run, again, the line is on leg-stump, Mutumbami kneels down and sweeps, the ball takes the glove and goes between Sarfraz's legs. The umpire doesn't spot that, gives that as leg byes]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to S Raza, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, Raza nudges it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Mutumbami, leg byes, 1 run, slower and on leg-stump, Mutumbami fails to connect with the sweep, the ball kisses the thigh pad and deflects off the keeper's pad to backward square]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to S Raza, 1 run, tossed up on off and middle, Raza goes down on one knee and sweeps to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to S Raza, <b>SIX</b>, lovely shot! Good use of the feet. Flighted delivery on off, Raza skips out of the crease, gets to the pitch and lofts it handsomely, just about clears the rope at long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to S Raza, no run, opens the bat face and guides it to short third man, wanted the run but is sent back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to S Raza, 1 run, short and outside off, Raza punches to sweeper cover and retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to S Raza, no run, back of a length around off, Raza punches it to the left of backward point, Yasir Shah dives full length to his left and makes a stunning stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Mutumbami, 1 run, length delivery outside off, Mutumbai pushes at it  and gets an inside edge that rolls away towards short fine leg, the batsmen hare across for a quick single as Riaz fires a direct-hit at the non-striker's end, Mutumbami's bat got stuck before the crease when he was about to get in, he just about gets his foot down in time before the ball strikes the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire called for a run-out check. Mutumbami is the batsman in question. He has just made it. Not Out]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to S Raza, 1 run, too straight, on middle and leg, Raza glances it to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Mutumbami, 1 run, on a length close to off, Mutumbami knocks it to the left of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to S Raza, 1 run, Azam continues bowling the slower one, Raza is deceived by that, drives uppishly to sweeper cover, the bottom hand comes off the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[The <b>batting powerplay</b> has been enforced]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Mutumbami, no run, slower through the air, Mutumbami gets an inside edge onto the pad, the ball lobs to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Mutumbami, no run, low full toss on off, Mutumbami turns it gently to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Mutumbami, no run, angled across the right-hander, Mutumbami plays for the turn and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Richmond Mutumbami, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chibhabha, <b>out</b> Caught by Sarfraz Ahmed!! Oh dear! Anti-climax! Chibhabha stands his ground and looks up at the sky. He can't believe that the umpire raised his finger. He has to wait for his maiden hundred. Nonetheless, a fantastic innings comes to an end. It was tossed up outside leg, spun further away, Chibhabha kneels down and looks to sweep, misses and Sarfraz Ahmed collects, goes up for the caught behind. Umpire Shozab Raza took a long time before raising the dreaded finger. Closer replays suggest that the ball might have brushed the handle of the bat. <b>Chibhabha c Sarfraz Ahmed b Shoaib Malik 99(100) [4s-11 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shoaib Malik to Chibhabha, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to S Raza, 1 run, flatter and on the stumps, Raza nudges it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to S Raza, no run, flighted from round the wicket, Raza comes down the track, yorks himself and squeezes it to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Chibhabha, no run, full delivery on the stumps, Chibhabha ships it straight to the fielder at mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chibhabha is on 99</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to S Raza, 1 run, opens the face of the bat and guides this back of a length delivery outside off to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to S Raza, no run, good change of pace from Azam, Raza was lining up for the big slog over the leg-side, fails to connect by a long way]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Chibhabha, 1 run, full and on the stumps, Chibhabha drives it past the non-striker and down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to S Raza, 1 run, full just outside off, Chibhabha drives it to the left of cover, the batsmen cross over for a quick single even though the fielder threw the ball at the striker's end, he was well in though]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Chibhabha, 1 run, clips this length delivery angling in on middle stump line through square leg, gets to the other end with a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chibhabha, 1 run, floated up on the stumps, Chibhabha comes across and works it to long-on for a single, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chibhabha, no run, goes deep in the crease and pushes this slower delivery to the left of mid-wicket, can't get through for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to S Raza, 1 run, down the leg-side, Raza kneels down and sweeps it straight to the fieldet at deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to S Raza, no run, tossed up on middle stump line, Raza drives it straight to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Chibhabha, 1 run, slower through the air and on the stumps, Chibhabha turns it to the right of mid-wicket and gets across for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to S Raza, 1 run, works this flighted delivery down to long-on and gets to the other end]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shoaib Malik, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to S Raza, 1 run, opens the face of the bat and knocks this length delivery through the covers, only a single available]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to S Raza, no run, length delivery just outside off, Raza punches it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to S Raza, no run, just short of a good length and around off, Raza comes across and punches it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to S Raza, 2 runs, slower ball outside off, Chibhabha hangs on the back foot and punches it through extra cover, sweeper runs to his right in the deep and the batsmen take two before he cuts it off]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to Chibhabha, 1 run, just short of a good length and on the stumps, Chibhabha hangs back and nudges it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Azam to S Raza, 1 run, bowls a freebie first up and gets away with it, this was a low full toss on the pads, Raza clips it straight to the fielder at short fine leg, either side of the fielder and it would have been a boundary. The batsmen take a single as the fielder fumbled a little]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Hammad Azam, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to S Raza, 1 run, floated up just outside off, Raza drives it down to long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to S Raza, no run, pushed through quicker, Raza blocks it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to S Raza, no run, bowled slower through the air and around off, Raza once again gets an inside edge that rolls away to his right off the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to S Raza, no run, another googly that was bowled slower and on the stumps, Raza gets forward and pushes at it, gets an inside edge onto the pad and the ball rolls away to his right]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to S Raza, no run, googly that was bowled quicker and on middle and leg, Raza defends it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, 1 run, flatter and turning away outside off, Chibhabha stays back and punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, 1 run, jumps in the crease and drops this shortish delivery behind square leg, calls for a single and gets it easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, 2 runs, short of a good length and outside off, Chibhabha opens the face of the bat and guides it to the left of backward point, the batsmen take two before third man runs to his right and fields it]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, 3 runs, angling in on middle stump line, Raza goes slightly across and works it through mid-wicket, the fielder in the deep runs to his left and cuts it off just before the rope, the batsmen take three in the meantime]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, no run, knocks this length delivery outside off to mid-off, can't get the single away]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, no run, touch fuller and just outside off, Raza comes forward and punch-drives it past a diving short cover, both the batsmen were out of their crease looking for the single, but decide against it as the ball went to the left of the fielder at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, no run, back of a length delivery well outside off, Raza shoulders arms]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to S Raza, 1 run, cuts this flatter delivery outside off to sweeper cover, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to S Raza, no run, short once again from Yasir Shah, Raza pulls it straight to mid-wicket, who misfields but the batsmen don't go through with the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, 1 run, bowls this one slower on middle and leg, Chibhabha nudges it through backward square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, <b>FOUR</b>, short and turning away outside off, Chibhabha rocks back and looks to cut, the ball takes the outside edge and runs away to the third man fence. Lucky, but he won't mind it one bit]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, no run, shortens his length slightly and bowls it on middle and leg, Chibhabha defends it into the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to S Raza, 1 run, flighted delivery just outside off, Raza drives it down to long-off after coming forward]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, 1 run, on a good length and outside off, Raza punches it towards sweeper cover off the back foot, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, 1 run, on a good length and angling in on off, Chibhabha punches it to the left of mid-on, hares across for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, 1 run, full delivery just outside off, Raza leans forward and drives it to sweeper cover, gets off the mark with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, no run, just short of a good length and jags back sharply from outside off, Raza just about gets his bat down in time as the ball kept a little low as well, the ball rolls away towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to S Raza, no run, fuller delivery just outside off, Raza comes across and drives it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place for Raza]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, 1 run, on a good length and outside off, Chibhabha knocks it to sweeper cover and gets to the other end]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, <b>wide</b>, short and wide outside off, Chibhabha leaves it for the keeper and the umpire exercises his arms]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Sami [5.0-1-17-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to S Raza, no run, drives this flighted delivery straight to the man at cover after stepping out]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to S Raza, no run, punches this quicker one towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sikandar Raza, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Sean Williams, <b>out</b> Caught&Bowled!! Williams is gone! Yasir Shah gets his second wicket of the innings. This was tossed up on the stumps, Williams takes a step forward and looks to drive. He checks his shot and ends up chipping it straight to the bowler, who snaffles it with ease. <b>Sean Williams c and b Yasir Shah 5(9)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Yasir Shah to Sean Williams, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught&Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Sean Williams, no run, Yasir drags his length back seeing Williams give the charge, Williams can only turn it towards square leg, can't get the single away]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, 1 run, slightly flatter and around off, Chibhabha goes on the back foot and punches it down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, no run, slower and on middle and leg, Chibhabha defends off the front foot, the ball rolls away into the leg-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sean Williams, no run, bumper from Riaz just outside off, Williams sways away from the line and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sean Williams, no run, yorker length ball tailing in on middle stump line, Williams did well to jam it out to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chibhabha, 1 run, back of a length delivery on middle and leg, Chibhabha goes across and tucks it away behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sean Williams, 1 run, opens the face of the bat and punches this towards point, calls for a quick single and makes it easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[Coming back to Masakadza's dismissal, his disappointment could well have been because of the decision. Replays show that it might have hit his wrist band instead of the glove.]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chibhabha, 1 run, pulls this shortish delivery through square leg and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chibhabha, no run, back of a length delivery angled across off, Chibhabha defends off the back foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Sean Williams, no run, punches this flatter one towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Sean Williams, no run, flighted delivery around off, Williams gets forward in defence]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Sean Williams, 2 runs, opens the face of the bat and guides it square of the wicket, good running ensures that they come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Sean Williams, 2 runs, kneels down and paddles it past short fine, Azam gives chase and makes a mess of it near the rope, allows the batsmen to come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sean Williams, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, <b>out</b> Caught by Hafeez!! Yasir Shah strikes and the stand-in skipper Masakadza makes a slow walk back to the hut. This was floated up outside off, Masakadza goes for the reverse sweep and the ball hits him around the glove area, goes onto the foreram and lobs up in front of the slip, Hafeez dives forward and takes a good catch. Masakadza will be very disappointed with himself as the slip was put in place just before this ball and he might not even have hit it. <b>H Masakadza c Hafeez b Yasir Shah 18(20) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, no run, <b>beaten!</b> This one turns away from a length just outside off, Masakadza was prodding forward in defence, the ball turns away past the outside edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yasir Shah [6.0-0-26-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, 1 run, Masakadza goes across to this good length ball angled across off, he clips it through mid-wicket and will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, <b>FOUR</b>, Masakadza was surprised by bit of extra bounce there, this was a length delivery angling away outside off, Masakadza pushes at it, the extra bounce takes the outside edge and runs away to the third man fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, no run, back of a length delivery on the pads, Masakadza can't tuck it away, it rolls away into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, no run, on a good length and on off, Masakadza drops it in front of point and takes two steps forward, Yasir Shah runs forward, gathers the ball and underarms it at the striker's end. Masakadza has to rush back in and does so with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, no run, just short of a good length and on off, Masakadza goes slightly across and punches it down to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to H Masakadza, no run, length delivery on off, Masakadza defends it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz [3.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, 1 run, goes on the back foot and punches this flatter delivery down to long-on, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a good shot from Masakadza, this was tossed up on the stumps, Masakadza kneels down and slog sweeps it over backward square leg, it runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, 2 runs, once again Hafeez bowls this flatter around off, Masakadza goes deep in the crease and punches it wide of long-off, comes back for the second with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, no run, flatter around off, Masakadza punches it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, 2 runs, waits for this slower delivery on middle stump line, Masakadza laps it towards fine leg, Anwar Ali from deep backward square leg runs to his right, makes a mess by juggling the ball 3-4 times and allows the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chibhabha, 1 run, comes down the track and wanted to whip this hard, the ball rolls away towards long-off off the outside half of the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, no run, googly on leg, Masakadza fails to nudge it into the on-side and wears it on the pad, there was half an appeal from the Pakistani players but it was surely going down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, 1 run, tucks this flighted delivery through mid-wicket and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, 2 runs, shortish and wide outside off, Chibhabha cuts it to sweeper cover, gets back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, no run, flighted delivery just outside off, Chibhabha blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, no run, tossed up outside off, Chibhabha drives it straight to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, no run, slower just outside off, Chibhabha defends off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chibhabha, 1 run, full and on the stumps, Chibhabha drives it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chibhabha, <b>wide</b>, down the leg-side, called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, 1 run, sweeps this tossed up delivery to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, no run, leans forward and blocks it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chibhabha, 1 run]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, 1 run, punches this flatter delivery towards long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chibhabha, 1 run, sweeps this arm ball behind square on the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, 1 run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Chibhabha lofts it towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, 1 run, tossed up on middle stump line, Masakadza goes across and drives it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to H Masakadza, no run, bowls this one quicker and outisde off, Masakadza backs away and punches it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, 1 run, gives this one more air on off, Chibhabha comes down the track and drives it down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, no run, full delivery on off, Chibhabha leans forward and defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, 2 runs, flatter delivery on the stumps, Chibhabha nudges it through mid-wicket, gets back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chibhabha, 1 run, flatter delivery on off, Chibhabha kneels down and sweeps it behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chibhabha, no run, full on off, Chibhabha defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to H Masakadza, 1 run, tossed up on the stumps, Masakadza drives it down to long-on to get off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Hamilton Masakadza, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Sibanda, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Finally, Sibanda's struggle at the crease comes to an end. Sibanda gives the charge to this tossed up delivery turning in towards the stumps, he fails to connect with the ball and it crashes into the off stump. <b>Sibanda b Hafeez 13(47)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Hafeez to Sibanda, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chibhabha, 1 run, goes for the slog sweep, doesn't get it off the middle of the bat. Luckily for him, the ball falls in the vacant mid-wicket region]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chibhabha, no run, shortish delivery on the stumps, Chibhabha makes room and cuts it towards cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, 1 run, full outside off, Chibhabha drives it towards sweeper cover, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, <b>SIX</b>, floated up on the stumps, Chibhabha kneels down and slog sweeps it over the deep mid-wicket fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, no run, tossed up outside off, Chibhabha wafts at it away from tghe body and the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, no run, flatter delivery outside off, Chibhabha punches it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Sibanda, 1 run, comes down the track and bunts it through the covers for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Sibanda, no run, flighted delivery around off, Sibanda skips out of the crease and defends]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Sibanda, 1 run, to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chibhabha, 1 run]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chibhabha, no run]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chibhabha, 2 runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chibhabha, <b>FOUR</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Hafeez to Chibhabha, no run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Hafeez, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Sibanda, no run, the googly from Yasir, Sibanda lunges forward defensively, he didn't pick the length and gets an inside edge onto the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Sibanda, no run, Yasir drops one short and on Sibanda's pads, he comes down the track on the flick and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, 1 run, flighted delivery and well outside off, driven in front of square on the off-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, no run, appeal for LBW, this was the slider from Yasir, Chibhabha was lunging forward in defence and is struck on the pads, was it sliding down leg? The umpire certainly thought so]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, <b>FOUR</b>, flighted delivery and just outside off, Chibhabha comes down the track and drives it back over the bowler's head, a couple of bounces and over the ropes, brings up his <b>fifty</b> as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, no run, fuller length delivery and on Chibhabha's pads, he looks to turn it towards the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chibhabha, 1 run, on a good length and on Chibhabha's pads, turned towards mid-wicket for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chibhabha, no run, on a length and just outside off , defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sibanda, 1 run, short of a length and in that channel outside off, Sibanda drops it with soft hands and calls for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chibhabha, 1 run, length ball and on Chibhabha's pads, tucked away past mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chibhabha, no run, fuller length delivery and on Chibhabha's pads, turned towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chibhabha, <b>FOUR</b>, wrong line from Riaz, length ball and on Chibhabha's pads, he gets inside the line and flicks it very fine for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Sibanda, no run, tossed up and on the stumps, Sibanda lunges forward defensively]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, 1 run, this one is given more air, Chibhabha presses forward and gets an inside edge behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Sibanda, 1 run, flighted and on off, Sibanda looks to drive and gets a thick inside edge towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Sibanda, no run, tossed up and on off, Sibanda comes down the track, doesn't get to the pitch of the ball and defends it off his pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Sibanda, no run, Sibanda comes down the track, almost yorked himself in the process, jams it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Sibanda, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Sibanda stays behind the line and dabs it towards backward point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sibanda, 1 run, short of a length and just outside off, dabbed to the left of backward point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chibhabha, 1 run, fuller length delivery and slanting across the right-hander, Chibhabha throws his bat at that, gets a bottom edge that rolls away in front of the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chibhabha, no run, short of a length and slanting across the right-hander, steered away straight to the fielder at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sibanda, 1 run, back of a length and on Sibanda's pads, tucked away past square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sibanda, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Sibanda stays behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sibanda, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Sibanda prods it back towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, no run, flighted delivery and just outside off, Chibhabha goes back and looks to defend, gets an inside edge behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Sibanda, 1 run, this one is given more air by Yasir, Sibanda comes down the track and eases it down towards long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, 1 run, tossed up and just outside off, Chibhabha gets forward and drives it past cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Chibhabha, no run, loud shout for LBW, but the ball was slipping down the leg-side, Chibhabha was looking to work it towards the on-side, the impact was in front of leg-stump, would have been sliding down]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Sibanda, 1 run, slower and wider from Yasir Shah, worked wide of cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yasir Shah to Sibanda, no run, tossed up and just outside off, Sibanda lunges forward in defence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Yasir Shah, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sibanda, 1 run, back of a length and angling across Sibanda, dabbed away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sibanda, no run, Riaz keeps it short and just outside off, Sibanda prods across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Chibhabha, 1 run, short of a length and angling across Chibhabha, worked away in front of mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sibanda, 1 run, too straight from Riaz, ends up drifting onto Sibanda's pads, nudged behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sibanda, no run, on a good length and slanting across the right-hander, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Riaz to Sibanda, no run, short of a length and on the off-stump channel, Sibanda is cramped for room as he pushes it back towards the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Wahab Riaz, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Chibhabha prods forward and pushes it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, 2 runs, on a good length and just outside off, worked in front of square on the on-side for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, width on offer from Anwar Ali, Chibhabha leans into the front foot drive and caresses it square past cover-point for back-to-back boundaries]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, <b>FOUR</b>, nicely played by Chibhabha, length ball from Anwar Ali, Chibhabha picks up the length early, bends down low and flicks it over backward square leg, beats the man in the deep for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, 1 run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, driven firmly and to the right of mid-off, the fielder makes a half stop and allows a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, Sibanda shimmies down the track to a length ball and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>short, wide and four</b>, width on offer from Sami, Chibhabha presses across and goes hard on the cut, beats the fielder at point and races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Chibhabha walks forward and pushes it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, no run, short of a length and just outside off, dabbed straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, no run, length ball on Chibhabha's pads, turned straight to the fielder at mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, no run, short of a length and shaping away from the right-hander, he looks to dab it towards third man and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, 2 runs, on a length and on Chibhabha's pads, nudged away behind square on the on-side. Anwar Ali is slow onto the ball, Chibhabha runs hard and gets back for the second run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, lovely line from Anwar Ali, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, draws Sibanda forward before shaping away, beats Sibanda's outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, 1 run, on a good length and well outside off, dabbed away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, <b>FOUR</b>, too straight from Anwar Ali, came from wide of the crease and angled one onto Chibhabha's pads, whipped away past square leg for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, no run, another slower off-cutter from Anwar Ali, punched straight to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, no run, on a good length and in that corridor outside off, Chibhabha presses half-forward and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, <b>FOUR</b>, that should break the shackles! Width on offer from Anwar Ali, Chibhabha gets on top of the bounce and cracks it square past point for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, tad fuller and shaping away from outside off, Sibanda gets a big stride forward, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, fuller length delivery and holding its line outside off, Sibanda covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, short of a length and angling back into Sibanda, he prods across and defends it back at the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, tad fuller and shaping away from outside off, Sibanda covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, on a good length and just outside off, punched with a straight bat towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, left alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, 1 run, pitched up and holding its lin eoo, Sibanda prods half-forward and gets an inside edge behind square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, 1 run, tad fuller and holding its line outside off, pushed to the right of cover-point, the fielder dives and deflects the ball towards the man at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, no run, the slower ball from Anwar Ali, he rolled his fingers across it, defended towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, no run, on a length and just outside off, defended back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Chibhabha gets half-forward and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, no run, on a length and well outside off, Chibhabha plays with soft hands and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, Sami keeps it on a good length and in that channel outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, tad fuller and in that channel outside off, Sibanda drops it in front of backward point, Chibhabha wants a single and is sent back]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, 1 run, short of a length and well outside off, Chibhabha chops it in front of backward point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, no run, on a length and just outside off, Chibhabha gets half forward and defends it towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Chibhabha presses across and defends it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, width on offer from Sami, Chibhabha gets on top of the bounce and cracks it square behind point, Riaz gets across from third man, but the ball beats him to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, Anwar Ali keeps it full and on the stumps, driven back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, 1 run, on a good length and just outside off, Chibhabha drops it in front of mid-on and calls for a quick single. Riaz fails to gather the ball cleanly and Chibhabha makes it with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, no run, tad fuller and in that corridor outside off, Chibhabha stays behind the line and pushes it towards short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, 1 run, on a length and holding its line outside off, dabbed to the left of backward point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, back of a length and in that channel outside off, Sibanda punches it straight to the fielder at short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, Anwar Ali shortens his length and gets it to hold its line outside off, stayed a tad low as well, Sibanda ws pushing away from his body and is beaten]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, no run, short of a length and just outside off, punched off the backfoot and straight to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Chibhabha gets a good stride forward and drives it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, leg-stump half-volley from Sami, drifts onto Chibhabha's pads, he gets inside the line and flicks it handsomely over mid-wicket for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Chibhabha stays besides the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, no run, fuller length delivery and on Chibhabha's pads, he looks to flick and misses, Sami goes up in an appeal for LBW, but the ball was slipping down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, no run, short of a good length and holding its line outside off, Chibhabha gets a big stride forward, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Sibanda gets a good stride forward and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Sibanda prods across and defends it with soft hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, 1 run, a direct hit might have made things interesting, on a good length and well outside off, Chibhabha leans forward and punches it in front of mid-off, calls for a quick single. Azhar is quick onto the ball and has a shy at the bowler's end, the batsman was <b>struggling had there been a direct hit</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, no run, short of a length and angling across the right-hander, Chibhabha slashes at that and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, no run, fuller length delivery and in that channel outside off, Chibhabha covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Chibhabha, no run, fraction too straight from Anwar Ali, ends up driftintg onto Chibhabha's pads, turned towards the on-side where the fielder makes a tumbling stop]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Anwar Ali, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chibhabha, 1 run, short of a length and angling back into Chibhabha, he was cramped for room as he poked forward, gets an inside edge towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, leg byes, 1 run, wrong line from Sami, drifts onto Sibanda's pads, he looks to flick and misses, the ball rolls away towards long leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, <b>wide</b>, Sami slips this one well down the leg-side, Sibanda is happy to let it go, called as a wide. Zimbabwe are off and running]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Sibanda presses forward and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[Looks like Sibanda's bat has cracked. The substitute is running out with a replacement..]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, Sibanda prods forward and drives it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, Sami shortens his length and gets it to hold its line outside off, Sibanda was in two minds, makes a late call to let it go, the ball rolls away off the face of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sibanda, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from outside off, Sibanda covers the line, lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Sami has the new ball. We are set for the start of the first ball.. Two slips in place..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sibanda and Chibhabha are at the crease. Sibanda is on strike. Sami will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Zimbabwe</b> (Playing XI): Chamu Chibhabha, Vusi Sibanda, Hamilton Masakadza(c), Sean Williams, Richmond Mutumbami(w), Sikandar Raza, Charles Coventry, Graeme Cremer, Tawanda Mupariwa, Brian Vitori, Tinashe Panyangara]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan</b> (Playing XI): Azhar Ali(c), Mohammad Hafeez, Shoaib Malik, Haris Sohail, Asad Shafiq, Sarfraz Ahmed(w), Hammad Azam, Anwar Ali, Wahab Riaz, Mohammad Sami, Yasir Shah]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Masakadza:</b> 'We have made four changes. Utseya misses out with sickness, Ervine is out injured, Chigumbura misses out as well. We have another change. We need to put up a big score on the board.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Azhar Ali:</b> 'We will bowl first. We wanted to bowl in dry conditions. Same team']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pitch Report:</b> 'Another track that should help the batsmen. Win the toss and bat first, nothing in it for the bowlers,' reckons <b>Rameez Raja</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan have won the toss and have opted to field</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[There's some injury news from the Zimbabwe camp. Craig Ervine has been ruled out of the remainder of the series with a hamstring injury. The visitors suffered a further blow with skipper Chigumbura dealt a two-match ban for slow overate in the first match. Charles Coventry is expected to feature today as the hosts look to make a comeback into the series.]]></line><line><![CDATA[It was a comprehensive victory for the hosts in the first ODI on Tuesday. Batting first, they piled up a massive 375 on the board. Shoaib Malik made a hundred on his ODI comeback, Azhar Ali continued his rich vein of form while there were fifties for Mohammad Hafeez and Haris Sohail as well. Zimbabwe's reply was spirited with Elton Chigumbura smacking a fine 117, his maiden ODI hundred. Hamilton Masakadza chipped in with a run-a-ball 73 but the visitors still fell short by 41 runs, despite making their highest ever score in an ODI against a Test playing nation. Can the visitors do better today? Hello and a warm welcome to the second ODI between Pakistan and Zimbabwe.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Preview by <b>Siddharth Vishwanathan</b><br/><br/>Pakistan carried the momentum of their T20I success into the first ODI and their batsmen put on a magnificent show. For the first time, Pakistan's top four went past fifty, with Shoaib Malik leading the way with a brilliant 76-ball 112 as they notched up 375 for 3. However, their smiles would have been tempered with the way Zimbabwe responded with the bat, finishing on 334 for 5 and losing by a margin of 41 runs.<br/><br/>Zimbabwe's fight showed their determination but it also exposed the problems that Pakistan's bowling department faces. The likes of Anwar Ali and Mohammad Sami were dispatched to all parts of the Gaddafi stadium and it needed the experience of Wahab Riaz, who finished with figures of 3 for 47, to help the hosts avoid a major embarrassment.<br/><br/>Heading into the match, Zimbabwe have suffered a big jolt while Pakistan will be aiming for a polished performance to clinch the series.<br/><br/><b>Venue:</b> Gaddafi stadium, Lahore<br/></b>Starts:</b> 16:00 local<br/><b>Weather:</b> Clear skies with a high of 42 degrees<br/><br/><b>Team news</b><br/><br/><b>Pakistan</b><br/><br/>The bowling was below-par in the first ODI and they may be tempted to bolster their experience in the bowling. Anwar Ali, who had figures of 10-0-81-1, might be replaced by Junaid Khan while Sami, who was making a comeback after three years, might be given another chance after a poor first match.<br/><br/><b>Probable XI</b><br/><br/>1 Mohammad Hafeez, 2 Azhar Ali (c), 3 Shoaib Malik, 4 Haris Sohail, 5 Sarfraz Ahmed, 6 Asad Shafiq, 7 Hammad Azam, 8 Wahab Riaz, 9 Yasir Shah, 10 Anwar Ali/Junaid Khan, 11 Mohammad Sami<br/><br/><b>Zimbabwe</b><br/><br/>Heading into this match, they have suffered a major blow. Elton Chigumbura, who blasted 117 off 95 balls, has been suspended for the remaining two ODIs due to a slow over-rate offence. His absence will throw the team composition in disarray and it will be interesting to see how who will captain the side in his absence. Chigumbura's absence could see Roy Kaia, the 23-year-old Mountaineers allrounder, making his debut on Thursday.<br/><br/><b>Probable XI</b><br/><br/>1 Vusi Sibanda, 2 Sikandar Raza, 3 Hamilton Masakadza, 4 Roy Kaia, 5 Sean Williams, 6 Craig Ervine, 7 Richmond Mutumbami, 8 Prosper Utseya, 9 Tinashe Panyangara, 10 Chris Mpofu, 11 Brian Vitori]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Zimbabwe</b> (From): Vusi Sibanda, Sikandar Raza, Hamilton Masakadza, Sean Williams, Elton Chigumbura, Craig Ervine, Richmond Mutumbami, Prosper Utseya, Brian Vitori, Chris Mpofu, Tinashe Panyangara, Chamu Chibhabha, Charles Coventry, Graeme Cremer, Roy Kaia, Tawanda Mupariwa]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan</b> (From): Azhar Ali, Mohammad Hafeez, Haris Sohail, Shoaib Malik, Asad Shafiq, Sarfraz Ahmed, Hammad Azam, Wahab Riaz, Anwar Ali, Mohammad Sami, Yasir Shah, Imad Wasim, Mohammad Rizwan, Babar Azam, Junaid Khan, Ahmed Shehzad]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>268</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>7</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>50</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Zimbabwe">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>179</playerid>
					<name>Vusi Sibanda</name>
					<batsman-name>Sibanda</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sibanda</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>13</runs>
					<balls>47</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>M Hafeez</bowler>
					<bowlerId>360</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>436</playerid>
					<name>Chamu Chibhabha</name>
					<batsman-name>Chibhabha</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chibhabha</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>99</runs>
					<balls>100</balls>
					<fours>11</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>S Malik</bowler>
					<bowlerId>33</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sarfraz Ahmed</fielder>
						<fielderId>881</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>425</playerid>
					<name>Hamilton Masakadza</name>
					<batsman-name>H Masakadza</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>H Masakadza</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>18</runs>
					<balls>20</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Yasir Shah</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8064</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Mohammad Hafeez</fielder>
						<fielderId>360</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>441</playerid>
					<name>Sean Williams</name>
					<batsman-name>Sean Williams</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sean Williams</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>5</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Yasir Shah</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8064</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Yasir Shah</fielder>
						<fielderId>8064</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9354</playerid>
					<name>Sikandar Raza</name>
					<batsman-name>S Raza</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Raza</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>100</runs>
					<balls>84</balls>
					<fours>8</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9352</playerid>
					<name>Richmond Mutumbami</name>
					<batsman-name>Mutumbami</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mutumbami</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>7</runs>
					<balls>26</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>A Ali</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1052</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Asad Shafiq</fielder>
						<fielderId>6481</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3460</playerid>
					<name>Charles Coventry</name>
					<batsman-name>C Coventry</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Charles Coventry</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>10</runs>
					<balls>8</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Riaz</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1051</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sarfraz Ahmed</fielder>
						<fielderId>881</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>278</playerid>
					<name>Graeme Cremer</name>
					<batsman-name>Cremer</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Cremer</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Riaz</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1051</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ahmed Shehzad</fielder>
						<fielderId>1787</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3465</playerid>
					<name>Tinashe Panyangara</name>
					<batsman-name>Panyangara</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Panyangara</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>175</playerid>
					<name>Tawanda Mupariwa</name>
					<batsman-name>T Mupariwa</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mupariwa</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8020</playerid>
					<name>Brian Vitori</name>
					<batsman-name>Vitori</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Vitori</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>179</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>83</runs>
				<overs>18.3</overs>
				<batsman>Vusi Sibanda</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Sibanda</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>425</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>114</runs>
				<overs>24.2</overs>
				<batsman>Hamilton Masakadza</batsman>
				<batsman-name>H Masakadza</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>441</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>122</runs>
				<overs>26.4</overs>
				<batsman>Sean Williams</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Sean Williams</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>436</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>156</runs>
				<overs>34.3</overs>
				<batsman>Chamu Chibhabha</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Chibhabha</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9352</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>209</runs>
				<overs>43.6</overs>
				<batsman>Richmond Mutumbami</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mutumbami</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>3460</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>238</runs>
				<overs>46.5</overs>
				<batsman>Charles Coventry</batsman>
				<batsman-name>C Coventry</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>278</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>258</runs>
				<overs>48.4</overs>
				<batsman>Graeme Cremer</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Cremer</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>4</wides>
			<noballs>1</noballs>
			<legbyes>5</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>10</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Pakistan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>31</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Sami</name>
					<bowler-name>M Sami</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sami</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>53</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1052</playerid>
					<name>Anwar Ali</name>
					<bowler-name>A Ali</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Anwar Ali</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>55</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1051</playerid>
					<name>Wahab Riaz</name>
					<bowler-name>Riaz</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Riaz</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>55</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8064</playerid>
					<name>Yasir Shah</name>
					<bowler-name>Yasir Shah</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Yasir Shah</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>40</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>360</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Hafeez</name>
					<bowler-name>M Hafeez</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Hafeez</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>6</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>33</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6272</playerid>
					<name>Hammad Azam</name>
					<bowler-name>H Azam</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Azam</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>14</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>33</playerid>
					<name>Shoaib Malik</name>
					<bowler-name>S Malik</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shoaib Malik</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>13</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6633</playerid>
					<name>Azhar Ali</name>
					<bowler-name>Azhar Ali</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Azhar Ali</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8299</playerid>
					<name>Haris Sohail</name>
					<bowler-name>H Sohail</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sohail</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6481</playerid>
					<name>Asad Shafiq</name>
					<bowler-name>Shafiq</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shafiq</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>881</playerid>
					<name>Sarfraz Ahmed</name>
					<bowler-name>S Ahmed</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sarfraz Ahmed</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>269</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>4</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>47.2</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Pakistan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>6633</playerid>
					<name>Azhar Ali</name>
					<batsman-name>Azhar Ali</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Azhar Ali</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>102</runs>
					<balls>104</balls>
					<fours>8</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>T Mupariwa</bowler>
					<bowlerId>175</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sean Williams</fielder>
						<fielderId>441</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>881</playerid>
					<name>Sarfraz Ahmed</name>
					<batsman-name>S Ahmed</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sarfraz Ahmed</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>22</runs>
					<balls>28</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Chibhabha</bowler>
					<bowlerId>436</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>360</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Hafeez</name>
					<batsman-name>M Hafeez</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Hafeez</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>15</runs>
					<balls>24</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Cremer</bowler>
					<bowlerId>278</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Charles Coventry</fielder>
						<fielderId>3460</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6481</playerid>
					<name>Asad Shafiq</name>
					<batsman-name>Shafiq</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shafiq</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>39</runs>
					<balls>59</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Cremer</bowler>
					<bowlerId>278</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sikandar Raza</fielder>
						<fielderId>9354</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8299</playerid>
					<name>Haris Sohail</name>
					<batsman-name>H Sohail</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sohail</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>52</runs>
					<balls>49</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>33</playerid>
					<name>Shoaib Malik</name>
					<batsman-name>S Malik</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shoaib Malik</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>36</runs>
					<balls>20</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6272</playerid>
					<name>Hammad Azam</name>
					<batsman-name>H Azam</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Azam</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1052</playerid>
					<name>Anwar Ali</name>
					<batsman-name>A Ali</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Anwar Ali</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1051</playerid>
					<name>Wahab Riaz</name>
					<batsman-name>Riaz</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Riaz</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>31</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Sami</name>
					<batsman-name>M Sami</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sami</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8064</playerid>
					<name>Yasir Shah</name>
					<batsman-name>Yasir Shah</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Yasir Shah</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>881</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>46</runs>
				<overs>8.4</overs>
				<batsman>Sarfraz Ahmed</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Ahmed</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>360</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>68</runs>
				<overs>14.3</overs>
				<batsman>Mohammad Hafeez</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Hafeez</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6481</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>153</runs>
				<overs>31.4</overs>
				<batsman>Asad Shafiq</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Shafiq</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6633</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>209</runs>
				<overs>40.1</overs>
				<batsman>Azhar Ali</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Azhar Ali</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>1</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>3</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Zimbabwe">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>3465</playerid>
					<name>Tinashe Panyangara</name>
					<bowler-name>Panyangara</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Panyangara</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8.2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>42</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>175</playerid>
					<name>Tawanda Mupariwa</name>
					<bowler-name>T Mupariwa</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mupariwa</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>48</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8020</playerid>
					<name>Brian Vitori</name>
					<bowler-name>Vitori</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Vitori</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>52</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>436</playerid>
					<name>Chamu Chibhabha</name>
					<bowler-name>Chibhabha</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chibhabha</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>10</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>278</playerid>
					<name>Graeme Cremer</name>
					<bowler-name>Cremer</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Cremer</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>52</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>441</playerid>
					<name>Sean Williams</name>
					<bowler-name>Sean Williams</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sean Williams</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>53</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>425</playerid>
					<name>Hamilton Masakadza</name>
					<bowler-name>H Masakadza</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>H Masakadza</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>5</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9354</playerid>
					<name>Sikandar Raza</name>
					<bowler-name>S Raza</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Raza</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>5</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>179</playerid>
					<name>Vusi Sibanda</name>
					<bowler-name>Sibanda</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sibanda</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9352</playerid>
					<name>Richmond Mutumbami</name>
					<bowler-name>Mutumbami</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mutumbami</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3460</playerid>
					<name>Charles Coventry</name>
					<bowler-name>C Coventry</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Charles Coventry</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



