<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes" ?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="14761" >
		<type>T20</type>
		<gameDesc>2nd T20I</gameDesc>
		<series>Zimbabwe tour of Pakistan, 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>Pakistan</home>
		<away>Zimbabwe</away>
		<teamsabbr>PAK vs ZIM</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>PAK</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>ZIM</awayabbr>
		<homeId>3</homeId>
		<awayId>12</awayId>
		<venue>Gaddafi Stadium, Lahore</venue>
		<startdate>24 05 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>24 05 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Zimbabwe</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>Pakistan won by 2 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>Pakistan</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns></wonbyruns>
			<wonbywickets>2</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch></manofmatch>
		<manofseries>Mukhtar Ahmed</manofseries>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Ahmed Shahab</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Ahsan Raza</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Shozab Raza</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Azhar Khan</Name>
			<Country>Pak</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>14:00</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150524172858</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>Pak</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>Zim</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>176</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>8</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>19.4</batteamovers>
		<status>Pakistan won by 2 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>8582</playerid>
			<name>Bilawal Bhatti*</name>
			<batsman-name>B Bhatti</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Bhatti</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>13</runs>
			<balls-faced>5</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>1</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>10408</playerid>
			<name>Imad Wasim</name>
			<batsman-name>Imad Wasim</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Imad Wasim</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>4</runs>
			<balls-faced>5</balls-faced>
			<fours>0</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>8020</playerid>
			<name>Brian Vitori*</name>
			<bowler-name>Vitori</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Vitori</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>3.4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>36</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>428</playerid>
			<name>Chris Mpofu</name>
			<bowler-name>Mpofu</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Mpofu</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>25</runs>
			<wickets>2</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>20</maxovers>
		<target>176</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>9468</playerid>
<name>Mohammad Rizwan</name>
<player-runs>6</player-runs>
<player-balls>7</player-balls>
<runs>161</runs>
<wicket-nbr>8</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>428</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Mpofu</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>2</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>4</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>9</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[2 W 1 Wd 1 . . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>6 . 2 4 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. . . . . .<b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. . . . . .]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_PAK_ZIM/PAK_ZIM_MAY24/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[This is <b>Sidhant Maheshwari</b> and <b>Krishna</b>, signing off. Take care!]]></line><line><![CDATA[The action now shifts to the ODIs where these two teams will lock horns in a 3-match ODI series. The first ODI will be played on Tuesday. Don't forget to join us then for all the action.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Cricket finally returned to Pakistan and their fans must be extremely happy that they started on a winning note. After a Mukhtar Ahmed special guided them to a win in the last game, it was his 40-ball 62 today that kept Pakistan in the hunt and eventually, Bhatti took them over the line.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shahid Afridi:</b> I am happy with how these two matches got completed without any fuss. Thanks to the crowd for turning up here. The new talent coming out is good, but they need some polishing. We will hopefully get a few good players that we can take to the WorldT20. We thought we  will restrict them to 150-155, but they scored really well in two overs. As a captain, I had confidence in Bilawal Bhatti that he will take us home. Only the doctor will know, I will see him when I go to the hospital (talking about his injury). The boys have delivered what was expected from them. Thanks to the Zimbabwe cricket team as well, it was a good series.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shahid Afridi too spoke in Urdu. Here's the translation of his interview:]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mukhtar Ahmed</b> is also the <b>Man of the Series</b> for amassing <b>145 runs</b> in the 2-match series]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mukhtar Ahmed:</b> It was not an easy game, there was a lot of pressure on us. My playing style is like that  and that's why people don't feel that I am under pressure. 175 is a good score and we needed to get going right from the very start. I like to play aggressive cricket and I will continue to play in the same way.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mukhtar Ahmed spoke in Urdu. We have translated his interview for you.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mukhtar Ahmed</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his <b>40-ball 62</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, Zimbabwe managed to better their score from the first match. They scored 175, courtesy of another good opening partnership and fifty from Sean Williams. Towards the end, captain Chigumbura joined the party as he hit three consecutive sixes off Sami's bowling. His departure in the final over of the innings though put the brake on their scoring and Zimbabwe failed to cross the 180-run mark.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The debutant, Nauman Anwar, then hit a few good shots before he was caught at the boundary rope by Sibanda. Shoaib Malik failed to cash in on the opportunity and departed early. Mukhtar too departed after a good looking 40-ball 62. Afridi came out and hit a six before getting out off the very next ball. Akmal too was caught plumb in front while trying to slog one out of the park. Rizwan failed to get his team past the finishing line and at that moment, it looked like that Zimbabwe might run away with the game. However, Bhatti had other plans and he gave his team a series win with a boundary off the fourth ball of the final over.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bhatti had a very poor game with the ball, but he has done the job for his team with the bat. His 5-ball 13 under pressure took his team past the finishing line. Like last game, Pakistan started off well with the bat. Mukhtar Ahmed once again looked in exceptional touch and got good support from Shehzad. Shehzad though fell in the 5th over with 44 runs on the board.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Vitori looks very disappointed while the players exchange handshakes with each other. Coventry tries to calm him down as they walk off the field. The Pakistani team too walks out to shake hands with their counterparts.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Bhatti, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>Pakistan win the series 2-0!</b> The crowd has gone berserk at the Gaddafi Stadium. Coming back to the ball, it was a low full toss outside off, Bhatti drives it through extra cover and there was no stopping that ball the moment it crossed the infield]]></line><line><![CDATA[Chigu is marshalling his troops around]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Bhatti, 2 runs, this was bowled fuller and outside off, Bhatti goes hard on the drive, only manages to slice it to the right of third man, who runs to his right and stops the ball, the batsmen take two in the meantime]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Bhatti, no run, yorker slightly wide outside off, Bhatti reaches for it and tries to squeeze it out, fails to connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Bhatti, <b>SIX</b>, that's a <b>massive hit</b> at this stage of the game. This was bowled on a length and angled across off, Bhatti slogs hard and clears the long-on fence easily]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brian Vitori [3.0-0-24-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan need 12 runs in 6 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Imad Wasim, no run, slower in pace, short and slightly wide outside off, Wasim gives the charge and wanted to flat-bat it hard, fails to lay bat on the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Imad Wasim, no run, Wasim premeditates and wanted to play the lap shot over short fine leg, doesn't hit it properly and the ball rolls away to the left of the bowler, can't even get the single away]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Bhatti, 1 run, just short of a good length and outside off, Bhatti knocks it to the left of point and the batsmen cross over for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Bhatti, <b>wide</b>, bowls this one down the leg-side, Bhatti fails to connect with the glance and the umpire exercises his arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Imad Wasim, 1 run, full and outside off, Wasim drives it uppishly through square of the wicket, gets a single and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bilawal Bhatti, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Rizwan, <b>out</b> Caught by S Raza!! Mpofu is down on his knees after taking this wicket. It's a great catch from Raza. This was a slower ball on a length outside off, Rizwan slogs across the line but goes through the shot early, he doesn't make the desired connection. Raza from deep mid-wicket runs forward to his right, dives and takes a great catch. This game just keeps on getting interesting. <b>Rizwan c S Raza b Mpofu 6(7)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mpofu to Rizwan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Rizwan, 2 runs, on a good length and angling in on middle and leg, Rizwan comes across and works it behind square on the on-side, the batsmen take two before the fielder stops the ball in the deep]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>17 runs needed from 12 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Imad Wasim, 2 runs, works this tossed up delivery on middle and leg through square leg, good running and a poor throw ensure that they easily complete the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Rizwan, 1 run, Rizwan premeditates and backs away, Williams follows him with a quicker one, he bunts it down to long-on and was looking for the second, he had to put in the dive to get back inside the crease and the fielder quickly fired the throw at the non-striker's end]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Imad Wasim, 1 run, comes across to this flighted delivery on the stumps, eases it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Imad Wasim, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Anwar Ali, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Poor cricket from Ali, this was a full toss from Williams, Ali comes down the track and wanted to whack it hard. Instead of making a connection with the ball, he ends up yorking himself and the ball crashes into the leg stump. <b>Anwar Ali b Sean Williams 2(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sean Williams to Anwar Ali, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Rizwan, 1 run, fuller on the stumps, Mohammad nudges it to deep mid-wicket and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Anwar Ali, 1 run, darted quicker on off stump line, Ali works it through mid-wicket and gets to the other end, he slipped while turning back for the second and Rizwan asks him to stay at the other end]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sean Williams [3.0-0-26-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>23 runs needed from 18 balls</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Anwar Ali, 1 run, back of a length delivery angling down leg, Ali helps it down to fine leg and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Anwar Ali, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to U Akmal, <b>out</b> Lbw!! That's as plumb as it gets. This was the slower ball from Mpofu, Akmal wanted to slog it out of the park after kneeling down. He misses it completely and the ball hits him in line with the middle stump. The bowler started appealing and tumbled over. By the time the umpire nodded and raised his finger, Mpoful was lying flat on the pitch and celebrating. Anyway, it is a big wicket for Zimbabwe in this situation. <b>U Akmal lbw b Mpofu 30(21) [4s-1 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mpofu to U Akmal, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to U Akmal, <b>SIX</b>, <b>tonked!</b> This was once again full and outside off, Akmal lofts it over the long-off fence. The fielder was interested for some time but it sailed well over his head]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to U Akmal, no run, full and outside off, Akmal drives it hard towards cover, who dives to his left and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to U Akmal, byes, 2 runs, poor effort from the keeper there. It was a slower short ball from Mpofu, Akmal fails to run it down to third man, the keeper doesn't collect it cleanly and the batsmen take two byes]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to U Akmal, no run, slower back of a length delivery outside off, Akmal punches hard but picks out the fielder at point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Mpofu [2.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Rizwan, no run, shortish and slightly wide outside off, Rizwan chops it towards backward point, he was looking for the single there but Akmal was not interested]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to U Akmal, 1 run, bowls slightly fuller and on the stumps, Akmal goes for the loft, but gets it off the inside half of the bat. The ball goes on the bounce to the fielder at long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to U Akmal, 2 runs, bowls this slightly wide outside off, Akmal lofts it over extra cover, the batsmen take two before sweeper runs to his right and fields the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Rizwan, 1 run, length delivery just outside off, Rizwan opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to U Akmal, 1 run, gives the charge and mistimes the slog down to long-on as he had to really reach out for it, gets to the other end with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to U Akmal, no run, just short of a good length and just outside off, Akmal punches hard but finds the non-striker at the other end, who couldn't get out of the way. The batsmen can't take a single as the ball rolls away towards extra cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brian Vitori [2.0-0-19-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to U Akmal, 1 run, backs away and knocks this flatter delivery through point for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Rizwan, 1 run, kneels down and sweeps this tossed up delivery to deep backward square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to U Akmal, 1 run, nudges this flatter delivery on the pads through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to U Akmal, <b>SIX</b>, <b>caught but falls over the rope!</b> This was short from Williams, Akmal pulls it high over mid-wicket, Vitori in the deep takes the catch, but loses his balance and falls over the rope. The umpire signals a six]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Rizwan, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Afridi, <b>out</b> Caught by S Raza!! Boom-Boom is gone and the crowd has gone silent. This was bowled quicker by Williams, Afidi lines up for another slog, but this time he skies it very high. There were two fielders converging around the mid-on region, Raza almost crashed into him while trying to take it. He did well to hold onto it on the second attempt. The Pakistani captain makes his walk back. <b>Afridi c S Raza b Sean Williams 7(3) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sean Williams to Afridi, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Afridi, <b>SIX</b>, Afridi goes big and he has cleared the rope quite comfortably. He goes leg-side to this flighted delivery and lofts it over the wide long-off fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sean Williams [2.0-0-11-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to U Akmal, <b>FOUR</b>, darted on the stumps, Akmal gets under the ball and whips it magnificently to the cow corner fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to U Akmal, 2 runs, quicker on the stumps, Akmal punches it wide of long-off and comes back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Afridi, 1 run, nudges this flatter delivery on the pads to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shahid Afridi, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>out</b> Caught by Sibanda!! This is a big, big wicket for Zimbabwe. The dangerman Mukhtar is gone. This was flighted on the stumps, Mukhtar backs away and lofts it through the line. He didn't quite get underneath the ball and offers a simple catch to Sibanda at long-on, who moves to his left and takes a simple catch. <b>Mukhtar Ahmed c Sibanda b S Raza 62(40) [4s-6 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[S Raza to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Mukhtar Ahmed, 2 runs, employs the reverse sweep and toe-ends it over cover. Just about clears the leaping fielder at cover, comes back for the second quite easily]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Mukhtar Ahmed, 2 runs, low full toss on the pad, Ahmed kneels down and paddles it fine, gets back for the second before the fielder in the deep runs to his right and stops the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to U Akmal, 2 runs, tossed up outside off, Akmal lofts it inside-out over extra cover, the batsmen take a couple before the fielder hunts it down]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, drills this fuller delivery down to long-on, gets to the other end with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to U Akmal, 1 run, <b>dropped!</b> That's a poor effort from the Mpofu, this was fairly short and down leg, Akmal swivels and pulls it in the air towards deep backward square leg, Mpofu near the boundary rope dives over it and fails to connect. A very poor effort from the medium-pacer]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to U Akmal, no run, flatter on off and middle, Akmal punches it to the left of mid-wicket, who runs across and dives to stop the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, Mukhtar backs a long way and Utseya follows him with a quicker and flatter delivery, Mukhtar just about manages to knock it down towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Mukhtar Ahmed, 2 runs, quicker on the stumps, Mukhtar whips it wide of long-on, good running ensures that they come back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, in the blockhole around off, Mukhtar drags it off the inside half of the bat towards deep mid-wicket, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>consecutive fifty</b> for Mukhtar, this was dragged flatter and slightly wide outside off, Ahmed cuts it to the right of backward point, it was uppish but in the gap, runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to U Akmal, 1 run, flatter outside off, Akmal cuts it to the left of backward point, who dives to his left but can't stop the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, Raza drags his length back as Mukhtar gave him the charge, Mukhtar punches it uppishly down to long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to U Akmal, 1 run, on the pads this time around, Akmal nurdles it towards short fine leg and the batsmen cross over for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;S Raza to U Akmal, no run, quicker just outside off, Akmal backs away and looks to cut, can't beat the man at short third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sikandar Raza, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Mukhtar Ahmed, 2 runs, Mukhtar backs away and Utseya follows him with quicker one, he nudges it through square leg and gets back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to U Akmal, 1 run, floated up outside off, Akmal drives it to sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Umar Akmal, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Shoaib Malik, <b>out</b> Shoaib Malik Run Out!! Brilliant bit of fielding by Utseya. This is the first time that Shoaib Malik has been run-out in T20 cricket. It was bowled flatter and quicker as Malik gave the charge, he punches it to the right of the bowler, who quickly goes across and stops the ball. Malik was not expecting Utseya to throw the ball, but the bowler quickly gets up and releases the throw towards the striker's end. By the time Malik tried to get in, the direct-hit from Utseya had already crashed into the stumps. <b>Shoaib Malik run out (Utseya) 7(7) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Utseya to Shoaib Malik, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire has been called in to check a run-out chance. Malik is the man in question. Malik is gone, he is short of his crease. The big screen displays 'OUT'.]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, short and following the batsman who was backing away, Mukhtar splices the pull and the ball rolls away down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, flatter just outside off, Malik stays back and slogs it hard, the ball goes on the bounce to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, Mukhtar backs away and Utseya follows him with a quicker one, Mukhtar punches it wide of long-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shoaib Malik, <b>FOUR</b>, poor ball to end the over from Cremer, it was way short and it got the punishment it deserved, Malik goes deep in the crease and pulls it to the deep mid-wicket fence. Spoils what was turning out to be a good over]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, on the pads once again, Mukhtar nudges it behind square on the on-side and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, shortish outside off, Mukhtar cuts it to the right of point, who dives and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Mukhtar Ahmed, 2 runs, Mukhtar makes slight room and Cremer bowls this one on his pads, Mukhtar works it away through square leg, good running ensures that they come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, flatter outside off, Malik looks to cut but ends up chopping it to the left of cover, gets to the other end with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Shoaib Malik, no run, gives this one more air outside off, Malik leans forward and drives it straight to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Mukhtar Ahmed, 2 runs, touch quicker and outside off, Mukhtar goes deep in the crease and punches it past extra cover, the batsmen take two before the sweeper gets around in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Shoaib Malik, 1 run, nudges this delivery on middle and leg through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Shoaib Malik, no run, flatter and turning in around off, Malik punches it back to the bowler, who dives to his right and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Shoaib Malik, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Nauman Anwar, <b>out</b> Caught by Sibanda!! Utseya strikes for Zimbabwe. It was not a wicket-taking delivery, but Zimbabwe won't mind it one bit. This was quicker and short outside off, Anwar goes for the pull but the ball hits him high on the bat, Sibanda at long-on stations himself in front of the rope and takes a well-judged catch. <b>Nauman Anwar c Sibanda b Utseya 18(10) [4s-2 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Utseya to Nauman Anwar, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, poor bowling from Utseya, he is bowling it way too short, Mukhtar pulls it to deep backward square leg and the batsmen cross over for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, short and down the leg-side, Utseya got away with one there as Mukhtar pulls it straight to short fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Nauman Anwar, no run, Anwar tries to put the bowler off by moving around the crease, Anwar bowls this flatter just outside off, it was bowled slower as well. Anwar tries to cut it, but fails to connect, <b>19 runs came off the over</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Comes round the wicket now]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Nauman Anwar, <b>FOUR</b>, now the reverse sweep from Anwar and he connects really well with it. It was a flighted delivery around off, Anwar sends it over short third man and the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Nauman Anwar, <b>SIX</b>, that's a magnificent shot from Anwar, this was tossed up outside off, Anwar goes down on one knee and slog sweeps it over the cow corner fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, quicker and fuller on middle and leg, Mukhtar whips it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>SIX</b>, Mukhtar backs away and smashes this flatter delivery over the long-on fence. Even though he had to reach out to play that shot, he cleared the boundary rope by quite some distance]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Cremer to Mukhtar Ahmed, 2 runs, starts off with a shortish delivery on the stumps, Mukhtar pulls it wide of long-on, the fielder dives to his right and stops the ball, the batsmen run for a brace]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Graeme Cremer, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Nauman Anwar, <b>FOUR</b>, once again Utseya bowls this quicker and flatter, Anwar goes deep in the crease and flat-bats it straight down the ground, the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Nauman Anwar, 2 runs, kneels down and sweeps this behind square on the on-side, the fielder runs to his right to stop the ball in the deep and the batsmen take two in the meantime]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, flatter from Utseya, Mukhtar punches it to sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>wide</b>, down the leg-side, Mukhtar fails to sweep it fine, called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Nauman Anwar, 1 run, flat-bats this flatter delivery to the left of the bowler, who leaps up but the ball evades him, a single down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, pushed through quicker and on middle and leg, Mukhtar works it towards backward square leg, the batsmen take a quick single. A direct-hit at the striker's end would have been interesting but by the time the keeper took the bails off, Anwar was in]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Utseya to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a freebie from Utseya, he bowls this way too short, Mukhtar had all the time in the world to rock back, he pulls it to the deep mid-wicket fence with ease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Prosper Utseya, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Nauman Anwar, no run, backs away and Williams offers him a full toss, he hits it straight to the fielder at extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, gives the charge and drills this to the right of mid-off, who dives full length and saves some runs for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, Mukhtar looks to go big on the on-side, but ends up getting an inside edge onto the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Nauman Anwar, 1 run, flatter from Williams, Anwar slogs, the ball goes on the bounce to the fielder at deep mid-wicket, gets off the mark with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, stays back to this tossed up delivery on middle and leg, whipped to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, quicker and on the pads, Mukhtar fails to flick it away, the ball rolls away back on the pitch off the pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Nauman Anwar, no run, on a length and angled across off, Anwar defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Nauman Anwar, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>out</b> Caught by Sibanda!! Shehzad departs trying to score big during the mandatory powerplay. This was a short delivery outside off, Shehzad goes for the pull but gets a top-edge, Sibanda at mid-off takes the simplest of catches. <b>Ahmed Shehzad c Sibanda b Vitori 18(17) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Vitori to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>FOUR</b>, bowls this on middle stump line, Shehzad mistimes the whip through mid-wicket but the ball had enough legs to reach the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, just short of a good length and outside off, Shehzad drills it hard but straight to the man at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, on a length and angling away outside off, Shehzad slashes and misses]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, short and slightly wide outside off, Shehzad cuts it to the left of backward point, who dives and saves a certain boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, comes down the track and Williams drags his length back, Shehzad punches it to long-off and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Ahmed Shehzad, 2 runs, backs away and whips this flighted delivery through square leg, comes back for the second with ease]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>FOUR</b>, shortish and wide outside off, Shehzad cuts it through backward point, the ball crashes into the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, kneels down and sweeps well but picks out backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, flatter delivery on the pads, Mukhtar turns it through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sean Williams to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, drills this flighted delivery back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, goes across and clips it through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>dropped!</b> This was short and slightly wide outside off, Mukhtar backs away a touch and cuts it straight to backward pont, where Williams tries to take it over his head, but the ball bursts through his hands and runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, down the leg-side, Shehzad tickles it to the left of the keeper, who doesn't stop it cleanly after moving across, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away towars the short fine leg region]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Ahmed Shehzad, <b>FOUR</b>, Shehzad walks right across his stumps and flicks this length delivery over backward square leg, the fielder dives to his left, but allows the ball to escape through]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Ahmed Shehzad, leg byes, <b>FOUR</b>, slower ball on the stumps, Shehzad lines up for the big slog and fails to connect, the ball runs away to the right of the keeper off the thigh pad, third man was inside the circle and it runs away]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, down the leg-side, Shehzad fails to glance it fine and the ball goes towards the keeper off the pad]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, Vitori ends his over with a good ball, it was angled across off. Mukhtar tries to run it down to third man, but the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, overcompensates and bowls this on the pads, all Mukhtar had to do was to tuck it away behind square on the on-side, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>edged and four!</b> This was bowled fuller and slightly wide outside off, Mukhtar goes for the drive and throws the kitchen sink at it, gets a thick outside edge that runs away past slip and into the third man fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>wide</b>, down the leg-side, Mukhtar fails to tickle it fine, called a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Mukhtar Ahmed, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot!</b> Short and enough width on offer, Mukhtar hangs back and cuts it to the left of backward point, third man runs to his right but the ball was too quick for him]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, slashes hard at this widish delivery outside off, gets it to the right of third man and the batsmen take another single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vitori to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, full delivery angled across off, Shehzad drives it to the left of mid-off and the batsmen pinch a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Brian Vitori, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Shehzad drops it in to the left of the bowler and was looking for the single there, has to rush back in as the bowler was running towards the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Ahmed Shehzad, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Shehzad gets behind the line and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, <b>in the air and safe!</b> This was a slower ball outside off, Mukhtar looks to go hard at it and miscues it completely, the ball was in the air for quite some time, but falls in front of the fielder at long-on, who was running forward to try and take it. The batsmen take a single in the meantime and Mukhtar survives]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Mukhtar Ahmed, no run, Mukhtar goes across to this fuller delivery and mistimes the loft towards mid-on, the ball bounces twice before reaching the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Ahmed Shehzad, 1 run, full delivery shaping in on off and middle, Shehzad looks to work it through the on-side, gets an inside edge onto the pad, the batsmen take a single as the ball dribbles away towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mpofu to Mukhtar Ahmed, 1 run, full delivery slightly wide outside off, Mukhtar slices the drive and the ball rolls away to the right of third man, he gets off the mark with a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mukhtar Ahmed and Ahmed Shehzad are at the crease. Mukhtar Ahmed is on strike. Mpofu will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back. The Pakistani openers are walking out to the middle. Mpofu will open the bowling. He has a slip in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Now, it is upto their bowlers to try and make amends from their performance in the last game. Can they restrict Pakistan? Or will Pakistani batsmen continue to dominate the proceedings? Join us in a short while to find out.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sibanda though departed just one short of his maiden T20I fifty. EltonChigumbura came out and blasted Sami for three consecutive sixes and at that stage, Zimbabwe were looking good for a score above 180. However, Chigumbura's wicket in the final over and Coventry missing out on his first two balls, meant that Zimbawe could only make 175 in their 20 overs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Zimbabwe have manged to better their score from the last game but only by 3 runs. They'll feel that they should have got more than their current score. Masakadza and Sibanda started off in usual fashion, hitting the Pakistani bowlers all over the park. Masakadza though fell trying to up the scoring rate. Williams came out and thrashed the Pakistani bowlers, while Sibanda gave him good support from the other end.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Charles Coventry, 2 runs, finally he connects with a shortish delivery, he pulls it to the right of long-on, good running ensures that the batsmen come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Charles Coventry, no run, once again Coventry makes room and looks to slog it out of the park, fails to make a connection with his back of a length delivery]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Charles Coventry, no run, backs away and looks to smack one out of the ground, he fails to connect and the keeper collects]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sean Williams, 1 run, low full toss from Sami, Williams helps it towards extra cover and sets off, the fielder fires a quick throw at the non-striker's end and by the time Sami took the bails off, Williams was inside the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[Third umpire called in to check a run-out decision. This looks close, but Williams probably made his ground. The third umpire is taking his time and he decides that it is 'Not Out'.]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sean Williams, <b>FOUR</b>, full and on batsman's pads, it was almost on a yorker length, Williams did well there to work it behind square on the on-side, finds the gap and the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Charles Coventry, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, <b>out</b> Caught by Ahmed Shehzad!! Chigu departs after a quickfire 21. This was bowled fuller and outside off, Chigumbura goes deep to get under it, he tries to launch it over long-off but doesn't get the desired distance on that. Shehzad at long-off moves to his left and takes the catch. <b>Chigumbura c Ahmed Shehzad b Sami 21(9) [6s-3]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Sami to Chigumbura, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sami will continue from round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sean Williams, no run, bowls this short and way too quick, Williams looks to pull it out of the ground but can't connect]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Chigumbura, 1 run, pushed through quicker on leg, Chigumbura mistimes the whop through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sean Williams, 1 run, mistimes the loft once again towards long-on, the ball goes on the bounce to the fielder and the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Chigumbura, 1 run, Afridi bowls the quicker one and Chigumbura can only mistime the loft towards long-off, only a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Chigumbura, no run, darts this one towards the batsman who was lining up for the big slog, he misses and the keeper too can't collect it cleanly. Can't get a bye though]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sean Williams, 1 run, goes for the reverse sweep this time but fails to connect properly. The ball rolls away towards point and the batsmen take a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Sean Williams, leg byes, 1 run, Sami follows Williams who was backing away, he looks to work this full delivery on the pads behind square but fails to connect, the batsmen sneak in a leg bye as the ball rolls away into the on-side off the pad]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, 1 run, this time Sami bowls a yorker on leg stump line, Chigumbura whips the flick through square leg, Williams wanted the second run but the fielder did well to throw the ball quickly towards the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, <b>SIX</b>, third consecutive six for Chigu and Sami is being thrashed all over the park. He ends up bowling another full toss in trying to bowl the yorker, Chigu gets under it and tonks it up and over the long-on fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, <b>SIX</b>, <b>back-to-back</b> sixes for the Zimbabwean captain. It was full outside of, Chigumbura lofts it inside-out over deep extra cover and that went a mile]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, <b>SIX</b>, Chigu might have missed out on the previous ball, but this time he smashes it out of the park. A low full toss outside off, Chigumbura swings hard and smokes it over the deep extra cover fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to Chigumbura, no run, bowls this very full and well outside off, Chigumbura looks to drive it through the off-side, but fails to connect and the keeper collects]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Sami [2.0-0-12-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sean Williams, <b>SIX</b>, what a way to get to your <b>maiden T20I fifty</b>. This was floated up, Williams kneels down and slog sweeps it over square leg, there was protection in the deep but the ball sails over the fielder quite comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sean Williams, 2 runs, backs away and lofts this flighted delivery to the right of extra cover, the batsmen come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Elton Chigumbura, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sibanda, <b>out</b> Caught by Anwar Ali!! Sibanda falls just one short of his maiden T20I fifty. This was bowled flatter by Afridi, Sibanda slogs across the line but doesn't get the distance. Ali at deep mid-wicket runs to his right and juggles the ball twice before holding onto it with his help of his body. <b>Sibanda c Anwar Ali b Afridi 49(46) [4s-2 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Afridi to Sibanda, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sean Williams, 1 run, shortish from Afridi, Williams pulls it down to long-on, only a single on this occasion]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sean Williams, 2 runs, <b>in the air and safe!</b> This was tossed up on middle stump line, Williams slog sweeps it but doesn't get it off the meat of the bat, the skier falls in front of the deep mid-wicket fielder, who was running forward to try and take it]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sibanda, 1 run, flatter and cramping Sibanda for room as he was backing away, he pulls it towards deep square leg for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shahid Afridi [2.0-0-20-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Sibanda, 1 run, another full toss from Bhatti and Sibanda once again fails to make the most of it. He can only bunt it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Sibanda, 2 runs, banged in short at the batsman, Sibanda swivels and mistimes the pull through mid-wicket, long-on runs forward to his right and throws it towards the non-striker's end, Williams though makes it in time]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Sibanda, 2 runs, low full toss outside off, Sibanda jams it hard on the ground and the ball bounces over the leaping bowler, good running ensures that the batsman come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Sean Williams, 1 run, banged in short and at the batsman, Sibanda pulls it behind square on the on-side, the fielder quickly runs to his right in the deep and keeps them down to a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Sibanda, 1 run, bowls this one just outside off on almost a yorker length, Sibanda jams it out to the left of extra cover and gives the strike back to Williams]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Sibanda, no run, full and in the slot outside off, Sibanda drills the drive straight to Afridi at extra cover, who fires a throw at the non-striker's end. Williams has to rush back inside the crease]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Bilawal Bhatti [2.0-0-24-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sibanda, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Sibanda drives it down to long-off, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, 1 run, bowls this flatter seeing Williams back away a touch, he pulls it straight to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sibanda, 1 run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Sibanda whips it to deep mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, 1 run, drills this tossed up delivery straight back to the bowler, who misfields and the batsmen cross over for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, 2 runs, goes for the reverse sweep and gets it over the infield, the fielder at sweeper cover runs to his right and misfields, the batsmen take two in the meantime]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>50 of the partnership</b> comes up with this boundary, this was a low full toss from Malik, Williams kneels down and sweeps this magnificently, splits deep square leg and deep mid-wicket to perfection]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, slower bouncer from Ali, Sibanda ducks under it and leaves it for the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, 1 run, another off-pace short ball just outside off, Williams gently pulls it through mid-wicket and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, <b>FOUR</b>, back-of-the-hand slower short ball on the stumps, Williams backs away, waits for the ball to arrive and pulls it through mid-wicket, the fielder in the deep runs to his right but the ball evades him and crashes into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a great shot. It was full and around off, Williams goes across and whips this through square leg, the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, 1 run, slower short ball from Ali, Sibanda plays a controlled pull through square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, full toss on the pads, Sibanda fails to work it away into the on-side, the ball rolls away towards the keeper off the pad, he dives to his left and stops the ball, the batsmen can't get a leg bye]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sibanda, 1 run, eased down to long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, 1 run, Williams makes room and cuts this flatter delivery outside off to extra cover, Shehzad did really well there to dive to his right and stop the ball, the batsmen can take only a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sibanda, 1 run, goes across slightly and works this flighted delivery down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, 1 run, floated up around off, Williams drives it down to long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sibanda, 1 run, works this flighted delivery through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sibanda, no run, almost a return catch to the bowler, this was tossed up on the stumps, Sibanda drills it back to the bowler, the ball bounces just in front of Malik, who dives to his left and stops the ball with his left hand]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, 1 run, bowls this slightly wide outside off, Sibanda reaches out and guides this delivery to the left of backward point, gets to the other end for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, 1 run, pulls this shortish delivery through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, <b>no ball</b>, bumper from Ali, Williams watched it sail over his head, the umpire calls it no-ball because it was the second bumper of the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, 3 runs, bit straighter in line, Sibands clips it off his pads through mid-wicket, the fielder in the deep did well to run to his left, slides and flicks it back in time to save a run for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, 1 run, slower back of a length delivery outside off, Williams pushes it in front of cover and sets off, completes the single easily in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, <b>FOUR</b>, short and wide outside off, Williams cuts it to the deep extra cover fence, the fielder in the deep runs to his left but the ball was far away from his reach]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sean Williams, 2 run, slower short ball outside off, Williams plays a controlled pull behind square on the on-side, the batsmen come back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Anwar Ali [1.0-0-8-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, 1 run, advances down the track ands lofts this gently towards long-off, the batsmen take a single as the ball rolls away towards the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sibanda, 1 run, full toss on the stumps, Sibanda pulls it to deep mid-wicket, only a single on this occasion as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, 1 run, once again Williams gives the charge and Malik drags his length back slightly, Williams chips it towards long-on, the fielder takes it on the bounce and the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sibanda, 1 run, goes slightly across and works this flighted delivery on middle stump line through mid-wicket, the batsmen were looking for the second there but it's not available]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sibanda, no run, another one that's bowled around the blockhole, Sibanda squeezes out the drive back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sibanda, no run, in the blockhole this time, Sibanda jams it out back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sean Williams, <b>FOUR</b>, once again Williams advances down the track and whips this over mid-wicket, long-on runs to his left but the ball was too far away from him]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sean Williams, <b>FOUR</b>, that's great use of the feet from Williams, he comes down the track and lofts this tossed up delivery over the bowler, the fielder from long-off runs to his left but the ball wins the race]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sibanda, 1 run, flatter outside off, Sibanda punches it towards sweeper cover and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sean Williams, 1 run, eases this down to long-off after stepping out of the crease]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sean Williams, no run, defends this flatter delivery back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sibanda, 3 runs, flighted delivery on the stumps, Sibanda whips it through mid-wicket, Sami and Malik were charging towards the ball from long-on and deep mid-wicket, both try to stop the ball and collide, the batsmen take three in the meantime]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[There's a collision in the outfield, both the fielders involved are down on the ground. Actually, Sami slipped near the rope and he rams his knee into Malik's head. Malik was down on the ground, but is up on his feet now.]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sibanda, 1 run, low full toss on the stumps, Sibanda helps it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sibanda, no run, flatter and on off, Sibanda punches it towards mid-wicket, who dives to his left and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sean Williams, 1 run, floated up on off, Williams leans forward and drives it down to long-off, gets off the mark with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sean Williams, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to H Masakadza, <b>out</b> Caught by Anwar Ali!! Pakistan get the first breakthrough, Masakadza is not at all happy with himself. This was tossed up on the stumps, Masakadza goes for a big hit over long-on, but doesn't quite get under it. Anwar Ali at long-on takes a simple catch and the Pakistani players mob Shoaib Malik. <b>H Masakadza c Anwar Ali b Shoaib Malik 39(32) [4s-4 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Shoaib Malik to H Masakadza, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to Sibanda, 1 run, flighted delivery on middle stump line, Sibanda goes across and turns it through mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shoaib Malik to H Masakadza, 1 run, starts off with a very full delivery around off, Masakadza drills it down to long-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shoaib Malik, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to H Masakadza, 1 run, pushed through quicker and on middle and leg, Masakadza punches it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sibanda, 1 run, drops this in front of cover and sets off for a quick single, makes it comfortably in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sibanda, no run, floated up and spinning away outside off, Sibanda looks to drive off the front foot, the turn beats him on the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to Sibanda, 2 runs, flatter and well outside off, Sibanda chases it and goes hard on the cut, the ball flies to the right of short third man, the batsmen come back for the second before the ball is hunted down]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to H Masakadza, 1 run, pulls this shortish delivery down to long-on, gets to the other end with a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Afridi to H Masakadza, 2 runs, clips this delivery on middle and leg wide of long-on, comes back for the second easily]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Shahid Afridi, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Sibanda, <b>SIX</b>, that's a good shot from Sibanda, this was flighted on the stumps, Sibanda lofts it through the line, there was a fielder at long-on but the ball sails over him quite comfortably, good way to end the over]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Sibanda, no run, tossed up just outside off, Sibanda pushes it straight to extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to H Masakadza, 1 run, touch flatter from Wasim, Masakadza helps it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Sibanda, 1 run, floated up just outside off, Sibanda leans forward and drives it down to long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Sibanda, no run, quicker and on off, punched back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to H Masakadza, leg byes, 1 run, looks to whip this through the on-side, fails to connect and the ball rolls away into the on-side, the batsmen sneak in a leg bye]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to H Masakadza, 1 run, <b>50 of the partnership</b> comes up with this single, this was a back of a length delivery on middle and leg, Masakadza pulls it through square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to H Masakadza, <b>no ball</b>, Bhatti tries to bowl another slower ball but ends up bowling a beamer down leg, the umpire immediately calls it a no-ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Sibanda, 1 run, angling in on the stumps, Sibanda works it through square leg and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Sibanda, <b>wide</b>, slower ball that goes down leg, called a wide by the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Sibanda, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>smashed!</b> Length ball outside off, Sibanda leans forward and loft-drives it to the right of mid-off, who had no chance of stopping that, runs away to the fence in a jiffy]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to H Masakadza, 1 run, back of a length delivery on middle stump line, Masakadza whips it uppishly through mid-wicket, he was looking for the second there but decides against it in the end]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to H Masakadza, <b>wide</b>, slower ball bumper from Bhatti, Masakadza drops his wrists and lets it go, the umpire calls it a wide as it was over the batsman's head]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Sibanda, 1 run, on a length and around off, Sibanda drills the drive back to the bowler, who bends down in his followthrough and parries the ball towards mid-off with his left hand, the batsmen cross over for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Sibanda, no run, back of a length delivery angling in on off and middle, Sibanda blocks it to the left of the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Bilawal Bhatti [1.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Sibanda, 1 run, tossed up on middle and leg, Sibanda clears his front leg and whips it to long-on, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to Sibanda, no run, flatter and on the stumps, Sibanda punches it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to H Masakadza, 1 run, Masakadza advances and Wasim drags this slightly wide, Masakadza bunts it to the left of extra cover, who fires the throw at the striker's end, the keeper can't collect it cleanly and the batsmen sneak in a run on the overthrow]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to H Masakadza, no run, darted on middle and leg, Masakadza kneels down and sweeps it straight to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to H Masakadza, <b>FOUR</b>, Masakadza gives the charge this time around and lofts it over the bowler's head, he didn't time this properly but it had enough legs to reach the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Imad Wasim to H Masakadza, no run, floated up on the stumps from round the wicket, Masakadza drills it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Imad Wasim, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the debutant to chance his arm.]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, 1 run, full and on the stumps, Masakadza jams it hard on the pitch, the ball rolls away past the non-striker and the batsmen take a single before the fielder gets around]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, no run, makes room and wanted to go inside-out over cover, but Sami takes the pace off the ball. Masakadza can't connect and the ball goes on the bounce to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, no run, full and on off and middle, Masakadza drives it down to mid-on, can't get the single away]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, no run, back of a length delivery around off, Masakadza punches it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, <b>SIX</b>, that's been <b>clobbered!</b> This was full and outside off, Masakadza reaches out to the pitch of the ball and tonks it straight down the ground, the ball just about clears the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[Looks like Afridi has done some harm to his hand while fielding that ball. He has gone off the field to receive some treatment.]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, no run, Masakadza gives the charge this time around and drills this length ball to the left of mid-off, Afridi did well to quickly move to his left and stop the ball as the ball was travelling quickly]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to Sibanda, no run, short of length delivery just outside off, Sibanda hangs back and punches it to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to H Masakadza, 1 run, another short delivery from Bhatti, this time Masakadza rocks back and pulls it magnificently, picks out deep square leg and can only get a single this time around]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to H Masakadza, no run, banged in short and at the batsman, Masakadza sways away from the line and drops his wrists to let that go]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to H Masakadza, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>three in three for Masakadza!</b> This was very well played. Bhatti shortens his length this time around and bowls it outside off, Masakadza waits inside the crease and opens the face of the bat at the last time, gets it fine and to the right of the keeper. Third man was squarer and was in no position to stop that]]></line><line><![CDATA[Afridi is currently having a chat with Bhatti]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to H Masakadza, <b>FOUR</b>, poor start to Bhatti's over, another one that's been <b>smacked!</b> This was full and around off, Masakadza once again leans forward and lofts it over the bowler, runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhatti to H Masakadza, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>that's been smashed!</b> This was full and in the slot, Masakadza comes on the front foot and drills it to the left of the bowler, who had no chance of stopping that. It races away to the fence in no time]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Bilawal Bhatti, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, 1 run, full and slightly wide outside off, Masakadza goes hard on the drive, gets an outside edge that flies towards third man, goes on the bounce to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, 2 runs, Masakadza premeditates and goes across before the ball was even bowled. Sami fires it in the blockhole, Masakadza squeezes it out through mid-wicket, good running ensures that they come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, 2 runs, angling in on middle stump line this time around, Masakadza hoicks it over mid-wicket, didn't time it too well but it had enough on it for the batsmen to come back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, no run, just short of a good length and angling in on off, Masakadza jams his bat hard at it, he was looking for the single but decides against it as the ball was rolling away towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, no run, another good delivery in the channel outside off, Masakadza puts his front foot forward and pushes at it, the ball shapes away just a touch and beats the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sami to H Masakadza, no run, gets this one to shape away from a fuller length outside off, Masakadza leaves it alone]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammad Sami, right-arm fast, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sami to share the attack with Ali. He has a slip in place too.]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to H Masakadza, 1 run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Masakadza drops it into the off-side and sets off for a quick single, the batsmen complete it quite comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, 3 runs, <b>uppish and safe!</b> This was full outside off, Sibanda goes for another lofted drive, slices it in the air, Malik at cover-point runs to his right, extends his right hand and gets his fingertips on the ball, the ball rolls away towards the sweeper cover region, Malik gives chase and hauls the ball back in time to save a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, another delivery that's short and on the stumps, Sibanda lines up for the pull but fails to connect with it, wears it on the stomach]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, back of a length delivery on the stumps, Sibanda gets behind the line and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a cracking shot to get off the mark. This was once again pitched up outside off, Sibanda comes forward, gets to the pitch of the ball and loft drives it over mid-off and the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Anwar Ali to Sibanda, no run, poor shot from Sibanda, this was full outside off, he goes for the drive and misses the ball completely, the ball goes past the outside edge and into the hands of the keeper]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sibanda and H Masakadza are at the crease. Sibanda is on strike. Anwar Ali will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Zimbabwean openers are walking out to the middle. Anwar Ali will open the bowling first up. He has a slip in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Afridi:</b> 'This is the right time to give the youngsters a chance in front of this crowd. We've made three changes. Bowling first is not a bad idea at all. The pitch is very similar to what we had in the last game. A total of 150-155 will be a good total to chase. Playing in home conditions and playing in Lahore is always special. The crowd in Lahore is actually great. The youngsters need to get used to playing in home conditions as well.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Chigumbura:</b> 'We are going to bat first. We're really happy with the conditions. We want to put up a good score and try to defend it. Our bowling in the first six overs wasn't that great and we want to change that in this game. Hopefully, we can do well this time around. Panyangara is injured and Mutumbami is also out.']]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pitch Report:</b> 'It's a brand new track but similar to the one used earlier. There's some grass but it's only there to bind the surface. Conditions will be tough for the bowlers and the batters should enjoy it. Win the toss and bat first,' reckons <b>Ramiz Raja</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Three changes for Pakistan - <b>Nauman Anwar</b> and <b>Imad Wasim</b> make their debut in place of Mohammad Hafeez and Wahab Riaz. <b>Mohammad Rizwan</b> gets a game at the expense of Sarfraz Ahmed. Zimbabwe too have made two changes - <b>Prosper Utseya</b> and <b>Chamu Chibhabha</b> replace Tinashe Panyangara and Richmond Mutumbami.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Zimbabwe</b> (Playing XI): Hamilton Masakadza, Vusi Sibanda, Charles Coventry(w), Elton Chigumbura(c), Sean Williams, Sikandar Raza, Graeme Cremer, Chamu Chibhabha, Chris Mpofu, Brian Vitori, Prosper Utseya]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan</b> (Playing XI): Mukhtar Ahmed, Ahmed Shehzad, Shoaib Malik, Umar Akmal, Shahid Afridi(c), Anwar Ali, Mohammad Rizwan(w), Bilawal Bhatti, Nauman Anwar, Mohammad Sami, Imad Wasim]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Zimbabwe have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Pakistan might have won the game, but it was the Pakistani fans, who turned out to be the real winners. Finally, their wish of witnessing an international cricket game came to fruition after a gap of 6 years. Despite heavy security, it was a full house at the Gaddafi. Zimbabwe too will be happy with the kind of support they received despite being the visiting team. We will have the toss and the teams in a short while from now. Stay tuned.]]></line><line><![CDATA[For Zimbabwe, their bowlers were clobbered all over the park in the initial few overs. Even though they pulled things back towards the end, they were always chasing the eight ball and rightfully, ended up on the losing side. For them, Hamilton Masakadza and captain Chigumbura's form were the few positives they could take out from their performance in the first game.]]></line><line><![CDATA[After posting a competitive 172 on the board, Zimbabwean bowlers failed to seize the advantage as Pakistani openers - Mukhtar Ahmed and Ahmed Shehzad, smacked them all over the park. Their 142-run opening stand was the cornerstone of their run-chase. Pakistan though will be skeptical about the performance of their middle order which suffered a mini-collapse during the final few overs. It was their captain, Shahid Afridi, who stayed calm and finished the game with a boundary off the first ball he faced.]]></line><line><![CDATA[After winning their first game on their return to home after a gap of 2271 days, Pakistan will now be hoping to take the winning momentum forward into this game. Hello and a very warm welcome to the second T20I between Pakistan and Zimbabwe. Zimbabwe were comprehensively beaten in the first game and they'll be looking to turn their fortunes around when they step out on the field at the Gaddafi Stadium.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview:</b><br/><br/>International cricket returned to Pakistan after a hiatus of six years and they did well to tick all the right boxes, be it on the field or off it. They would be hoping to carry forward the momentum gained from the five-wicket win in the first T20I against Zimbabwe, when the two teams lock horn once again for the second T20I at the Gaddafi stadium, Lahore on Sunday.<br/><br/>On paper, Zimbabwe are no match for the Asian giants, but Pakistan know very well that their fans all around the world are not just expecting a dominant effort against a weaker opponent throughout the series, but the goal is put forward a team performance that will help distance themselves from the tag of a 'mercurial' team.<br/><br/>Ahmed Shehzad and Mukhtar Ahmed stole the spotlight with the bat, but Pakistan would be hoping for a better effort from their bowlers. Elton Chigambura led from the front for the visitors and he will continue to be the key man for Zimbabwe.<br/><br/><b>Venue:</b> Gaddafi Stadium, Lahore<br/><b>Date:</b> May 24, 2015<br/><b>Time:</b> 19:00 IST<br/><b>Weather:</b> Sunny with maximum temperature expected to reach 45 degree Celsius<br/><br/><b>Team News:</b><br/><br/><b>Pakistan</b><br/><br/>After a good performance in the 1st T20I, it is highly unlikely that Pakistan will ring in any changes. The young players enjoyed the home conditions and even though comeback man Mohammad Sami proved to be expensive, he took three wickets that should ensure a place for him in the second T20I. Shoaib Malik, on the other hand, had a forgettable comeback with the bat, but did his bit with the ball and finished the game as the most economical bowler from either side. It will be interesting to see whether skipper Shahid Afridi will persist with Malik or will be tempted to give Hammad Azam a go.<br/><br/><b>Probable XI:</b> 1. Mukhtar Ahmed, 2. Ahmed Shehzad, 3. Mohammad Hafeez, 4. Shoaib Malik/Hammad Azam, 5. Umar Akmal, 6. Sarfraz Ahmed (wk), 7. Shahid Afridi (C), 8. Anwar Ali, 9. Bilawal Bhatti, 10. Mohammad Sami, 11. Wahab Riaz.<br/><br/><b>Zimbabwe</b><br/><br/>To their credit, Zimbabwe withstood a good bowling effort from Pakistan to notch up 172 thanks to Hamilton Masakadza and Chigambura, but their bowling effort lacked the edge and Pakistan were never really troubled in the chase. They let the home team score over 100 runs in the first 10 overs and if there is any change in the Zimbabwe playing XI it should be in the bowling department. Tawanda Mupariwa might replace Chris Mpofu, who had a forgettable day on Friday with figures of 3-0-32-0.<br/><br/><b>Probable XI:</b> Hamilton Masakadza, Vusi Sibanda, Charles Coventry (wk), Elton Chigambura (C), Sean Williams, Sikander Raza, Richmond Mutumbami, Graeme Cremer, Tinashe Panyangara, Chris Mpofu/Tawanda Mupariwa, Brian Vitori.<br/><br/><b>Stat:</b> Zimbabwe have lost all their six previous T20 encounters against Pakistan.<br/><br/><b>Quotes:</b> <br/><br/>"I know when you win all the lapses are covered over, but there were missed opportunities and I will ensure those will be dealt honestly." Pakistan coach <b>Waqar Younis</b> talking about lapses in the field.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pakistan</b> (From): Mukhtar Ahmed, Ahmed Shehzad, Mohammad Hafeez, Shoaib Malik, Umar Akmal, Sarfraz Ahmed(w), Shahid Afridi(c), Anwar Ali, Bilawal Bhatti, Wahab Riaz, Mohammad Sami, Mohammad Rizwan, Hammad Azam, Nauman Anwar, Imad Wasim]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Zimbabwe</b> (From): Hamilton Masakadza, Vusi Sibanda, Charles Coventry(w), Elton Chigumbura(c), Sean Williams, Sikandar Raza, Richmond Mutumbami, Graeme Cremer, Tinashe Panyangara, Chris Mpofu, Brian Vitori, Chamu Chibhabha, Craig Ervine, Roy Kaia, Tawanda Mupariwa, Prosper Utseya]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>175</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>3</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>20</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Zimbabwe">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>179</playerid>
					<name>Vusi Sibanda</name>
					<batsman-name>Sibanda</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sibanda</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>49</runs>
					<balls>46</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Afridi</bowler>
					<bowlerId>142</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Anwar Ali</fielder>
						<fielderId>1052</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>425</playerid>
					<name>Hamilton Masakadza</name>
					<batsman-name>H Masakadza</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>H Masakadza</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>39</runs>
					<balls>32</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>S Malik</bowler>
					<bowlerId>33</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Anwar Ali</fielder>
						<fielderId>1052</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>441</playerid>
					<name>Sean Williams</name>
					<batsman-name>Sean Williams</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sean Williams</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>58</runs>
					<balls>32</balls>
					<fours>7</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>170</playerid>
					<name>Elton Chigumbura</name>
					<batsman-name>Chigumbura</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chigumbura</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>21</runs>
					<balls>9</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>M Sami</bowler>
					<bowlerId>31</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Ahmed Shehzad</fielder>
						<fielderId>1787</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3460</playerid>
					<name>Charles Coventry</name>
					<batsman-name>C Coventry</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Charles Coventry</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9354</playerid>
					<name>Sikandar Raza</name>
					<batsman-name>S Raza</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>S Raza</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>278</playerid>
					<name>Graeme Cremer</name>
					<batsman-name>Cremer</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Cremer</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>436</playerid>
					<name>Chamu Chibhabha</name>
					<batsman-name>Chibhabha</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Chibhabha</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>428</playerid>
					<name>Chris Mpofu</name>
					<batsman-name>Mpofu</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mpofu</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8020</playerid>
					<name>Brian Vitori</name>
					<batsman-name>Vitori</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Vitori</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>181</playerid>
					<name>Prosper Utseya</name>
					<batsman-name>P Utseya</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Utseya</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>425</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>68</runs>
				<overs>8.3</overs>
				<batsman>Hamilton Masakadza</batsman>
				<batsman-name>H Masakadza</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>179</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>136</runs>
				<overs>16.4</overs>
				<batsman>Vusi Sibanda</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Sibanda</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>170</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>168</runs>
				<overs>19.1</overs>
				<batsman>Elton Chigumbura</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Chigumbura</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>2</wides>
			<noballs>2</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>6</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Pakistan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1052</playerid>
					<name>Anwar Ali</name>
					<bowler-name>A Ali</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Anwar Ali</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>31</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>31</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Sami</name>
					<bowler-name>M Sami</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sami</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>38</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8582</playerid>
					<name>Bilawal Bhatti</name>
					<bowler-name>B Bhatti</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bhatti</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>31</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10408</playerid>
					<name>Imad Wasim</name>
					<bowler-name>Imad Wasim</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Imad Wasim</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>14</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>142</playerid>
					<name>Shahid Afridi</name>
					<bowler-name>Afridi</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Afridi</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>33</playerid>
					<name>Shoaib Malik</name>
					<bowler-name>S Malik</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shoaib Malik</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>23</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10383</playerid>
					<name>Mukhtar Ahmed</name>
					<bowler-name>Mukhtar Ahmed</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mukhtar Ahmed</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1787</playerid>
					<name>Ahmed Shehzad</name>
					<bowler-name>Ahmed Shehzad</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ahmed Shehzad</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1992</playerid>
					<name>Umar Akmal</name>
					<bowler-name>U Akmal</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>U Akmal</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9468</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Rizwan</name>
					<bowler-name>M Rizwan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rizwan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10407</playerid>
					<name>Nauman Anwar</name>
					<bowler-name>Nauman Anwar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Nauman Anwar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>176</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>8</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>19.4</totalovers>
		<declared></declared>
		<followon></followon>
		<batteam name="Pakistan">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1787</playerid>
					<name>Ahmed Shehzad</name>
					<batsman-name>Ahmed Shehzad</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ahmed Shehzad</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>18</runs>
					<balls>17</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Vitori</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8020</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Vusi Sibanda</fielder>
						<fielderId>179</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10383</playerid>
					<name>Mukhtar Ahmed</name>
					<batsman-name>Mukhtar Ahmed</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mukhtar Ahmed</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>62</runs>
					<balls>40</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>S Raza</bowler>
					<bowlerId>9354</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Vusi Sibanda</fielder>
						<fielderId>179</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10407</playerid>
					<name>Nauman Anwar</name>
					<batsman-name>Nauman Anwar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Nauman Anwar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>18</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>P Utseya</bowler>
					<bowlerId>181</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Vusi Sibanda</fielder>
						<fielderId>179</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>33</playerid>
					<name>Shoaib Malik</name>
					<batsman-name>S Malik</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shoaib Malik</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>7</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Prosper Utseya</fielder>
						<fielderId>181</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1992</playerid>
					<name>Umar Akmal</name>
					<batsman-name>U Akmal</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>U Akmal</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>30</runs>
					<balls>21</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Mpofu</bowler>
					<bowlerId>428</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>142</playerid>
					<name>Shahid Afridi</name>
					<batsman-name>Afridi</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Afridi</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>7</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Sean Williams</bowler>
					<bowlerId>441</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sikandar Raza</fielder>
						<fielderId>9354</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9468</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Rizwan</name>
					<batsman-name>M Rizwan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rizwan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>6</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mpofu</bowler>
					<bowlerId>428</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Sikandar Raza</fielder>
						<fielderId>9354</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1052</playerid>
					<name>Anwar Ali</name>
					<batsman-name>A Ali</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Anwar Ali</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>2</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Sean Williams</bowler>
					<bowlerId>441</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>10408</playerid>
					<name>Imad Wasim</name>
					<batsman-name>Imad Wasim</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Imad Wasim</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8582</playerid>
					<name>Bilawal Bhatti</name>
					<batsman-name>B Bhatti</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bhatti</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>13</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>31</playerid>
					<name>Mohammad Sami</name>
					<batsman-name>M Sami</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sami</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler></bowler>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder></fielder>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2></fielder2>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3></fielder3>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1787</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>44</runs>
				<overs>4.5</overs>
				<batsman>Ahmed Shehzad</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Ahmed Shehzad</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>10407</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>81</runs>
				<overs>8.3</overs>
				<batsman>Nauman Anwar</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Nauman Anwar</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>33</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>95</runs>
				<overs>10.4</overs>
				<batsman>Shoaib Malik</batsman>
				<batsman-name>S Malik</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>10383</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>117</runs>
				<overs>13.3</overs>
				<batsman>Mukhtar Ahmed</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mukhtar Ahmed</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>142</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>130</runs>
				<overs>14.2</overs>
				<batsman>Shahid Afridi</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Afridi</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1992</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>152</runs>
				<overs>16.5</overs>
				<batsman>Umar Akmal</batsman>
				<batsman-name>U Akmal</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1052</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>155</runs>
				<overs>17.3</overs>
				<batsman>Anwar Ali</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Ali</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>9468</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>161</runs>
				<overs>18.2</overs>
				<batsman>Mohammad Rizwan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Rizwan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>2</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>4</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>9</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Zimbabwe">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>428</playerid>
					<name>Chris Mpofu</name>
					<bowler-name>Mpofu</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mpofu</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>25</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8020</playerid>
					<name>Brian Vitori</name>
					<bowler-name>Vitori</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Vitori</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3.4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>36</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>441</playerid>
					<name>Sean Williams</name>
					<bowler-name>Sean Williams</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sean Williams</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>32</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>181</playerid>
					<name>Prosper Utseya</name>
					<bowler-name>P Utseya</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Utseya</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>31</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>278</playerid>
					<name>Graeme Cremer</name>
					<bowler-name>Cremer</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Cremer</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>27</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>9354</playerid>
					<name>Sikandar Raza</name>
					<bowler-name>S Raza</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>S Raza</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>19</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>425</playerid>
					<name>Hamilton Masakadza</name>
					<bowler-name>H Masakadza</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>H Masakadza</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>179</playerid>
					<name>Vusi Sibanda</name>
					<bowler-name>Sibanda</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sibanda</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>3460</playerid>
					<name>Charles Coventry</name>
					<bowler-name>C Coventry</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Charles Coventry</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>170</playerid>
					<name>Elton Chigumbura</name>
					<bowler-name>Chigumbura</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chigumbura</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>436</playerid>
					<name>Chamu Chibhabha</name>
					<bowler-name>Chibhabha</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Chibhabha</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>



