<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="13848">
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>3rd Match</gameDesc>
		<series>India and England in Australia Tri-Series, 2015</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>England</home>
		<away>India</away>
		<teamsabbr>ENG vs IND</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>ENG</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>IND</awayabbr>
		<homeId>9</homeId>
		<awayId>2</awayId>
		<venue>Brisbane Cricket Ground, Woolloongabba,  Brisbane</venue>
		<startdate>20 01 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>20 01 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>India</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>England won by 9 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>England</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns/>
			<wonbywickets>9</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch/>
		<manofseries/>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Kumar Dharmasena</Name>
			<Country>SL</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Mick Martell</Name>
			<Country>Aus</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Simon Fry</Name>
			<Country>Aus</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Andy Pycroft</Name>
			<Country>Zim</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>03:20</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>false</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150120085519</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>Eng</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>Ind</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>156</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>1</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>27.3</batteamovers>
		<status>England won by 9 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>6500</playerid>
			<name>James Taylor*</name>
			<batsman-name>James Taylor</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>James Taylor</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>56</runs>
			<balls-faced>63</balls-faced>
			<fours>4</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>385</playerid>
			<name>Ian Bell</name>
			<batsman-name>Bell</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Bell</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>88</runs>
			<balls-faced>91</balls-faced>
			<fours>8</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>8808</playerid>
			<name>Axar Patel*</name>
			<bowler-name>A Patel</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>A Patel</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>7.3</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>32</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>7909</playerid>
			<name>Mohammed Shami</name>
			<bowler-name>Shami</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Shami</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>4</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>23</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>154</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>6692</playerid>
<name>Moeen Ali</name>
<player-runs>8</player-runs>
<player-balls>12</player-balls>
<runs>25</runs>
<wicket-nbr>1</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>1530</bowlerid>
<bowlername>Binny</bowlername>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>1</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>4</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[. . 2 1 1 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. 1 . . . Wd . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 1 . 1 1 . <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>. 1 4 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2015/2015_AUS_IND_ENG/ENG_IND_JAN20/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[Australia sit pretty at the top of the table with 9 points while England with this win go to second place with 5 points. India will now have to win both their games and will have to depend upon the result of the Australia-England game. Do join us for that match on Friday. Until then, take care and Adios!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Steven Finn</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his career best figures of 5/33.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Morgan</b>: "It was an outstanding performance. We have been putting up good individual performances in the last 12 months and Finn was exceptional today. He has worked hard for the past year. Jimmy (Anderson) was excellent with the ball, it is great to have him back. He has been doing this for a number of years now. Australia are a very strong side and have the momentum, but we must focus on our game."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Dhoni</b>: "I don't think we batted really well, especially after choosing to bat first. The wicket was two paced and we didn't get any partnerships going. The batsmen had to be more selective with their shots. We are losing wickets when we try to accelerate. Staying four and a half months away from home is difficult, but we have to switch on and switch off. It is very demanding, but we need to switch on and assess and spend more time in the nets, or wait in the hotel if the need be. It is a special day for both the nations and hopefully it will be entertaining for the crowd (on playing Australia on January 26th)."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Presentation time</b>:]]></line><line><![CDATA[India's batting looks a worry. The decision to send Kohli at No.4 has not worked as the batsman has failed to get going in both the matches played so far. The time is also ticking for Dhawan, who has still not got it right, on the tour. The only positive for India in today's game was Stuart Binny, the all-rounder contributed with both bat and ball and justified his selection. Apart from that, it was another poor outing for the Indians.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The match was set-up beautifully for England by Steven Finn and James Anderson. The latter was excellent with the new ball, he got it to shape both ways and bowled tight lines. Finn, on the other hand, generated extra bounce and made good use of a fast Gabba wicket, he got his <b>maiden ODI 5-fer</b>. Moeen Ali played the supporting role to perfection.]]></line><line><![CDATA[England cruise to a comfortable win, they also gain the <b>bonus point</b>. It is their biggest ODI victory in terms of balls left against India. Once India were bowled out for 153, they were always playing catch-up. Even though Moeen Ali went cheaply, Ian Bell and James Taylor ensured that England did not stutter in the run-chase. Both batsmen got to their fifties and were involved in a 131-run stand. Bell was exceptional in his stroke play and this knock should give him confidence after getting out for a first ball duck against Australia.]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to James Taylor, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>England romp home by 9 wickets</b>. Both batsmen shake hands and hug each other. It was tossed up on middle, Taylor kneels down and paddles it fine, beats the fielder in the deep comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, 1 run, flighted on the stumps, Bell presents the full face and drives it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, quicker and just outside off, Bell chops the cut to the slip fielder]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to James Taylor, no run, good length ball on off and middle, Taylor moves across and on-drives it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Bell, 1 run, back of a length outside off, punched off the back foot square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to James Taylor, 1 run, short and down leg, Taylor stays inside the line and pulls it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to James Taylor, no run, slower ball bumper, Taylor sways out of the way and lets it pass]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Bell, 1 run, banged in mid-way down the wicket, Bell pulls it in front of square, Binny does the mopping up in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to James Taylor, 1 run, pitched up outside off, Taylor eases the drive to sweeper cover for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Players take <b>drinks</b> with England needing only 7 runs to seal the win.]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, flighted on off, Bell presses it to cover after coming forward]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, <b>wide</b>, darted down the leg-side, Bell shows no interest in playing that, wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, nice loopy delivery, Bell drives and finds the fielder at mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, slower and on off, Bell defends it solidly off the front foot to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, slightly short and just outside off, Bell cuts it straight to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to James Taylor, 1 run, <b>3rd ODI fifty for Taylor</b>, another batsmen who failed in the first game scores a fifty. It was the arm-ball, Taylor plays for the turn and the ball squirts off the inside edge to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to James Taylor, no run, flighted on off, Taylor comes down the track and works it to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Axar Patel [6.0-0-25-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Bell, no run, back of a length close to off, Bell hangs back and pats it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to James Taylor, 1 run, banged in halfway down the wicket, Taylor forehands the pull in front of square for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Bell, 1 run, again, the length is short and plenty of width on offer, Bell slashes it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Bell, 2 runs, shortish and just outside off, Bell rides the bounce and punches it to deep backward point for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Bell, no run, back of a length close to off, Bell opens the bat face and guides it towards gully]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Bell, no run, short and just outside off, Bell can't connect with the pull, he was outdone by the extra bounce and pace]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Bell, 3 runs, half tracker outside off, Bell goes deep in the crease and cuts it behind point, Umesh gives chase and pulls the ball in just before the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to James Taylor, 1 run, pushed through on off, Taylor whips it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Bell, 1 run, waits for the quicker delivery and steers it to short third man for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Bell, no run, too full and on the stumps, Bell squeezes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to James Taylor, 1 run, tossed up on off, Taylor comes down the track and works it off the inside part to the right of mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Raina to Bell, 1 run, flatter and on off, Bell stays back and punches it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Bell, 1 run, too full, almost a yorker length delivery, Bell digs it out wide of cover and retains strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Bell, no run, fullish and on off, Bell goes hard on the drive, the ball dribbles off the inner half to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to James Taylor, 1 run, short of length on off, Taylor shuffles across and tucks it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Bell, 3 runs, good length ball just outside off, Bell plays another fluent drive on the up to deep extra cover, the batsmen come back for three before the ball is hunted down by Rayudu in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Bell, <b>wide</b>, another off-speed bouncer, Bell allows it to sail over his head, wided for height]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Bell, no run, fuller and around off, Bell presents the straightest of bats and drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to James Taylor, 1 run, starts with a slower ball bouncer, Taylor top-edges the pull to fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammed Shami [1.0-0-8-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, another late cut, but this time it is closer to Raina at slip, who dives to his right and fields the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, not all that short, Bell uses the depth of crease and mistimes the pull to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, flatter and on off, Bell goes back and blocks it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, <b>FOUR</b>, classy shot! It was deftly done by Bell. Allows the ball to come and almost plays it off Dhoni's gloves, uses the pace of the bowler and late cuts it to the third man fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to James Taylor, 1 run, quicker and just outside off, Taylor goes hard on the drive, places it wide of cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, 1 run, floated up around off, Bell eases the drive to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to James Taylor, no run, short delivery from Umesh, Taylor fetches it from outside off and pulls it towards mid-wicket, the ball lands just before Axar. He was just outside the ring and specifically placed for that shot]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to James Taylor, 2 runs, back of a length and width on offer, Taylor taps the ball on the head and runs it down to third man, it was very fine and that allowed the batsmen to complete the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, 3 runs, on a length just outside off, Bell drives it on the up without much feet movement to deep extra cover. Another three and England are cruising along nicely]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to James Taylor, 1 run, short and wide outside off, Taylor cuts and picks out the sweeper cover fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to James Taylor, 2 runs, pitched up outside off, Taylor leans forward and drives it to deep extra cover for another brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to James Taylor, 2 runs, another loose delivery, slower delivery well down leg, Taylor helps it down to fine leg, he got it off the toe-end hence only the two]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, again, the length is tad short and outside off, Bell cracks a cut to the right of backward point this time, Jinks dives and saves a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, <b>FOUR</b>, superb shot! He has been trying this shot for the past couple of overs and this time he has got it in the gap. Fraction short and outside off, Bell cuts it to the left of backward point, no point chasing those]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, slower and on off, Bell defends solidly off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, shortish and just outside off, Bell cuts and finds the backward point fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, <b>FOUR</b>, Bell showing his class now, Axar overcompensates and drops this one short, Bell was waiting for it on the back foot, he pulls it over mid-on and picks up a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, 2 runs, easily done, loopy delivery around off, Bell makes a bit of room and lofts it inside out wide of long-off, comes back for the second]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to James Taylor, no run, 142kph bouncer at the batsman, Taylor is not afraid to take it on, he goes for the hook and fails to make contact. Nice carry through to Dhoni as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to James Taylor, no run, short of length on off, Taylor hops up and drops it to the on-side, he wanted the single but Bell sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, 1 run, short and on leg-stump, Bell helps it down to fine leg with a pull, Shami does the tiding up in the deep]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to James Taylor, 1 run, sloppy from Dhawan, Taylor glides the off-speed delivery towards gully, Dhawan fumbles and allows England to bring up their <b>100</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to James Taylor, <b>FOUR</b>, cracking shot! Overpitched delivery outside off, Taylor leans into the drive and creams it past mid-off, Kohli didn't even bother chasing it]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to James Taylor, no run, full and curling into the batsman, Taylor wrists it to mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, another one that is quicker in speed, Bell backs away slightly and steers it off the stumps to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to James Taylor, 1 run, goes on with the angle, Taylor gets inside the line and works it wide of mid-wicket for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to James Taylor, no run, pushed through on the stumps, Taylor presents the full face and knocks it back to Axar]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, 1 run, flighted just outside off, Bell opens up and drives it to deep extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, quicker and on off, Bell eases the drive and finds Rayudu at short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, flatter and on off, Bell guides it to point with an open bat face]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, 3 runs, slower delivery on the stumps, Bell is deceived in the drive, checks his shot and sends it past the bowler, Binny chases the ball from mid-on and does well to slide and stop the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, no run, back of a length close to off, Bell steers it to gully, straight to the fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, no run, bumper on off, Bell sways his head out of the way and lets it go through to Dhoni]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, 2 runs, Bell brings up his <b>32nd ODI fifty</b>, it is his first after 9 innings. Slower delivery on the pads, tickled away fine for a couple. He raises his bat to the crowd and the dressing room. Nice comeback after a first ball duck in the previous game]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, no run, pitched up just outside off, Bell drives and picks out cover to perfection]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to James Taylor, 3 runs, Taylor still can't middle with the pull, Umesh bangs it in short and on off, Taylor rocks back and pulls it over mid-wicket, Axar gives chase and keeps it down to three. Once again Taylor was not in control of that shot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to James Taylor, 1 run, walks into the drive and gets it past extra cover for a comfortable single down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to James Taylor, no run, arm-ball on off, Taylor goes right back and bunts it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, 1 run, throws this up on off, Bell drives it crisply to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, tad short and outside off, Bell cracks the cut straight to Jinks at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to James Taylor, 1 run, flighted around off, Taylor push-drives it towards extra cover, Kohli dives and makes a half stop, can't stop the single though]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, 1 run, tossed up outside off, driven along the ground to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, 1 run, Bell stands tall and caresses the back of a length delivery square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, no run, slower delivery just outside off, Bell covers the line and allows it to go through]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, no run, dug in mid-way down the pitch, Bell swivels and fails to connect with the pull, is hit on the right bicep]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to James Taylor, 1 run, well directed short delivery, the ball gets big on the batsman, Taylor takes it on and top-edges the pull, the ball goes couple of bounces to the fine leg fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, 1 run, short of length around off, Bell runs it off the face of the bat wide of the slip fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, no run, back of a length on the hips, Bell tucks it towards square leg, calls "wait on" to Taylor for the single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav [2.0-0-15-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to James Taylor, no run, stifled appeal for lbw, but umpire Martell says not-out. It was the arm-ball that skids on, Taylor is hurried into the back foot defensive, is rapped on the pads but the ball was heading down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to James Taylor, no run, tossed up, but goes straight on, Taylor drives it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, 1 run, shortish and just outside off, Bell cuts it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, gives the charge, Axar pulls the length back, Bell pats it in front of cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, another nice crisp drive, straight to Kohli at extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, floated up outside off, Bell middles the drive and finds the extra cover fielder]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to James Taylor, no run, on a length in the channel around off, Taylor does not bother with it]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to James Taylor, <b>FOUR</b>, poor delivery from Binny, strays it well down leg, Taylor bends his front knee and helps it on the way to fine leg, the fielder was square and it was easy pickings for Taylor]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, 1 run, Kohli saved three runs there, half volley on middle, Bell leans forward and drills the drive towards mid-off, Kohli dives to his right and makes an excellent save]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to James Taylor, 1 run, shortish and just outside off, Taylor runs it down to third man with an angled bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to James Taylor, no run, back of a length on off, Taylor bunts it off the back foot to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, 1 run, dug in halfway down the wicket, the line is on leg-stump, Bell rolls his wrists and pulls it along the ground to fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to James Taylor, no run, drags the length back, Taylor shuffles across and blocks it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to James Taylor, no run, flighted just outside off, Taylor drives and picks out Kohli at extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to James Taylor, no run, flatter and close to off, Taylor punches it to towards cover-point, Rayudu makes a fine stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, 1 run, slower and on off, Bell kneels down and paddles it to long leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to Bell, no run, goes on with the angle from round the wicket, Bell drives off the inside part to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A Patel to James Taylor, 1 run, starts with a tossed up delivery, Taylor drives it past cover and down to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Axar Patel, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, no run, fuller and on the fourth stump, Bell plays a free flowing drive straight to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, no run, shortens the length around off, Bell goes back and across, taps it to in front of short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to James Taylor, 1 run, pitched up just outside off, Taylor presses forward and drives it to the left of mid-off, Kohli has a shy at the non-striker's end, hits and the ball deflects onto umpire Dharmasena, who was not quick enough to get out of the way]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to James Taylor, no run, goes wide of the crease, keeps it on a length and gets it to straighten, Taylor waits for it to swing and then defends it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to James Taylor, no run, back of a length and bit of extra bounce, Taylor jumps up, gets on top of it and taps it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to James Taylor, no run, short of length on off, Taylor stays in the crease and drops it in front of point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to James Taylor, 3 runs, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, Taylor presents the full face of the bat and drives it towards mid-on. Bhuvneshwar is sloppy on the slide and it nearly runs away to the ropes, the batsmen take three runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to James Taylor, <b>FOUR</b>, Shami drops one way too short! He doesn't have the field for such bowling, pulled away off the front foot, races past square leg and into the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to James Taylor, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, Taylor prods across and defends it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to James Taylor, no run, short and wide from Shami, Taylor cuts it straight to the fielder at backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Bell, 1 run, short of a length and on off, Bell works it in front of mid-on for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Shami to Bell, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Bell gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammed Shami, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to James Taylor, no run, fuller length delivery and just outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, 1 run, on a good length and on the stumps, worked in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>cracking shot</b>, width on offer from Binny, Bell gets on top of the bounce and cracks it square on the off-side, no need to run for those]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, no run, tad fuller and on off, Bell gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping away from off, driven towards extra cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Bell presses across and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to James Taylor, no run, that's a brilliant stop from Rahane at backward point, width on offer by Bhuvneshwar, Taylor cracked it behind point. Rahane threw himself to his left and saved a certain boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to James Taylor, 2 runs, short and wide from Bhuvneshwar, Taylor slaps it hard onto the turf, it bounces over point and there's another couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to James Taylor, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Taylor gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to James Taylor, 2 runs, fuller length delivery and well outside off, Taylor gets a good stride across and drives it past cover, back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to James Taylor, 2 runs, Bhuvneshwar bangs one short and well outside off, Taylor swivels across and pulls it over mid-wicket, he didn't get hold of the shot but good enough to get over mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to James Taylor, no run, fuller length delivery and shaping back in, Taylor covers the line and defends it towards mid-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Bhuvneshwar Kumar [1.0-0-12-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, 2 runs, on a good length and just outside off, Bell dabs it to the right of Raina at 2nd slip and set-off, there's a shy at the stumps at the striker's end, Binny can't back-up in time and an extra run is conceded]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, no run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, driven towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, <b>FOUR</b>, <b>lovely shot</b>, full and wide from Binny, looking for the swing, Bell leans into the drive and caresses it past extra cover, beats Kohli to the ropes even as he dived in vain]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, no run, Binny shortens his length outside off, Bell presses across and defends it back at the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to James Taylor, 1 run, tad fuller and shaping away from off, dabbed away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to James Taylor, no run, on a good length and on the stumps, Taylor shuffles across and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. Two slips in place as Binny continues..]]></line><line><![CDATA[That will be the <b>supper break</b>. Excellent start from England, although they lost Moeen, lobbing Binny to mid-off. The seaming all-rounder did his bit, but the other two specialist pacers were a big let-down. Bell is looking in ominous touch and England need just another 113 runs to complete a crushing victory. Can India spark something special? Join us in a while for the remainder of the chase..]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, no run, fuller length delivery and well outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to James Taylor, 3 runs, full and wide from Yadav, Taylor leans forward and drives it past Kohli at mid-off, he chases it down and keeps them down to three runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, 3 runs, and now, short and wide from Yadav, he's providing no control for his captain, width on offer, punched off the back-foot and past point, good enough for three runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, <b>FOUR</b>, that's a freebie from Yadav, leg-stump half-volley, on Bell's pads, whipped away behind square on the on-side for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, no run, back of a length and on the stumps, Bell presses across and defends it towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, no run, full and on off, Bell presents the full face of the bat as he punches it back at the bowler. Yadav does well to bend down and stops the ball]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to James Taylor, no run, fuller length delivery outside off and holding its line, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to James Taylor, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Taylor shuffles across and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to James Taylor, no run, full and a hint of shape away, Taylor covers for the movement and defends it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to James Taylor, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Taylor shuffles across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, 1 run, the slower ball from Binny, ends up drifting onto Bell's pads, clipped away towards long leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, no run, full and floaty from Binny, at 133 kmph, driven towards mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to James Taylor, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Taylor shuffles across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, 1 run, too straight from Yadav, nudged away behind square for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, 2 runs, short and on the stumps, Bell swivels across and pulls it in front of square on the on-side, back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, no run, fuller length delivery and holding its line outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, 2 runs, wrong line from Yadav, drifts this one onto Bell's pads, tucked past mid-wicket for a couple of runs]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;U Yadav to Bell, no run, that's a good start from Yadav, on a good length and in that channel outside off, draws Bell forward and whizzes past the outside edge, he was rooted to his crease there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>James Taylor, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Moeen Ali, <b>out</b> Caught by Kohli!! Binny has struck! This was pitched up and curls away slightly, Moeen went for the lofted off-drive, gets it right of the toe-end of the bat, gets a lot of height but not the distance. Kohli settles underneath and takes a well-judged catch at mid-off. First wicket for India, but they need nine more, and pretty quickly as well. It was actually the slower ball from Binny, rolled his fingers across the seam and fooled the batsman. <b>Moeen Ali c Kohli b Binny 8(12) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Binny to Moeen Ali, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Moeen Ali, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Moeen prods across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, 3 runs, back of a length and just outside off, Bell stays back and punches it in front of cover-point, more runs for the batsmen as two fielders give chase, back for the third run]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, 2 runs, Binny keeps it full and outside off, Bell goes through with the lofted shot, doesn't get hold but manages to beat mid-off comfortably]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, no run, fuller length delivery outside off and holding its line outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, <b>FOUR</b>, nicely played! This was pitched up and held its line outside off, punched to the left of Binny, he dives but can't get to the ball, beats mid-off and races away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Moeen Ali, <b>FOUR</b>, that's hammered away! Just short of ideal length, allows Moeen to rock back and pull it over mid-wicket for a boundary, 12 from Bhuvneshwar's first over]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Moeen Ali, no run, on a good length and around off, defended with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Moeen Ali, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Moeen stays back and defends it with a straight bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Moeen Ali, 2 runs, Bhuvneshwar hasn't started well, length ball and on Moeen's pads, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Bell, 1 run, too straight from Bhuvneshwar, ends up drifting onto Bell's pads, worked behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Bell, <b>FOUR</b>, nicely played by Bell, back of a length and well outside off, Bell stands tall and cracks it square on the off-side, beats Rahane at point and races away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Bhuvneshwar to Bell, <b>wide</b>, Bhuvneshwar starts with one well down leg-side, called as a wide]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Bhuvneshwar Kumar, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Moeen Ali, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Moeen gets half forward and defends it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Moeen Ali, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Moeen stays back and punches it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Moeen Ali, no run, on a good length and around off, Moeen shuffles across and defends it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Moeen Ali, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Moeen stays back and defends it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Moeen Ali, no run, much better from Binny, on a good length and just outside off, Moeen gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Moeen Ali, 2 runs, short of a length and well outside off, Moeen makes room and carves it over backward point, back for the second run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Free Hit</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Binny to Bell, <b>no ball</b>, 1 run, Binny has overstepped first ball, slids one onto Bell's pads, tucked behind square for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Bell and Moeen Ali are at the crease. Bell is on strike. Binny will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. Binny will open the bowling for India. He did so in the last two ODIs against Sri Lanka.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Things unravelled after India took the batting powerplay. Dhoni fell, gloving a pull to the keeper. Axar Patel fell first ball and left with the number 10, Binny played one shot too many and perished. On the bowling front, it was the Finn and Anderson show. The former took his first ODI fifer while the latter chipped in with  4 wickets. <b>Together, their figures read 16.3-2-51-9</b>. India have been bowled out with 63 balls unused. We will have a short break and be right back with the England chase..]]></line><line><![CDATA[Kohli fell in the same way as he had during the Test series, nicking off Finn. The bowler then had Rayudu, caught at the wicket, but before that Raina had danced down the track to Moeen and was comprehensively beaten. Dhoni and Binny steadied the innings, both played their shots, but were circumspect in equal measure as well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[A sensational performance from England's bowlers. They kept things tight right from the start, didn't give the batsmen much room to play their shots. Dhawan perished early, once again unable to combat the swing. Rahane and Rayudu scratched together a fifty run stand. Both didn't look convincing, but just when India seemed to have weathered the storm, Rahane threw his wicket away, mistiming a hoick to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Shami, <b>out</b> Caught by Moeen Ali!! <b>India have been bundled out for just 153</b>. Another superb catch in the deep from Moeen, length ball from Anderson, Shami made room and sent it sailing high and over mid-wicket. On an Indian ground, it would have been somewhere in the stands, but this is the Gabba. Moeen circles around it, takes it in front of the ropes, makes sure that he doesn't touch the ropes and completes a blinder. <b>Shami c Moeen Ali b J Anderson 1(7)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[J Anderson to Shami, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Umesh Yadav, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Binny, <b>out</b> Caught by Eoin Morgan!! That's a brilliant catch from Eoin Morgan, Binny came down the track to a scrambled seam delivery, was looking to go over mid-off, doesn't get hold of the shot, gets plenty of height. Morgan runs back from mid-off, keeps his eyes on it completely and takes a well judged catch even as he tumbled onto the ground. India lose their ninth wicket. <b>Binny c Eoin Morgan b J Anderson 44(55) [4s-3 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[J Anderson to Binny, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Binny, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Binny stays behind the line and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Binny, leg byes, 1 run, Buttler isn't happy again, he thinks Binny nicked this one as he went for the pull, but umpire Dharmasena correctly ruled that it went off the top of the helmet, Binny was looking to pull and missed, the ball looped behind the keeper off the helmet]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Binny, <b>wide</b>, short and well down leg-side, Binny looks to help it on its way and misses, Buttler threw the ball in the air and started celebrating, nothing on the bat or glove though]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Shami, 1 run, on a length and just outside off, dabbed towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Shami, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Shami shuffles across and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Binny, 1 run, short and wide from Finn, Binny opens the face of the bat at the last moment and runs it down towards third man, drops well in front of Moeen Ali]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Binny, no run, Finn comes back with a short and wide ball, Binny was making room for the cut and missed]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Binny, <b>SIX</b>, Binny has decided to play his shots, this is smashed into the long-on stands, makes room to a full ball, gets underneath the length, swings through the line and sends it sailing over the ropes]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Shami, no run, full and on Shami's pads, clipped to the left of mid-wicket where the fielder makes a smart stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Shami, no run, short and just outside off, no room for Shami to free his arms, looks to ramp it over the keeper and misses. Why would you try such a shot at this stage of the innings?]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Shami, no run, full and on the stumps, Shami defends it back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Shami, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Shami shuffles across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mohammed Shami, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Bhuvneshwar, <b>out</b> Bowled!! <b>Cleaned up!</b> India are falling away like nine pins! This was an exceptional piece of bowling though, Anderson got this one to nip back in from a length before straightening, Bhuvneshwar was playing for the one that came back into him, he ends up playing down the wrong line. The ball curls past the outside edge and rattles the off-pole. England are all over India like a rash, Binny stands forlorn at the other end. <b>Bhuvneshwar b J Anderson 5(5)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[J Anderson to Bhuvneshwar, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Bhuvneshwar, 2 runs, some lovely timing from Bhuvneshwar there, presents the full face of the bat to a full ball and eases it past mid-on for a brace]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[This is Finn's <b>maiden five-wicket haul</b> in ODIs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Binny, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Binny does well to ride with the bounce as he defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Binny, <b>no ball</b>, Finn knocks off the stumps as as he delivered that ball, called as a no-ball, Binny pressed across in defence]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Bhuvneshwar, 3 runs, short and wide from Finn, Bhuvneshwar gets on top of the bounce and cuts it over point, the timing wasn't great though, Binny wants a third, and might have been struggling against a better throw]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Bhuvneshwar, no run, fuller length delivery and on the stumps, Bhuvneshwar presses forward and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Bhuvneshwar, no run, not the ideal hat-trick ball, full and well outside off, left alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Bhuvneshwar Kumar, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Bhuvneshwar Kumar walks in with Finn on a <b>hat-trick</b>. Two slips in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to A Patel, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Second successive duck for Patel, <b>fifer for Finn</b>. India are in huge trouble now. Finn came from round the wicket and gets this one to nip back into Patel, he was half forward, doesn't cover for the movement, might have got a slight inside edge as well, the ball went on to hit the top of middle and leg. Can India bat out their 50 overs? <b>A Patel b Finn 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Finn to A Patel, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Axar Patel, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Dhoni, <b>out</b> Caught by Buttler!! Dhoni is walking! The dropped chance doesn't cost England anything. This was banged in short and on the stumps, Dhoni shuffled across on the pull, just about feathers a glove through to the keeper. Buttler throws the ball in the air once again, but this time the umpire didn't need to make a decision. Dhoni walked away disconsolately. The stand has been broken, India are now down and in tatters. Fourth wicket for Finn. <b>Dhoni c Buttler b Finn 34(61) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Finn to Dhoni, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Dhoni, 1 run, Anderson drifts one onto Dhoni's pads, clipped away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Dhoni, no run, Anderson shortens his length around off, Dhoni shuffles across and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Dhoni, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Dhoni gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Dhoni, no run, width on offer from Anderson, Dhoni cuts but finds the man at point]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Dhoni, no run, short of a length and just outside off, Dhoni stays back and cracks it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Dhoni, no run, that will go down as a <b>dropped chance</b>, Anderson is the culprit, the ball didn't stick, but could Anderson have put in a better effort? On a good length and just outside off, Dhoni was early on the drive and scoops it to the left of the bowler, he sticks his left hand out and drops a clanger]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>James Anderson [6.0-2-15-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Binny, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Binny stays on the front foot and slaps it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Binny, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Binny plays with an open face as he guides it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Dhoni, 1 run, on a good length and on Dhoni's pads, he tucked it in front of square leg and calls Binny for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Dhoni, no run, fuller length delivery and in that channel outside off, Dhoni pushes lamely at that and is beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Dhoni, no run, back of a length and on the stumps, Dhoni moves across his stumps and defends it towards square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Dhoni, no run, short of a length and just outside off, defended towards the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Steven Finn [5.0-0-19-3] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[India have decided to take the <b>batting PP</b>, one over before it was due..]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now. A decent comeback for India this, Dhoni and Binny are taking some sort of control back after India were reduced to 67/5, still plenty of work ahead though]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, no run, Binny comes down the track to a well flighted delivery and smothers the spin as he eases it towards the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, <b>SIX</b>, <b>massive</b>, Binny is settling into his groove here, comes down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and lofts it back over the bowler's head, clears the ropes with ease and goes as far as 10 rows back into the stands]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, 1 run, Moeen Ali drifts one onto Dhoni's pads, clipped away behind square on the on-side for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, no run, flighted and just outside off, pushed towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, 1 run, tossed up and on off, Binny goes back and punches it towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[Dhoni has changed his bat, this one looks like it has a lot more wood on it]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, 1 run, flatter and on Dhoni's pads, clipped away behind square for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Binny, no run, on a good length and on the stumps, Binny pushed it in front of mid-on and set-off, Dhoni is quick to send him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Dhoni, 1 run, too straight from Woakes, worked away behind square on the on-side for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Dhoni, 2 runs, Woakes loses his line and drifts this one full and on Dhoni's pads, flicked away to the right of mid-on for a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Dhoni, 2 runs, Dhoni is good on anything short, this was banged in short and on the stumps, Dhoni swivels across, rolls his wrists and pulls it past Morgan at square leg, back for the second]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Binny, 1 run, back of a length and on Binny's hips, tucked away behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Binny, no run, Buttler goes up again, but there's no nick on this one either, Binny made room for the cut and missed by a long way. Buttler threw the ball up as soon as he took it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, no run, loud shout for <b>caught behind</b>, but it's not all that convincing, this was dropped short and just outside off, Dhoni made room for the cut, there wasn't any noise on that, the players go up, but the umpire's finger stays down]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, no run, Moeen drifts one wider outside off, driven back towards the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, 2 runs, that's excellent running from Dhoni, nudges a well tossed up ball behind square, runs hard and gets back for the second run]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, no run, tossed up and on off, Dhoni goes back and blocks]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, 1 run, flighted and on middle, Binny comes down the track and works it past square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, 2 runs, that's good batting from Binny, comes down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball, plays with the spin and lofts it over mid-wicket for a couple of runs]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Binny, 1 run, back of a length and on the stumps, Binny shuffles across and works it in front of square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Dhoni, 1 run, too straight from Woakes, worked away towards long-leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Dhoni, no run, length ball on Dhoni's pads, he turns it behind square on the on-side, there's a man there at backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Dhoni, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Dhoni stays back and pushes it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Dhoni, no run, tad fuller and just outside off, Dhoni shuffles across and defends it towards the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[Still no slips for Woakes]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Dhoni, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Dhoni gets behind the line and defends it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, 1 run, works it to long-on for a comfortable single]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, 1 run, turning in on middle and leg, Binny taps it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, no run, shortish and outside off, Binny cuts it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, 1 run, drifts it on leg, Dhoni lunges on the front foot and turns it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, no run, moves inside the line and works it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, no run, gets forward and defends it back]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Binny, no run, short of length on off, Binny punches it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Binny, <b>wide</b>, short on the stumps, Binny ducks, that was going well over the batsman]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Binny, <b>FOUR</b>, another lucky four! Woakes continues to bowl short, Binny rocks back and pulls, the ball takes the top-edge and flies to the fine leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Binny, no run, defends it off the back foot to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Binny, <b>FOUR</b>, lucky boundary for Binny! It was a shortish one from Woakes, the extra bounce pushes Binny inside the crease, he looks to defend off the back foot, the ball takes the outside edge and flies through the vacant slip cordon to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Binny, <b>FOUR</b>, Binny has thumped this into the off-side! He charges down the track and hammers this full delivery to the long-off fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Dhoni, 1 run, back of a length around off, Dhoni bunts it to short cover, where Ian Bell fires a direct hit at the non-striker's end, Binny is in, but the ball rolls into the leg-side after deflecting off the stumps and the batsmen take a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Woakes [4.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, 1 run, goes on the back foot and punches it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, 1 run, turning in on middle and leg, Binny works it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, no run, steps out of the crease and pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, no run, around leg, Binny leans forward and tucks towards leg slip]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, no run, turning in on leg, Binny turns it off the pads to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, no run, shortish on middle and leg, Binny gets inside the line and blocks with a straight bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Binny, 1 run, short from Broad again, Binny swivels back and mistimes the pull to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Binny, no run, gets behind the line and blocks it solidly down the pitch]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Dhoni, 1 run, dug in short by Broad, extra bounce on that one, Dhoni gets back and looks to pull, the ball goes off the glove to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Dhoni, no run, short of length and outside off, Dhoni flays it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Dhoni, no run, shortish on off, Dhoni hops inside the crease and tucks it behind square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Binny, 1 run, back of a length and outside off, Binny opens the face of his bat and helps it to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, no run, flighted and just outside off, Dhoni gets forward and defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, 1 run, comes down the track and taps it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, no run, leans on the front foot and defends it down the pitch]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, no run, full on off, Binny comes on the front foot and turns it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, 1 run, gets back to this shortish ball and punches it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, no run, flighted around off, Dhoni presses on the front foot and turns it off the inside half of the bat to short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Binny, 2 runs, back of a length on middle and leg, Binny punches it with a straight bat to long-on for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Binny, no run, banged in short on the stumps, Binny ducks underneath]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Dhoni, 3 runs, short of length and outside off, Dhoni punches it off the back foot to sweeper cover, Morgan gives the ball a chase, slides and drags it back in front of the rope]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Dhoni, no run, probing line outside off, this time Dhoni watches it closely and lets that go through]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Dhoni, no run, touch back of a length around off, Dhoni punches it in front of point]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Dhoni, no run, lovely delivery from Broad, draws Dhoni on the front foot, who looks to drive into the off-side, the ball shapes away and he is beaten neck and crop]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, 1 run, lunges forward on this flighted ball and pats it to cover-point for a brisk single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, no run, comes forward and turns it into the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, no run, tossed up outside off, Dhoni presses forward and drives it straight to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, 1 run, drifts it on leg, Binny gets down on one knee and sweeps it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, 1 run, moves across and taps it to long-on for a comfortable single]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, no run, flighted on off, Dhoni gets forward and drives it to the left of the bowler, who moves across and fields it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Binny, no run, back of a length on middle, Binny shuffles across and tucks it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Binny, no run, length delivery on off, Binny blocks it solidly off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Binny, no run, back of a length and outside off, Binny guides it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Binny, no run, defends a good length ball back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Binny, no run, good length ball outside off, Binny pushes it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Dhoni, 1 run, back of a length around off, Dhoni punches it off the bottom of the bat towards short cover, Broad picks up the delivery and fires a wayward throw towards the leg-side, allows the batsmen to run a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Stuart Broad [4.0-0-24-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Broad comes back into the attack, replacing Finn.]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, 1 run, pushed through around off, Dhoni presses on the front foot and dabs it to point for a brisk run]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, 1 run, uses his feet to step out of the crease and works it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, no run, flighted around off, Binny lunges forward and turns it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, 1 run, touch shortish on off, Dhoni gets back and flat-bats it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, 1 run, gets forward and taps it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip and leg slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, no run, turning around leg, Binny moves inside the line and looks to turn it into the leg-side, misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Binny, 1 run, back of a length around off, Binny shuffles across and tucks it through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Binny, no run, back of a length around off, Binny bunts it just in front of point]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Dhoni, 1 run, shortish one, Dhoni shuffles across and turns it with soft hands to square leg for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Dhoni, no run, full one from Finn again, Dhoni works it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Dhoni, <b>FOUR</b>, beautiful shot from Dhoni! It was a half-volley from Finn outside off, Dhoni gets forward, opens the face of his bat and drives it to the deep point fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Binny, 1 run, fuller delivery on middle, Binny leans forward and turns it to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, no run, comes on the front foot and defends it into the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, 1 run, 'catch it' is the call but the fielder does not get to it, Binny looks to clip this ball drifted on leg, gets an inside edge towards short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, no run, gets forward and turns it in front of square on the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Binny, no run, flighted on middle and off, Binny works it into the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, 1 run, drifts it on middle and leg, Dhoni clips it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, no run, tossed up on middle, Dhoni works it towards short mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Stuart Binny, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Rayudu, <b>out</b> Caught by Buttler!! Just when you thought Rayudu was getting comfortable at the crease, he has thrown it away. Third scalp for Finn and another victim of the extra bounce. It was a shortish one outside off, Rayudu stands tall and looks to guide this rising delivery, the ball goes off the toe-end of the bat and an easy catch for Buttler, who moved slightly to his left behind the stumps. <b>Rayudu c Buttler b Finn 23(53) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Finn to Rayudu, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Rayudu, no run, gets behind the line once again and defends it towards short cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Rayudu, no run, short of length on off, Rayudu defends it back, Finn gets forward and fields it]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Rayudu, no run, gets behind this back of a length delivery around off and defends with an angled bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Rayudu, no run, back of a length delivery on middle, Rayudu goes back and works it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Dhoni, 1 run, shortish one on the hips, extra bounce on that one, Dhoni looks to tuck, the ball takes the glove instead and rolls to short fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, 1 run, tucks it to square leg and gets off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, no run, another one on leg, Dhoni goes on the back foot and clips it just in front of square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, no run, on leg again, Dhoni is pushed inside the line and he turns it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Dhoni, no run, flighted on leg, Dhoni gets forward and pushes it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>MS Dhoni, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Raina, <b>out</b> Stumped!! Oh dear! India are crumbling here like a pack of cards. Raina navigated them out of troubled waters in the last match but has been beaten quite comprehensively here. Turn and bounce for Moeen Ali. Raina comes down the track even before the ball is bowled, misses it completely as it spins away into Buttler's gloves, who flicks off the bails in an instant. Raina was well out of his crease and had no chance of getting back in time. <b>Raina st Buttler b Moeen Ali 1(3)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Moeen Ali to Raina, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Stumped!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Moeen Ali to Raina, no run, flighted delivery on middle and off, Raina defends it off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Moeen Ali, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[India in trouble like the previous game. They were 59/3 against Australia.]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Rayudu, no run, touch fuller length on the pads, Rayudu tucks it behind square]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Raina, 1 run, on a length on off, Raina looks to defend off the back foot, the ball goes off the outside edge to third man for a streaky single]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Suresh Raina, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Kohli, <b>out</b> Caught by Buttler!! Kohli perishes even before he could face Anderson! The extra bounce has undone him, he walks away disappointed. The Indian supporters have gone quiet. Kohli goes chasing after this widish delivery, looks to guide this towards third man, gets a thickish outside edge and the ball travels safely into Buttler's gloves. <b>Kohli c Buttler b Finn 4(8)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Finn to Kohli, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Kohli, no run, continues to keep the length a touch short, Kohli blocks it with a straightish bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Kohli, no run, short of length on middle and off, Kohli goes on the back foot and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Kohli, no run, touch back of a length on middle and off, Kohli blocks it down the track with an angled bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Kohli, 1 run, shuffles across and clips this back of a length delivery towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Kohli, no run, length delivery around off, Kohli gets forward and defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Kohli, 2 runs, shortish and outside off, Kohli stands on his toes, reaches out and steers it uppishly to square third man, that did not come off the middle but he gets a couple]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Rayudu, 1 run, short of length and outside off, Rayudu opens the bat face and runs it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Kohli, 1 run, back of a length and angling in on middle and leg, Kohli works it to mid-wicket and gets off the mark straightaway]]></line><line><![CDATA[Another poor start for India, another top-order wobble. The batsmen look quite unsure and have not been confident with their shots. Kohli, who missed out in the previous game, will want to get some runs here. His real test will come against Anderson.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Some problems here with Rayudu. He has taken his left shoe off and is pointing towards his toe. He looks in pain. Has he twisted it while running? The physio comes out to attend to him and the umpires have decided to take <b>drinks</b> as well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Rayudu, 1 run, Woakes sees Rayudu charging forward and drags the length short, the batsman ends up whacking it to mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Woakes [3.0-0-7-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Rayudu, 1 run, short of length and outside off, Rayudu steers it with an open bat face to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Rayudu, no run, back of a length around off, Rayudu stays back and pats it towards the covers region]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Rayudu, no run, length delivery on middle and off, Rayudu pushes it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Virat Kohli, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Kohli is in at number 4. What can he do?]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Rahane, <b>out</b> Caught by James Taylor!! Very very poor from Rahane! This is the fifth time Rahane has got out to Finn. The extra bounce gets the better of him this time too like the previous game. He charges down the track and looks to heave this short ball, it hits him high on the bat and the ball shoots up towards mid-on, where Taylor takes a well judged catch running backwards. <b>Rahane c James Taylor b Finn 33(40) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Finn to Rahane, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Rayudu, 1 run, short of length and coming back into the batsman from outside off, Rayudu bunts it to gully for a brisk single]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Rayudu, no run, touch back of a length around off, Rayudu stays back and dabs it behind point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rayudu, 1 run, short of length and wide of off, Rayudu opens the face of his bat and helps it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rahane, 1 run, back of a length around off, Rahane bunts it to cover-point and sets off immediately, excellent running between the wickets]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rayudu, 1 run, good length delivery on middle, Rayudu drives it off the inside half of the bat to mid-on for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rayudu, no run, angled in on middle and leg, Rayudu moves inside the line and turns it in front of square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rayudu, no run, stays on the back foot this time and defends solidly with an angled bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rayudu, no run, length delivery on middle and off, Rayudu blocks it off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Rayudu, 1 run, back of a length on the pads, Rayudu glances it towards backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Rayudu, <b>FOUR</b>, nicely done by Rayudu! He shimmies down the track, reaches out to this widish delivery and flays it to the long-off fence, excellent timing from the young man. Brings up the 50 for India]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Rahane, 1 run, touch back of a length and outside off, Rahane flays it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Rayudu, 1 run, shuffles across and clips this length ball towards fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Rahane, 1 run, on the hips this time, Rahane neatly wrists it through backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Finn to Rahane, no run, back of a length on middle and leg, bit of a bounce there, Rahane tucks it and the ball drops on the wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Steven Finn, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Finn into the attack.]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rayudu, no run, good length ball just outside off, Rayudu looks to drive off the front foot and is beaten as the ball moves away]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rayudu, 2 runs, dug in short outside off, Rayudu shuffles across and drags the pull to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rayudu, no run, good length delivery on off, Rayudu comes on the front foot and drives it towards the bowler, who stops it with his boot]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rayudu, no run, shortish one outside off, Rayudu shuffles across and mistimes the pull towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rahane, 1 run, short of length and outside off, Rahane runs it down to third man with an open bat face]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rahane, 2 runs, on middle and leg, Rahane leans forward and clips it off the pads to deep backward square leg for a brace]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, no run, short ball from Anderson, Rayudu walks forward but doesn't go through with the shot, the ball beats the outside edge of his bat and goes through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, no run, in the channel outside off, Rayudu covers the line and leaves it alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rahane, 1 run, shortish one, Rahane moves across and hacks it towards deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rahane, no run, back of a length and coming back into the batsman a touch, Rahane defends it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, 1 run, shuffles across and works this length delivery towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, 2 runs, back of a length and outside off, Rayudu opens the face of his bat and runs it down towards third man, the ball just went past second slip]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rahane, no run, good length ball around off, Rahane pushes it just in front of point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rahane, <b>FOUR</b>, a streaky boundary for Rahane this time, he was drawn on the front foot by Broad with this full delivery outside off, Rahane drives at it, gets a thick outside edge that sails past slips to the third man fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rahane, no run, length delivery around off, Rahane gets forward and bunts it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rahane, <b>SIX</b>, fantastic shot! It was a short one from Broad on middle and leg, Rahane short-arm pulls it over the deep mid-wicket fence for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rahane, no run, stays back and defends this back of a length delivery around off into the covers region]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rayudu, 1 run, leg bye, looks to tuck into the on-side, the ball goes off the pads behind square]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Unsteady start for India. They have already lost Dhawan and attempting to play some wild shots here. They need to be more careful.]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, 1 run, keeps the length short, wide of off, Rayudu knocks it to cover for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, no run, back of a length and outside off, Rayudu backs away and guides it towards the slip cordon]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, no run, fuller one on off, Rayudu comes on the front foot and drives it hard, finds the fielder at mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, no run, on middle and leg, Rayudu defends it off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, no run, short of length and outside off, Rayudu flashes it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, no run, shortish and outside off, Rayudu goes chasing after it after coming down the track, flays at it and is beaten comprehensively]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rahane, no run, gets forward on this good length ball and taps it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rahane, 2 runs, length delivery just outside off, no feet movement from Rahane, mistimes the lofted drive wide of mid-off for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rahane, no run, fuller and coming back into the batsman from outside off, Rahane pushes it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rahane, 2 runs, Rahane gets forward and looks to drives this fuller length delivery into the off-side, gets a thick inside edge and the ball goes past the stumps to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rahane, no run, back of a length delivery on middle, Rahane tucks this into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Broad to Rahane, 2 runs, mistimed shot from Rahane but he gets a couple for it. It was a good length ball just outside off, Rahane gets forward and lofts it to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Stuart Broad, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Broad replaces Woakes. A slip and gully in place for him...]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, <b>FOUR</b>, short one this time, Rayudu swivels on the back foot and muscles the pull to the deep square leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, no run, this time Rayudu shimmies down the track a bit and flays at this back of a length delivery, the ball takes the bottom edge and crashes into the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rahane, 3 runs, short of length and wide of off from Anderson, Rahane gets back, makes a bit of room and punches it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rahane, 2 runs, flicks it off the pads to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rahane, no run, what was Rahane doing there? You cannot take on Jimmy Anderson like that! He comes down the track and looks to go big, the ball shapes back in, gets an inside edge onto the pads and the ball rolls behind towards the slips]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rahane, no run, touch back of a length around off, Rahane is half-forward and he defends it into the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Rayudu, no run, short of length and coming back into the batsman from outside off, Rayudu hops inside the crease because of the bounce and knocks it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Rayudu, no run, back of length ball around off, Rayudu defends it watchfully into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Rayudu, no run, good length ball on off, Rayudu presses forward and defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Rayudu, no run, Rayudu takes his bottom hand off the bat and mistimes the drive on this length delivery towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Rahane, 1 run, short of length and outside off, Rahane gets forward and drives at it, gets a thick outside edge that flies uppishly towards third man, he was lucky there was no gully there]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Rahane, no run, in the channel outside off, Rahane shoulders arms to it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, no run, <b>beaten neck and crop</b>, short of length and outside off, no feet movement from Rayudu as he looks to flash at it, the ball sails past the outside edge]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, no run, length ball around off, Rayudu shimmies down the track and punches it softly towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, no run, touch short of length and shaping back in from outside off, Rayudu lets that go through]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, no run, back of a length and coming back into the batsman, Rayudu defends it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, no run, length delivery just moving away a touch, Rayudu watches it closely and lets it go through]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, <b>wide</b>, slides it down leg, that was well over the batsman as well, wided by the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rahane, leg byes, 1 run, around leg, Rahane looks to tuck, the ball goes off the pads behind square]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Rahane, 1 run, keeps the length short and around off, Rahane dabs it behind point for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Rahane, no run, back of a length delivery on middle and off, Rahane defends it towards mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Rahane, no run, shortish one on the hips, a bit of extra bounce from Woakes, Rahane tucks it in front of square on the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Rayudu, 1 run, length delivery outside off, Rayudu backs away and guides it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Rahane, 1 run, fullish one on leg, Rahane leans forward and flicks it off the pads to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Rahane, 2 runs, overpitched by Woakes on off, Rahane comes on the front foot and drives it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Rayudu has come in at number three instead of Kohli. Remember, Kohli did not come at number three in the first game, either. He might bat at number 4 at the World Cup, perhaps.]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, no run, stays inside the line and bunts it in front of point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, no run, lovely delivery, Anderson is a master of swing! It was a back of a length one, shapes away just a touch, Rayudu prods at it with laden feet and the ball just about beats the outside edge of his bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, no run, short of length and around off, Rayudu stays back and dabs it towards point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, no run, comes on the front foot and pushes this back of a length delivery into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rayudu, no run, in the channel outside off, left alone by Rayudu]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ambati Rayudu, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Dhawan, <b>out</b> Caught by Buttler!! Anderson strikes and it is yet another failure for Dhawan! It was a good length delivery this time, angling across the left-hander, Dhawan listlessly pokes his bat at it, the ball takes the thick outside edge and goes through to the keeper. Beautiful delivery. He just invited Dhawan forward and the batsman ended nicking it off. <b>Dhawan c Buttler b J Anderson 1(5)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[J Anderson to Dhawan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Rahane, no run, back of a length on off, Rahane blocks it off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Rahane, no run, teasing line outside off, Rahane just presses in front and lets that go through]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Dhawan, 1 run, angled in on the hips, Dhawan deftly tucks it towards square leg and sets off for a brisk single]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Dhawan, no run, back of a length on middle and off, Dhawan pushes it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Dhawan, no run, touch shortish on leg, Dhawan is a tad surprised by the bounce, takes his bottom hand off the bat as the ball goes off the gloves in front of square on the leg-side, wants a single but decides to turn back]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Woakes to Dhawan, no run, back of a length on middle and off, Dhawan presses forward and defends it with an angled bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Chris Woakes, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Decent first over from Anderson. Woakes will be sharing the new ball with him. Two slips in place for him as well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rahane, no run, back of a length and just outside off, Rahane bunts it to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rahane, no run, a little bit of swing on offer, in the channel outside off, Rahane covers the sticks and shoulders arms to it]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rahane, no run, short of length on middle and off, Rahane defends it off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rahane, no run, coming back into the batsman, angling on the pads, Rahane presents the full face of the bat and blocks it back]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rahane, no run, back of a length again and width on offer, Rahane reaches out and knocks it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Anderson to Rahane, no run, short of length delivery to start off from Anderson, Rahane stands tall inside the line and flashes it behind point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rahane and Dhawan are at the crease. Rahane is on strike. J Anderson will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Indian openers are walking out to the middle. Dhawan and Rahane will be opening. The England players are taking their positions. Anderson will start proceedings with the new ball. Two slips to assist him. Here we go...]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>India</b> (Playing XI): Shikhar Dhawan, Ajinkya Rahane, Virat Kohli, Ambati Rayudu, Suresh Raina, MS Dhoni(w/c), Stuart Binny, Axar Patel, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Mohammed Shami, Umesh Yadav]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>England</b> (Playing XI): Ian Bell, Moeen Ali, James Taylor, Joe Root, Eoin Morgan(c), Ravi Bopara, Jos Buttler(w), Chris Woakes, Stuart Broad, James Anderson, Steven Finn]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Eoin Morgan:</b> "We would have batted as well. But we are not too worried. We will look to bowl well against them. <b>Anderson comes back</b>. He will be replacing Chris Jordan. The last game hurt us. Our start was not good but we managed to pull things back later. However, it was not enough. I have full confidence in the boys."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>MS Dhoni:</b> "We will bat first. It looks like a good wicket. There will be bounce for the fast bowlers and once we negotiate the new ball, it will be better. We have to get a win in this format. The last game was not too good for us but we have taken plenty of positives from it. We performed well in patches. We bowled well in the last few overs. We have made a couple of changes. <b>Rohit has a sore hamstring, Rayudu will come in his place. Binny comes in for Ashwin</b>."]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>India have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Pitch Report:</b> "It is a rock hard pitch. There will be a fair bit of bounce. The fast bowlers will enjoy bowling here but they need to get their lengths right. The nature of the pitch won't change much over the 7-hour period of play. There will be a lot of carry. But once you get set, it will be a very good track to bat on," reckon Sunil Gavaskar and Wasim Akram.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The weather in Brisbane has been erratic for the last couple of days. It was pouring last night and there is a fair bit of rain on the radar today. However, the good news is that it is sunny right now. There might be a few showers later but let's hope we get a full game. Toss and teams coming up in a few minutes. Don't go anywhere...]]></line><line><![CDATA[Meanwhile, for England it has been the same old story. A change in captain has done nothing to bring about a change in fortune for them. Their batting inconsistency has troubled them the most. Although skipper Eoin Morgan navigated them out of a tough situation, a below par total on the board was never going to stand chance against Australia's formidable batting line-up. Their bowling has been better in comparison but not too threatening. With James Anderson's return to the fold, after he missed the Sydeny game due to an injury, England might fancy their chances this time around.]]></line><line><![CDATA[One of the major problems that has troubled India repeatedly over the last few months is their bowling and their first game was no different. Except Bhuvneshwar Kumar, wayward line and lengths from the other bowlers ensured that Australia cruised in the middle overs. A spirited performance towards the end however, changed things drastically and it required James Faulkner's usual brilliance to haul the hosts over the finish line.]]></line><line><![CDATA[India's opening encounter against Australia in the tri-series was a competitive one. After days of being ridiculed for their Test performance, the duo of Rohit Sharma and Suresh Raina, showed just why they can compete with the likes of Virat Kohli in the shorter format of the game. Rohit's well-compiled century and Raina's resilience pushed India past the 250-mark after they were reduced to 59/3 at one stage. However, that was not enough.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview</b><br/><br/>India and England lost their opening games to Australia but the manner of their defeats sent out different signals. With both bat and ball, England were poor in Sydney while India had some positives to take from their defeat in Melbourne on Sunday. With the teams locking horns in Australia for the first time in 22 years, India will be aiming to register their first win on tour, knowing that England have won just three of their last 10 ODIs and are low on confidence. England need a turnaround desperately but that will not be easy against an Indian team that fought hard against Australia.<br/><br/><b>Team News</b><br/><br/><b>India</b><br/><br/>Rohit Sharma gave India 138 reasons to smile with his performance against Australia in Melbourne and his touch augurs well for the team. However, the same cannot be said about Shikhar Dhawan, who departed in the first over. The left-hander's lack of form is a source of real worry and his continued failures challenge the team. There have been calls for Ajinkya Rahane to step up as opener and it will be interesting to see if MS Dhoni decides to go with that in Brisbane.<br/><br/>The Indian bowlers came into their own with a spirited display towards the end of the opening match. Umesh Yadav, who strayed with the new ball, came back and bowled with pace and hostility. Bhuvneshwar Kumar held things up nicely until he went for 16 runs in what turned out to be the final over of the match. Mohammed Shami is under a cloud after walking off the MCG pitch with a fitness problem. Mohit Sharma or Dhawal Kulkarni could take his place if he is ruled unfit.<br/><br/><b>Probable XI</b><br/><br/>1. Rohit Sharma, 2. Shikhar Dhawan, 3. Ajinkya Rahane, 4. Virat Kohli, 5. Suresh Raina, 6. MS Dhoni (c and wk), 7. Axar Patel, 8. R Ashwin, 9. Bhuvneshwar Kumar, 10. Umesh Yadav, 11. Mohammed Shami/Mohit Sharma<br/><br/><b>England</b><br/><br/>There seems to be no end to England's woes in ODIs. They lost three successive ODI series and were out of depth in Sydney. The inconsistency at the top is a major source of worry. Only four batsmen average over 30, with Joe Root the only one with an average of over 40. Ian Bell averages 24 in the last 10 matches and his struggles have highlighted England's plight. Eoin Morgan's century against Australia held the middle-order together but he lacked support. England's batting must function as a unit if they are to change their fortunes.<br/><br/>England will welcome James Anderson back after he missed Sydney game due to an injury. Anderson will be valuable on a Gabba deck that is expected to assist swing and offer extra bounce. Stuart Broad looked rusty and the team will be hoping that he can get into rhythm.<br/><br/><b>Probable XI</b><br/><br/>1. Ian Bell, 2. Moeen Ali, 3. James Taylor, 4. Joe Root, 5. Eoin Morgan, 6. Ravi Bopara, 7. Jos Buttler, 8. Chris Woakes, 9. Chris Jordan, 10. Stuart Broad, 11. James Anderson<br/><br/><b>Stat</b><br/><br/>India and England have played two ODIs in Australia and have registered a win each. In the World Championship of Cricket in 1985, India won by 86 runs in Sydney while in the 1992 World Cup, England edged out India by nine runs.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>India</b> (From): Rohit Sharma, Shikhar Dhawan, Virat Kohli, Ajinkya Rahane, Suresh Raina, MS Dhoni(c/w), Axar Patel, Ravichandran Ashwin, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Mohammed Shami, Umesh Yadav, Ambati Rayudu, Stuart Binny, Mohit Sharma, Dhawal Kulkarni, Ishant Sharma, Ravindra Jadeja]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>England</b> (From): Ian Bell, Moeen Ali, James Taylor, Joe Root, Eoin Morgan(c), Ravi Bopara, Jos Buttler(w), Chris Woakes, Stuart Broad, James Tredwell, James Anderson, Chris Jordan, Steven Finn, Alex Hales]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>153</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>10</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>39.3</totalovers>
		<declared/>
		<followon/>
		<batteam name="India">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1447</playerid>
					<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
					<batsman-name>A Rahane</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rahane</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>33</runs>
					<balls>40</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Finn</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6317</bowlerId>
						<fielder>James Taylor</fielder>
						<fielderId>6500</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1446</playerid>
					<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhawan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhawan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>J Anderson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>65</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Jos Buttler</fielder>
						<fielderId>2258</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6311</playerid>
					<name>Ambati Rayudu</name>
					<batsman-name>Rayudu</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Rayudu</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>23</runs>
					<balls>53</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Finn</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6317</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Jos Buttler</fielder>
						<fielderId>2258</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Kohli</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>8</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Finn</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6317</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Jos Buttler</fielder>
						<fielderId>2258</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Raina</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[stumped]]></status>
					<bowler>M Ali</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6692</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Jos Buttler</fielder>
						<fielderId>2258</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dhoni</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>34</runs>
					<balls>61</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Finn</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6317</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Jos Buttler</fielder>
						<fielderId>2258</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1530</playerid>
					<name>Stuart Binny</name>
					<batsman-name>Binny</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Binny</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>44</runs>
					<balls>55</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>J Anderson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>65</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Eoin Morgan</fielder>
						<fielderId>624</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8808</playerid>
					<name>Axar Patel</name>
					<batsman-name>A Patel</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>A Patel</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>Finn</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6317</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1726</playerid>
					<name>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</name>
					<batsman-name>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>5</runs>
					<balls>5</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>J Anderson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>65</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7909</playerid>
					<name>Mohammed Shami</name>
					<batsman-name>Shami</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Shami</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>J Anderson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>65</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Moeen Ali</fielder>
						<fielderId>6692</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1858</playerid>
					<name>Umesh Yadav</name>
					<batsman-name>Umesh</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>U Yadav</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1446</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>1</runs>
				<overs>2.1</overs>
				<batsman>Shikhar Dhawan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dhawan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1447</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>57</runs>
				<overs>14.3</overs>
				<batsman>Ajinkya Rahane</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Rahane</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1413</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>64</runs>
				<overs>16.4</overs>
				<batsman>Virat Kohli</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Kohli</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>413</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>65</runs>
				<overs>17.2</overs>
				<batsman>Suresh Raina</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Raina</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6311</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>67</runs>
				<overs>18.6</overs>
				<batsman>Ambati Rayudu</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Rayudu</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>265</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>137</runs>
				<overs>36.1</overs>
				<batsman>MS Dhoni</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dhoni</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8808</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>137</runs>
				<overs>36.2</overs>
				<batsman>Axar Patel</batsman>
				<batsman-name>A Patel</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1726</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>143</runs>
				<overs>37.2</overs>
				<batsman>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Bhuvneshwar</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1530</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>153</runs>
				<overs>39.2</overs>
				<batsman>Stuart Binny</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Binny</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7909</playerid>
				<nbr>10</nbr>
				<runs>153</runs>
				<overs>39.3</overs>
				<batsman>Mohammed Shami</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Shami</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>1</noballs>
			<legbyes>3</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>7</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="England">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>65</playerid>
					<name>James Anderson</name>
					<bowler-name>J Anderson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>J Anderson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8.3</overs>
					<maidens>2</maidens>
					<runsoff>18</runsoff>
					<wickets>4</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6670</playerid>
					<name>Chris Woakes</name>
					<bowler-name>C Woakes</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Woakes</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>35</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>554</playerid>
					<name>Stuart Broad</name>
					<bowler-name>Broad</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Broad</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>33</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6317</playerid>
					<name>Steven Finn</name>
					<bowler-name>Finn</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Finn</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>33</runsoff>
					<wickets>5</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6692</playerid>
					<name>Moeen Ali</name>
					<bowler-name>M Ali</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Moeen Ali</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>31</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>385</playerid>
					<name>Ian Bell</name>
					<bowler-name>Bell</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bell</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6500</playerid>
					<name>James Taylor</name>
					<bowler-name>James Taylor</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>James Taylor</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8019</playerid>
					<name>Joe Root</name>
					<bowler-name>J Root</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>J Root</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>624</playerid>
					<name>Eoin Morgan</name>
					<bowler-name>E Morgan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Eoin Morgan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>571</playerid>
					<name>Ravi Bopara</name>
					<bowler-name>R Bopara</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bopara</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2258</playerid>
					<name>Jos Buttler</name>
					<bowler-name>J Buttler</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Buttler</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>156</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>1</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>27.3</totalovers>
		<declared/>
		<followon/>
		<batteam name="England">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>385</playerid>
					<name>Ian Bell</name>
					<batsman-name>Bell</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bell</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>88</runs>
					<balls>91</balls>
					<fours>8</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6692</playerid>
					<name>Moeen Ali</name>
					<batsman-name>M Ali</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Moeen Ali</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>8</runs>
					<balls>12</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Binny</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1530</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Virat Kohli</fielder>
						<fielderId>1413</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6500</playerid>
					<name>James Taylor</name>
					<batsman-name>James Taylor</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>James Taylor</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>56</runs>
					<balls>63</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8019</playerid>
					<name>Joe Root</name>
					<batsman-name>J Root</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>J Root</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>624</playerid>
					<name>Eoin Morgan</name>
					<batsman-name>E Morgan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Eoin Morgan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>571</playerid>
					<name>Ravi Bopara</name>
					<batsman-name>R Bopara</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Bopara</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2258</playerid>
					<name>Jos Buttler</name>
					<batsman-name>J Buttler</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Buttler</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6670</playerid>
					<name>Chris Woakes</name>
					<batsman-name>C Woakes</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Woakes</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>554</playerid>
					<name>Stuart Broad</name>
					<batsman-name>Broad</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Broad</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>65</playerid>
					<name>James Anderson</name>
					<batsman-name>J Anderson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>J Anderson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6317</playerid>
					<name>Steven Finn</name>
					<batsman-name>Finn</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Finn</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6692</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>25</runs>
				<overs>2.6</overs>
				<batsman>Moeen Ali</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Ali</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>3</wides>
			<noballs>1</noballs>
			<legbyes>0</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>4</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="India">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1530</playerid>
					<name>Stuart Binny</name>
					<bowler-name>Binny</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Binny</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>34</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>1</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1726</playerid>
					<name>Bhuvneshwar Kumar</name>
					<bowler-name>Bhuvneshwar</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Bhuvneshwar</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>18</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1858</playerid>
					<name>Umesh Yadav</name>
					<bowler-name>Umesh</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>U Yadav</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>6</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>42</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7909</playerid>
					<name>Mohammed Shami</name>
					<bowler-name>Shami</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Shami</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>23</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8808</playerid>
					<name>Axar Patel</name>
					<bowler-name>A Patel</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>A Patel</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7.3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>32</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>413</playerid>
					<name>Suresh Raina</name>
					<bowler-name>Raina</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Raina</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>7</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1446</playerid>
					<name>Shikhar Dhawan</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhawan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhawan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1447</playerid>
					<name>Ajinkya Rahane</name>
					<bowler-name>A Rahane</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rahane</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1413</playerid>
					<name>Virat Kohli</name>
					<bowler-name>Kohli</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Kohli</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6311</playerid>
					<name>Ambati Rayudu</name>
					<bowler-name>Rayudu</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Rayudu</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>265</playerid>
					<name>MS Dhoni</name>
					<bowler-name>Dhoni</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dhoni</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>