<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<scorecard>
	<match id="13809">
		<type>ODI</type>
		<gameDesc>4th ODI</gameDesc>
		<series>Sri Lanka tour of New Zealand, 2014-15</series>
		<matchday>1</matchday>
		<home>New Zealand</home>
		<away>Sri Lanka</away>
		<teamsabbr>NZ vs SL</teamsabbr>
		<homeabbr>NZ</homeabbr>
		<awayabbr>SL</awayabbr>
		<homeId>13</homeId>
		<awayId>5</awayId>
		<venue>Saxton Oval, Nelson</venue>
		<startdate>20 01 2015</startdate>
		<enddate>20 01 2015</enddate>
		<toss>
			<winner>Sri Lanka</winner>
			<decision>Batting</decision>
		</toss>
		<state>complete</state>
		<status>New Zealand won by 4 wkts</status>
		<result type="win">
			<winningteam>New Zealand</winningteam>
			<wonbyruns/>
			<wonbywickets>4</wonbywickets>
			
		</result>
		<manofmatch/>
		<manofseries/>
		<umpires>
		<Umpire1>
			<Name>Ian Gould</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</Umpire1>
		<Umpire2>
			<Name>Derek Walker</Name>
			<Country>NZ</Country>
		</Umpire2>
		<ThirdUmpire>
			<Name>Nigel Llong</Name>
			<Country>Eng</Country>
		</ThirdUmpire>
		<MatchReferee>
			<Name>Javagal Srinath</Name>
			<Country>Ind</Country>
		</MatchReferee>
		</umpires>
		<starttimeGMT>22:00</starttimeGMT>
		<prevDayPerGMT>true</prevDayPerGMT>
		<actualendGMT>20150120054544</actualendGMT>
	</match>
	<currentscores>
		<currentinningsno>2</currentinningsno>
		<batteamname>NZ</batteamname>
		<bwlteamname>SL</bwlteamname>
		<batteamruns>280</batteamruns>
		<batteamwkts>6</batteamwkts>
		<batteamovers>48.1</batteamovers>
		<status>New Zealand won by 4 wkts</status>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>1396</playerid>
			<name>Luke Ronchi</name>
			<batsman-name>Ronchi</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Ronchi</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>32</runs>
			<balls-faced>15</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>3</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<batsman>
			<playerid>205</playerid>
			<name>Daniel Vettori</name>
			<batsman-name>Vettori</batsman-name>
			<batsman-nickname>Vettori</batsman-nickname>
			<runs>7</runs>
			<balls-faced>4</balls-faced>
			<fours>1</fours>
			<sixes>0</sixes>
		</batsman>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>2281</playerid>
			<name>Thisara Perera</name>
			<bowler-name>T Perera</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>T Perera</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>8</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>58</runs>
			<wickets>1</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<bowler>
			<playerid>6729</playerid>
			<name>Sachithra Senanayake</name>
			<bowler-name>Senanayake</bowler-name>
			<bowler-nickname>Senanayake</bowler-nickname>
			<overs>9.1</overs>
			<maidens>0</maidens>
			<runs>57</runs>
			<wickets>0</wickets>
		</bowler>
		<maxovers>50</maxovers>
		<target>277</target>
<lastwicket>
<playerid>8982</playerid>
<name>Corey Anderson</name>
<player-runs>47</player-runs>
<player-balls>44</player-balls>
<runs>245</runs>
<wicket-nbr>6</wicket-nbr>
<bowlerid>0</bowlerid>
<bowlername/>
</lastwicket>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>7</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>8</total>
		</extras>
		<prevOvers><![CDATA[1 1 2 W 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>1 1 . 1 1 1 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 6 2 . 6 6 <b>&nbsp;&nbsp;|&nbsp;&nbsp;</b>4 ]]></prevOvers>
		<last-over>http://synd.cricbuzz.com/dinamalar/data/2014/2014_NZ_SL/NZ_SL_JAN20/over-detail.xml</last-over>
	</currentscores>
		<commentary>		
			<line><![CDATA[So, that's all we have for you from this game. Both teams will now lock horns on Friday at Dunedin. Remember, it is a day game and we hope to see you then. Until next time, take care.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kane Williamson:</b> I had a few days off which was nice. Just relaxed and caught up with my family and friends. Just wanted the shoulder to heal. It was nice to get off to a reasonable start. It is always nice to bat with other guys who are scoring freely. It was great initially with Elliott, before Anderson took over. Ronchi was just superb to finish it off the way he did. I am still very much working on my bowling and I am pretty happy with how it is progressing.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kane Williamson</b> is the <b>Man of the Match</b> for his knock of 103.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Brendon McCullum:</b> Really good effort from the bowlers to restrict them under 300. Williamson showed how experienced he is in formulating a gameplan. Also, Anderson and Ronchi finished it off in the end. There was probably a little bit more bounce here at the Oval. Pace was definitely there in comparison to last year. The crowd was really great. We don't know yet about Adam Milne (talking about his injured rib). The great thing about this team is that someone else will step up in case anything goes wrong. I will try to lead by example as they expect us to fight hard. Elliott had a tough time of late, but he showed strength of character and was one of the assets the selectors were keen to see. He is a great team man, and is a classy batsman at club level. The partnership he formed with Kane was crucial to getting us into this. Williamson has been wonderful and it's great to see him work his magic.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Angelo Mathews:</b>  After the start we got, I thought the lower order batted poorly. I thought Dilshan, Sangakkara and Mahela batted beautifully. It was a very good wicket but it didn't turn as much. It was a good batting track. We had to put pressure on the batsmen, but Kane batted brilliantly. The spinners have been bowling brilliantly, the wicket didn't get slow, but the spinners bowled well. We couldn't strike regularly.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>presentation ceremony</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Tim Southee was the pick of the bowlers for New  Zealand, taking 3/59 in his 10 overs. Both Milne and McClenaghan gave him good company as well, picking two wickets each.]]></line><line><![CDATA[After Sanga got out and  Mathews followed him back to the pavilion a ball later, Jayawardene decided to take the attack to the opposition. He helped Sri Lanka go past 250, but after  he got out just 6 short of his century, the Sri Lankan innings crumbled while trying to up the ante.]]></line><line><![CDATA[In the first innings, Sri Lanka started poorly as Karunaratne was out very early, but Dilshan and Sangakkara then put on a 100-plus partnership to steady  the innings. Dilshan fell after that and Sangakkara was joined by Jayawardene, who looked in superb touch, but both failed to reach their hundreds.  Sangakkara got out on 76 and during his innings, <b>he went past Sanath Jayasuriya</b> to become the <b>third highest run-scorer in ODIs</b>.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Sri Lankan bowlers weren't upto the mark and after taking three wickets early, they couldn't capitalize on the advantage.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Along with Elliott, Williamson put on a 88-run stand for the 4th wicket and helped New Zealand get closer to the total. After Elliott departed for 44, Anderson came to the crease and both Williamson and Anderson started accelerating, they put on a 79-run stand for the 5th wicket before Williamson departed. Anderson fell soon after and Ronchi, who had joined him at the crease after Williamson's wicket, finished things off in style for the home team. Ronchi's 32 runs off 15 balls meant that New Zealand won with 11 balls to spare.]]></line><line><![CDATA[This is a great victory for New Zealand after they got off to a poor start, losing Brendon McCullum in the 5th over. Guptill and Taylor also failed to get going and at one stage,  the Black Caps were reeling at 63/3. However, Kane Williamson, playing his second game of the tournament, had other plans in his mind. He was brilliant with the bat, notching up his 5th ODI ton.]]></line><line><![CDATA[New Zealand take a <b>2-1 lead</b> in the series. Ronchi and Vettori are extremely happy as they walk off the field. The players congratulate each other and shake hands.]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Vettori, <b>FOUR</b>, it's all over, it was a tossed up delivery outside off, Vettori comes on the front foot and drives it through covers. <b>New Zealand win by 4 wickets</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sachithra Senanayake [9.0-0-53-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Ronchi, <b>SIX</b>, slower ball from Perera, Ronchi gets under the line and smashes it over the long-off fence for the third six of the over, the <b>scores are level now</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Only <b>7 needed</b>  off 13 now]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Ronchi, <b>SIX</b>, on a good length and around off, Ronchi clears his front leg and smokes it over the long-off fence for another maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Ronchi, no run, slower ball on off, Ronchi drives it to mid-off, where Mathews puts in the dive and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Ronchi, 2 runs, low full toss from Perera, Ronchi heaves it to deep mid-wicket for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Ronchi, <b>SIX</b>, another full delivery on middle stump line, Ronchi gets under the ball and launches it over the long-on fence for a maximum, that's 10 runs in 2 balls from this over]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Ronchi, <b>FOUR</b>, full delivery on off, Ronchi clears his front leg and lofts it over mid-off for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[New Zealand need <b>25</b> more off 18 balls..]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Ronchi, 1 run, fullish just outside off, Ronchi drives it past the bowler for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Vettori, 1 run, slower bouncer at the batsman, Vettori pulls it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Ronchi, 1 run, in the channel outside off, Ronchi drives it to deep extra cover for another single]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Ronchi, no run, slower ball outside off, Ronchi drives it towards Mathews at mid-off, who gets hit on the shoulder while trying to field that ball, he looks in some pain]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Vettori, 1 run, fullish on the pads, Vettori tucks it away to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Ronchi, 1 run, on a good length and outside off, Ronchi eases it to long-off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Nuwan Kulasekara [8.0-0-46-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Ronchi, 1 run, full delivery on off, Ronchi drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Vettori, 1 run, full delivery on middle, Vettori moves across and works it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Daniel Vettori, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Ronchi, <b>out</b> Corey Anderson Run Out!! Anderson is run-out here. It was full toss on the pads, Ronchi can't put it away fine. There was a loud appeal as the ball hits the pad, but the umpire turns it down. The batsmen go through in search of a single as the ball rolls away towards Dilshan at backward point. There was some confusion in running between the wickets and Anderson stopped in the middle of the pitch, while Dilshan quickly runs in, picks the ball and throws at the striker's end, a direct-hit catches him short. This is another big break for the Lankans. <b>Corey Anderson run out (Dilshan) 47(44) [4s-2 6s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[T Perera to Ronchi, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Ronchi, 2 runs, bowls a low full toss this time, Ronchi chips it towards mid-wicket, where the fielder dives to his left while trying to take the catch, the ball evades him and rolls away to the deep and the batsmen take two]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Corey Anderson, 1 run, moves across and looks to run it down towards third man, ends up getting an outside edge and the ball runs away towards third man for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Ronchi, 1 run, angling into the pads, Ronchi tucks it away behind square for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Corey Anderson, <b>FOUR</b>, that was poor fielding from Chandimal, he over ran the ball there, Anderson gets down on one knee and sweeps this flighted delivery to deep square leg fence, where Chandimal can't stop the ball and the batsmen collects four]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Corey Anderson, 2 runs, pushed through on leg, Anderson clips it towards fine leg, the fielder from deep square leg runs to his left and saves two runs for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Corey Anderson, 2 runs, flatter delivery from Herath, Anderson whips it away towards the cow corner fence, the batsmen take two before the ball is hunted down]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Ronchi, 1 run, floated up on the pads, Ronchi works it to deep fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Ronchi, <b>wide</b>, drifting down leg this time, wided by the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Corey Anderson, 1 run, flighted delivery on the pads, Anderson eases it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Corey Anderson, no run, on middle and leg stump line, Anderson tucks it away behind square on the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Luke Ronchi, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, <b>out</b> Bowled!! This is a big wicket for Sri Lanka. He shuffles across way too much while trying to work this fullish delivery into the on-side. Meanwhile, he exposes his leg stump and misses the ball completely, the ball crashes into the leg stump. End of an outstanding innings from Williamson. <b>Williamson b T Perera 103(107) [4s-6 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[T Perera to Williamson, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, 2 runs, fuller in length and on leg stump line, Williamson moves across slightly and chips it over mid-wicket for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Corey Anderson, 1 run, on a good length and outside off, Anderson comes on the front foot and drives it towards deep extra cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Corey Anderson, no run, fuller in length and on off, Anderson makes room and drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Corey Anderson, no run, another yorker length delivery just outside off, Anderson jams it out into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, 1 run, yorker on middle stump line, Williamson squeezes it out into the off-side and the batsmen steal a quick run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Thisara Perera [5.0-0-24-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, 1 run, Williamson completes his <b>5th ODI century</b> with this single, it was tossed up on off and Williamson skips out of the track, he eases it down to long-off for a single, this is a commendable effort from the Kiwi vice-captain]]></line><line><![CDATA[Williamson on 99...]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Corey Anderson, 1 run, another full delivery on middle, Anderson clips it off his pads to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, 1 run, fullish outside off,  Williamson works this one to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Corey Anderson, 1 run, gets down on one knee and sweeps it hard to deep backward square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, 1 run, skips out of the track and works it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Corey Anderson, 1 run, goes on the back foot and pushes it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Corey Anderson, <b>wide</b>, slider down the leg-side, wided by the ump]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Corey Anderson, 1 run, comes on the front foot and drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Corey Anderson, <b>SIX</b>, flighted delivery just outside off, Anderson gets down on one knee and slog sweeps it over the deep mid-wicket fence for a maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 1 run, floated on the pads, Williamson works it backward of square on the on-side for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Corey Anderson, 1 run, flighted delivery on middle and off, Anderson sweeps it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Corey Anderson, 2 runs, shorter delivery on off, Anderson reverse sweeps it in front of square on the off-side for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 1 run, skips down the track and flicks it to deep square leg for a run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Corey Anderson, no run, comes on the front foot and pushes it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, 1 run, goes on the back foot and punches it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, skips down the track and lofts it over the mid-wicket fielder fo runs across and cuts it off boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Corey Anderson, 1 run, quicker delivery outside leg, Anderson flicks it to deep mid-wicket for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Corey Anderson, no run, flighted delivery on the pads, Anderson tucks it to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, 1 run, tossed up on middle and off, Williamson eases it to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rangana Herath [6.0-1-14-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Batting poweplay yielded <b>33 runs</b> for New Zealand]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 1 run, short delivery on off, Williamson makes room and slaps it square of the wicket on the off-side for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Corey Anderson, 1 run, comes on the front foot and drills it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Corey Anderson, <b>SIX</b>, flatter delivery on the pads, Anderson gets down on one knee and sweeps it over the deep backward square leg fence for half a dozen]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 1 run, floated outside off, Williamson gets down on one knee and sweeps it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Corey Anderson, 1 run, flighted delivery on off, Anderson leans forward and eases it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 1 run, short delivery on the stumps, Williamson pulls it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Williamson, 1 run, slower delivery just outside off, Williamson opens the face of the bat and dabs it to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, low full toss outside off, Williamson makes room and slices it past the backward point fielder for yet another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Corey Anderson, 1 run, good length delivery on off, Anderson comes forward and drives it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Corey Anderson, <b>FOUR</b>, slower boncer down the leg-side, Anderson pulls it off the back foot to the backward square leg fence for another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Corey Anderson, no run, yorker on the stumps, Anderson digs it out to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Corey Anderson, no run, short of length delivery outside off, Anderson misses out on the cut]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Corey Anderson, 1 run, shimmies down the track and chips it in towards to long-on for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Corey Anderson, no run, tossed up on the stumps, Anderson sweeps it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Corey Anderson, no run, flighted delivery well outside off, Anderson gets down on one knee and misses the sweep, the ball goes off the pad to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 1 run, skips down the track and guides it to backward point for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, no run, leans forward and sweeps this ball on leg-stump to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Corey Anderson, 1 run, skips down the track and drives it between extra cover and mid-off for a run]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Corey Anderson, 1 run, slower bouncer on off, Anderson pulls it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Williamson, 1 run, slower delivery on off, Williamson eases it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Williamson, no run, good length delivery on the pads, Williamson tucks it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, fuller length delivery just outside off, Williamson comes on the front foot and creams the drive to the deep extra cover fence for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Williamson, no run, slower delivery on off, Williamson comes on the front foot and dead-bats it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Williamson, no run, short of good length delivery just outside off, Williamson gets on top of the bounce and drives it to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Nuwan Kulasekara [6.0-0-30-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Corey Anderson, no run, presses forward and defends it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 1 run, short delivery on the stumps, Williamson rocks back and pulls it straight to the deep mid-wicket fiedler]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, no run, comes on the front foot and smothers it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Corey Anderson, 1 run, tossed up on off, Anderson comes forward and drives it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Corey Anderson, no run, floated across off, Anderson pushes it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 1 run, slider down the leg-side, Williamson gets down on one knee and sweeps it to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>batting powerplay</b>!]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Corey Anderson, no run, pushed across off, Anderson smashes it staright to the fiedler at cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Williamson, 1 run, leans forward and works it to square leg for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Williamson, <b>SIX</b>, quicker delivery on the leg-stump line, Williamson shimmies down the track and launches it over the deep mid-wicket fence for his first maximum]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Corey Anderson, 1 run, comes on the front foot and drives it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Williamson, 1 run, goes on the back foot and eases this one to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Corey Anderson, 1 run, flatter delivery on off, Anderson slaps it hard to long-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Corey Anderson, 1 run, skips down the tack and chips is uppishly to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 1 run, gets down on one knee and sweeps it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Corey Anderson, 1 run, flatter on off and middle, Anderson comes forward and eases it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Corey Anderson, no run, flighted delivery just outside off, Anderson leans forward and drives it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Corey Anderson, no run,]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 1 run, tossed up outside off, Williamson sweeps it to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sachithra Senanayake [4.0-0-20-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Corey Anderson, no run,]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Corey Anderson, no run,]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Williamson, 1 run, shortens the length a touch, Williamson goes back and punches it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Williamson, no run, leans forward and blocks it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Corey Anderson, 1 run, googly on middle and turning away, Anderson goes back and eases it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Corey Anderson, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, <b>out</b> Caught by Thirimanne!! Mendis finally breaks this dangerous partnership for Sri Lanka. This was a flighted delivery outside off, Elliott skips down the track, looks to go inside out, ends up slicing it in the air to Thirimanne at extra cover, who completes an easy catch. <b>Elliott c Thirimanne b J Mendis 44(58) [4s-3]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[J Mendis to Elliott, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, 2 runs, flighted delivery around off, Williamson gets down on one knee and sweeps it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, 2 runs, shimmies down the track once again and works it to deep mid-wicket for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Elliott, 1 run, floated across off, Elliott skips down the track and eases it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Elliott, no run, goes on the back foot and punches it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Elliott, no run, flighted delivery on off, Elliott comes forward and pushes it to the left of Herath, who dives and makes a stop]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Elliott, no run, flatter delivery on off, Elliott skips down the track and pushes it to the right of the bowler, who comes across and stops it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rangana Herath [5.0-1-9-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Herath replaces Dislshan in the attack]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, 1 run, steps out of the crease again and eases this flighted delivery on middle stump line to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Williamson, 1 run, floated up outside off, Williamson bunts it towards sweeper cover off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Williamson, no run, comes down the track and pushes this tossed up delivery to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, 1 run, flatter on the stumps, Elliott goes back and punches it towards deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, <b>FOUR</b>, goes down on one knee and sweeps this delivery down leg to the fine leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, no run, sliding down leg, Elliott fails to sweep it fine, the ball clips the pad on its way to the keeper]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Williamson, no run, comes down the track before defending this flighted delivery]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Williamson, no run, backs away and looks to hit it through the off-side, but ends up pushing this flighted delivery back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Elliott, 1 run, flatter outside off, Elliott stays back in the crease and guides it towards cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Elliott, <b>FOUR</b>, floated up on middle stump line, Elliott plays the reverse paddle with the back of the bat, the ball runs away to the third man fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Elliott, <b>FOUR</b>, drags this one short and Elliott gives the charge, he pulls it hard to the fine leg fence, the ball reached the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Williamson, 1 run, pushed through on leg, Williamson comes down the track and bunts it down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, no run, pushed through quicker on off, Elliott was pushing hard at it, the ball rolls away towards cover off the outside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Williamson, 1 run, gives the charge and eases this slowish delivery to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, 1 run, floated up around off, Elliott kneels down and sweeps hard and in the air, the ball bounces just in front of the deep backward square leg fielder and the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Williamson, 1 run, flighted delivery on off and middle, Williamson comes down the track and bunts it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Williamson, no run, quicker one on the stumps, Williamson blocks it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, 1 run, pushed through on leg, Elliott works it towards short fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Elliott, 1 run, Elliott hangs on the back foot and punches this flatter one to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Elliott, 2 runs, goes down on one knee and sweeps this flighted delivery to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Williamson, 1 run, flighted delivery on leg, Williamson stays on the back foot and works it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Elliott, 1 run, pushed through on the pads, Elliott tucks it away behind square for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Williamson, 1 run, flatter on the stumps, Williamson goes back in the crease and punches it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Dilshan to Williamson, 2 runs, shortish delivery from Dilshan, Williamson pulls it to deep mid-wicket for a brace]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tillakaratne Dilshan, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Williamson, 1 run, tossed up on off, Williamson drives it to long-off and he will keep the strike. That also brings up Williamson's <b>14th fifty</b> in ODIs]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, 1 run, floated up just outside off, Elliott goes down on one knee and drags the sweep to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Williamson, 1 run, flatter on off and middle, Williamson punches it down to long-on and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Williamson, no run, quicker one on the stumps, Williamson goes back in the crease and punches it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, 1 run, drags his length back a touch after seeing the batsmen give the charge, Elliott pushes it down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Williamson, 1 run, floated up on middle and leg, Williamson eases it down to long-on, that brings up the <b>50-run</b> partnership between these two]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 1 run, slows this one slightly on middle and leg, Williamson moves across a touch and tucks it away to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Elliott, 1 run, on the pads, Elliott works it behind square and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Elliott, no run, Sanga was appealing for the lbw here, but it came off the bat. It was pushed through on middle stump line, Elliott looks to reverse sweep it, can't make a proper connection and the ball rolls away into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 1 run, comes down the track and chips it towards long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Elliott, 1 run, flighted on middle and leg, Elliott gives the charge and bunts it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 1 run, flatter on the stumps, Williamson goes deep in the crease and works it behind square on the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Williamson, 1 run, flighted delivery on middle and leg, Williamson sweeps it to short fine leg and the batsmen pinch a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, 1 run, pushed through on middle stump line, Elliott puts his bat in front of the pad and pushes it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Williamson, 1 run, flatter on the stumps, Williamson goes deep in the crease and punches it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, 1 run, tossed up on off, Elliott leans forward and drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, no run, gives the charge and looks to work this slowish delivery into the on-side, he closes the bat face a little too early and gets a leading edge that rolls away into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, no run, floated up outside off, Elliott sweeps hard, but straight to backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Elliott, 1 run, 'Catch' was the call, but it was never going to carry to the fielder, it was floated up on off and middle, Elliott sweeps hard and in the air, but the ball bounces well short of the fielder at deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 1 run, steps out of the crease and eases this one down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Elliott, 1 run, pushed through on middle, Elliott gets down on one knee and sweeps it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Elliott, no run, floated up around off, Elliott drives it back to the bowler off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 1 run, flatter outside off, Williamson makes room and cuts it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Elliott, 1 run, skips down the track and eases it down to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, 1 run, flighted delivery on off, Elliott comes on the front foot and drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, no run, tossed up on off, Elliott drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Williamson, 1 run, floated up on middle stump line, Williamson sweeps it towards backward square leg, where the fielder dives and makes a half-stop, the batsmen take a single before the ball is fielded]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, drags his length back and bowls this around leg, Williamson camps on the back foot and pulls it to the deep backward square leg fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, 1 run, quicker this time and around off, Elliott drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, <b>wide</b>, wrong' un from Mendis that goes down the leg-side, wided by the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;J Mendis to Elliott, no run, floated up outside off, Elliott pushes at it, the ball rolls away towards backward point off a soft outside edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Jeevan Mendis, right-arm leg break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 2 runs, loopy delivery on off, Williamson moves across and paddles it fine for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Elliott, 1 run, floated up on middle, Elliott sweeps it behind square for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Elliott, no run, slightly flatter this time around, Elliott pushes it back in the direction of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Elliott, 2 runs, gets down on one knee and sweeps this flighted delivery on middle and leg to fine leg, the batsmen run for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 1 run, tossed up on middle stump line, Williamson eases it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, no run, floated up outside off, Williamson comes down the track and looks to loft it over mid-off, doesn't time it that well, the ball just bounces in front of the mid-off fielder and luckily for Williamson, he is still out there]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off, Williamson goes deep in the crease and punches it to sweeper cover, retains the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, no run, back of a length delivery around off, Williamson goes on the back foot and punches it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Elliott, 1 run, on a good length and outside off, Elliott dabs it towards third man and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, 1 run, angled on the pads, Williamson works it to fine leg after moving across slightly]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Elliott, 1 run, just short of a good length and outside off, Elliott guides it down to third man after opening the face of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, 1 run, touch too straight from Perera, Williamson tucks it away to fine leg for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Elliott, no run, Elliott goes down on one knee and looks to sweep this tossed up delivery around leg, he fails to connect and is hit on the pad, there was an appeal, but the ball was going down leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 1 run, quicker one on the stumps, Williamson goes deep in the crease and works it towards fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Elliott, 1 run, steps out of the crease and works this flighted delivery on leg to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Williamson, 1 run, on off and middle stump this time, Williamson turns it towards deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Elliott, 1 run, pushed through on the pads, Elliott works it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Senanayake to Elliott, no run, flatter on the stumps, Elliott pushes it to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Sachithra Senanayake, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Starts from round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Elliott, 1 run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Elliott hops up in the crease, opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, 1 run, length delivery on middle stump line, Williamson works it to deep square leg from the crease, the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, no run, just short of a good length on off and middle, Williamson turns it towards mid-wicket after moving across a touch]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Williamson goes on the back foot and mistimes the punch towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, no run, length delivery just outside off, Williamson comes on the front foot and knocks it towards mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, 2 runs, length delivery on middle stump line, Williamson flicks it behind square on the on-side for a brace]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Elliott, no run, quicker one on middle and leg, Elliott backs away a touch and bunts it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Elliott, no run, pushed through on off and middle, Elliott pushes at it off the front foot, the ball rolls away towards mid-wicket off the inside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Elliott, no run, flighted delivery around off, Elliott pushes it towards cover after coming down the track]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Elliott, no run, tossed up on off, Elliott lunges forward in defence]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Elliott, no run, gives this one more air on off and middle, the ball turns away and Elliott was pushing at it, the ball rolls away towards point off the outside half of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Elliott, no run, floated up on off, Elliott leans forward and dead-bats it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, no run, in the channel outside off, Williamson comes forward and pushes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, on a good length and just outside off, Williamson was looking to run it down to third man after opening the face of the bat, he gets an outside edge that rolls past the keeper and runs away to the third man fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Elliott, 1 run, on a good length and outside off, Elliott comes on the front foot and drives it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, 1 run, angling into the pads, Williamson flicks it uppishly and the ball bounces just in front of the fielder at mid-wicket, who couldn't stop the ball, the ball dribbles away towards the mid-on region and the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, no run, another short of length around off, Williamson punches it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Elliott, 1 run, back of a length delivery outside off, Elliott pushes it towards cover-point and sets off for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Elliott, 1 run, flighted delivery just outside off, Elliott leans forward and bunts it towards cover, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Elliott, no run, it was a flighted delivery on off, Elliott comes on the front foot and pushes it towards the point region, he sets off for a single, but Williamson wasn't interested, the fielder from backward point runs in and fires a throw, Elliott rushes back in and the dive saves him there, had it been a direct-hit, Elliott would have been a goner]]></line><line><![CDATA[The TV umpire has been called in to judge a run-out appeal. Was his bat in the air when he was diving forward? He was in and the decision is 'Not Out']]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Elliott, no run, tossed up on middle, Elliott presses forward and defends it into the leg-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Elliott, no run, floated up on middle and leg, Elliott blocks it into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Elliott, no run, tossed up around off, Elliott takes a step forward and drives it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Grant Elliott, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A leg slip in place now]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Ross Taylor, <b>out</b> Caught by Sangakkara!! Taylor's poor run continues as he departs for another single digit score. It was flatter and just outside off, Taylor goes on the back foot and looks to cut, he was cramped for room and ends up edging it to the keeper, who takes a good catch. <b>Ross Taylor c Sangakkara b Herath 8(23)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Herath to Ross Taylor, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, no run, short of length delivery just outside off, Williamson goes back and dabs it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, no run, on a length around off, Williamson presents the full face of the bat and blocks it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, no run, good length delivery on off, Williamson leans forward and drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, <b>FOUR</b>, fuller length delivery on middle, Williamson comes on the front foot and flicks it in the air over the mid-wicket fielder for a superb boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, no run, short of length delivery on off, Williamson goes back and blocks it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Ross Taylor, 1 run, good length delivery nipping in a touch from outside off, Taylor comes forward and pushes it with soft hands in front of the mid-on fielder for a quick single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Ross Taylor, 1 run, floated across off, Taylor leans forward and drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, 1 run, tossed up delivery on off, Williamson comes on the front foot and eases it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, no run, flighted delivery on off, Williamson comes forward and smothers it to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, no run, goes on the back foot and blocks it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, 2 runs, straying on the pads, Williamson comes across and glances it to fine leg for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, no run, tossed up delivery on off, Williamson comes forward and defends it to the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Ross Taylor, no run, short of length delivery just outside off, Taylor goes back and cuts it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Ross Taylor, 2 runs, good length delivery just outside off, Taylor comes on the front foot and looks to work it to the on-side, gets a leading edge square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Ross Taylor, no run, good length delivery on off, Taylor comes forward and slices it to short third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, 1 run, short of good length delivery just outside off, Williamson cuts it to sweeper cover for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, no run, short of length delivery just outside off, Williamson goes on the back foot and punches it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;T Perera to Williamson, no run, slightly back of a length ball on off, Williamson pushes it to the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Thisara Perera, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, 1 run, shortens the length a touch, Williamson goes on the back foot and works it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Ross Taylor, 1 run, flighted delivery on off, Taylor leans forward and eases it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Ross Taylor, no run, slider down the leg-side, Taylor comes across and misses the glance]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Ross Taylor, no run,]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Ross Taylor, no run, shimmies down the track and drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, 1 run, tossed up on off, Williamson skips down the track and drives it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Ross Taylor, no run, on a length around off, Taylor comes on the front foot and defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Ross Taylor, no run, good length delivery on middle, Taylor comes forward and punches it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Williamson, 1 run, short of good length delivery on off, Williamson stays inside the crease and punches it to mid-on and sets off for a quick single, the mid-on fielder has a shy at the non-striker's end, but Williamson was well in]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Williamson, no run, good length delivery on off, Williamson comes forward and pushes it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Williamson, <b>wide</b>, bouncer over the batsman's head, wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Ross Taylor, 1 run,]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Ross Taylor, <b>wide</b>,]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Ross Taylor, no run,]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, no run,]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, no run, tossed up delivery on off, Williamson comes forward and pushes it to the right of Herath]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, no run, floated on middle, Williamson skips down the track and pushes it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Williamson, no run, flighted delivery on off, Williamson gets well forward and smothers it]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Ross Taylor, 1 run, tossed up just outside off, Taylor comes on the front foot and drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Herath to Ross Taylor, no run, tossed up delivery on off, Taylor skips down the track and drives it back to the bowler, who moves to his right and stops it with his right foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Rangana Herath, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[A slip in place for Herath]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Williamson, no run, good length delivery on off, Williamson blocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Ross Taylor, 1 run, length delivery outside off, Taylor steers it down to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Ross Taylor, no run, short of length delivery just outside off, Taylor goes back and punches it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Ross Taylor, no run, bouncer on the stumps, Taylor ducks under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Ross Taylor, no run, good length delivery outside off, Taylor comes on the front foot and slices it towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Williamson, 1 run, good length delivery outside off, Williamson opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Ross Taylor, no run, fuller length delivery on off, Taylor drives it off the front foot to silly mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Ross Taylor, no run, fuller length delivery on off, Taylor comes on the front foot and defends it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Ross Taylor, no run, good length delivery on off, Taylor comes forward and blocks it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Ross Taylor, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Guptill, <b>out</b> Caught by Sangakkara!! Both the openers are back in the hut. This was short of good length delivery which bounces a touch extra, Guptill was pushing at it from the crease, gets an outside edge, which is snaffled up by Sanga, who dives to his right and takes a one handed screamer. <b>Guptill c Sangakkara b Mathews 20(27) [4s-1 6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Mathews to Guptill, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Williamson, 1 run, length delivery on the pads, Williamson comes forward and clips it to deep mid-wicket for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Guptill, leg byes, 1 run, fuller length delivery on the pads, Guptill misses the flick, the ball goes off the pads to the left of Sanga who dives and shells it, the ball rolls to the short fine leg fielder]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Williamson, 2 runs, short of length delivery just outside off, Williamson rocks back and cuts it to squarish third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Williamson, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Williamson punches it off the back foot to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Guptill, 1 run, short of good length delivery on off, Guptill punches it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Guptill, no run, play and a miss! Good length delivery outside off, Guptill leans forward, plays a loose drive and gets beaten]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Guptill, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Guptill rocks back and punches it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Williamson, 1 run, good length delivery outside off, Williamson opens the face of the bat and runs it down to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Guptill, no run, short of length delivery just outside off, Guptill goes back and punches it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Guptill, no run, back of a length delivery just around off, Guptill defends it off the back foot to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Williamson, 1 run, short of good length delivery outside off, Williamson chops it back to third man for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Williamson, no run, short of length delivery just outside off, Williamson lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Guptill, 1 run, length delivery in the channel outside off, Guptill comes forward and eases it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Guptill, <b>SIX</b>, good length delivery just outside off, Guptill comes on the front foot and lofts it over the long-off boundary for a magnificent six. That ball travelled <b>92 metres</b> and timing on that was brilliant]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Guptill, <b>wide</b>, length delivery down the leg-side, wide called]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Williamson, 2 runs, back of a length delivery just outside off, Williamson goes on the back foot and punches it square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kane Williamson, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Brendon McCullum, <b>out</b> Kulasekara gets the big fish early in the innings. This was a short of length delivery just outside off, McCullum mistimes the pull to Perera at mid-on, who moves across to his left and takes a good catch. New Zealand have lost there captain early. Caught by T Perera!! <b>Brendon McCullum c T Perera b N Kulasekara 11(11) [4s-2]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[N Kulasekara to Brendon McCullum, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Guptill, 3 runs, short of length delivery just outside off, Guptill camps on the back foot and cuts it square of the wicket on the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Guptill, <b>FOUR</b>, short delivery wide outside off, Guptill goes back and cuts it hard to the sweeper cover fence for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Guptill, no run, length delivery on the pads, Guptill pushes it to silly mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Guptill, no run, good length delivery just outside off, Guptill slaps it hard to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Brendon McCullum, no run, length delivery on off, McCullum comes forward defends it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Brendon McCullum, no run, short of good length delivery on off and middle, McCullum comes forward and misses the flick, the ball takes the pad above the knee roll and hits Sanga on the shoulder]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, good length delivery on the pads, McCullum leans forward and flicks it to deep backward square leg, where the fielder from deep square leg comes across and puts in a dive to stop it, but while stopping the ball he makes contact with the ropes which results in a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Brendon McCullum, no run, length delivery which keeps very low just outside off, McCullum gets his bat down in time, ends up bottom edging it to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Guptill, 1 run, length delivery on middle, Guptill works it off the front foot to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, fuller length delivery on middle, McCullum comes on the front foot and flicks it to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Guptill, no run, good length delivery outside off, Guptill comes forward and drives it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Guptill, 2 runs, short of good length on off, Guptill drives it from the crease to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Guptill, no run, on a length on off, Guptill comes forward and defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Guptill, no run, length delivery on off, Guptill gets well forward and blocks it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, short of good length delivery shaping into the right-hander, McCullum cuts it to cover-point for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Brendon McCullum, no run, length delivery angling into the batsman, McCullum comes across and misses the glance, the ball runs off the pad to short fine leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Guptill, no run, on a length just outside off, Guptill presses forward and defends it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Guptill, no run, short of length delivery just outside off, Guptill goes back and punches it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Guptill, no run, good length delivery on off, Guptill comes forward and pushes it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Guptill, no run, back of a length delivery around off, Guptill gets behind the line and blocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Guptill, no run, fullish delivery on off, Guptill gets well forward and defends it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Mathews to Guptill, no run, fuller length delivery on middle, Guptill comes on the front foot and defends it to the on-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Angelo Mathews, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Guptill, 1 run, short of length delivery on middle, Guptill goes back and punches it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Brendon McCullum, 1 run, short of good length delivery just outside off, McCullum comes forward and cuts it to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Brendon McCullum, <b>FOUR</b>, straying on the pads, McCullum comes across and helps it along to the fine leg fence to get off the mark]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Brendon McCullum, no run, good length delivery coming in from outside off, McCullum defends it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[Sanga is upto the stumps for Baz]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Guptill, 1 run, length delivery swinging back into the right-hander, Guptill flicks it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Guptill, no run, on a length and shaping back into the right-hander, Guptill blocks it to mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;N Kulasekara to Guptill, <b>wide</b>, good length delivery swinging down leg, wide signalled]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Guptill and Brendon McCullum are at the crease. Guptill is on strike. N Kulasekara will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Welcome back.. Kulasekara will start the proceedings for Sri Lanka with a slip in place]]></line><line><![CDATA[Jayawardene then stabilized the innings with Thirimanne, putting on 65 runs for the 5th wicket before Thirimanne departed. Jaywardene also perished soon after while trying to accelerate the scoring, falling short of a ton by 6 runs. At the end, Sri Lanka folded for 276 and the Black Caps need 277 runs to take a 2-1 lead in the series. The run-chase starts in a short while from now. Stay tuned.]]></line><line><![CDATA[Earlier, Sri Lanka got off to a poor start, losing opener Karunaratne when the team score was just 11. Dilshan and Sangakkara then steadied the innings with a 102-run stand, increasing the run-rate in the process as well. After Dilshan got out, Sanga was joined by Jayawardene at the crease, who was in sublime touch. Sanga, in the meanwhile, became the third highest run-scorer in ODIs, going past Sanath Jayasuriya. Both batsmen batted well, but Sangakkara got out in the 34th over. Mathews then came to the crease and was out the next ball as well.]]></line><line><![CDATA[New Zealand must be delighted with how they pulled things back in the last few overs. At one stage, when Sangakkara and Jayawardene were batting, Sri Lanka looked all set to achieve a total in excess of 300, but the Black Caps bowlers bowled really well towards the end. Southee was the pick of the bowlers, taking 3 wickets and he was well supported by Milne and McClenaghan, who picked up 2 wickets each.]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Herath, <b>out</b> Caught by Williamson!! Sri Lanka have been bowled out here. It was a short delivery at the batsman, Herath goes for the pull, but gets a top-edge and Williamson at short mid-wicket takes an easy catch. <b>Herath c Williamson b McClenaghan 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[McClenaghan to Herath, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Herath, <b>wide</b>, down the leg-side and the umpire calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Senanayake, 1 run, fuller delivery outside off, Senanayake slices the drive towards sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Senanayake, <b>wide</b>, full and way wide outside off, Senanayake can't connect with it and the umpire calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Rangana Herath, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[49.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to N Kulasekara, <b>out</b> N Kulasekara Run Out!! This is just crazy! Brendon McCullum has been flying all over the park today. Another great bit of fielding from him. It was on a fuller length just outside off, Kulasekara clears his front leg and goes for the loft, McCullum runs to his right from mid-off and flies in the air to his right, trying to take the catch, but he floors it as he falls hard on the ground. However, he was quick to react and he picked the ball up very swiftly, fires in the throw at the non-striker's end and McClenaghan takes the bails off, catching Kulasekara short. McCullum has just been magnificent on the field. <b>N Kulasekara run out (Brendon McCullum/McClenaghan) 4(7)</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[McClenaghan to N Kulasekara, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Run Out!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Senanayake, no run, another full one on the pads, Senanayake can't clips it into the on-side, wears another on his pad, the ball rolls away into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Senanayake, no run, full on the pads, Senanayake fails to work it fine, the ball hits him on the pads, there was an appeal, but maybe it pitched outside leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to N Kulasekara, 1 run, slower ball on the pads, Kulasekara works it uppishly towards mid-wicket, where the ball bounces just in front of Vettori]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to N Kulasekara, 2 runs, fullish delivery on the stumps, Kulasekara backs away and lofts it inside out over cover, the batsmen take two before Anderson from sweeper cover gets around and cuts it off]]></line><line><![CDATA[Comes round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sachithra Senanayake, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to J Mendis, <b>out</b> Caught by Vettori!! Mendis goes now and Sri Lanka are eight down now. It was a full toss just outside off, Mendis was looking to go over cover, but ends up slicing it in the air. Vettori at extra cover gets under it and takes the simplest of catches. <b>J Mendis c Vettori b Southee 12(10) [6s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Southee to J Mendis, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[48.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to J Mendis, no run, fullish and wide outside off, Mendis reaches out, but can't put bat on it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[47.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Mendis, 1 run, yorker from McClenaghan, Mendis digs it out and the ball runs past the off-stump, the batsmen pinch a single, but it wasn't very far away from the stumps]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to J Mendis, no run, down the leg-side, Mendis was making room and can't put bat on it, the umpire also doesn't call it a wide, strange umpiring that]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to N Kulasekara, 1 run, yorker length ball little wide outside off, Kulasekara reaches out and jams it towards backward point, where a misfield allows the batsmen to go through with the single]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to N Kulasekara, no run, fuller delivery outside off, Kulasekara again looks to guide it down to third man and fails to make a connection once again]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to N Kulasekara, no run, slower and fuller on off, Kulasekara drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[47.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to N Kulasekara, no run, comes from round the wicket and bowls it on a length outside off, Kulasekara was looking to run it down to third man, the ball goes past the blade]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [8.0-0-53-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Nuwan Kulasekara, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to T Perera, <b>out</b> Caught by Brendon McCullum!! Super catch from Baz. Brilliant piece of fielding from the Kiwi captain. It was a full toss outside off, Perera was looking to go inside-out over extra cover, but mistimes it completely. Brendon McCullum runs to his right from mid-off, puts in a full length dive and completes a brilliant catch. <b>T Perera c Brendon McCullum b Southee 5(6)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Southee to T Perera, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to T Perera, <b>wide</b>, full and way wide outside off, the umpire calls it a wide]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to J Mendis, 1 run, widish delivery outside off, Mendis reaches out and jams it towards the third man region]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to J Mendis, <b>SIX</b>, great pickup shot from Mendis, it was angling in on odd and middle stump line, Mendis moves across and flicks it over the deep backward square leg fence for a six]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to T Perera, 1 run, fuller in length and outside off, Perera looks to go big over mid-wicket, gets a thick outside edge that drops just short of the fielder at third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to T Perera, 2 runs, on a good length and outside off, Perera opens the face of the bat and guides it past backward point, the batsmen take two before the ball is hunted down]]></line><line><![CDATA[46.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to J Mendis, 1 run, back of a length delivery on leg, Mendis pulls, but can't time it properly, the ball rolls away towards square leg, he got it high on his bat and that's why couldn't get the timing right]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tim Southee [8.0-1-44-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to J Mendis, 1 run, another full on on off and middle stump line, Mendis clips it past square leg, he was looking for the second there, but Perera sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to J Mendis, 2 runs, fuller now and angling in on middle stump line, Mendis moves across and works it to deep backward square leg for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to J Mendis, no run, back of a length delivery wide outside off, Mendis swings hard, but fails to make a connection]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Jeevan Mendis, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to M Jayawardene, <b>out</b> Caught by Ronchi!! This is a big breakthrough for New Zealand. Jayawardene misses out on his ton as well. It was the off-cutter on a length and angling away outside off, Jayawardene was looking to run it down towards third man after opening the face of the bat. He ends up edging it towards the keeper, who dives to his right and takes a good catch. It was a great knock from Jayawardene though. <b>M Jayawardene c Ronchi b Corey Anderson 94(82) [4s-9 6s-3]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Corey Anderson to M Jayawardene, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to T Perera, 1 run, angling into the pads, Perera works it to deep mid-wicket and gets off strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[45.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to T Perera, no run, length delivery on off and middle stump line, Perera pushes it towards short cover off the outside half of the bat]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[44.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, <b>FOUR</b>, a boundary to end the over, it was banged in short and at the batsman, Jayawardene swivels and pulls it to the fine leg fence, great shot as he rolled his wrists over it to send it along the ground]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, 2 runs, another full toss on the middle and leg, Jayawardene bunts it to deep mid-wicket off the inside half of the bat, he comes back for the second run as well]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to T Perera, 1 run, fuller in length outside off, Perera goes opens the face of the bat and lofts the drive towards sweeper cover, who collects it on the bounce]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Thisara Perera, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Thirimanne, <b>out</b> Bowled!! Thirimanne perishes while trying to go big. He was not very comfortable out there. It was a fullish delivery on off and middle, Thirimanne lines up for the big slog after going down on his knee, fails to connect and the ball crashes into the stumps. The length was not there to hit a shot like that and Thirimanne pays the price for it. <b>Thirimanne b McClenaghan 19(31) [4s-1]</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[McClenaghan to Thirimanne, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Bowled!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Thirimanne, no run, good yorker from McClenaghan, Thirimanne jams it out to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[44.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, 1 run, full toss on the pads, Jayawardene helps it to fine leg for a single]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[43.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Thirimanne, no run, another short delivery from Anderson, Thirimanne mistimes the pull to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Thirimanne, no run, on a good length and just outside off, Thirimanne opens the face of the bat and pushes it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to M Jayawardene, leg byes, 1 run, another one on the pads, Jayawardene fails to glance it fine and is very unhappy with himself, the ball rolls away behind square on the on-side after clipping the thigh pad, the batsmen sneak in a leg bye]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to M Jayawardene, <b>FOUR</b>, banged in short and at the batsman, Jayawardene goes for the pull, the ball takes the arm-guard and runs away to the fine leg fence, given as runs by the umpire though]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Thirimanne, 1 run, slightly wide outside off, Thirimanne cuts it to the squarish third man region]]></line><line><![CDATA[43.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to M Jayawardene, 1 run, just short of a good length and on the stumps, Jayawardene opens the face of the bat and guides it to the right of the keeper for a single, didn't come off the middle of the bat though]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Corey Anderson [1.0-0-9-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Anderson, who has only bowled a single over so far, comes back into the attack]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Thirimanne, no run, full and tailing in on leg stump line, Thirimanne fails to clip it into the on-side and is hit on the foot, there was an appeal, but the ball was definitely going down leg with the angle there]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, 1 run, touch too straight from Jayawardene, Jayawardene tucks it away to deep square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, <b>FOUR</b>, another great shot from Jayawardene, it was fuller in length and outside off, Jayawardene opens the face of the bat and drives it past a leaping backward point, Anderson from sweeper cover runs across to stop the ball, but the ball beats him to the fence. Anderson rams into one of the umbrella stand just outside the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, 2 runs, full toss from McClenaghan, Jayawardene works it through mid-wicket off the inside half of the bat, the batsmen take two]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, <b>FOUR</b>, back of a length delivery just outside off, Jayawardene waits for it and ramps it to the third man fence, what great improvisation from Jayawardene there]]></line><line><![CDATA[42.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Thirimanne, 1 run, length delivery around off, Thirimanne comes on the front foot and bunts it in front of mid-off, Brendon McCullum runs forward, picks the ball and fires in the throw at the non-striker's end, Thirimanne puts in the dive, but would have still been out, great fielding effort from the Kiwi captain]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[41.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to M Jayawardene, <b>FOUR</b>, back of a length delivery on the stumps, Jayawardene heaves it to the long-on fence, he didn't time it that well, but the ball had enough legs to reach the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Thirimanne, 1 run, bowls this one on middle stump line, Thirimanne moves across and wrists it towards mid-on, the batsmen steal a quick run]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to M Jayawardene, 1 run, fuller in length and angling in on the pads, Jayawardene clears his front leg and clips it to deep backward square leg for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to M Jayawardene, no run, fullish delivery slighlty wide outside off, Jayawardene has to reach out and he ends up jamming it out towards backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Thirimanne, 1 run, banged in short and at the batsman, Thirimanne pulls it to deep square leg and sends it along the ground after rolling his wrists over it]]></line><line><![CDATA[41.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Thirimanne, no run, just short of a good length delivery angling away outside off, Thirimanne looks to run it down to third man, but fails to connect and the keeper gloves it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[40.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Thirimanne, 1 run, angling into the pads, Thirimanne works it to mid-wicket and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, 1 run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Jayawardene guides it past backward point after opening the face of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, no run, bumper that sails over the batsman's head, can't understand how it was not given as a wide, Jayawardene was not happy with the decision]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Thirimanne, 1 run, on a good length and outside off, Thirimanne opens the face of the bat and bunts it square of the wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Thirimanne, no run, length delivery just outside off, Thirimanne leans forward and pushes it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[40.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Thirimanne, <b>FOUR</b>, back of a length delivery outside off, Thirimanne flashes hard it, the ball flies off the outside edge, goes over the slip fielder's head and runs away to the third man fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[39.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Thirimanne, 1 run, good length delivery just outside off, Thirimanne opens the face of the bat and slices it uppishly it past backward point for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Thirimanne, 2 runs, back of a length delivery just outside off, Thirimanne camps on the back foot and punches it to to deep extra cover for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to M Jayawardene, 1 run, short of length delivery just outside off, Jayawardene goes on the back foot and cuts it to square third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to M Jayawardene, <b>FOUR</b>, fuller length delivery on middle, Jayawardene comes on the front foot and lofts it over a leaping mid-off fielder for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to M Jayawardene, no run, short delivery on middle, Jayawardene looks to ramp it over the keeper's head, but couldn't manage to get bat on it]]></line><line><![CDATA[39.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Thirimanne, 1 run, back of a length delivery outside off, Thirimanne opens the face of the bat and glides it to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Baz asks Milne to go off the field because of his injury concern. Milne obliges and Nathan McCullum is on the field for him]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, no run, good length delivery on middle, Jayawardene tucks it to mid-wicket off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, no run, fuller length delivery on off, Jayawardene drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, <b>FOUR</b>, fuller length delivery on off, Jayawardene comes on the front foot and drives it straight sown the ground for another magnificent boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, no run, short of length delivery outside off, Jayawardene guides it to gully]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Thirimanne, 1 run, fuller length delivery on middle, Thirimanne flicks it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[38.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Thirimanne, no run, good length delivery on off, Thirimanne drives it off the front foot to mid-off]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [4.0-0-21-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Adam Milne appears to have issue with his rib area, he probably won't bowl any more in this innings, but he's on the field]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Thirimanne, 1 run, back of a length delivery outside off, Thirimanne goes on the back foot and guides it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Thirimanne, no run, short of length delivery outside off, Thirimanne pushes it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to M Jayawardene, 1 run, back of a length delivery outside off, Jayawardene guides it off the back foot to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to M Jayawardene, no run, short of length delivery outside off, Jayawardene dabs it to the widish slip and thinks about a single but Thirimanne sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Thirimanne, 1 run, back of a length delivery outside off, Thirimanne glides it off the back foot to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[37.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to M Jayawardene, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off, Jayawardene dabs it to third man]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Tim Southee [5.0-1-24-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, 1 run, flighted delivery on off, Jayawardene comes forward and drives it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, <b>SIX</b>, tossed up on off, Jayawardene skips down the track and lofts it over the long-off fence to get to his <b>77th ODI fifty</b>. The timing on that was magnificent as the ball travelled <b>92 meteres</b>, that was an effortless stroke]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, no run, goes on the back foot and cuts it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, no run, shortens the length again, Jayawardene tucks it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Thirimanne, 1 run, shortish on the pads, Thirimanne nudges it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[36.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, 1 run, fullish on middle, Jayawardene comes on the front foot and eases it to long-on]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kane Williamson [6.0-0-41-1] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Thirimanne, no run, back of a length delivery on the hips, Thirimanne nudges it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Thirimanne, no run, short of length delivery outside off, Thirimanne lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Thirimanne, no run, fullish again outside off, Thirimanne comes on the front foot and drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Thirimanne, no run, fuller length delivery outside off, Thirimanne leans forward and drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to M Jayawardene, 1 run, good length delivery on off, Jayawardene shuffles across and works it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[35.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to M Jayawardene, no run, back of a length delivery on off, Jayawardene goes back and defends it off the back foot to the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Time for the <b>batting powerplay</b>!]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Thirimanne, no run, stays inside the crease and looks to run this flatter delivery down to third man, he almost gives a chance to the first slip fielder, but luckily for Thirimanne, it went to the left of the slip fielder and not into his hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Thirimanne, no run, flighted delivery on off, Thirimanne blocks it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, 1 run, shortens the length a touch, Jayawardene pushes it to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, no run, flighted delivery on off, Jayawardene comes forward and pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, no run, goes on the back foot and cuts it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[34.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, no run, comes on the front foot and defends it to the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[33.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to M Jayawardene, 1 run, back of a length delivery outside off, Jayawardene guides it to square third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to M Jayawardene, no run, <b>did he get an edge there?</b> It was a fuller length delivery down the leg-side, Jayawardene was looking to glance it fine, there was a sound as the ball passed the bat, the keeper collects it and Milne thought that Jayawardene got a faint nick there, but umpire Gould turns the appeal down, Hot-Spot shows that there was indeed a little edge on that and Snicko confirms it well, lucky escape for Jayawardene there]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Thirimanne, 1 run, fuller length delivery outside off, Thirimanne comes forward and looks to drive, he gets an outside edge that runs away towards third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Thirimanne, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Thirimanne lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[Hat-trick ball for Milne]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Lahiru Thirimanne, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Mathews, <b>out</b> Caught by Ronchi!! Back-to-back wickets for Milne. This was a back of a length delivery on the hips, Mathews comes across and gets a faint edge while he was looking to glance it fine, the umpire says 'Not-Out', New Zealand opts to review and gets it right. Mathews has gone for a golden duck here. <b>Mathews c Ronchi b Milne 0(1)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Milne to Mathews, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Angelo Mathews, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[New Zealand reviews for a caught behind on Mathews, Milne's footing is fine, Hot-Spot shows a little tickle off the bat. Mathews has to go.]]></line><line><![CDATA[33.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Sangakkara, <b>out</b> Caught by Guptill!! Milne strikes against the run of play. This was slightly back of a length delivery just outside off, Sangakkara chips it straight to Guptill at short cover, who jumps a bit and takes it with both hands. Sanga is not happy with himself as he walks back. <b>Sangakkara c Guptill b Milne 76(83) [4s-8 6s-1]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Milne to Sangakkara, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, no run, goes back and fends it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, 2 runs, goes on the back foot and turns it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, 1 run, floated across off, Sangakkara drives it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, no run, slider down the leg-side, Sangakkara misses the nudge, the bowler and the keeper appeal, but the umpire says 'Not-Out']]></line><line><![CDATA[32.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, 1 run, tossed up on off, Jayawardene comes down the track and lofts it inside out over cover for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[32.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, no run, flighted delivery on off, Jayawardene comes forward and pushes it to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[31.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Sangakkara, no run, bouncer at the batsman, Sangakkara ducks under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Sangakkara, no run, back of a length delivery on off, Sangakkara guides it to gully]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to M Jayawardene, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off, Jayawardene opens the face of the bat and guides it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to M Jayawardene, <b>FOUR</b>, fullish again on middle, Jayawardene comes on the front foot and flicks it superbly through the mid-wicket region for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to M Jayawardene, 2 runs, fuller length delivery on off, Jayawardene comes forward and looks to go over the on-side, gets it off the outer half of the bat in the air to the sweeper cover region. Jayawardene closed the bat too early, so the ball went to the deep point fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[31.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Sangakkara, 1 run, short of length delivery outside off, Sangakkara pushes it off the back foot to sweeper cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Adam Milne [4.0-0-17-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, 1 run, flatter delivery on the pads, Sangakkara tucks it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, no run, tossed up on leg, Sangakkara sweeps it to short fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, 1 run, floated on off, Jayawardene comes forward and drives it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, 1 run, tossed up delivery on off, Sangakkara skips down the track and mitimes the whip to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, no run, flighted delivery on off, Sangakkara skips down the track and pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[30.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, no run, floated across off, Sangakkara comes forward and pushes it to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Daniel Vettori [7.0-0-33-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Sangakkara, 1 run, back of a length delivery angling into the batsman on middle and leg, Sangakkara bunts it down to mid-on and the batsmen rush through for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, 1 run, angling into the pads, Jayawardene gets an inside edge onto the pad, the ball rolls away into the on-side and the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, <b>wide</b>, bumper that sails way over Jayawardene's head, wided by the umpire]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, no run, short of length delivery outside off, Jayawardene cuts it towards backward point, who dives to his left and stops the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Sangakkara, 1 run, length delivery outside off, Sangakkara leans forward and drives it to sweeper cover for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, 1 run, on a good length and on middle stump line, Jayawardene wrists it towards mid-wicket with soft hands, the batsmen pinch a quick run]]></line><line><![CDATA[29.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Sangakkara, 1 run, just short of a good length and just outside off, Sangakkara punches it to sweeper cover and the batsmen cross over]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[28.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Sangakkara, 1 run, floated up around off, Sangakkara eases it down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Sangakkara, no run, goes down on one knee and sweeps this to short fine leg, who puts in the dive and saves a certain boundary for his team]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, 3 runs, shortish delivery outside off, Jayawardene hangs back and dabs it past short third man after opening the face of the bat, the batsmen take three before the ball is hunted down]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, <b>SIX</b>, another maximum for Jayawardene, it was a tossed up delivery on the stumps, Jayawardene comes down the track and launches it over the cow corner fence, great shot that]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Sangakkara, 1 run, flatter delivery just outside off, Sangakkara goes back in the crease and punches it towards sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[28.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Sangakkara, no run, quicker one on off and middle, Sangakkara pushes it back to the bowler off the front foot]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[27.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, no run, on a good length and outside off, Jayawardene comes on the front foot and taps it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, no run, good bumper from McClenaghan, it was banged in short and on leg, Jayawardene ducks under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, no run, on a good length and outside off, Jayawardene shoulders arms this time around]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, no run, back of a length delivery angling away outside off, Jayawardene hangs inside the crease and defends it into the off-side with soft hands]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, 2 runs, just short of a good length and a little wide outside off, Jayawardene stays on the back foot and cuts it to deep backward point, the fielder from sweeper cover runs across, slides and keeps the batsmen down to a couple with his fielding]]></line><line><![CDATA[27.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to M Jayawardene, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Jayawardene pushes at it away from his body, the ball goes past the outside edge]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan [2.0-0-13-0] is back into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, 1 run, floated up on middle stump line, Jayawardene moves across and tucks it away in front of square on the on-side, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Sangakkara, 1 run, gives the charge and chips this flighted delivery straight down the ground, the batsmen take a single as the ball goes on the bounce towards the long-on fielder]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, 1 run, quicker one around off, Jayawardene moves across and works it to deep mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Sangakkara, 1 run, flighted delivery just outside off, Sangakkara leans forward, opens the face of the bat and pushes it towards the sweeper cover region]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Sangakkara, no run, flatter on the stumps, Sangakkara hangs back and punches it to the left of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[26.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, 1 run, pushed through on the pads, Jayawardene comes down the track and flicks it to deep square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[25.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, no run, floated up on off and middle, Sangakkara takes a step forward and works it to short mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, 1 run, slightly shortish a little wide outside off, Jayawardene hangs back and cuts it square of the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, no run, straight roller on the stumps, Jayawardene blocks it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, no run, flighted delivery just outside off, Jayawardene pushes it into the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, 1 run, pushed through on middle stump line, Sangakkara tucks it away past square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[25.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, tossed up outside off, Sangakkara leans forward and drives it through the covers for a boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[24.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, no run, works this one into the on-side after moving across]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, no run, defends this flighted delivery into the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, no run, turned to short mid-wicket off the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Sangakkara, 1 run, another flatter one from Williamson, Sangakkara punches it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, 1 run, flatter on the stumps, Jayawardene stays inside the crease and pushes it to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[24.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, <b>FOUR</b>, tossed up around off, Jayawardene drives it off the front foot, short cover misfields and the ball runs away towards the deep extra cover fence, the mid-off fielder gives chase, but to no avail]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[23.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, no run, floated up on off, Sangakkara defends]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, 1 run, floated up on middle stump line, Jayawardene works it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, 1 run, tucks this one away to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, 1 run, floated up on off, Jayawardene eases it to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, 1 run, tossed up on middle and leg, Sangakkara works it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[23.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, no run, a huge appeal from Vettori, but the umpire says 'Not Out', it was floated outside leg and went on with the angle towards the batsman, who was looking to sweep. Sanga missed and the ball hits him on the pad, the Kiwis think about the review, but decide against it after Ronchi pointed out that he believed that it was missing leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[22.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Sangakkara, 1 run, tossed up on off, Sangakkara comes down the track and drives it to long-off, he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, 1 run, flighted delivery on middle and leg, Jayawardene bunts it down to long-on for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, no run, quicker one just outside off, Jayawardene pushes it in front of cover and was looking for a single, Sanga sends him back]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, <b>SIX</b>, super shot from Jayawardene, it was a flatter one from Williamson, Jayawardene skips out and heaves it over the long-on fence for a six]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Sangakkara, 1 run, tossed up on off, Sangakkara drives it to long-off after coming on the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[22.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Sangakkara, no run, wide outside off, Sangakkara chases it and cuts it towards backward point, who dives and makes the stop]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[21.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, no run, flighted delivery on the stumps, Jayawardene tucks it away to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, no run, floated up on off and middle, Jayawardene leans forward and defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, no run, shortish outside off, Jayawardene hangs back and cuts it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, no run, floated up around off, Jayawardene pushes it to cover off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to M Jayawardene, no run, on middle and leg stump line again, Jayawardene defends it towards mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[21.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, 1 run, pushed through on middle and leg, Sangakkara works it to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[20.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Sangakkara, 1 run, tossed up on middle and leg, Sangakkara drives it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Sangakkara, no run, Ohh dear! McClenaghan has <b>dropped a sitter</b>. It was tossed up on middle and leg, Sangakkara moves across, gets down on one knee and sweeps it straight to McClenaghan at short fine leg, who drops a dolly]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, 1 run, shortish outside off, Jayawardene cuts it to deep backward point off the back foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, no run, quicker one just outside off, Jayawardene waits for it and dabs it towards backward point after opening the face of the bat]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to M Jayawardene, no run, floated up just outside off, Jayawardene pushes it into the off-side off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Mahela Jayawardene, right handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[20.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Dilshan, <b>out</b> Caught by Guptill!! Dilshan is gone. He hits it straight to the fielder here. This was a tossed up delivery on off, Dilshan skips down the track, drives uppishly and straight to Guptill at short cover. Softest of dismissals for the Sri Lankan opener. <b>Dilshan c Guptill b Williamson 44(57) [4s-4]</b>]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[Williamson to Dilshan, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Caught!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Dilshan, 1 run, eases this flighted delivery on off down to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Dilshan, no run, skips down the track, gets to the pitch of the ball and defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, 1 run, tossed up on middle, Sangakkara eases it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, Sangakkara brings up his <b>92nd ODI fifty</b> with this boundary, it was floated up on middle stump, Sangakkara comes down the track and chips it over mid-wicket, the fielder from long-on runs to his left, puts in the dive, but the ball trickles away to the fence, this also brings up the <b>100-run partnership</b> between these two]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, tossed up on off, Sangakkara skips out and lofts it over the mid-off fielder, the ball races away to the fence]]></line><line><![CDATA[19.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, no run, flighted delivery on off, Sangakkara leans forward and dead-bats it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[18.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Sangakkara, 1 run, tossed up on off, Sangakkara presses forward and drives it to long-off for another single]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Dilshan, 1 run, flatter delivery from Williamson this time, Dilshan backs away and punches it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, floated up on off, Dilshan steps out of the crease and drives it beautifully past a diving short cover, the ball runs away to the fence in no time]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Sangakkara, 1 run, tosses it up on middle stump line, Sangakkara gives the charge and eases it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Sangakkara, no run, floated up on off, Sangakkara comes on the front foot and pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[18.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Williamson to Dilshan, 1 run, pushed through on middle and leg, Dilshan moves across and tucks it away through mid-wicket, the batsmen think about the second run, but decide against it]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Kane Williamson, right-arm off break, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Spin from both ends as Williamson now comes into the attack. He will start from round the wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Dilshan, 1 run, gives the charge to this flighted delivery on off, he bunts it to the left of the bowler, who dives and gets a hand on it, but can't stop it completely, the ball rolls away towards long-off and the batsmen take a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Dilshan, no run, goes on the back foot and punches it to cover this time]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Dilshan, no run, floated up on off and middle, Dilshan defends off the front foot]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, 1 run, gives this one more air on middle and leg, Sangakkara works it to mid-wicket for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Dilshan, 1 run, tossed up on off, Dilshan eases it dopwn to long-off for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[17.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Dilshan, no run, quicker one on the stumps, Dilshan gets hurried into the push, the ball takes the inside edge onto the pad and rolls away behind square on the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[16.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Dilshan, 1 run, back of a length delivery on the pads, Dilshan tucks it away to fine leg and he will keep the strike]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Sangakkara, 1 run, shaping in on middle and leg, Sangakkara clips it to mid-wicket and gets to the other end]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Sangakkara, 2 runs, just short of a good length and little wide outside off, Sangakkara hangs back and cuts it square of the wicket for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Sangakkara, no run, on a good length and around off, Sangakkara leans forward and pushes it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Sangakkara, no run, back of a length delivery on off, Sangakkara goes on the back foot and pushes it in front of cover, the batsmen were looking for a single, but can't take it as the fielder was quickly onto the ball]]></line><line><![CDATA[16.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, touch too straight from Elliott, it was down the leg-side and Sangakkara glances it fine, the ball runs away to the fence]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Drinks</b> are on the field now]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Dilshan, 2 runs, shortish a little wide outside off, Dilshan hangs back and cuts it to deep backward point for a brace]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Dilshan, no run, floated up on off, Dilshan defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, 1 run, tossed up on middle stump line, Sangakkara eases it down to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Dilshan, 1 run, pushed through on the pads, Dilshan works it behind square on the on-side for a single]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Dilshan, no run, Dilshan gives the charge and Vettori drags his length back, Dilshan chops it towards cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[15.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Dilshan, no run, flatter delivery on the stumps, Dilshan bunts it towards mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Sangakkara, no run, short of length delivery outside off, Sangakkara shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Sangakkara, <b>wide</b>, length delivery wide outside off, wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Sangakkara, 2 runs, fuller length delivery outside off, Sangakkara comes on the front foot and drives it to Southee at deep point, who throws it back towards the keeper, but it bounces awkwardly in front of Ronchi, who couldn't collect it properly and as a result the batsmen take an extra run]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Sangakkara, no run, good length delivery outside off, Sangakkara leans forward and drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Sangakkara, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Sangakkara guides it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Dilshan, 1 run, fuller length delivery just outside off, Dilshan drives it off the front foot to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[14.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Dilshan, no run, fuller length delivery on leg, Dilshan pushes it to mid-wicket]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[13.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Dilshan, 1 run, tossed up on off, Dilshan comes down the track and eases it to long-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, 1 run, floated on off and middle, Sangakkara tucks it to deep mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Dilshan, 1 run, flatter on off, Dilshan drives it off the front foot to long-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Sangakkara, 1 run, goes on the back foot and works it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Dilshan, 1 run, tossed up delivery just outside off, Dilshan skips down the track and drives it inside out to long-off for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[13.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Vettori to Dilshan, no run, flighted delivery on off, Dilshan blocks it back to the bowler]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Daniel Vettori, left-arm orthodox, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Sangakkara, no run, bouncer at the batsman, Sangakkara ducks under it]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Sangakkara, no run, good length delivery on off, Sangakkara pushes it to mid-off and sets off for single, Dilshan sends him back in time]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Sangakkara, <b>SIX</b>, fuller length delivery just outside off, Sangakkara skips down the track and heaves it between deep mid-wicket and long-on for the first maximum of the match]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Sangakkara, no run, slightly back of a length delivery on off, Sangakkara gets behind the line of the ball and defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Dilshan, 1 run, good length delivery outside off, Dilshan cuts it to sweeper cover for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[12.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Elliott to Dilshan, no run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Dilshan pushes it to point]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Grant Elliott, right-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Elliott replaces Anderson after just an over]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dilshan, 1 run, good length delivery on middle and off, Dilshan pushes it wide of mid-on for another run]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Sangakkara, 1 run, back of a length delivery on the stumps, Sangakkara goes back and nudges it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dilshan, 1 run, short of a length delivery on middle, Dilshan tucks it to mid-wicket for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Sangakkara, 1 run, fuller length delivery on off, Sangakkara drives it to cover-point]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Sangakkara, no run, length delivery on off, Sangakkara blocks it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Sangakkara, no run, good length delivery just outside off, Sangakkara comes forward and defends it to the off-side]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[11.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Sangakkara, <b>5 wides</b>, woah! What was that? Bouncer on off, which was way way over the batsman as well as the keeper]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[A slip in place for McClenaghan]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, back of a length delivery angling away outside off, Dilshan goes back and cuts it past the backward point fielder for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Sangakkara, 1 run, length delivery on the pads, Sangakkara tucks it to deep square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Dilshan, 1 run, fuller length delivery on off, Dilshan drives it off the front foot to sweeper cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Sangakkara, 1 run, fuller length delivery on middle, Sangakkara gets forward and pushes it to mid-on for a quick single]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Sangakkara, no run, back of a length delivery on off, Sangakkara defends it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[10.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Corey Anderson to Sangakkara, 2 runs, good length delivery on the pads, Sangakkara flicks it to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Corey Anderson, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sangakkara </b>has now become the <b>leading run-scorer</b> for Sri Lanka in ODIs, going past Sanath Jayasuriya]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dilshan, no run, short of good length delivery on off, Dilshan defends it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, short delivery at the batsman, Dilshan goes on the back foot and pulls it backward square on the on-side for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dilshan, no run, back of a length delivery on middle, Dilshan goes back and blocks it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dilshan, no run, fuller length delivery on the pads, Dilshan flicks it to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dilshan, no run, good length delivery on the pads, Dilshan gloves it to the keeper, but the umpire didn't spot it, it was a stifled appeal from the New Zealanders as well, Dilshan is lucky to be there]]></line><line><![CDATA[9.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;McClenaghan to Dilshan, no run, bouncer at the batsman, Dilshan looks to pull and misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Mitchell McClenaghan, left-arm fast medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Sangakkara, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Sangakkara leaves it alone]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, fantastic shot, short of length delivery on middle, Sangakkara rocks back and pulls it perfectly in front of square on the on-side for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Dilshan, 1 run, good length delivery outside off, Dilshan steers it to third man for a run]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Dilshan, <b>wide</b>, good length delivery down the leg-side, wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Dilshan, <b>wide</b>, straighter delivery angling down the leg-side, wided by the ump]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Dilshan, no run, good length delivery outside off, Dilshan defends it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Dilshan, no run, fuller length delivery on the pads, Dilshan flicks it to mid-wicket]]></line><line><![CDATA[8.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Dilshan, <b>FOUR</b>, half-volley on off and middle, Dilshan gets forward and presents the full face of the bat as he drives it to the right of the bowler for a glorious boundary]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[7.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Sangakkara, no run, another fuller length delivery on off, Sangakkara pushes it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, fuller length delivery outside off, Sangakkara leans forward and creams the drive to the deep extra cover fence for a boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Dilshan, 3 runs, good length delivery outside off, Dilshan gets on top of the bounce and drives it on the up between extra cover and mid-off, McCullum chases hard from mid-off, puts in a dive and saves one run for his team, in the process he rams face first into the advertisement hoardings. Great bit of commitment from Baz there. That must have hurt him there]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Dilshan, no run, fullish and swinging away outside off, Dilshan leans forward and mistimes the drive to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Dilshan, no run, fuller length delivery on off, Dilshan gets forward and defends it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[7.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Dilshan, 2 runs, short of length delivery on off, Dilshan goes back and pulls it to to deep mid-wicket for a couple]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[6.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Sangakkara, no run, good length delivery on off, Sangakkara pushes it back to the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, short delivery on middle, this time Sangakkara rocks back and pulls it superbly to the deep square leg fence for another boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Sangakkara, no run, fullish again outside off, Sangakkara leans forward and drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Sangakkara, no run, fuller length delivery on off, Sangakkara drives it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Sangakkara, <b>FOUR</b>, edged and over the keeper's head for a boundary. This was a short delivery on middle, Sangakkara was in no position to play the pull, the ball lobs of the glove and flies over the keeper's head to the third man fence for a streaky boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[6.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Sangakkara, no run, good length delivery wide outside off, Sangakkara is happy to let that go to the keeper]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Dilshan, no run, short of length delivery outside off, Dilshan opens the face of the bat and dabs it to backward point]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Dilshan, <b>wide</b>, short delivery down the leg-side, wide called]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Dilshan, no run, fuller length delivery on off and nipping in a touch, Dilshan comes on the front foot, gets an inside edge onto the pads, a muted LBW appeal is turned down]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Dilshan, no run, short of good length delivery around off, Dilshan knocks it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Sangakkara, 1 run, fuller length delivery on off and middle, Sangakkara leans forward and works it to the left of mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Sangakkara, no run, short of length delivery just outside off, Sangakkara goes back and defends it the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[5.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Dilshan, 1 run, short of length delivery just outside off, Dilshan punches it to cover]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[4.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Sangakkara, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Sangakkara defends it to point]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Sangakkara, no run, short of length delivery outside off, Sangakkara defends it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Sangakkara, no run, good length delivery on off, Sangakkara pushes it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Sangakkara, no run, fuller length delivery outside off, Sangakkara lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Kumar Sangakkara, left handed bat, comes to the crease</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to D Karunaratne, <b>out</b> Lbw!! This time Southee has his man and New Zealand strike early. This was again a fuller length delivery swinging back into the left-hander, Karunaratne comes on the front foot and looks to flick, but misses, the ball hit him below the knee roll in front middle and leg, Karunaratne has a chat with Dilshan whether to take the review and decides against it. <b>D Karunaratne lbw b Southee 5(16)</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Southee to D Karunaratne, <b>THATS OUT!!</b> Lbw!!]]></line><line><![CDATA[4.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to D Karunaratne, no run, huge shout for LBW, the umpire shakes his head though. This was a fuller length delivery swinging back into the left-hander, Karunaratne leans forward, looks to work it to the on-side and misses, the ball hits him low on the pads, but that might have been going down leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[3.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Dilshan, no run, good length delivery outside off, Dilshan leans forward and drives it to mid-off]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Dilshan, no run, short of good length delivery shaping away a touch outside off, Dilshan was pushing at it, the ball sails past the outisde edge of the bat and through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Dilshan, no run, short of length delivery around off, Dilshan goes back and defends it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Dilshan, no run, short of length delivery on off, Dilshan gets behind the line of the ball and blocks it to cover]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to D Karunaratne, 1 run, back of a length delivery just outside off, Karunaratne guides it to third man]]></line><line><![CDATA[3.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to D Karunaratne, no run, good length delivery swinging in on leg-stump, Karunaratne comes across and misses the glance]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[2.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Dilshan, no run, short of length delivery outside off, Dilshan lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to D Karunaratne, 1 run, short of good length ball on the pads, Karunaratne tucks it to backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to D Karunaratne, no run, fuller length delivery outside off, Karunaratne comes forward and looks to drive, the ball goes past the inside edge of the bat and through to the keeper]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Dilshan, 1 run, good length delivery on the pads, Dilshan flicks it to fine leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to Dilshan, no run, good length delivery on middle and swinging away a touch, Dilshan misses the flick and gets hit near the box]]></line><line><![CDATA[2.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to D Karunaratne, 1 run, fuller length delivery swinging into the left-hander, Karunaratne leans forward, gets an inside edge to deep backward square leg]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[1.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Dilshan, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Dilshan mistimes the pull to mid-on]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to D Karunaratne, leg byes, 1 run, back of a length delivery on the hips, Karunaratne misses the glance, the ball takes the thigh pad to square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Dilshan, 3 runs, good length delivery outside off, Dilshan comes on the front foot and drives it between extra cover and mid-off, Baz chases it from mid-off, slides and stops it from reaching the boundary]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to Dilshan, no run, good length delivery around off, Dilshan comes on the front foot and pushes it to the right of the bowler]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to D Karunaratne, 1 run, short of good length delivery coming into the left-hander, Karunaratne nudges it to deep backward square leg]]></line><line><![CDATA[1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Milne to D Karunaratne, no run, back of a length delivery outside off, Karunaratne pushes at it and misses]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>Adam Milne, right-arm medium, comes into the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.6&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to D Karunaratne, 1 run, length delivery nipping back into the left-hander, Karunaratne leans forward and flicks it to deep backward square leg, he almost fell over after playing that stroke]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.5&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to D Karunaratne, no run, full again and coming in on off, Karunaratne leans forward and pushes it to the off-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.4&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to D Karunaratne, no run, fullish delivery outside off, Karunaratne shoulders arms]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.3&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to D Karunaratne, no run, full again and shaping back in on off, Karunaratne comes on the front foot and gets an inside edge onto the pads]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.2&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to D Karunaratne, no run, fuller length delivery nipping back into the left-hander, Karunaratne comes forward and pushes at it, the ball goes off the inside half of the bat to the on-side]]></line><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to D Karunaratne, no run, fullish again and swinging in from outside off, Karunaratne lifts his bat and lets it go]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[0.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Southee to D Karunaratne, <b>wide</b>, fuller length delivery swinging down the leg-side, wide called]]></line><end-of-over>end of over</end-of-over><line><![CDATA[<b>D Karunaratne and Dilshan are at the crease. D Karunaratne is on strike. Southee will open the attack</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[Karunaratne and Dilshan are in the middle, Karunaratne will be on strike. Southee will start the proceedings for New Zealand with two slips in place.]]></line><line><![CDATA[For Sri Lanka, Herath comes in place of Prasad]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sri Lanka</b> (Playing XI): Dimuth Karunaratne, Tillakaratne Dilshan, Kumar Sangakkara(w), Mahela Jayawardene, Angelo Mathews(c), Lahiru Thirimanne, Thisara Perera, Jeevan Mendis, Nuwan Kulasekara, Sachithra Senanayake, Rangana Herath]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>New Zealand</b> (Playing XI): Brendon McCullum(c), Martin Guptill, Kane Williamson, Ross Taylor, Grant Elliott, Corey Anderson, Luke Ronchi(w), Daniel Vettori, Tim Southee, Mitchell McClenaghan, Adam Milne]]></line><line><![CDATA[New Zealand have made 3 changes - Williamson, Elliott and Milne come in place of Latham, Nathan McCullum and Henry.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sri Lanka have won the toss and have opted to bat</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Sri Lankan bowlers have done well from time to time, but they still lack consistency. Bowling against batsmen like Brendon McCullum is no easy task, but they need to focus more on the right line and lengths. Herath, Senanayake and Dilshan have bowled well, but need the same kind of support from their pacers. It should be a cracker of a contest. Toss and teams coming up in a short while. Stay tuned.]]></line><line><![CDATA[For Sri Lanka, Dilshan's century in the second ODI showed that they are up for a fight. His ton helped Sri Lanka win their first game on the tour. With the likes of Sangakkara, Jayawardene and Mathews in the team, Sri Lankan batting looks very solid. However, they will be up against the likes of Southee, Milne and McClenaghan. The Kiwi bowlers have bowled good line and lengths, making life difficult for the visitors.]]></line><line><![CDATA[The Black Caps will be a little worried about Ross Taylor's current form as he hasn't looked confident with the bat. Grant Elliott is all set to make a return to the team, with Latham expected to sit this game out, in accordance with New Zealand's rotation policy. The Kiwis will also take a late call on whether Kane Williamson is fit to play this ODI or not.]]></line><line><![CDATA[After the third ODI got washed out, the 7-match series has now effectively become a 6-game series. With both teams tied at 1-1, today's game is going to be very important for both the teams. Hello and welcome to the fourth ODI between New Zealand and Sri Lanka.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Preview</b><br/><br/><b>Overview:</b><br/><br/>The seven-match series moves to the north-west of New Zealand, to the city of Nelson, with the teams level at 1-1. The recent performances of Brendon McCullum's men have slowly improved their World Cup stocks from 'dark horses' to 'possible semi-finalists'. A win in Nelson tomorrow will not only reinforce their current standing in World cricket but also give them a crucial lead in the tune-up series. That holds true for Sri Lanka, too. After an indifferent performance in the first ODI, they put up a far better show in Hamilton. A win in Nelson, will mark a good turnaround of fortunes after the drubbing in the Test series.<br/><br/><b>New Zealand:</b><br/><br/>Brendon McCullum has stood head and shoulders above his mates in terms of performances. His blitz in the first ODI was followed by an equally entertaining century in the second. Much of the team's fortunes hinges on how McCullum goes at the top of the order. That isn't to say that New Zealand is a one-man team. In fact, their pace bowling combination of Trent Boult, Adam Milne and Mitchell McClenaghan have been thoroughly impressive. The middle-order's competence against quality spin remains an area of concern. Ross Taylor, after being rested for the opening encounter, has struggled to get going. Ditto for Tom Latham despite a dogged 42 in the abandoned third ODI. Grant Elliott will take his place in the middle-order and New Zealand will take a late call on Kane Williamson's fitness.<br/><br/><b>Sri Lanka:</b><br/><br/>Sri Lanka fought back well after the defeat in Christchurch. Tillakaratne Dilshan's century in Hamilton gave them a much needed win on the tour. With Mahela Jayawardene, Kumar Sangakkara and Angelo Mathews around, the batting still looks capable. They will however, be vary of Lahiru Thirimanne's no-show. While their pacers have gone for plenty in the face of McCullum's onslaughts, the return of Rangana Herath and his combination with Sachithra Senanayake holds Sri Lanka in good stead. Dilshan meanwhile has emerged as a capable bowling option for Mathews and could prompt the skipper to play an extra seamer.<br/><br/><b>Pitch and Conditions:</b><br/><br/>In a stark contrast to the weather in Auckland, Nelson is expected to be bright and sunny.<br/><br/><b>Stats and Trivia:</b><br/><br/>Kumar Sangakkara is 17-runs shy of overtaking Sanath Jayasuriya and becoming Sri Lanka's top run-getter in ODI history.]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Teams:</b>]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>Sri Lanka</b> (From): Dimuth Karunaratne, Tillakaratne Dilshan, Kumar Sangakkara(w), Mahela Jayawardene, Angelo Mathews(c), Lahiru Thirimanne, Thisara Perera, Jeevan Mendis, Sachithra Senanayake, Nuwan Kulasekara, Suranga Lakmal, Dinesh Chandimal, Shaminda Eranga, Rangana Herath, Dhammika Prasad, Lasith Malinga]]></line><line><![CDATA[<b>New Zealand</b> (From): Martin Guptill, Brendon McCullum(c), Tom Latham, Ross Taylor, Grant Elliott, Corey Anderson, Luke Ronchi(w), Nathan McCullum, Tim Southee, Mitchell McClenaghan, Matt Henry, Daniel Vettori, Kane Williamson, Adam Milne, Kyle Mills, Trent Boult]]></line>		
		</commentary>
	<innings no="1">
		<totalruns>276</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>10</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>49.3</totalovers>
		<declared/>
		<followon/>
		<batteam name="Sri Lanka">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>7952</playerid>
					<name>Dimuth Karunaratne</name>
					<batsman-name>D Karunaratne</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>D Karunaratne</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>5</runs>
					<balls>16</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[lbw]]></status>
					<bowler>Southee</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1057</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>105</playerid>
					<name>Tillakaratne Dilshan</name>
					<batsman-name>Dilshan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Dilshan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>44</runs>
					<balls>57</balls>
					<fours>4</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Williamson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6326</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Martin Guptill</fielder>
						<fielderId>1457</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>104</playerid>
					<name>Kumar Sangakkara</name>
					<batsman-name>Sangakkara</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Sangakkara</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>76</runs>
					<balls>83</balls>
					<fours>8</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Milne</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7625</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Martin Guptill</fielder>
						<fielderId>1457</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>101</playerid>
					<name>Mahela Jayawardene</name>
					<batsman-name>M Jayawardene</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>M Jayawardene</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>94</runs>
					<balls>82</balls>
					<fours>9</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>CJ Anderson</bowler>
					<bowlerId>8982</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Luke Ronchi</fielder>
						<fielderId>1396</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1629</playerid>
					<name>Angelo Mathews</name>
					<batsman-name>Mathews</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Mathews</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Milne</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7625</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Luke Ronchi</fielder>
						<fielderId>1396</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6243</playerid>
					<name>Lahiru Thirimanne</name>
					<batsman-name>Thirimanne</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Thirimanne</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>19</runs>
					<balls>31</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>McClenaghan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7624</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2281</playerid>
					<name>Thisara Perera</name>
					<batsman-name>T Perera</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>T Perera</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>5</runs>
					<balls>6</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Southee</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1057</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Brendon McCullum</fielder>
						<fielderId>201</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6470</playerid>
					<name>Jeevan Mendis</name>
					<batsman-name>J Mendis</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>J Mendis</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>12</runs>
					<balls>10</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Southee</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1057</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Daniel Vettori</fielder>
						<fielderId>205</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>507</playerid>
					<name>Nuwan Kulasekara</name>
					<batsman-name>N Kulasekara</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>N Kulasekara</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>4</runs>
					<balls>7</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Brendon McCullum</fielder>
						<fielderId>201</fielderId>
						<fielder2>Mitchell McClenaghan</fielder2>
						<fielderId2>7624</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6729</playerid>
					<name>Sachithra Senanayake</name>
					<batsman-name>Senanayake</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Senanayake</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>1</runs>
					<balls>3</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>277</playerid>
					<name>Rangana Herath</name>
					<batsman-name>Herath</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Herath</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>1</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>McClenaghan</bowler>
					<bowlerId>7624</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Kane Williamson</fielder>
						<fielderId>6326</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>7952</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>11</runs>
				<overs>4.2</overs>
				<batsman>Dimuth Karunaratne</batsman>
				<batsman-name>D Karunaratne</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>105</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>113</runs>
				<overs>20.1</overs>
				<batsman>Tillakaratne Dilshan</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Dilshan</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>104</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>180</runs>
				<overs>33.1</overs>
				<batsman>Kumar Sangakkara</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Sangakkara</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1629</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>180</runs>
				<overs>33.2</overs>
				<batsman>Angelo Mathews</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Mathews</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6243</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>245</runs>
				<overs>44.3</overs>
				<batsman>Lahiru Thirimanne</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Thirimanne</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>101</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>253</runs>
				<overs>45.3</overs>
				<batsman>Mahela Jayawardene</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Jayawardene</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>2281</playerid>
				<nbr>7</nbr>
				<runs>268</runs>
				<overs>46.6</overs>
				<batsman>Thisara Perera</batsman>
				<batsman-name>T Perera</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6470</playerid>
				<nbr>8</nbr>
				<runs>270</runs>
				<overs>48.2</overs>
				<batsman>Jeevan Mendis</batsman>
				<batsman-name>J Mendis</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>507</playerid>
				<nbr>9</nbr>
				<runs>273</runs>
				<overs>49.1</overs>
				<batsman>Nuwan Kulasekara</batsman>
				<batsman-name>N Kulasekara</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>277</playerid>
				<nbr>10</nbr>
				<runs>276</runs>
				<overs>49.3</overs>
				<batsman>Rangana Herath</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Herath</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>14</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>2</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>16</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="New Zealand">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1057</playerid>
					<name>Tim Southee</name>
					<bowler-name>Southee</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Southee</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>59</runsoff>
					<wickets>3</wickets>
					<wides>4</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7625</playerid>
					<name>Adam Milne</name>
					<bowler-name>Milne</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Milne</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>28</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7624</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell McClenaghan</name>
					<bowler-name>McClenaghan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>McClenaghan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9.3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>58</runsoff>
					<wickets>2</wickets>
					<wides>8</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8982</playerid>
					<name>Corey Anderson</name>
					<bowler-name>CJ Anderson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Corey Anderson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>19</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1064</playerid>
					<name>Grant Elliott</name>
					<bowler-name>Elliott</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Elliott</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>3</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>19</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>205</playerid>
					<name>Daniel Vettori</name>
					<bowler-name>Vettori</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Vettori</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>10</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>41</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6326</playerid>
					<name>Kane Williamson</name>
					<bowler-name>Williamson</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Williamson</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>50</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<bowler-name>B McCullum</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Brendon McCullum</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1457</playerid>
					<name>Martin Guptill</name>
					<bowler-name>M Guptill</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Guptill</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>521</playerid>
					<name>Ross Taylor</name>
					<bowler-name>Ross Taylor</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ross Taylor</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1396</playerid>
					<name>Luke Ronchi</name>
					<bowler-name>Ronchi</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Ronchi</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	<innings no="2">
		<totalruns>280</totalruns>
		<totalwickets>6</totalwickets>
		<totalovers>48.1</totalovers>
		<declared/>
		<followon/>
		<batteam name="New Zealand">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>1457</playerid>
					<name>Martin Guptill</name>
					<batsman-name>M Guptill</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Guptill</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>20</runs>
					<balls>27</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Mathews</bowler>
					<bowlerId>1629</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Kumar Sangakkara</fielder>
						<fielderId>104</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>201</playerid>
					<name>Brendon McCullum</name>
					<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Brendon McCullum</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>11</runs>
					<balls>11</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>N Kulasekara</bowler>
					<bowlerId>507</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Thisara Perera</fielder>
						<fielderId>2281</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6326</playerid>
					<name>Kane Williamson</name>
					<batsman-name>Williamson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Williamson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>103</runs>
					<balls>107</balls>
					<fours>6</fours>
					<sixes>1</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[bowled]]></status>
					<bowler>T Perera</bowler>
					<bowlerId>2281</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>521</playerid>
					<name>Ross Taylor</name>
					<batsman-name>Ross Taylor</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ross Taylor</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>8</runs>
					<balls>23</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>Herath</bowler>
					<bowlerId>277</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Kumar Sangakkara</fielder>
						<fielderId>104</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1064</playerid>
					<name>Grant Elliott</name>
					<batsman-name>Elliott</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Elliott</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>44</runs>
					<balls>58</balls>
					<fours>3</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[caught]]></status>
					<bowler>J Mendis</bowler>
					<bowlerId>6470</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Lahiru Thirimanne</fielder>
						<fielderId>6243</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>8982</playerid>
					<name>Corey Anderson</name>
					<batsman-name>CJ Anderson</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Corey Anderson</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>47</runs>
					<balls>44</balls>
					<fours>2</fours>
					<sixes>2</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[runout]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder>Tillakaratne Dilshan</fielder>
						<fielderId>105</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1396</playerid>
					<name>Luke Ronchi</name>
					<batsman-name>Ronchi</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Ronchi</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<runs>32</runs>
					<balls>15</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>3</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>205</playerid>
					<name>Daniel Vettori</name>
					<batsman-name>Vettori</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Vettori</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>7</runs>
					<balls>4</balls>
					<fours>1</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[batting]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>false</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1057</playerid>
					<name>Tim Southee</name>
					<batsman-name>Southee</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Southee</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7624</playerid>
					<name>Mitchell McClenaghan</name>
					<batsman-name>McClenaghan</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>McClenaghan</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7625</playerid>
					<name>Adam Milne</name>
					<batsman-name>Milne</batsman-name>
					<batsman-nickname>Milne</batsman-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<runs>0</runs>
					<balls>0</balls>
					<fours>0</fours>
					<sixes>0</sixes>
					<status><![CDATA[dnb]]></status>
					<bowler/>
					<bowlerId>0</bowlerId>
						<fielder/>
						<fielderId>0</fielderId>
						<fielder2/>
						<fielderId2>0</fielderId2>
						<fielder3/>
						<fielderId3>0</fielderId3>
					<yetToBat>true</yetToBat>
				</player>
			</players>
		</batteam>
		<fallofwickets>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>201</playerid>
				<nbr>1</nbr>
				<runs>24</runs>
				<overs>4.5</overs>
				<batsman>Brendon McCullum</batsman>
				<batsman-name>B McCullum</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1457</playerid>
				<nbr>2</nbr>
				<runs>41</runs>
				<overs>7.3</overs>
				<batsman>Martin Guptill</batsman>
				<batsman-name>M Guptill</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>521</playerid>
				<nbr>3</nbr>
				<runs>63</runs>
				<overs>15.1</overs>
				<batsman>Ross Taylor</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Ross Taylor</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>1064</playerid>
				<nbr>4</nbr>
				<runs>151</runs>
				<overs>32.1</overs>
				<batsman>Grant Elliott</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Elliott</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>6326</playerid>
				<nbr>5</nbr>
				<runs>230</runs>
				<overs>43.6</overs>
				<batsman>Kane Williamson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>Williamson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
			<wicket>
				<playerid>8982</playerid>
				<nbr>6</nbr>
				<runs>245</runs>
				<overs>45.4</overs>
				<batsman>Corey Anderson</batsman>
				<batsman-name>CJ Anderson</batsman-name>
			</wicket>
		</fallofwickets>
		<extras>
			<byes>0</byes>
			<wides>7</wides>
			<noballs>0</noballs>
			<legbyes>1</legbyes>
			<penalty>0</penalty>
			<total>8</total>
		</extras>
		<bowlteam name="Sri Lanka">
			<players>
				<player>
					<playerid>507</playerid>
					<name>Nuwan Kulasekara</name>
					<bowler-name>N Kulasekara</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>N Kulasekara</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>51</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>3</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>1629</playerid>
					<name>Angelo Mathews</name>
					<bowler-name>Mathews</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Mathews</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>yes</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>4</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>16</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>277</playerid>
					<name>Rangana Herath</name>
					<bowler-name>Herath</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Herath</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9</overs>
					<maidens>1</maidens>
					<runsoff>39</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>2</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>2281</playerid>
					<name>Thisara Perera</name>
					<bowler-name>T Perera</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>T Perera</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>8</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>58</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6729</playerid>
					<name>Sachithra Senanayake</name>
					<bowler-name>Senanayake</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Senanayake</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>9.1</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>57</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6470</playerid>
					<name>Jeevan Mendis</name>
					<bowler-name>J Mendis</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>J Mendis</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>7</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>40</runsoff>
					<wickets>1</wickets>
					<wides>1</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>105</playerid>
					<name>Tillakaratne Dilshan</name>
					<bowler-name>Dilshan</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Dilshan</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>2</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>18</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>7952</playerid>
					<name>Dimuth Karunaratne</name>
					<bowler-name>D Karunaratne</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>D Karunaratne</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>104</playerid>
					<name>Kumar Sangakkara</name>
					<bowler-name>Sangakkara</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Sangakkara</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>yes</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>101</playerid>
					<name>Mahela Jayawardene</name>
					<bowler-name>M Jayawardene</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>M Jayawardene</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
				<player>
					<playerid>6243</playerid>
					<name>Lahiru Thirimanne</name>
					<bowler-name>Thirimanne</bowler-name>
					<bowler-nickname>Thirimanne</bowler-nickname>
					<captain>no</captain>
					<keeper>no</keeper>
					<overs>0</overs>
					<maidens>0</maidens>
					<runsoff>0</runsoff>
					<wickets>0</wickets>
					<wides>0</wides>
					<noballs>0</noballs>
				</player>
			</players>
		</bowlteam>
	</innings>
	
</scorecard>